Bye-bye, Lan
As they say, what goes around comes around
The five elements endlessly cycle
These five-element gourds
You just take sixty-four of them
Blessed with wealth and fortune
Watched over by luck and prosperity
I'll give you another 20% off
That's the total price
Take a look
As long as the old man goes out with dignity
Sure, don't you worry
Leave the professional stuff to the professionals
Cash or scan to pay?
I'll scan
Here
Thanks for your business
Take care now
Honey
I know you're still mad at me, I...
Sir
We're already divorced
Please mind what you call me
It's all my fault, every bit of it
So how about this
Hit me
Hit me a few times
Go on, hit me
What did you ever do wrong?
You did nothing wrong
I'm the one who's wrong
I'm the one who ran off with the money, Chen Xiaofang
When your dad threw that money in my face
I caught it with my face without hesitation
I'm just a crazy woman who's blinded by money
Get away from me
You're not that kind of person
Honey
You look great in this outfit
Red really suits you
Are you out of your mind?
These are burial clothes
If you like them, they're yours
Take them, take them
We started this shop together
You can abandon me
But you can't abandon our kid
Master Zhou, come on
Just think of me as a bad woman who used you and left
You're not
Just treat me like this handful of joss paper
And toss me away
See? Just like this
Chen Xiaofang, have you no conscience?
I totally forgot, I'm sorry
My brother can't do anything right
Always leaving stuff lying around
Quick, quick
You didn't get hurt, did you?
It hurts!
See? When something goes wrong, it's always someone else's fault
That's not what I meant
Yiran
Why are you in such a rush to find me?
Right
Let me tell you
Now Wu Huilian's words are really coming true
What I'm doing now is just a waste of effort
All for nothing
Can you believe it?
Every job I found for her
Either they don't want her
Or she can't handle it
I mean, in a place this small
Why does even a dishwasher need to be a connection hire?
Ms. Li Yiran
You're a connection hire too
Welcome to Paradise Funeral Home
Let's build something great together
Ms. Chen Xiaofang
I'll take a photo of you right now
And you can immediately attend
the annual Social Commerce Queen Awards ceremony
Yiran
Auntie Huilian's looking for a job, right?
Send her to my second uncle's place.
My second uncle runs an Escape Room.
We've got connections too, you know.
Oh, right.
Yiran.
I know that
you're a little scarred by Escape Rooms,
but his second uncle's place
might be just right for you and Auntie Huilian.
After all,
you two did put on a show at the zoo.
Exactly.
My second uncle's place
is hiring a ton of NPCs right now.
NPCs?
That could actually work.
Then, thank you so much.
I won't be polite then, Zhou Fang.
Because she really needs this job.
So we'll go tomorrow.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
So grateful.
This, this...
It's fine.
I broke it.
You send the money, I'll clean up.
Okay, okay.
I'll transfer it to you in a bit.
You two chat.
I'll head out.
Bye-bye.
You go too.
Yiran.
Why'd you come out?
I've got one more favor to ask.
What is it?
Xiaofang, right now,
she won't listen to a word I say.
She just won't listen to reason with me.
You're her best friend.
Point me in the right direction, would you?
Since you're asking me,
I'll be straight with you.
These past few years you two have been through a lot,
and I more or less
know a bit about what's going on with you two.
I can tell you really love her,
and you're really good to her too.
But here's the thing,
you can't keep acting like a kid who never grows up,
always leaning on your family so much.
When problems hit, you just laugh it off,
clowning around, and the matter just blows over.
Is that gonna work?
If this thing with your dad isn't settled,
there'll always be a rift between you and Xiaofang.
I shouldn't say too much.
Think it over yourself,
what Xiaofang really wants.
I'm off.
I'm always laughing it off like a kid.
Chen Dayou.
Two hundred.
Here.
Thanks, boss.
Zhao Qiang.
Two hundred.
Thanks, boss.
Wang Daren.
Two hundred.
Here.
Thanks.
Wu Huilian.
One hundred fifty.
Listen, from now on,
be more careful about who you hire.
Don't bring any Tom, Dick and Harry onto the cart.
Just look at these women.
They eat a whole lot
and do hardly any work.
Why do you talk so much crap?
What's wrong with women, huh?
Isn't your mom a woman?
Weren't you born from a woman?
Aren't your grandmas women too?
Crazy woman, say that again!
Give me back my money.
Why the hell should I?
Keep it up and you won't get a cent.
Son of a bitch, the boss gave three hundred.
And you're only giving one-fifty!
Watch out, your kid'll be born without an asshole!
You don't want the job anymore?
Say that again!
Just hand over the money.
It's fine, it's fine.
Let's go, come on.
You idiot.
Crazy woman.
Idiot.
Enough, stop it.
Keep it up and you won't get a cent!
It's fine, it's fine now.
Don't fight with him.
You don't even know his background.
I earn my money with my own two hands.
So what?
Why should I let him push me around?
We still gotta rely on him for work later.
The world's a big place,
is he the only one who can find us gigs?
Okay, okay.
Hurry up and change your clothes.
Or Yiran'll find out when we get back.
Let's go.
So dopey.
Hand me the bag.
I'm so mad.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Thank you, boss, thank you.
Sun Yongfu.
Two hundred.
Thank you, boss.
You ready yet?
Okay, okay!
Coming!
Hurry up!
Coming, coming, coming!
It's really about to rain.
Really?
It's starting to drizzle a bit.
Hold this for me, quick!
Take this bag too.
Okay, sure, sure.
Oh no, my foundation!
Do I look too dark?
Add some foundation, it'll be fine.
Add some foundation.
Here, dig out my lipstick.
Okay, okay, okay.
Is it too pale?
It's fine.
You look like you crawled out of a flour barrel.
Why does this damn frozen pork stink so much?
It reeks!
Smells so good!
Perfect, I'm starving.
What tasty stuff did you make?
Go wash your hands.
You made so many dishes
Like a beggar who found gold
I was just practicing at home
Eat it or don't, your call
Of course I'll eat it!
You can't finish all this alone anyway
Not bad at all
You made it just for me
What do you mean, just for you?
I told you, I'm just practicing
What's it got to do with you?
Well, if you're just practicing
then I'll give you a proper review
This chicken, it'll do
Let's look at this fish
As for the fish
it's passable too
But overall
it's still a bit worse than mine
Just quit talking
and eat
You little egg
always lecturing the hen
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so long-winded?
Can't you just eat properly?
I haven't even said a word
and I'm long-winded?
I want some fish.
Get it yourself.
What, you don't have hands?
Fine, I'll get it myself, then.
Delicious!
Here, have another one.
Eat more fish.
Makes you smart.
It's really good.
No talking while eating.
Stop talking and just eat.
One last thing.
A girl who can cook
is just so pretty.
And one more thing.
You'll cook again tomorrow, right?
Cook, my ass.
Just eat what you get.
Making a head is fine too.
Let's do a Lion's Head Meatball then.
Eat some more.
This fish is really well cooked.
Li Yiran cooked such a great meal yesterday.
I ate three bowls of rice.
Had a whole plate of chicken.
And a whole fish too.
I was so stuffed I couldn't sleep all night.
So I didn't get up this morning.
Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
It's fine, we'll make it.
We'll make it in time.
We'll make it.
Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
Why does that figure look so familiar?
Yiran!
Good morning!
The morning air is so nice!
We two came out for some exercise.
We ate way too much last night.
Right, right.
We're getting some exercise.
Enough, stop the act.
Come home with me, Wu Huilian.
I found you a job.
And you stop exercising too, Uncle Daren.
I lined up a job for you as well.
Not sure if it'll work out.
But...
if it does pan out,
you'd deliver food for them by day,
and run your stall at night.
Sounds good, sounds good.
Thank you!
Let me take that.
Let's go.
The two of us
really weren't out here to make money.
We just came out for some exercise, I mean.
That's how you stay healthy.
Right.
Health is wealth.
We need to exercise.
Life is all about staying active.
You two are over a hundred years old combined.
How'd you learn to lie like this?
No, no.
The two of us add up to ninety-six.
Is that even the point?
My hair's just gone a little gray.
Come exercise with us.
You're already up anyway.
What were you two thinking?
Your uncle does have some taste.
Of course.
Our whole family shares the same taste.
Back in the day,
I fell for you at first sight.
What's an escape artist?
An Escape Room.
I'm not doing any prison break.
I just got out of the joint.
It's not a real prison break.
They put people in a sealed room,
and you find clues to get out.
It's just playing a game.
Playing a game.
Auntie Huilian.
They want you to go in
and play an NPC.
What's an NPC?
An NPC is basically role-playing.
It means you get to act.
Acting, I can do that.
I even played a bear once.
Isn't that right?
Uncle.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This one's probably a bit out of her mind.
Uncle.
Tomorrow I'll bring you the Food Stall Beauty.
Where's the beauty you promised?
Why'd you send some old lady instead?
Auntie Huilian studied acting and was even on TV.
No way. Take her away.
Come on, dear uncle.
I promised Xiaofang I'd handle it.
Just pull a few strings for me.
Or I'll tell Grandma on you.
Boss Jiang.
I've finished my resume.
And here's my ID.
Please, have a seat.
Let me take a look.
Wu Huilian.
Present!
Sorry, I...
I... it's just a habit of mine.
Didn't scare you, did I?
No, no, it's fine. Sit, sit.
Please, have a seat.
Yiran
I bought you some milk tea
Careful, it's hot
Here
Thanks
How did you handle this?
Why does Auntie Lan still need an interview?
Doesn't that just prove
that my uncle's a reliable guy?
Just like me
Exactly
It's only right
But honestly
I hadn't met him before, you know
I always thought
your uncle was one of those
balding, beer-bellied, greasy middle-aged guys
No way that's possible
My uncle happens to be
a widely acknowledged golden bachelor
Tall and handsome
Charming and dashing
A rich kid who doesn't sponge off his family
He's got 168 hobbies
Why don't you introduce yourself?
Well, actually
I've done all kinds of jobs
I've hauled bricks
Painted walls
Carried frozen pork
Sold barbecue
I
I've even done time in prison
Wait a second
You... you've been in prison?
Didn't Zhou Fang tell you earlier?
Zhou Fang just told me you were
the Food Stall Beauty
When I was young
I wasn't bad-looking
That old nickname
Friends just made it up for fun
I didn't expect Zhou Fang to be so honest
telling you all that
You... you're pretty honest yourself
Well
It's fine
The thing is
in our line of work
you really need to get into character
you need to know how to act
I can do that, I can
I once played someone's mom
And I did a pretty good job
I was also at
You see
that Cute Pet Park
I played Bear One
I was the internet-famous animal
Lots of people loved me
No, no
We don't play animals
It's more like
shooting a movie
Sometimes you laugh, sometimes you cry
Crying isn't easy
Most people just can't cry on cue
Struggling to cry just doesn't work
So, you see
As for me
my tear glands are super active
Basically in three to five seconds
the tears just start flowing
And let me tell you
Don't cry, okay, alright
It's fine, fine, fine
I'm also great at professional mourning
Okay, okay, okay
I did mourning gigs all over the countryside
And I charged a really high fee too
Eight hundred yuan a session
If it weren't for my daughter
She didn't like me doing this job
I'd probably still be doing it now
Watch me cry and tell me if it's good
It's good
It's just that
My grandma says about him
Of the three unfilial acts, he's guilty of two
Not marrying, and having no kids
Zhou Fang
Your uncle couldn't possibly be...
No way, absolutely not.
Besides crying,
do you have any, you know,
special skills?
Let me tell you,
I'm a real smooth talker.
As long as you don't say stop,
I can tell you stories nonstop.
Three days and three nights,
and the story never repeats.
Tell me one.
Come on, tell me one.
Well, um...
Being put on the spot makes me nervous.
Now I can't think of anything.
Wait, maybe some other time.
I'll tell you slowly, I really will.
Later.
Let's talk about it later, okay?
So, about this job of mine,
when can I start working?
Why don't you go
and try it out first?
Welcome to Dr. Wu's secret hospital
I'm about to dismember you now
Oh man, this cord isn't long enough
Get another one
I've been waiting forever
One of my legs has gone numb already
Xiaofang, why'd you lie down on that thing?
Hurry, get down, get down, get down
I was just running a test for you
You're the NPC
You can't get scared, Auntie Huilian
You two scared the hell out of me
These are all the real deal
Then swap it out
Come on, just switch it out
Auntie Huilian
You look so glamorous!
Still got that charm, huh?
Am I right?
Food Stall Beauty, living up to the name!
I love this cheongsam!
Let's take a photo, take a photo!
Take a picture, take a picture!
Come on, one shot!
Boss Jiang
Now that's the vibe!
Who are you?
Why'd you stick on a fake beard?
You're hilarious.
I'm just here to run lines with you.
Rehearse your lines with you.
Don't hit me.
Run what lines?
Boss Jiang wants to test your line delivery.
I picked a scene for you.
It's from In the Mood for Love.
Recite it.
In the Mood for Love.
I love that one.
Tony Leung and Maggie Cheung,
both actors I really like.
Come on, recite it.
Fine, I'll recite it.
Why so pushy?
Why are there so many lines?
Why the sudden urge to go to Singapore?
For a change of scenery.
To escape all the gossip.
As long as we know there's nothing to it.
That's what I thought at first too.
I felt the same way.
I believed...
I believed we wouldn't end up like them.
I never expected...
that you'd really fall for me.
I didn't expect it either.
But there's nothing to be done.
You're my own flesh and blood.
I don't like that.
Stick to the script.
Say the lines as written.
Where were we?
I never expected it either.
I can't remember what comes next.
Come on, hold it in.
Can you do me a favor?
What?
Peel off that fake beard, would you?
It's painful to look at.
What are you doing?
Don't laugh, my beard's about to fall off.
If you had an extra boat ticket,
would you take me along with you?
Aren't you the one going to Singapore?
Am I the one going to Singapore?
Wu Huilian, tired of your job, are you?
Just act it out properly, okay?
Fine, fine, fine.
If...
you had an extra boat ticket,
would you take me to Shanghai?
Aren't you going to Singapore?
Singapore requires a visa.
I've done time in prison.
I don't know if I could even get the visa.
Act it out or don't, your choice.
Seems like you don't want this job.
No matter where you go,
as long as you have an extra ticket,
I'll follow you.
Brilliant.
I have to say,
your improvised take on it
was actually pretty good.
Here, take the script.
Take it.
Start work tomorrow.
This big one, this big one.
Give it a try.
Together, let's all dig in!
Come on, come on.
Eat up, everyone.
Okay, okay, you have one too.
It's really delicious.
Alright, alright.
Taste it, taste it.
Okay, okay.
Come on, come on.
Not bad, right?
The flavor's really good.
Smells great, doesn't it?
Come on.
Here's a toast to you.
Thank you.
For giving me this job opportunity.
Thank you, Boss Jiang.
What are you mumbling about?
Hurry up and drink.
That's it, good girl.
Thanks, thanks.
Come on, second round.
From now on,
we're one big happy family.
One family.
How did we become one big happy
family so quickly?
Wang Daren.
The company is my home.
So tell me, Boss Jiang and I,
aren't we one big happy family?
Aren't we?
We are, right?
Come on, drink up.
Drink it.
And go grill five more chicken hearts.
You got it.
That's about enough out of you.
Last round.
Come on.
Still drinking?
For this one, I'm standing up to toast.
Boss Jiang.
As for me,
I've got a shady past.
I've done time.
But you never looked down on me.
From now on, you're my true boss.
I'm sticking with you.
Okay, okay, okay.
Bottoms up.
She, she...
She's had too much to drink.
She's a little drunk.
Can't hold her liquor, three drinks and she's out.
Kids shouldn't butt in when adults are talking.
No need to bow, no bowing.
No, no bow, bow.
But we've still gotta drink!
Okay, okay.
Drink up, drink up!
Fine, fine, we can drink.
Come on, come on.
Wait, hold on a sec.
Before I drink, let me say something.
Just one thing.
Now, this job, you know,
was set up by my nephew.
So there's that connection,
but mostly it comes down to skill.
Come on, now that I've said all that,
let me toast you again.
More drinking?
From now on, you're my guy.
For you, I'd go through fire and water.
Come on, bottoms up!
Bottoms up!
Boss Jiang, you've had the skewers,
and you've tasted the flavor.
You know Uncle Daren's skills now.
So, what we just talked about earlier,
giving Wang Daren the company catering.
That shouldn't be a problem, right?
Well, well...
These skewers are delicious.
And the price is affordable too.
No problem, no problem, no problem.
Thank you, Boss Jiang!
No, no, no.
Tell you what, Boss Jiang,
let me grill you another one.
Sure, sure.
No need, no need, no need.
Let me tell you,
That's enough, Wang Daren.
Let me tell you, he's from Shandong.
He can really hold his drink.
Alright, alright, Wang Daren.
Your flesh
is only time,
time that keeps slipping away.
Chen Xiaofang!
Auntie Lan, what brings you here?
Finally caught you!
I mean, let me tell you,
I need to ask you for a favor.
Here, let me help you.
Sure, go ahead.
If I can help, I definitely will.
It's like,
I got that new job, you know,
and that job,
it's kind of complicated.
I've got to play some creepy nurse,
and also play Maggie Cheung,
play lots of characters.
So I want you to coach my acting.
This job
is so important for me and Li Yiran.
Acting, you know,
once you get one, you get them all.
Do you still remember
the animal imitation I taught you?
Of course I remember.
Didn't you have me
watch that Animal World show
and act like a big brown bear?
Right.
I remember.
But this is playing a ghost.
I've never seen a ghost, you know.
How am I supposed to play a ghost?
Then just watch some horror movies,
play a ghost, scare some people.
That way you can achieve
truly listen, truly see, truly feel.
You coming or what?
Coming, Amin!
That's the feeling.
That's exactly the feeling.
That's the feeling right there.
I got it.
Wrong way
No, you got the right place.
Mr. Zhou
You scared me!
Are you okay?
Zhou Fang
Xu Wumei
Hey
Honey
Is your hand okay?
Did I hit you too hard?
Look at you, what a disgrace
Zhou Fang
You are driving me crazy!
Pulling this spooky nonsense on me again
I know you love horror movies
So
I wanted to surprise you
Xu Wumei, hurry, go
Honey
You know I've always been a coward
But for you
Even through hell and high water
Even facing demons and ghosts
I wouldn't hesitate for a second
That's right
Our Mr. Zhou is usually scared of a cockroach
And today he dressed up as a ghost
Just forgive him, come on
Honey
In this life, I'm yours forever
I'll be buried with you even in death
I'll haunt you even after death
What the hell are you doing?
You scared the crap out of me!
Blasting it that loud
You scared yourself
and now you're blaming me?
I'm practicing
I'm imitating, got it?
Love what you do
I've got ambition, you know
How come you're not scared at all?
The sound's all wrong.
But it looks the part.
Son of a bitch.
Being a ghost is way harder than being alive.
Am I right or what?
Son of a bitch, what kind of oranges did you buy?
They're sour as hell.
What a psycho!
Are you out of your mind?
What are you yelling about?
You scared my girlfriend!
Idiot.
Let's go, come on.
Guess I'm still pretty scary, huh?
Well, not totally un-scary at least.
Huilian, what are you doing?
You scared me!
Boss Jiang
Oh, it's you
What's wrong?
Don't even ask
A customer filed a complaint against me
About what?
That my ghost act wasn't scary enough
So boring.
That's it, I'm not coming back here.
Mommy!
Is it really that bad?
It gets even worse.
Is this real or fake?
No idea.
You go in first.
Me? Me first?
Can't you be more professional?
Can't you put in some effort?
Look at this.
Total waste of our money.
Seriously.
Come on, try harder.
Being human is way harder than being a ghost, right?
Son of a bitch, you hit me?
Come on!
Who hit me?
Are you crazy?
Stop hitting! Stop it!
I really wanted to do it well.
But I... I...
No matter how hard I try,
I just can't ever get it right.
What should I do?
Could you give me a hand?
Well, I happen to be heading somewhere.
It might just help you out.
What kind of place?
You'll see when we get there.
Let's go.
Move.
Come on.
Huilian, hold on tight!
Where are we going?
To a secret place.
Wu Huilian
Don't be scared
It's okay, come here
This is my secret hideout
No one will bother you here
Yell all you want, give it a try
Give it a try
Come on
Come on, come on
Wu Huilian
Don't be afraid
Why so quiet?
Did you do something wrong?
Be bolder
Hands
Open your hands, come on
Three, two, one, go
Wu Huilian
Don't be afraid
Again
Wu Huilian
Don't be afraid
You know what?
After yelling like that
you actually seem to feel pretty good
Feels great, doesn't it?
Wanna give it another try?
Let's add some spooky sound effects
Like at work
that "stay back!" kind of thing
Wanna try?
Come on, one, two, three
Come at me!
Come on!
I'm not scared of you!
That feels so good!
This place is really great
Whenever you're stressed out
or feeling down
you can just scream your heart out
Right?
Yeah
Let's yell together!
Yell together
Son of a bitch!
I'm not scared of you!
Come hit me!
I don't even want today's pay
Thanks for looking out for me
Huilian
I like you
What did you say?