(Peace)
According to our father's decree,
now that you've reclaimed Yunzhou City,
you are the Crown Prince of Daxing.
Congratulations, Qian.
(Prince Qian)
(Young Emperor Youning)
Reclaiming our ancestral land
is the duty of us Xiao descendants.
It was also won
with the lives of our soldiers.
The credit is not mine alone.
From now on, in the imperial court,
to govern the state
and ensure its peace,
we brothers will still need
to work together.
Qian,
my...
My birth mother was of low status,
and she passed away too soon.
I was fortunate
to receive the Empress's affection,
and she raised me herself.
How could I ever dare,
and I have never coveted the throne.
Since you were four and came to my side,
I've never treated you as an outsider.
This is a sachet Mother prayed for
at Fahua Temple.
I've put mugwort leaf,
angelica, borneol,
and Chinese gall inside.
Keep it.
Qian,
I can't accept this.
Wearing it will keep you safe.
If you ever get injured,
you can also use it for emergencies.
Take it.
=Blossoms of Power=
(Adapted from the novel, After My
Bloom, All Flowers Wither by Jin Huang)
=Episode 16=
Regarding today's events,
I thank Your Highness
and Commandery Princess.
Yunhuai,
there's no need for such formalities.
You did it all for us,
going to the Duke of Xie's Manor alone.
It gave us the chance to coordinate
from the inside and out
to find the secret room
and capture the Duke of Ying.
We have you to thank for everything.
Physician Xie,
I'll escort you back to
your private estate in the suburbs.
The carriage is already waiting
outside the city gate.
Please.
When we work together,
with just a single glance,
we understand each other completely.
Without a word,
we can anticipate
each other's next move.
We're perfectly in sync.
A match made in heaven.
Perhaps it's just that we're both
skilled at precise calculations.
It has nothing to do with anything else.
For a companion you know and love,
isn't understanding
and chemistry what one seeks?
You took the Duke of Ying away.
When will we interrogate him?
He has indeed been
afflicted with a strange poison.
He also had a bit of a scare.
He needs a day or two to recuperate.
When the time comes,
I will personally go
to Duke of Wei's Manor
to pick you up so we can go together.
(Liquor)
You like the rain.
Let's watch it a little longer then.
♪In the warm days, a gentle breeze
blows open the blossoms on a tree♪
♪How else would I think of someone?♪
♪A faint taste of longing on my lips♪
♪Like a thousand twists and turns♪
♪Gone forever,
yet I savor the memory again and again♪
(Duke of Wei's Manor)
Your Highness, what's wrong?
After getting caught
in the rain that day,
not only did I catch a cold,
but I also developed a fever.
If you don't believe me,
feel for yourself, Commandery Princess.
Thank you for your concern,
Commandery Princess.
Did you imprison the Duke of Ying
in the capital's suburbs?
Of course.
I couldn't possibly
bring a living person
into the East Palace.
Forget one living person,
even if it were ten living people,
if you wanted to,
you could do it.
I never thought that in your heart,
I am so incredibly capable.
The road ahead is uneven. Be careful.
Don't worry.
My riding skills are one of a kind
in the palace.
One of a kind, really?
Do you even know how? Let me do it.
I've always been frail.
I can't endure such a bumpy ride.
You all wait here.
(Gazing at the Mountain From Afar)
I hope you find the real culprit today
and solve this long-standing mystery.
All the evidence points
to the Duke of Ying.
This is indeed, in all these years,
the closest I've ever been to the truth.
Thank you
for joining me in this.
Your Highness,
you are truly formidable.
No one ever took you seriously.
And so you
hid your true abilities,
secretly controlled everything,
and decided matters of life and death.
I've invited you here
to ask you
if you recognize this person.
Stop beating around the bush.
I bought
this poison myself.
But as for poisoning a child,
I would never do such a thing.
So, you mean to say
you weren't trying to harm me?
That's right.
This poison
was meant for Xiao Juechong.
You've always resented my father.
Prince Qian
was the Empress Dowager's
eldest legitimate son.
That Xiao Juechong
is merely an adopted son raised
under the Empress Dowager's name.
The Empress Dowager treated him
as her own.
And Prince Qian
cared for him deeply
and taught him with great care.
But he took advantage
of the chaos of war
(Yunzhou City)
and was treacherous and ungrateful.
(Young Duke of Ying)
All soldiers, hear my command!
- Yes!
March out!
What's the situation?
We've sent out
several more groups of scouts.
Prince Qian is blessed by the heavens.
He'll surely return victorious.
(Yunzhou City)
It's the signal.
Assemble the troops
and open the city gates!
Reinforce Prince Qian!
- Yes!
Quickly!
Wait!
All soldiers of the army,
defend the city to the death.
What are you talking about?
- Duke of Ying.
- Don't be rash.
- Prince Qian is surrounded!
- Duke of Ying.
Are we just going to stand by
and watch him die?
- Archers, nock your arrows.
- Are you going to watch Prince Qian
die on the battlefield?
The city gates...
He is your older brother!
Your older brother!
Must not
be opened!
What are you doing?
Qian!
He refused to send reinforcements.
With vicious ambition,
he caused Prince Qian's death,
then claimed the throne himself!
How dare you!
My imperial uncle died
on the battlefield.
How can you misplace your anger
on my father?
That Xiao Juechong
had long coveted the throne.
It's just that Prince Qian
was too kind and benevolent.
He never once suspected
his younger brother.
As for me,
I was Prince Qian's second-in-command.
My only goal was to avenge him.
But I never expected
that this poison
would be used by someone else
to do their dirty work.
What do you mean?
As for who wanted to poison you,
I didn't see it with my own eyes.
I cannot say for sure.
I can only offer you
one piece of advice.
Do not place too much trust
in your father.
In his heart, there is only the throne.
There is no
brotherhood...
let alone
the bond between father and son...
Your Highness,
how do you plan to handle this next?
Duke of Ying
was a renowned general, as famous as
the Duke of Wei
and the Marquis of Shunan.
He committed a crime
and has paid for it with his life.
His remains
should be buried in his ancestral tomb.
Your Highness, you seem to regret this.
Yes.
This time,
I thought the Duke of Ying
was the real poisoner.
I didn't expect
it would all be for nothing.
What the Duke of Ying said
implicated His Majesty.
It was because that bowl
of cherries in sweet cream
was personally fed to me by my father.
This isn't the first time
I've heard these rumors.
But I remember clearly.
When I was five,
I was in danger during the spring hunt.
I was attacked by a wild wolf.
My father risked his life to save me.
He was covered in blood.
When I was little, I'd cry all night.
To lull me to sleep,
my father would gently pat my back
and stay up all night.
One day,
I caught a cold.
To take better care of me,
he reviewed his memorials
at my bedside.
In my heart,
he is the best father there is.
Well then, today,
at least we've ruled out
the Duke of Ying.
We're one step closer to the truth.
Are you trying to comfort me?
We're investigating this case together.
We'll face it all, thick and thin.
Even if we find nothing,
I don't want to see you so disheartened.
For more than ten years,
I've been investigating this case.
The loneliness I've felt,
the loss,
the confusion,
and even the despair,
no one has ever known.
Since I was nine,
I had forgotten what joy felt like.
But now,
I know.
♪Frost that melts at a single smile♪
♪How can you be this wonderful♪
♪Every answer I gave♪
♪Was both bittersweet and absurd♪
♪Hiding my tear-filled eyes
when I hurt you♪
♪How hard it truly was?♪
♪The wounds that healed
with just a little comfort♪
♪Never knowing I was lost♪
Can you not take it off?
♪Why don't you take me away?♪
I know you're feeling down,
so I won't hold it against you.
♪You'll never♪
Thank you for your compassion.
Your kindness to me today
is something I'll remember
for the rest of my life.
(Duke of Wei's Manor)
Your Highnesses, what brings you here?
My brother and I have come...
First, to thank you,
and second,
to bid you farewell.
Farewell?
Regarding my uncle's matter,
I know it was you
and Crown Prince who mediated,
allowing my uncle to be buried
in the ancestral tomb.
The Valiant Army
wasn't implicated either.
Although the Duke of Ying
made a mistake,
it doesn't erase
all of his past merits.
He deserves to be respected.
With my uncle gone,
the Valiant Army
will inevitably face turmoil.
I have requested a decree
from my father.
I'm going to take my uncle's place
guarding Anlan.
My father has already approved it.
I will lead my troops out tomorrow.
You've made up your mind?
I've lived under the protection
of my uncle and my older brother.
Now,
my uncle has passed away,
and my mother has been demoted.
I can't let my brother
manage everything alone.
I'll go guard Anlan,
while Changping stays in the capital
to handle the aftermath
of the secret prison.
The Duke of Ying's Valiant Army,
which struck fear into the hearts
of our enemies, is now in your hands.
The Duke of Ying's spirit in heaven
will be gratified.
After this parting, we'll be far apart.
I don't know when we'll meet again.
I hope that you
will take good care of yourself
and stay safe.
You too, Your Highness.
Then I wish you success
in the wider world ahead,
and may you achieve great things.
I don't know what's going on.
My dad suddenly wants to send me
to the Court of Judicial Review.
What terrible thing did you do?
Did your father
turn you in for the greater good?
(Wang Jue, Marquis of Zhenbei's Son)
I don't know.
He found out there was an
opening at the Court of Judicial Review.
Why don't you pretend
to be sick and get out of it?
The Court of Judicial Review
has issued the order.
I've been officially accepted.
Aren't you close with Vice Minister Cui?
Can you put in a good word for me?
Anyone can do an easy job like that.
Can you ask him to let me off the hook?
Best Young Master in the whole world,
please save me.
Seeing how sincerely you're begging me,
I'll help you out.
Although Vice Minister Cui is stubborn,
he'll still listen
to what I have to say.
You're a true friend.
No.
Wang Jue is useless
at both books and brawls.
He'll cause trouble for you later.
He's happier being a playboy.
Please reconsider.
I said no, and I mean it.
Come on, we've been
through thick and thin together.
I thought you'd forgotten.
Come.
Go!
Stop.
Beat him!
Don't be so unreasonable.
Organizing case files doesn't require
literary or martial skill.
He just needs to be literate.
Why is there a sudden opening
at the Court of Judicial Review?
Do you think that the day
after you mentioned Wang Jue to me,
he got transferred
to the Court of Judicial Review,
so he can no longer
fool around with you,
is quite a coincidence?
Young Master,
aren't you flattering yourself?
This opening has always been there.
It's perfect for someone
who is physically weak,
can't speak well,
and isn't very bright.
Are you mocking me?
Cui Jinbai,
have you forgotten
what it's like to be under me?
It seems you have fully recovered.
If you're so loyal to your friend,
why don't you switch places
with Wang Jue?
Organizing case files isn't hard at all.
You just need to number the files
as you organize them.
One.
♪The moonlight is sewn together
by the dusk♪
Two.
No, no.
My chest hurts, my hand hurts, too.
It looks like I won't be better
for at least half a month.
I won't disturb you any longer.
Why are you blushing?
My condition is getting worse.
I have shortness of breath.
I must go back and lie down.
I won't disturb you
while you're on duty.
Did you hear?
Duke of Wei has returned.
(Mingde Gate)
The Duke of Wei is so impressive.
Here he comes!
Quick, look!
That's the Duke of Wei.
Youyou!
(Shen Yueshan, Duke of Wei)
Father.
Now that you're in the imperial capital,
you've become so mature.
You're no longer the same
boisterous little girl you used to be.
But,
who told you to wait at the city gate?
The wind is so strong.
What if you catch a cold?
The imperial capital
is thousands of miles from northwest.
I was worried about you.
I also wanted to see you sooner.
Don't be so willful again.
Father, let's go back to the manor.
That the Duke of Wei's daughter
is to ride in such a carriage,
isn't it a bit too delicate?
Youyou,
tell me, does your brother
hold a grudge against me
from a past life?
All he does is anger me.
I already told him
that of all the princes,
you must not choose
that sickly Crown Prince.
But he told me
that the Crown Prince
is the most suitable man for you.
Youyou,
you...
are not really going
to marry him, are you?
His Majesty has already
decreed the marriage.
Can you really call it off, Father?
For my precious daughter,
is there anything your father can't do?
Let's return to the manor.
I'll wash up
and change my clothes first.
Then I'll go to the palace
to pay my respects to His Majesty.
I want to see for myself
who this Crown Prince is.
(Taiji Hall)
Duke of Wei has arrived.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
May Your Majesty be in good health.
Yueshan,
dispense with the formalities.
You're still as robust
as you were back then.
You entrusted northwest to me.
I could only do my utmost.
With you there,
northwest is safe.
Huayong,
Duke of Wei and I are sworn brothers.
Quickly, pay your respects
to your honorary uncle.
Honorary Uncle,
you've worked hard guarding the border.
When I reviewed northwest military
reports at the Ministry of War,
I often came across your brilliant
strategies. I have long admired you.
You flatter me.
Your Highness, you are of royal blood.
Your words do me too much honor.
Yueshan, you're too modest.
You deserve the praise.
From now on,
we will be in-laws.
Huayong will be like a son to you.
Xihe
grew up by my side.
Northwest is a harsh place,
so I couldn't help but dote on her.
That made her spoiled and headstrong.
When I wasn't around,
she willfully agreed to this marriage.
I am worried
that she might offend Crown Prince.
Honorary Uncle,
Xihe is exceptionally intelligent,
bold, and decisive.
As for our marriage,
we both thought it through carefully.
We are certain about each other.
Your Highness,
forgive my bluntness,
but your face is fairer than a maiden's,
and your features
are as fine as a painting. Your build
doesn't look very sturdy.
You are truly not my ideal choice
for a son-in-law.
Any father who considers his daughter
the apple of his eye
would find fault
with the man
who marries his precious treasure.
The fact that you love Xihe so dearly
makes me very happy.
I have always held my daughter
in the palm of my hand,
guarding her carefully.
Of course, I must
entrust her to someone...
who can protect her.
I have also mastered martial arts.
Some other day,
I will seek your guidance.
You?
Fine.
Some other day, we will
have a friendly match.
Thank you.
Your Highness,
don't thank me too soon.
My daughter
isn't someone
who can be married off so easily.
The Crown Prince is no exception.
Take care.
(Duke of Wei's Manor)
Youyou,
I'm back.
Greetings, Father.
Have you had your evening meal?
Xihe prepared dinner for me.
In that case,
it's getting late.
You should rest early.
If you need anything, just find Qing.
Then, Father,
you should also rest early.
I...
will come pay my respects again
tomorrow.
Youyou.
Father.
You're here.
I just saw Ruo was here.
Why did you let her go
after just a few words?
Sit down first.
Because of Xiao,
I don't know how to face Ruo,
let alone how to dote on her.
Father,
since I came to the manor
and met Ruo,
she is indeed intelligent,
gentle, and well-mannered.
Her mother's evil deeds
have nothing to do with her.
You shouldn't
take your anger out on her.
If you just spend more time with her,
you'll naturally figure out
how to get along with her.
Xihe,
I...
really feel that you've changed.
But I find it very strange.
Why did you agree
to marry the Crown Prince?
He's just as the rumors say,
like a willow in the wind,
fragile and weak.
How could he become
a son-in-law of the northwest?
What?
I say a few words about him,
and you're already displeased?
Of course not.
Then tell me,
did you fall for the Crown Prince
just for his looks?
Yes,
he is
quite handsome.
Only a real man like your father
and brothers will do.
It's my fault.
It's my fault for losing my mind
and sending you to the imperial capital.
But have you seen
the Crown Prince's legs and arms?
They're too skinny.
With those skinny legs and arms,
one push and he'd fall over.
When I was talking to him,
I was worried my voice was too loud
and that I might scare him
into fainting.
Father,
you're strong and powerful.
Of course, you'd think everyone
You're...
You're defending him.
That's not what I mean.
I'm just being fair.
Besides, I didn't fall for his looks.
I've already explained all the reasons
to my brother.
I'm sure he's already told you.
It's not that I don't trust you.
I don't trust that future son-in-law
of mine.
All right, all right.
You should go back and rest for now.
Tomorrow,
I'll take you to see
your maternal grandfather.
Then I'll find a chance
to size him up for you again.
(Tao Residence)
Xihe.
Father-in-law.
Grandfather.
It seems you're doing well.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, why are you here?
His Highness often comes to visit me.
Early this morning,
he also sent over a meal meticulously
prepared by the East Palace.
I told him Xihe would be back today.
We're all family.
Minister Tao, Duke of Wei,
you can just call me Huayong.
My esteemed Father-in-law,
I have come to pay my respects.
You're only here
for a short three-day stay.
You didn't need to make a special trip.
You could have just had Xihe
relay a message.
Now that I'm in the imperial capital,
it would be improper
not to pay a formal visit.
I may be a crude man,
but I still know basic etiquette.
Xihe, come on.
Let's go inside.
I see
you've lost so much weight.
I have lost a little weight recently.
It seems you are already used to
being scorned by your father-in-law.
But don't worry.
Before long,
you'll be able
to act like a father-in-law yourself.
This rascal.
He's cunning from head to toe.
He's not to be underestimated.
He's just like a northwestern wolf.
Grandfather.
Where are Uncle, Aunt, and Xun?
Your uncle's father-in-law
is celebrating his birthday,
so he went with your aunt and Xun
to her family's home.
See?
For decades, he's been the same.
Attentive and doting on his wife.
That's a truly great son-in-law.
He is.
Unlike some people
who are so thoughtless.
I call it being meticulous
beneath a rough exterior.
Lacking composure.
I call it being bold and unrestrained.
You're over a hundred years old
combined.
Why are you still bickering
like children?
Father, coming to Grandfather's house
has made you quite eloquent
and argumentative.
Please excuse us, Your Highness.
Minister Tao, you and Duke of Wei
don't treat me like a stranger.
This lively atmosphere
is what makes it feel like a family.
It's truly heartwarming.
As long as you are willing,
the Tao family will always welcome you.
Thank you, Minister Tao.
Since returning to the imperial capital,
I've received so much care
from you and Xihe.
I've been using the aromatic bath
Xihe prepared for me
every day. My knees
don't even hurt anymore.
The scented charcoal Xihe sent me
is especially fragrant
and long-lasting.
Much better than what we have
in the palace.
I've always been sensitive to the cold,
so this winter has been
much more comfortable.
Besides,
the sachet Xihe gave me
is very refreshing.
I smell it every day,
and it keeps my spirits high.
I've been much sharper and
more efficient in handling my duties.
Father, Grandfather,
I suddenly feel like making a few dishes
to go with our drinks.
- Absolutely not.
There's an outsider here.
Why should we let him get a free meal?
In a few days,
when a certain someone is long gone,
you can make fewer dishes.
You don't have to work so hard.
The wontons Xihe made for me
were exquisite.
I learned by watching her
and have been practicing diligently
at the East Palace.
How about
you try my handiwork today?
Then we'll have to trouble you,
Your Highness.
Our elders still have things to discuss.
Let's go to the kitchen
and make wontons.
Northwestern wolf.
I thought when the Duke of Wei arrived,
you'd send him directly
to see my father.
Don't read too much into it.
I don't want to cause trouble
for my father,
nor do I want His Majesty
to be displeased with him.
But the Duke of Wei was very direct
with me
about his disapproval.
but didn't mention
your concerns.
I suppose
you never told him
that you don't want to marry me.
For some troublesome people,
I clean up my own mess.
I don't pass the buck to my father.
The way you say one thing
but mean another
is always so cute.
I've really never seen Youyou like this.
Standing next to that northwestern wolf,
they really look like a pair
of loving newlyweds.
What am I saying?
(Residence of the Heir
of the Marquis of Shunan)
Young Master, it's time to eat.
I'm not hungry.
You see, now that the secret prison case
is solved,
Commandery Princess Zhaoning
found the time
to take care of you.
This was sent from Duke of Wei's Manor.
Did Xihe make it?
Not to eat something made by Xihe
would be such a shame. I'll eat.
The Duke of Wei has returned
to the capital recently
and Xihe still has time
to make porridge for me?
Delicious.
Young Master ate the whole bowl
of porridge.
He even said it tasted good.
Then I'll bring more tomorrow.
Then I'll have to trouble you,
Vice Minister Cui.
You traitorous backstabber!
You'll just pass along things
from anyone, won't you?
Don't give Jin Shan a hard time.
I told him to hide it.
You're injured.
If you don't eat more,
how will your wound heal quickly?
What does my recovery
have to do with you?
What are you looking at?
You're the one
sneaking into my residence,
and you think you're in the right?
You're right.
Why should I be sneaky?
I'll just go in openly.
You just wait.
I'll settle the score with you.
- No...
- Stone Cui.
Vice Minister Cui.
Vice Minister Cui!
Stone Cui.
You may leave.
Go.
Cui Jinbai.
Listen to me.
I was wrong before.
I shouldn't have,
in order to avoid the princess,
used you as a shield.
Don't worry.
From now on,
I absolutely won't bother you anymore.
Is that all you have to say to me?
That's all.
Listen to me.
Bu Shulin,
I have feelings for you.
♪The story is sketched anew♪
♪The moonlight is sewn together
by the dusk♪
♪The tide engulfs the lines on my palm♪
Are you okay?
♪Pushing me to converge with you♪
Have you gone mad?
We are both men.
Are you?
What do you mean?
Don't worry.
I will never tell anyone.
You have your concerns.
But I
just want you to understand my feelings.
Don't come any closer.
♪Reaching out to touch you♪
I don't care what you know.
But you'd better remember this.
I will always be the heir
of the Marquis of Shunan.
Always.
I swear to the heavens
I won't breathe a single word.
Didn't you hear me clearly?
I said I will always be the heir
of the Marquis of Shunan.
I understand.
You can't let go of your duty to Shunan.
It's okay. I don't care.
♪Without a single word of goodbye♪
You've worked so hard
to get to this position.
I am the sole heir of the Bu family.
We can't be like this.
Don't you forget.
I'm the Deputy Chief of Justice.
Judging character and cases is my duty.
I'm certain
this isn't just wishful thinking.
Get out.
Get out right now.
Remember to eat properly.
Duke of Wei,
I am here to escort you.
To win Xihe's heart,
you must rely on your own abilities.
I won't say another word.
Even if you do everything
to please my father and brother,
it's useless.
♪I've hidden so many words♪
♪Too reluctant to tell you♪
♪So never uncover♪
♪The sand that slips away
with one grasp♪
♪The flower that withers
after one bloom♪
♪Silently buried deep inside my heart♪
♪Every answer I gave♪
♪Was both bittersweet and absurd♪
♪Hiding my tear-filled eyes
when I hurt you♪
♪How hard it truly was?♪
♪The wounds that healed
with just a little comfort♪
♪The lies made whole
with a single embrace♪
♪Pretending to be brave
as if I'd never been hurt♪
♪It's a shame I never could♪
♪Give you a moon in return♪
♪With the same open heart you loved me♪
♪I've crossed the wasteland of memories♪
♪Never knowing I was lost♪
♪Why don't you take me away?♪
♪Lead me out of this endless game
of hide-and-seek♪
♪You'll never♪
♪Know how much I long to, long to♪
(No animals were harmed
in the making of this film)