(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the RoV Pro League
2026 Summer World Grand Final.
And here are our two finalists.
A lot of people probably wonder
why we were born.
Some say it's to find happiness.
Others say it's to find
the meaning of life.
But as for me...
I was born to...
win!
For as long as I can remember,
- I've only had one dream.
- Hit it.
Jump.
Die.
And that's to be the best gamer
that no one can beat.
(P'Three is the GOAT.)
(No one can take him down.)
(GMs, stop nerfing the heroes)
(and just nerf him already.)
Triple Kill!
I don't care if I'm playing
against pros or streamers.
I don't care what game it is.
And? Now what?
Hey, hey. There you go.
You sure that's called running?
Hurry, hurry. Come on.
Yeah.
Sorry, kid. I'm just too good...
There's only ever one outcome.
GG, EZ, bro. Way too easy.
And that's for me to win,
win, and win again.
Easy?
Isn't that easy?
This is too easy.
Don't you think so?
Tell you what,
let's play this game instead.
I'll carry you guys to a higher rank.
I'll drop the code.
Come join me, alright?
If you wanna get a higher rank,
come on in.
- Help.
- Help me, Soh.
- Ow!
- Soh!
- Help!
- James, Arm...
- Hey!
- Faster, come on.
- Hurry.
Ouch!
What are you up to, Derpy Kid?
You damn bear!
Let's end this game, baby.
(Survivors escaped. You lost.)
You goddamn bear!
(Did P'Three just get wrecked?
For real?)
(Derya is the support player,)
(but Thr33Gamer is the sufferer.
LOLOLOLOL.)
Derya...
Derya, I'm coming for you.
Derya, I'm hunting you down,
you damn bear!
Whoa, everyone.
That was one hell of a moment.
He was something else.
I've never seen P'Three
lose his cool like that before.
Now I'm dying to see
what that damn bear actually looks like.
Guys,
I don't think...
I can help myself anymore.
I can't help
giving this AAA game five stars.
This is seriously so wholesome, guys.
And I've run out of ways to praise it.
I thought it'd be just a survival game,
but in the end,
I was in a flood of tears.
The love between
an ordinary person and a killer
really touched my heart, guys.
Anyway, I want to thank
the other five people
for coming along
on this journey with me.
I hope we'll get to play together again
in the next game.
This game is seriously amazing.
Soh, we've got a problem.
James, Arm...
- Wait,
- Wait.
you already know?
I know.
- That?
After waiting five years for this game,
the killer ends up
killing the main character
even though they're still in love.
Jeez!
That's not it, man.
The one who's about to die
isn't the guy in the game.
It's you.
Am I going to die?
How is that even possible?
Derya, I'm hunting you down,
you damn bear.
The killer you juked last night...
was Thr33Gamer.
(Found you, you damn bear. @Thr33Gamer)
(P'Three has been looking for you
since yesterday. @Thr33Gamer)
(Time for a rematch, bro. @Thr33Gamer)
(Let's share this
so P'Three sees it. @Thr33Gamer)
Sh*t, look at that.
The viewer count...
- Five thousand...
Sh*t, where the hell
did they all come from?
(Add me right now
before I come hunting for you.)
- Holy sh*t.
P'Three!
Hold on.
You're about to strike it rich, man.
Look at all these donations.
Having you guys here
is worth more than
a billion dollars to me.
Hold up.
Are you acting weird, too?
I have other reasons.
Like what?
I think P'Three is acting a bit weird.
He's so desperate to beat you
because he's trying to
get his pride back.
He lost to a total no-name
like you, you know.
If you run away now,
you'll be running forever.
But...
I wasn't trying to embarrass him.
Yeah, I know that.
But does he know that, too?
What am I supposed to do, then?
Just throw a match or two
and let him win.
Do I really have to do that?
Or do you want him and his toxic fans
to keep trashing you
for the rest of your life?
You want that?
That's not too bad...
Talk some sense into him.
You need to decide now,
Soh.
What's your name?
Uh...
It's Soh.
Thought it was "Derpy."
Based on your channel name.
Oh...
I named it after a gun in a game,
Derya MK12.
What a nerd.
You play a lot of FPS games, P'Three.
I figured you'd know that.
How dare you!
Derya MK...
Hearing that name makes me hungry.
By the way, have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Whoa.
Hurry up and eat it.
Really? Can I have this?
Thank you.
Because tonight...
I'm gonna slaughter you
in cold blood.
You won't be able to eat
for the next three days.
(P'Three finally won.)
(Now that's more like
the P'Three we know.)
(Doesn't anyone else think
that damn bear threw the game?)
(Thought it was just me.
He was losing on purpose, wasn't he?)
(Just look at P'Three's face.)
That's it.
It's finally over.
Wait...
Now what?
I'm done with this.
You damn bear!
You think I, Thr33Gamer,
wouldn't notice...
that you lost on purpose?
- I didn't lose on purpose.
- Liar!
I'm sorry.
Fine, I admit it.
I let you win on purpose.
I just wanted you
to get your pride back,
and I was scared
of your fans coming for me.
Get my pride back?
Are you trying to
low-key call me trash,
having some kid throw the game
so that I could win?
I'm sorry, P'Three.
I'll do whatever you want.
Anything.
I'll even bark like a dog if you want.
Well, let me hear it, then.
Uh...
Wait...
Sh*t,
that was cute.
Don't you worry, Derpy Kid.
This time,
I promise you
there's definitely
going to be a rematch.
No!
No...
Please stop.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Please don't.
No.
No...
No!
Sh*t, this salmon is so damn good.
Thanks for the treat, Soh.
Your beef with P'Three is over,
and you made enough from donations
to treat us to a buffet.
Finally, everything's settled, right?
What?
Why is the salmon so spicy?
Are you alright, Soh?
You've been zoning out all day.
I was just thinking about someone.
Thinking about someone?
- Who were you thinking about?
- Yeah, who?
Well,
it's P'Three.
- What? You were thinking about P'Three?
- Oh, look at you.
- I knew it.
No.
It's not like that.
I was just thinking
about the fact that...
he knew I was losing on purpose.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna run it back for a rematch.
Again?
Dude, this is like
the third time already.
Won't your fans think you're being
a sore loser picking on a kid?
A guy like me wins through pure skill.
I don't need anyone
throwing the game for me.
If I didn't throw it
and ended up winning again,
don't you think his fans
would haunt me for the rest of my life?
You don't have to wait that long.
I'll make sure
my fans trash you right now.
If you don't agree
to a rematch right now...
At this point, I'd rather hide
than get my head bashed in
because no matter what...
- There's gotta be a rematch.
- there will never be a rematch.
(I knew you from RoV.
You're such an amazing Support.)
(I'm a fan, and I'm rooting for you.)
Thank you. I'll do my best
to keep improving.
(Knew you from P'Three's channel.)
(Hey, Derpy Kid. You asleep yet?)
Whoa, P'Three?
(What? Did P'Three just DM you?)
(Oh, P'Three's here.)
- Uh... I mean...
- (Answer him first, Derpy Kid.)
A lot of P'Three's fans
are watching me now.
Thank you, guys.
I'm gonna play one last match.
Does anyone want to join me?
If you do,
I'm about to create a room.
Ready, everyone?
The room code is...
(Derpy Kid, why aren't you
answering my text?)
(P'Three's here.)
(You don't need to give me your time.)
(Spend it with him.)
(Is something wrong, P'Three?
I'm about to go to bed.)
(Are you a 3-year-old?
Going to bed at 9 PM?)
(You were just asking your viewers
to play a second ago.)
Uh, guys...
I'm getting sleepy now.
I think I'll head out for today.
See you next time.
Bye-bye, everyone.
(Trying to run away?)
Gosh, I totally forgot
the app is linked to my phone.
(I know you're trying to
delete the app. Don't even try.)
Is he a stalker or something?
(No, I'm not, P'Three.)
(I'm seriously too sleepy right now.)
(Really? Prove it with a selfie)
(so I know you're not lying.)
Do I really need to do that?
Is he messing with me?
(I'm getting kind of sleepy, too.)
(What kind of monkey is that?
It looks so funny.)
(A B-Ape.)
Isn't it supposed to be an ape?
(Wait, did you mean an ape?)
(Yeah, it can be a B-Ape, too.)
(Really? I didn't know that.)
(Jeez, this is sending me.)
Sending him?
(I'm sorry, P'Three.)
(By the way, did you mean that
I should send you something?)
(Seriously, Derpy Kid?)
(I'm not really up on today's slang.)
Gosh, Derpy Kid.
Sending him?
What is it?
He wants me
to send him something?
Sending him...
Send him off?
Sending him off.
(Do you think
I should wear this on stream?)
(Do you want to be a monkey that badly?)
(You dummy, I was just joking.)
(Oh, were you?)
(Derpy Kid, I have a question.)
(How come you never use a cam
while streaming?)
(Oh, I don't have a facecam.)
(What? You're a streamer
without a facecam?)
(My channel doesn't get
many viewers anyway.)
(And I figured whoever does drop in)
(is probably there for the gameplay.)
(Nobody would want to see my face.)
(I would.)
Mookrata?
(Wait a minute.)
(Are you saying)
(I use a facecam
just to show off my looks?)
So, somtam?
- Gosh, we just had it yesterday.
- No, that's not what I meant.
I wasn't trying to insult you.
I was just talking about my viewers.
Who are you talking to?
I'm starving. Let's go get some food.
(Send me your address.)
(I'm buying you a facecam.)
(Come on, there's no need.)
(I planned on streaming
without it anyway.)
(Come on,
don't you wanna give it a try?)
(When viewers see the streamer's face,)
(it helps them enjoy the game better.)
(It's way better
than just hearing our voices.)
Who are you texting?
You can't stop smiling.
P'Three!
You're Thr33Gamer, right?
You're so handsome in person.
Can we take a photo together?
Sure, come on.
Can you do the cat ears?
- Sure. Absolutely.
- (I get where you're coming from,)
(but as for me,)
(I think I'd be more comfortable)
(if I could keep my life
and games separate.)
(I only started streaming
because my friends told me to.)
(They said it would help me
be more confident.)
(But seeing my viewer count grow)
(makes me want to improve the channel.)
(And it's all
because I met you, P'Three.)
(Thank you so much.)
What's with that smile now?
Mind your own business.
What do you want? Just eat.
(I'm tired of texting.)
(Can we hop on a call instead?)
(Uh... Sure, sir.)
(No need to call me sir.)
You're not as talkative
as you were in the chat.
Then I won't call you that
anymore, sir.
Oh...
I won't call you "sir"
anymore, sir. Oh...
(Sorry, sir. Ugh!)
What are you even saying?
What?
(Are you only talkative
when you're talking to your partner?)
No, that's not it.
I don't even have one.
I'm still just a student.
Come on.
You can be a student
and date at the same time, kiddo.
(Really?)
So...
do you have a partner yet, P'Three?
I'm looking for one.
I hope you find them soon.
Who knows? I might've
already found them today.
I just don't realize it yet.
Well, that's possible.
We walk past
hundreds of people every day.
I might've already met you today.
Me?
How could you have met me?
You don't even know what I look like.
You're right.
So when do I get to meet you?
Oh...
P'Three, I'm getting pretty sleepy.
I'm going to bed now.
Goodnight, P'Three.
(Everything's set. If you're okay,
I'll post it right away.)
(If Derya MK12 loses to Thr33Gamer,
he must stream with his cam on.)
PECHTECH is gonna sponsor you
for a whole year?
That's so sick.
It's not sick, James.
How is it not?
Just think about it.
P'Pech is giving Soh
a full year of sponsorship.
What would he get?
Upgrading the channel and video quality.
Getting more income, followers,
and all kinds of other sponsors.
Wow, it's all good news.
Yeah, that's if he wins.
Have you read what happens if he loses?
Dammit.
(If Derya MK12 loses to Thr33Gamer,)
(he must stream with his cam on.)
Sh*t, with a cam on?
Yeah, exactly.
Who the hell came up
with this face reveal idea?
Could it be P'Three?
Why always me?
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna say yes?
Hey, don't get so stressed out.
I'll ask my friend for you.
What are you doing, Arm?
He's using AI to calculate
your chances of surviving Threenos.
"Threenos"?
My AI buddy says you only have
a 45% chance of winning.
Sh*t.
It really is always you.
Hey, but if you get serious,
no one can beat you.
If you want this to end,
you'll have to fight him one more time.
Trust me.
In this game,
there's no honor among thieves.
If you want to be a survivor,
you have to outsmart the hunter.
How's that? Pretty deep, huh?
Yeah.
Thanks a lot, guys.
(P'Three, did you have anything to do)
(with P'Pech wanting me
to use a facecam?)
(I'm in.)
(I didn't suggest it.
Sorry for the late reply.)
(I did talk to him
about changing the rules,)
(but he wouldn't budge.)
(If you're not okay with it,
you don't have to say yes.)
(Got it. See you, bro.)
Come on, don't be so stressed out.
We'll help you out, right, James?
Yeah, we've got your back.
Yeah.
Are you Mr. Soh?
Yes.
There's a parcel for you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
(FRAGILE)
If I lose,
do I really have to do a face reveal?
(Unknown: Waiting to see you lose.
I just wanna see your face.)
- (Just do it. You'll lose anyway.)
- (I'm sharing this.)
- (Face reveal. Face reveal.)
- (I'm on P'Three's side.)
- (Got many kills today?)
- (Face reveal. Face reveal.)
- (I'm so invested.)
- (We want a face reveal.)
- (Face reveal. Face reveal.)
- (Talk as big as you do off-camera.)
What are you afraid of, Derpy Kid?
I'm right here with you.
If anyone tries to bully you,
just let me know.
I'll take care of them.
I know you have your eyes closed.
Don't you want to open them
and look at me?
So, those who want to see
Soh's face reveal,
drop a comment and tell me why.
"Wanna know if he's handsome?"
Good question.
How could he be more handsome than me?
"You want to see his face?"
Yeah, so do I.
Alright, alright.
Calm down. I get it.
I'll make it happen for you guys.
Alright? I'll make sure of it.
But don't pressure him.
What if he runs away?
Or you won't get to see me
play against that damn bear.
You'll definitely see it today.
(Thank you, P'Three.)
(It felt like
you were right next to me,)
(comforting me the whole time.)
(Who's texting you? Let me see.)
(Is it the damn bear?
You can't stop smiling.)
(Gosh, I'm so here for this.)
Won't tell you.
(Come on, Soh.)
(Show the world what you've got
and crush this famous streamer.)
(Are you ready, Soh?)
I am.
James, Arm, how's the progress?
Over halfway. Hurry up.
Ow.
Do it properly. Stay focused.
Sh*t, come help me.
My heart is racing.
P'Three is definitely getting close.
Do it faster.
Do I need to show you how?
Sh*t, run!
Where are you?
Where are you going, Derpy Kid?
Just let me catch you.
Where do you think you're going?
Come and let me catch you, Derpy Kid.
Let me tell you something.
About that whole "no camera" thing,
I can understand that.
But I'm not gonna throw the game
like someone did.
Take it easy.
Let's just talk this out.
I'm sorry, P'Three.
My friends told me there's no honor
among thieves in this game.
I might not be a thief,
but I'm among them.
So, I have to play like one.
You goddamn bear!
Help.
- Help!
- James, Arm?
- Help me out.
- Hurry.
Where are you, Derpy Kid?
Sh*t.
Where are you hiding, Derpy Kid?
Hey,
where's your friend?
I don't know.
You don't?
Over there?
Derpy Kid,
do you know why
I like playing as the killer?
It's because...
I like you,
especially when your heart is racing.
Where is he?
Hey!
- Derpy Kid.
- Go, go. Quickly.
Hurry.
Derpy Kid!
Where are you going?
You've got nowhere left to run.
Come sit right here.
I'm gonna give you
a very warm welcome.
Don't even think about escaping me.
Should we keep playing for a bit longer?
Fine.
But...
you need to beg me.
Make it cute and adorable,
and I might consider letting you go.
Well,
if you're that eager
for the face reveal, suit yourself.
P'Three, please.
Please let me go.
Pretty please, P'Three?
Please, I'm begging you.
To put it simply,
there's no honor among thieves.
P'Three!
P'Three, no.
No! No...
No.
Soh, you lost.
You have to keep your promise.
A stream...
with your facecam on.
(You lost. Now keep your promise.)
(Turn on your facecam.
Everyone's waiting.)
Do I really have to do it?
Hello, everyone. It's Soh here.
(This is...)
(my first time using a facecam.)
I might be a little awkward.
So, please be kind to me.
(Derpy Kid.)
(Yes?)
(I just wanted you to know that
the reason I wanted to see your face)
(wasn't about winning.)
(I just really wanted to know you.)
(When I'm ready,)
(you'll be the first person
on this channel)
(to see my real face.)
(GG.)
(You, too.)
(You're the best.)
(Thank you. Thank you so much.)
(Oh...)
(I'm still feeling pretty shy.
I'm not really used to this yet.)
(But...)
(Uh...)
(Can you guys slow down the chat a bit?)
(I can't keep up.)
The bear head had me dying last night.
Right, Preaw?
Totally. He was tricky.
- Yeah.
- What do you think, P'Jack?
Great reflexes.
Perfect game sense.
A true natural-born support.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're supposed to
give me the spotlight.
I beat him, you know.
Fine, whatever.
P'Toobtub,
say something nice
about our team captain.
What?
Hey.
Is something wrong, bro?
For this year's tournament,
I might...
withdraw.
- What?
- You'll withdraw?
Why, bro?
I'm gonna be a dad soon.
- What?
- A dad?
So that means...
P'Jane, your girlfriend...
Is she pregnant?
- Huh?
- With four kids?
Four months!
Four kids would stretch her out.
But does that mean
you're going to leave
B.S. Brothers like this?
I'm not leaving you guys.
I'm just stepping behind the scenes
to look at the big picture
and be your coach.
Do you know which position
our team is missing?
The Support.
Correct.
And where are we
going to find one?
I think I have someone in mind.
Hello, everyone.
It's me.
(I need to talk to you
about something important.)
(Can we meet?)
(Where?)
(If you don't mind,
I'll come over to your room.)
(I already got your address
from P'Pech.)
(All that's left is for you
to give me permission to come over.)
Hey, we're heading out now.
Hey, don't go yet.
- What's up?
- Uh, I'll be right back.
Just a second, okay?
P'Three...
He asked to come to my room.
- What?
- To your room?
No, no, no.
Just turn him down, Soh.
Asking to come over
when you aren't even close yet?
Isn't that a bit dangerous?
Look at you.
Are you guys already close?
Not at all.
You can let him come over
if you're okay with it,
and we'll keep you company, okay?
Just set a date and time with him.
Alright, we're off.
I still have to help Arm
carry cases of water up to his room.
Look at him. He's so tiny.
I'll go drop you off.
I'm going to drop my friends off first.
Be back in a bit.
(What day and what time
do you want to meet?)
Sorry, guys.
I was just talking with my friends.
Just a second, guys.
I think they forgot something.
Hello, ma...
Hello, ma boy.
(Wait, was that P'Three's voice?)
(Did anyone else hear that?)
Hello, ma fans.
It's your one and only Three right here.
(Oops, what are you doing
in Soh's room?)
You want to know what I'm doing here?
Hmm...
Maybe to ask him to be my boyfriend.
If you don't shut down your PC properly,
it might crash, kiddo.
Uh...
Uh, it won't crash.
Anyway,
are you...
really here to ask me
to be your boyfriend?
No, I was just messing with you.
Whoa, whoa, seriously?
P'Three, don't mess with me like that.
Why can't I?
Do you actually want me
to do it for real?
No.
So, now that you've come all this way,
what's the important thing
you want to talk about?
Well, before we get to that,
can you...
take off that bear head first?
Can't we just talk like this?
Look, the reason I'm here talking to you
is because I trust you a lot.
I want you to trust me as well.
Hey, it's alright.
We can do it your way.
I'll just wait until you're ready.
It's okay, P'Three.
If it's you,
I think I'm ready.
Come here, let me help you.
Is there something on my face?
It's your champion aura.
My champion aura?
Come join me.
Hello, ma boy.
Hello, ma boy!
Hello.
Three, you're being so cringe.
Hello, ma boy.
What do you think would happen
if P'Three and Soh were alone together?
Man, I don't even want to imagine it.
I bet P'Three would make Soh
so nervous he'd literally freeze up.
Come on, you're exaggerating.
But I think if P'Three
approaches him sincerely,
he'll eventually open up, won't he?
- I guess.
- Yeah.
Are you coming?
I already have a boyfriend.
What the hell?
I'm not coming.
She's weird.
Who's he calling weird?
Hello, ma...