On average,
a person encounters
1,000 people per day.
Which amounts to
29.2 million people
in a lifetime.
The probability of
two people meeting
is 4 in 100,000.
The probability of
getting to know each other
is 5 in 10 million.
And the probability of
falling in love
is only 1 in 1.5 billion.
Liking someone
is a rare occurrence.
So,
when you meet someone who
resonates with you on the same frequency,
it's an incredible
stroke of luck.
But that kind of luck
depends on perfect timing.
Cut.
This is a dating show.
Everyone signed up
to find love.
So what's so lucky
about that?
Meeting on this show
is its own kind of luck.
I told you,
this show is about
taking charge of love.
I'll revise it later.
Your turn,
Henry.
We've gotten
46 applications so far.
First up, the sweet guy.
He's warm, friendly,
and adorable.
He plays guitar too.
Next.
Okay, the second type
is the "bat" boy.
He's hot, cool,
and says
whatever's on his mind.
"Bat" boy?
What's that?
A sexy boy.
Okay.
Okay. Next up,
the class clown.
He's a total dork.
Funny,
always joking around.
Are we really
putting people in boxes?
You like labeling people
that much?
Then what would you be?
Short and feisty?
I'm just trying
to brainstorm.
How many ideas
have you got?
Let's see...
Five.
Come back after fifty.
Lisa, I've got one.
This is January.
She was one of YouTube's
first big influencers.
Her popularity's
slowed down,
but she's still
well known.
Still has a fanbase.
Keep her.
Next is Phil.
He first got noticed
during lockdown.
He's an influencer
and singer.
He blew up recently
after his friends
Clare and Lucas broke up.
He went after Lucas,
and the clip went viral.
I'm not letting go.
Hey! Let go!
You're the cheater here.
And you're making her
play the happy couple?
What kind of man are you?
Own what you did.
Mind your own business!
Clare is my business.
He could work.
Have you reached out
to his manager or agency?
Yeah, but we haven't
heard back yet.
Cole,
he graduated from BYC too.
Know him?
I doubt he'll come.
I don't care how you do it.
I want both of them here
by next week.
It's been a while.
Remember me?
Which one
do you like better?
This one or this one?
(Elevator doors closing)
They're about the same.
About the same?
(Elevator doors closing)
Hi, Phil.
I'm Candy.
I reached out to you,
but I guess
you missed my email.
No worries, though.
Cole knows you.
He's pretty handsome
in person!
The show's called
Love Algorithm.
Three guys and three women
live together
and try to find a match.
Life's too short.
So go after what you want.
Especially when it
comes to love.
You wrote that?
Your dating show's
gonna be a blast.
With Cole,
there's always drama
and messy relationships.
Right?
Let's take a break.
Alright.
Hey, give it back.
Seriously?
Not even one sip?
Nope.
Thanks.
You drank the whole thing!
Hey,
Yaowei! Wenhan!
Jing Tong?
Get over here
and help me!
I got you.
I'll help you too.
Looks like you're
doing well here.
Are you really
gonna do it?
Do you want me to?
Can we stick to business?
This is business.
You can't even
button your own shirt?
Chin up.
So, are you taking
Jing Tong to the prom?
You gonna ask her?
No.
Then
neither of us
goes with anyone.
Fair,
yeah?
Yeah.
And this.
What's this?
Our band outfits.
You wear one,
I'll wear the other.
Here?
Picture us up on stage.
Shining...
Sparkly, sparkly!
Sparkly, sparkly! Haha!
I'm not doing your show.