[Episode 21]
I'm not here as the party being audited.
If you're here as my boyfriend,
you're even more out of line.
This is my job.
I can handle it.
Hello.
I'm safe.
Okay. Wait for me at the gas station.
- Miao Jing.
- Also!
If you jump in again next time
without even telling me,
just because it pops into your head,
I'm seriously not coming home.
Are you coming home?
Didn't you tell me to stay with a coworker?
That doesn't count anymore.
I have something to do.
- Where are you going?
- To pick up a colleague.
Cen Ye?
Get out.
300 yuan, please.
Have you been waiting long?
Go buy two bottles of water.
- How much would you like?
- 300 yuan.
Sir.
Your tank is almost full.
Did you just fill it up?
It's fine. Just put some in.
Okay.
Hello.
Settle pumps three and four together.
Pump three is done. 300 yuan.
One moment for Pump four.
Mr. Chen?
You had business at the checkpoint, too?
I'll drive you back later.
I still need to ride shotgun with Miao.
She has to drive me back.
What? Did you buy a car
before getting a license?
I haven't driven in ages. I'm rusty.
What's wrong with your lips?
You go on back.
Let's go.
Thanks for the gas money.
Dinner's on me next time.
I'll keep Mr. Cen here to talk about work.
You've learned to bite back, Miao.
What?
Nothing. I just never knew you had this side.
I'm a little jealous.
What are you laughing at?
You're bringing up old times.
I'm not sure how to answer appropriately.
After all, I'm your subordinate.
I have to think before talking to you.
It's after hours now.
This isn't your boss bringing up old times.
Do men all think office romances
are exciting and irresistible to women?
You're in a mood.
Today's investigation didn't go well.
Haoyun's convoy changed license plates
before reaching the checkpoint.
Tao Jiang was there, too.
Tao Jiang was there?
Yes.
But it was too far away.
I couldn't get a clear shot.
And the convoy wasn't Haoyun's registered one.
If we hand this over to Hongshen,
we still lack the data to back it up.
- They're very careful.
- Then we'll have to draw them out.
That said,
we've already got the bait ready.
You mean Ding Lei?
You'll have to take one for the team.
When your brother finds out,
a few threats won't settle it.
Aren't you going to ask what he said?
I can guess.
A rough guy like me just can't make sense
of the way you work.
Officially, I can't say anything.
But personally,
if you keep letting Miao Jing walk through fire
for your career and your plans,
I won't let you get away with it.
[Teng City Traffic Police Detachment]
This is your document. Keep it safe.
Thank you.
Let me see your document.
Hi, I'd like to report a case.
Hello.
A truck scraped your car.
So the other driver wasn't in the truck?
It was in the middle of nowhere,
so I didn't dare wait there.
I took a photo of the license plate.
This is it.
Could you help me contact the owner?
I want to go through insurance.
Sure. One moment.
Please write this down.
The owner's contact number is...
Hello.
What is it?
- You two both did two trips yesterday, right?
- Yes.
- Mr. Tao. Mr. Tao.
- Sit down, sit.
Mr. Tao, this is the shift schedule.
Where is Bai? Everyone was supposed to
be on time for this meeting.
Bai's truck got scraped.
He went to the traffic police to handle it.
- A scrape?
- Yes.
How could there be a scrape right now?
Which license plate?
The one he drives himself.
Call Bai. Call until he picks up.
Today's meeting is off.
- Why the sudden cancellation?
- The meeting is canceled.
Who told you to come?
- I came on my own.
- Bai doesn't know you.
I'll tell him it's been handled. Just leave.
Whose number goes on the report?
Chen Yi, do you know what you're doing?
If you want to keep looking into your case,
leave now.
Mr. Chen.
Sorry.
- Bai.
- Mr. Chen.
Mr. Tao asked which mediation room we're in.
- Over there, Room Three.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Hello.
- Mr. Tao.
- Where's the person who reported it?
It was just a minor accident.
They already paid and left.
What's the use of paying?
Do you know how many eyes are on us right now?
That plate has only been put up a few times.
And it just happens to get scraped
in the middle of nowhere?
Well...
Trucks all have blind spots.
It's normal that we didn't see it, right?
Bai, this isn't about a scrape at all.
Someone's looking into us.
Where's Chen Yi?
Mr. Chen was just here.
Someone is making moves behind the scenes.
The audit team's heat is on us now.
What does that mean?
The one who filed the report is the head
of Mingtong's audit team.
Ding Lei.
He was in charge of the old warehouse,
where Cen Ye found fake freight volume.
To distract Mingtong and Associates,
he set his sights on Bai's truck.
Using a decoy was clever.
If he keeps digging,
we won't have time to handle Cen Ye.
We'll be lucky to get out in one piece.
I'll tell Mr. Zhang about this.
You tell Ding Lei to keep his mouth shut.
Come in.
- You wanted to see me, Mr. Chen?
- Have a seat.
I hear Cen has been throwing his weight around
in your team.
I have resources and connections.
Honestly, all I need is a chance.
He won't be above me forever.
Really?
Because I think you're not far
from him taking you down.
What do you mean?
A package I just intercepted from Cen Ye.
See for yourself.
[Customer Transaction Details]
How did he get all this?
You didn't cover your tracks,
and Cen Ye found leverage on you.
What good is losing your temper now?
I'm telling you, if I hadn't stopped it today,
this complaint would have been mailed.
Not just you, Haoyun would be in trouble too.
That's impossible.
Haoyun is waiting for Hongshen's final payment.
Doesn't Cen Ye care if he ruins this listing?
What are you thinking? Don't you get it?
Either way, you and Supervisor Wang go to jail,
while Hongshen and I lose the money.
Mr. Chen.
Since you managed to stop that letter,
you've already thought of a way, right?
If this gets exposed,
it won't help any of us.
What happened today stays in this room.
Hongshen can't find out.
Resign right now.
I'll handle Supervisor Wang.
Resign?
If you don't want your life ruined,
get out quietly.
I didn't know you had the nerve.
When you asked me for the shipping label,
you didn't say it was for this.
But the problem is solved, isn't it?
You're hiding it from both sides.
Zhang Bin won't be that easy to fool.
[Mr. Zhang]
Mr. Zhang, he's here.
Okay. Send him in.
Mr. Zhang, you wanted to see me?
Did you know that
raising fish isn't that different
from raising people?
Most people never realize
they actually spend their entire lives
in a tank just a little bigger than this.
Take Ding Lei, for example.
During the audit,
he grabbed plenty for himself.
But in the end, a few casual words
from you scared him into coughing it all up.
Ding Lei used to be a good dog.
But now he can't stay.
He wanted to shake down Haoyun.
But once he found out about the fleet's
plate swaps, he wanted out.
He didn't dare take any more money.
So, you can't do much if you're that timid.
Don't worry.
I've got dirt on him and Supervisor Wang.
Even if he leaves, he won't dare run his mouth.
I can't find a single flaw
in anything you said.
But there is one thing I don't understand.
The registered contact for that plate is Bai.
None of the port vehicles' business
has anything to do with you.
Why do you have to get involved?
Zhai Feng Mao fooled me once.
I won't let anyone fool me twice.
- That's why Zhai Feng Mao is dead.
- That's why he's dead.
Since you know how to handle the auditors,
I won't bring anyone else in.
You're in charge of this.
And then?
Then you and Tao Jiang switch places.
All port-bound trucks are yours now.
Yi.
I brought you to Haoyun not to work in freight.
Yi, think bigger.
Work hard, and bigger deals will come.
Zhai Feng Mao is dead.
But let me remind you,
no one can just cut ties with the past.
What are you doing here?
After they called you away,
I waited for you to come home.
Forget it. I'm sweaty. It's dirty.
Let's go home.
Chen Yi.
Why are you always like this?
Like what?
Forget it. Let's go upstairs.
[Chen's Rice Cakes]
[Tomb of My Beloved Wife, He Wen Jie]
Wen.
It's been a long time.
A couple of days ago,
Chen Yi bought new bedding for the house.
It had little flowers on it.
I know you wouldn't have liked it.
But he meant well.
Miao Jing is back, too.
She's nothing like she used to be.
She's grown into a lovely lady.
But she's still as thoughtful as ever.
She still remembers my favorite tea
and your favorite food.
She bought these rice cakes for you.
Try some.
Now, the kids are all grown up.
They have minds of their own.
Some things are beyond my control now.
If you were here,
maybe they would listen to you.
I wish you were here.
[Station Chief's Office]
Come in.
Qian.
Still not giving up?
Take a look.
Look at you. You've even got gray hair now.
Everyone gets old.
Before I'm too old to keep working,
I just want to put this to rest.
[Teng City Public Security Bureau]
[Notice of Inquiry]
All right. I understand.
Go home and wait.
I'll submit a report to the higher-ups.
Qian, I'm very confident this time.
I know what you're thinking.
I'll report to the higher-ups.
You know this case, inside and out.
If a special task force is formed,
be ready to be assigned to it.
Got it.
Bye.
When the Criminal Investigation wanted you,
you should have gone.
Any case would be easier than working
at the station.
Do you regret it?
I don't.
My home is here. Where else would I go?
Bye.
Miao Jing, do you have hair gel?
Setting spray.
I'm heading over. See you in a bit.
Can you help me?
Birthday.
October 16.
Identification number.
197 what?
1987-10-16.
Star sign.
Libra.
Blood type: AB.
First met on February 16, 2009.
Favorite...
Why are you shaking?
- Stop acting like a punk on your wedding day.
- Stop kicking me. You've left a mark.
I'm nervous, man. Look, I'm sweating already.
You know what, Yi?
He was just standing here muttering to himself.
Anniversaries, Qiao's identification
number, phone number...
I looked up
the bride-pickup quiz questions last night.
Put it this way. Back in the entrance exam,
if I'd worked even half this hard, one of
the three of us would've made it to college.
You really need to take a break. You don't
even know where your name goes on a test.
Get out of here. Look at us.
Do any of us look like good students?
I'm a little scared.
What if they ask something really heartfelt?
Like what I can promise her and all that.
You know I'm not good with words.
If I say too much, I might overpromise.
And marriage can't run on empty promises.
What do you think, Yi?
When you get married,
they'll block your door too.
Start drafting your answers now.
They're almost ready over there.
Let's go up and pick up the bride.
- Let's go. Go, go, go.
- Let's go.
- Don't be nervous. Good luck.
- I'm going in.
- Good luck.
- Let's go.
You can do it.
- Wrong way. Over here. This way.
- You can do it.
You can do it.
Let's go. You can do it.
- Coming!
Which one is the liquor?
- If it's not enough. I'll go get more.
- Never mind that. Let's...
Come on. You're up so early.
Have some candy, sweetie.
No. Stop messing with me.
- Alright.
- Seriously, don't bother her.
I'll deal with her.
- It's pretty.
- I'll add some more over here.
What would I do without you?
It's so beautiful. I love it.
Quick, close your eyes.
There's a knock at the door.
- Are they here?
- Li Qiao, your friend is here.
Come in.
- Miao Jing.
- Qiao.
- You're here.
- Happy wedding!
- Thank you.
- Stay seated. Keep going.
- Ya Ya, take care of them for me.
- Sure. Have some candy.
- May your life be sweet.
- Thank you.
Here, have some water.
- Come, sit here.
- Right. Take a look at our lovely bride.
Look at the photos the bride took.
- Aren't they beautiful?
- What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm happy.
Here.
- The groom is here!
- He's here, he's here!
- What do we do?
- Hurry! Block the door, quick!
- Don't panic. Don't panic.
- Hide the shoes!
- Block the door!
- What do we do?
Block the door!
Hurry, block it.
What should I do? What should I do?
Where do I hide?
You're gorgeous. Just keep being gorgeous.
- Okay.
- Don't be nervous.
Don't panic.
Okay.
They're here.
Don't shove.
- How can you block the door?
- Show us some sincerity!
Here you are.
Are these red envelopes enough?
There are only a few.
Not enough to share, right?
More. We need more.
- Is it enough?
- Not enough.
Be generous. Hand them all over.
That's all we've got. Nothing left.
- Open the door! Open up!
- Is it enough?
We're getting rich!
Incoming wealth!
What is this? Wait, what is this?
For a wedding pickup, do we need this web?
Man, what is this thing?
We can't let you marry the bride that easily.
That's right.
This is called the Web of Fate.
In a minute, you have to crawl through it.
Dodge all the wrong romantic distractions,
cross every obstacle,
and reach your red thread of fate.
You're taking advantage of my bad leg.
- How am I supposed to do this?
- It's not hard at all.
It's not hard. It's very simple.
Yi, with your skills, can you help me out?
How is it me again?
Come on, Yi.
Yi, I'm begging you.
- The best man!
- Who can I do it with?
You can go against...
Didn't Miao Jing infiltrate their side?
Send her out from your team.
- She and Yi are a good match.
- Just for fun, just for fun.
Miao Jing! Miao Jing!
- Come on.
- Step up. Go, go, go!
Help me out.
- Yi.
- Come on.
- Go on.
- Everyone's in agreement, right?
- Of course.
On my command.
Here.
You can do it!
- You owe me a private dinner.
- I'll arrange a private table for you.
Ready? On my command.
Three, two, one. Go.
Her question is,
when did my heart race the most?
As if I'd let you hear it. Seriously.
Okay, that's a pass.
So shy!
Hold on.
Okay, last question.
But before you answer this one,
let's have someone here warm you up first.
How about our handsome groomsman?
Yi!
We'll throw in two tables just for you.
Two tables just for you.
What promise, from the heart,
can you make to her?
As long as she is safe and sound
and happy, that's enough.
Great!
So cheesy.
That answer was so bland.
- What do you mean?
- That's too bland!
That's what I think too.
I think our groomsman
is going easy on the groom today.
- No.
- Exactly.
- He's just being perfunctory.
- Definitely.
Exactly.
Hold on.
When the groom answers, he needs to speak up,
so the bride can hear him, right?
Make sure she hears you.
Louder.
Qiao, I...
I'll buy you a big house
and give you a good life.
I won't lie to you. We'll be good together.
I... love you.
Great!
Is that enough?
That's good. Good.
Go.
Let's go.
[Wang Family Wedding Banquet]
[Mr. Wang Bo and Ms. Li Qiao]
Why is there another problem?
Didn't we settle this yesterday?
When the host arrives, we need to meet him.
I'll meet the host and go over things.
They're here.
Qiao, look who's here.
Sweetie.
Come here.
Qiao.
- What a good girl.
- I missed you guys.
You look so pretty.
Auntie.
Thank you.
Come over here, sweetie.
That's right. Come here.
- This is from him.
- Thank you.
Hope you have a baby soon.
What do you say to Auntie?
- Here, have some candy.
- Thank you. Here.
Tell Auntie, happy wedding.
Auntie, happy wedding.
Good girl. Sit over here.
- Have some water. Good.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- This is from your uncle and me.
- Thank you.
Your sister is swamped with work.
- She couldn't make it.
- She couldn't make it?
Who was that third question directed at?
Whoever picks up the cue.
- Have some wedding candy.
- Sure.
This is Bo's wedding.
And you're playing Casanova here?
What do you mean?
Have you even thought
about our future together?
It's over!
We're in trouble, Bo.
Bo.
Come here.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Qiao's friend, Hong, just called.
- She said something came up.
- She can't make it at the last minute.
Hong? Hong is the bridesmaid, right?
Yes. We need someone to fill in for her.
The bridesmaid can't make it?
Then I...
What's her height and weight?
Her height?
She's about the same build. About this tall.
Then, Miao Jing, could you help us today
and fill in for her?
How about I do it?
I've never been a bridesmaid before.
Okay. We're short on time.
Let's go.
Tell me again about the process over there.
- Hurry, let's go.
- Right.
The groom goes out first in a minute.
And then...
- See you later. Thank you.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- Bo!
Great-aunt! Great-aunt is here.
You're all grown up.
Of course I have.
Come. I'll take you to meet
my mother-in-law. Let's go.
Here, I'll show you the way. Let's go.
Dear family and friends,
welcome to the wedding celebration
of Wang Bo, son of the Wang family,
and Li Qiao, daughter of the Li family.
At this moment, I'm sure the couple
is ready to walk down the aisle.
Family and friends,
let's give them a round of applause.
Please welcome our bride and groom.
At this moment, with all our family
and friends as witnesses,
our couple has arrived at the altar.
Bridesmaid, please hold the bouquet for now.
And now, please face each other.
Dear groom,
do you take this woman to be your wife?
To love her, protect her,
and stand by her for life?
Do you?
I do.
Do you take him as your husband?
To love him, protect him,
and stand by him for life?
Do you?
I do.
Thank you. Let's bless them once more.
Wonderful!
I now announce, groom,
you may kiss your bride.
Three, two, one.
Congratulations to our lucky friend.
Please introduce yourself to everyone.
Are you here for the groom or the bride?
Please share your wishes, too.
Bo said when he picked up the bride
that you two should cherish each other.
His promise for the future was made
for both of you.
So I hope, rain or shine,
you'll always be there for each other,
for the rest of your lives.
Great.
Thank you.
I never realized
the pool hall could feel this empty.
Bo told me
you gave him 50,000 yuan for his new place.
I'm on my own. I don't really need much money.
I haven't touched a cent
of those dividends from the pool hall.
I just treated it as a loan to Bo.
From now on, you can be Bo's kid's godfather.
I'll be the second godfather.
I know what you're like.
You always do things quietly.
But all the good you've done, we remember it.
If anything comes up, don't keep it bottled up.
Talk to us anytime.
Got it.
I was just thinking about this. Someday...
Bo, Qiao, and their kid.
You, your future...
wife, and your kid.
That makes five of us.
We'll go to a big open meadow,
no one else around, just us.
We'll go camping. Nothing to worry about.
Just relax and enjoy it.
[Diagonal Billiards Club]
[Professional Billiards Training for Teens]
Things have been chaotic these past few days.
Thank you all for working overtime.
Any plans this weekend?
I'll take everyone to the beach for two days.
You pick the place.
The company will cover everything.
Really?
Jing.
No need. Mingtong and Associates
will cover the team's expenses.
- Where should we go?
- Let's go to Puli Island in Country Jin.
Since it's a team-building trip,
we should go abroad.
Right, Jing?
It's a fun place.
What is it, Mr. Chen?
Let's go to Sannan Island.
With so many of us leaving the country,
getting visas would be a hassle.
That works too.
Whatever the boss says.
A trip at all is good enough.
Fine. Either way, it's better than
burying ourselves in reconciliations here.
Absolutely. Yeah.
Sure. No problem.
- Should we buy some necessities? Should we?
- Yes.
- Can we expense them?
- Go ask. No way.
We need sunscreen and stuff.
- Yeah!
- Let's make a list.