Stop sulking already.
Smile.
No matter what your thoughts are,
they have to stop now.
We are only servants. We can only respect him
as one of royal family members.
I saw you enjoy talking to her.
Do you like her?
Dad wanted you to be engaged to Siri.
You know it well that I like Siri.
What's the name of the female vendor in front of the school?
(In unison) Saijai.
She wanted me to give you some snacks.
Who are they? What are they doing in the back?
Your Highness?
Phob?
Hey! Tin!
Tin!
How did you take care of him?
Why did you let him get drunk like this?
You're such a big waste, you servant!
Tin! Tin!
You need to take your master back home right now.
And I will tell on you to my dad that you took him to drink.
Go! Just go!
Bring him here. Hurry up!
Watch out! Don't fall!
Here.
Oh my!
Why are you so drunk like this?
Why, Tin?
Oh, you poor thing.
You're done here, you should take a shower.
I will take care of him.
Let's go.
What?
Why don't you let your son take care of him?
That's right. He can help him get changed.
- You're a woman, you can't do it.
- That's right.
- But…
- You should go. Come on.
Phob, take care of him, okay?
We should go.
Nual? Come on.
Phob, you need to clean him well.
Let's go.
♪ The sun ♪
♪ and the ground are far away. ♪
♪ They are too far apart ♪
♪ and they are unreachable. ♪
♪ Even they are destined ♪
♪ not to be together, ♪
♪ I don't believe that I could only have you in my dream. ♪
♪ Will it be possible ♪
♪ for us to be in love? ♪
♪ It seems so far away ♪
♪ that we couldn't see the end. ♪
♪ I won't have a change of heart. ♪
♪ It's just like the sun ♪
♪ that got to meet the ground at dawn. ♪
♪ It was a brief moment but ♪
♪ I will wait to see ♪
♪ the first light of the day. ♪
Phob!
You shouldn't have taken him to go partying this late.
I tried to stop him.
Stop talking back to me.
You need to pack up
you need to visit your aunt in Ayutthaya with me in two days.
Phob.
Nual said that you will visit your relatives in Ayutthaya, right?
That's right, Your Highness.
For how many days?
A few days, I guess.
- About last night…
- If there is nothing else,
I really need to pack my stuff, Your Highness.
Phob!
I…
There you are.
Actually,
Princess Ruethaisiri is here to see you.
She is talking to your grandma right now.
Got it.
Ruethaisiri just learned how to bake a cake
and she's kind enough to share some to us.
You should try, honey.
Please come and sit with me.
Thank you so much.
Oh my goodness,
the cake looks so good
just like the giver.
It's just like a match made in heaven.
Stop talking already, come on.
You don't want to marry me, do you?
Why did you bring it up?
You've changed since you heard about our engagement.
It seems like you're not comfortable to talk to me.
I…
I still like you the same.
But…
- I just..
- You were forced, weren't you?
I see you as a sister.
When I learned that we needed to get married, I was shocked.
I understand you completely.
We're the 'suitable' couple.
My dad designated my whole entire life.
If we don’t come with titles,
perhaps we could have more freedom in our lives.
You don't want to get married either?
Can we say no to our parents?
What about this?
I will ask my father
to postpone the wedding.
When I come back from the UK,
we can talk about it again.
We should be grown enough by then,
and we need to be firm when we tell the parents
that we don't like each other like that.
I think our fathers should understand.
Good idea.
[We need to talk.]
You called me here,
what can I do for you?
We need to talk.
Can we talk tomorrow?
It's getting late
and it is inappropriate.
What do you mean by 'inappropriate'?
We used to sneak out here to hang out all the time.
That was before this.
Right now,
it is not the same anymore.
What is not the same?
I am still the same.
Is it you
who changed?
At the bar last night,
you still haven't told me
why you tried to avoid me?
Please let it go, don't mind me.
Of course, I do.
Phob, I will leave for the UK soon,
you wish me to leave when things are uncleared like this?
Perhaps,
it is better that way.
Excuse me.
Coward!
You're not Phob that I used to know.
Is this what you want?
You kissed other and now you're acting like this.
I know what happened last night.
You kissed me
and I knew it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it was an accident.
An accident?
What do you mean?
You still haven't told me the truth.
What do you want me to say?
You want me to say that a servant took advantage of his master?
That I didn't know my place?
That I thought of you in inappropriate way?
So that you can be disgusted by me even more?
Do you still think that you're disgusting to me?
♪ The sun ♪
♪ and the ground are far away. ♪
♪ They are too far apart ♪
♪ and they are unreachable. ♪
♪ Even they are destined ♪
♪ not to be together, ♪
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You're dreaming
and you will wake up soon.
If this is a dream,
then I want to stay in my dream forever.
I don't want to wake up.
Then you should keep on dreaming like this.
♪ It seems so far away ♪
♪ that we couldn't see the end. ♪
♪ I won't have a change of heart. ♪
♪ It's just like the sun ♪
But soon
you will study abroad.
So what?
Are you saying that you won't
wait for me when I study in the UK?
I don't care if it will be months, or years,
or all my life,
I will wait for you and you only.
No matter what,
I will forever
be your Phob.
Aren't you the cutest?
I love you.
I love you, too, Your Highness.
It's late, where have you been?
I couldn't sleep so I went out to get some fresh air.
We're here to say goodbye, Your Highness.
We will visit our relatives in Ayutthaya
for a couple days.
You should go
and take care of your relatives until they get better,
then you can come back.
Phob, take this.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You should be gone forever.
You have such a foul mouth.
If you're quiet, nobody would think that you're a mute.
Let's go, Phob.
I wish you two a safe trip.
Come in.
What is it, Tin?
About…
my study in the UK.
What about it? Is there a problem?
Everything is fine.
But I need to ask you a favor.
Is it possible
that Phob could go to the UK with me?
You two can't be apart, can you?
Actually, I think that
Phob is a bright student.
If any of the departments issue scholarships to study in the UK,
I think Phob should join the test.
He could be there to take care of you.
Thank you, Dad.
He wanted Phob to go to the UK with him?
What is going on?
Why did you ask Dad to send Phob to the UK with you?
You should have asked for me.
Oh, come on.
Honestly, you should focus on passing the tests here first.
Are you underestimating me?
You see him better than me?
You only focus on him…
I just figure it out.
What are you talking about?
I saw it the other night
in the back of the bar.
I know what you did.
What did you see?
You're completely drunk.
Right?
So you can Phob can go clubbing all the time?
Stop talking nonsense already.
Why did he act so surprised like that?
They're so weird.
[Ayutthaya]
Thank you so much, Nual.
Actually, I'm not feeling bad at all.
You and Phob shouldn't come all the way here.
It's okay, Cham.
We should be on vacation once in a while.
Well, I need to rest.
Make yourself at home.
Mom?
Aunt Cham looks fine to me.
Should we go back now?
I think we should stay for a while.
We don't need to rush back.
What? Mom!
What are you talking about?
You're moving to Ayutthaya?
Yes, Your Highness.
My relatives can help us.
I think
I will find something to sell
and I can take care of my sick relatives.
Why is it so sudden?
Is everything okay?
That's right. Or you think that
we don't take good care of you?
You can tell me if something is bothering you.
Everything is fine, Your Highness.
I can be who I am
because of this place.
I don't know how to
pay back for your kindness.
It's just that I need to take care of my sick relatives.
And that's all.
Nual? What about Phob?
He will stay with me.
He won't be back.
Nual! Nual!
My dad told me that
he wants Phob to join the test for a scholarship to study in the UK with me.
Please let him go with me.
Your Highness.
I'm forever grateful
for your kindness to both of us.
But…
Phob has to stay here with me.
You're about to get in a way of his entire future.
You know that he's a fast learner and a bright student.
You know that he deserves better education.
I know it well.
But this is the only way…
to protect him
and…
to protect your honor.
What are you talking about?
Who would hurt Phob?
What did my honor have anything to do with it?
Your Highness,
please trust me.
This is for the best.
♪ The sun ♪
♪ and the ground are far away. ♪
♪ They are too far apart ♪
- Do you know what it is?
- Like what?
Like Ngoh!
You saw me as an ugly and dirty-looking guy, didn't you?
I mean you look like Ngoh when he shows his real self.
Ngoh's skin is covered with gold.
But I'm just a servant,
I am nothing like him.
Nobody would toss me a garland
like she did to him.
No garland
but you can have the cotton rose.
So it means that
you choose me, right?
Can you help me
- find a rental house in the area?
- Sure.
Are you sure about moving back here?
You're not staying in the palace anymore?
- Or your masters…?
- All of them
are so kind to me and my son.
That's why
we shouldn't go back there.
What did you just say?
We're not going back to the palace?
Mom! Mom!
What do you mean by us not going back to the palace?
You heard what I said. We will stay here.
- You can't go back.
- Why is that?
You should ask yourself that.
What did I do?
That night, under a cotton rose tree,
I saw you
and Prince Tinnakorn.
If you saw us,
then you would know
that we shared the same feeling.
Why do you have to stop people who are in love?
Didn't you hear what you just said?
It is the truth.
I am speaking the truth.
The prince and I, we are in love.
You can't love him like that.
You should revere him.
- Because he is your master.
- So what?
I can revere him
and let him be my lover. Can't I do that?
- You're about to ruin his reputation.
- Ruin because of what?
Because I am a man?
Or because I am a servant and he is my master?
Both of them.
You should have known
that the sky is high and the ground is low.
You shouldn't dragged the sky to stoop to the ground level.
Mom,
nobody is higher or lower when it's about love.
It is about our hearts.
If the sky and the ground got in my way,
if to be a master and a servant got in my way,
I will destroy them all.
Phob!
Phob! Come back here.
Co..Colo…
nel…means...
a senior commissioned military officer.
Did I get it right?
Damn it! I enunciated it wrong.
Why does it write like that and enuciate like that?
Damn you rain! Stop raining already.
Is that…
Phob?
Tin?
Where are they going?
Didn't I tell you to study?
I just saw Phob
and Tin running to the main's quarters.
- So I was about to…
- You need to go back to your room to study.
Phob!
I thought that I would never see you again.
What happened?
Why both of you need to move out?
I don't get it.
Your Highness,
my mom found out about it.
She knows about us.
What did you just say?
Is it the reason why she wanted you to move out?
What should we do?
Don't you worry.
I will not let anything to get in our way.
I will not give up
and you can't give up either.
Phob, I talked to my dad about going to the UK.
He said that you can join the scholarship's test and follow me.
If you pass the test, you will join me.
We can study abroad together.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We will go there together.
Phob,
you are soaking.
I think you should get changed.
And I will bring you to meet my dad tomorrow.
He will talk to Nual for you.
I don't think Nual would disagree with him.
What is it?
You know what?
I thought that I would never see you again.
Well, you're seeing me now.
Are you still not satisfied?
What if I say that I'm not yet satisfied?
So what do you want me to do?
To satisfy you?
It's late and it's pouring rain.
What are they doing?
Where are you going?
Dad?
What are you doing here?
I really saw Phob.
Tin is with him, too. I don't know what they are up to.
Are you going back to study? Nicely?
But Dad?
Yes.
Your Highness!
Dad!
- What happened between Phob and I ended that night.
- Of course, I trust you.
It's the other that I don't trust.
Not fair! Siam will be in big trouble.
People started to question whom the government is ruling for.
You used to live in Varakulvatin Palace, didn't you?
We should hurry up and follow the plan as we discussed.
Tin, I think that is Phob.