(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
(The Pro League is
every esports player's dream.)
(It's the spotlight)
(that will turn an ordinary kid)
(into a pro with a bright future.)
(I'm sure this isn't
the first time you've heard this name.)
(Standings)
(B.S. Brothers,)
(also known as Bullsh*t Brothers,)
(the Pro League team
that just won't stay dead.)
(P'Pech from PECHTECH)
(saw our potential)
(and decided to sponsor us.)
(Ever since then,)
(we've grown into
one of the Pro League teams.)
(And right now, I think...)
(we are ready
to reach even higher ground)
(because this is
the golden age of B.S. Brothers.)
If you join the B.S. Brothers,
fame, money,
or the chance to join a world-class team
won't be far out of reach, right?
Me? Seriously?
What's with that face?
Are you seriously that shocked
with excitement?
Why do you want me
to join B.S. Brothers?
After playing with you that day,
I saw your potential.
B.S. Brothers is a team
of top-tier pros and beasts
who have god-tier skills.
Just like you.
If we had you on our team,
we'd definitely be even stronger.
But I'm not really interested
in any of that.
Maybe you should try
asking someone else.
No one else has caught my eye.
In my eyes,
there's only you, Derpy Kid.
- Who's gonna replace him in time?
- Yeah.
We have to submit the roster soon, too.
What are we gonna do?
What on earth are you guys doing?
How do you expect to win like that?
I told you to push! Push!
Which hero are you playing?
Wukong.
Wukong? Get out of my cafe. I hate him.
If you know you're gonna die,
heal up first.
Trying to show off
just to end up feeding.
Jeez.
Just go home.
You saw our skills, right?
- I was so cracked just then.
- I'm about to crack your faces now.
Get out of my cafe.
You guys played like total trash.
You can take some time
to think about it.
I'm not in a rush.
(Where is this person
you had in mind?)
(I have to submit the roster
by midnight tomorrow!)
You can give me your answer tomorrow.
What?
Tomorrow? So soon?
You said you weren't in a rush.
What do you want to eat? Salmon?
I just had...
You can always eat more.
My treat, okay?
See you tomorrow.
Adios.
P'Three... Wait, P'Three.
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪(Am I missing you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
Are you asking Soh to join the team?
Yeah.
I am.
I have your permission, right, Arm?
I'm over here.
Oh...
Hey.
What's so funny? Come here.
Get closer.
What's going on?
I don't know.
So, what's the verdict?
Got an answer for me yet?
Hmm?
But judging by the look in your eyes,
I already know what your answer is.
Make me happy. Let me hear it.
I...
I think...
there are many players out there
better than me.
This guy's skills are actually insane.
The Pro League seems cool,
but I don't think
my skills are there yet.
(Hey, we need to
submit the roster by midnight!)
Getting into the Pro League
is a huge opportunity,
right, James?
I'm Arm.
When did you guys switch places?
We didn't even switch.
Exactly. Tell your friend
that he's turning down
an opportunity everyone is dying for.
Well, he's right.
Going pro comes with great benefits.
Girls will be screaming for you,
and if you have a lot of fans,
- you'll make a fortune from donations.
- Exactly.
That's not even including the salary.
Well said.
But the decision is yours.
Why would you say that?
Or...
are you not saying yes
because you don't like me?
No, why would you think that?
Well... I mean...
I challenged you to a match,
made you do a face reveal,
and even barged into your room.
I knew it.
Please don't cry, P'Three.
Don't cry.
It's not like that at all.
It's not that I don't like you.
Then what is it, Soh?
Or is B.S. Brothers
not as cool as other teams?
Uh...
Don't cry, P'Three.
(I'll get him today.)
It's not about you or B.S. Brothers.
It's about me.
And what is...
I just want to play games for fun.
I don't want to compete with anyone.
I'll go get some water.
Does anyone want anything?
What's the deal?
What's going on with him?
- You tell him.
- No, you!
One of you, come on.
I mean, Soh is shy as hell.
Plus, he's socially awkward as f*ck.
Breaking down his own walls
to stream and actually talk to people
is already a big step for him.
It's way more complicated
than you think.
I'll explain everything
when we have time.
Derpy Kid,
I'll have a glass
of butterfly pea lemonade,
mixed with orange juice.
Add some green soda, orange juice,
red soda,
and some chrysanthemum tea as well.
Just mix it all together.
Very good.
Now we've got time.
Well...
And now, we've reached
(36th Youth Block-Building Competition)
the final stretch
of the 36th Youth
Block-Building Competition.
But I must say
there's one team
that stands out above all others,
and that is Soh's team
as the captain of this team has been
the solo youth block-building champion
for three consecutive years.
He's the favorite
to win this competition.
Let's give all of the teams
a round of applause!
- Soh! Soh! Soh!
Whoa, I can't believe...
that Soh has made a mistake
at the very last second.
It's okay. Stay focused.
Let's see how he handles this situation.
Sh*t!
Was it really that bad?
Playing games for fun and competing
are two different things.
The pressure is
on a whole different level.
For real, P'Three.
I'm not saying he will never say yes,
but to change the mind of someone
with such high walls,
you're gonna have to climb over them.
Can you guys be my ladder?
What ladder?
No matter how high those walls are,
I'll make it over them.
What the hell is this drink?
What was he pointing at?
Hey, Arm, we have
more shopping to do, right?
Shopping for what?
Oh, right! Yeah, yeah.
We're heading out then.
- Bye, P'Three. See you, Soh.
- Yeah, see ya.
- Bye-bye.
- Where are you going? Let me come, too.
Hey, Soh.
Soh...
Look...
I really want you on my team.
Though I know you have your reasons
for not being ready,
I still want you
to give me a chance anyway.
Just give me one day.
In just one day,
I'll make you open up to me.
If the day ends
and you're still saying no,
I won't bother you ever again.
I'll show you how I zoom.
Come on, I'll show you
how I drive in reverse.
- Shouldn't you watch the road?
- Oh, right.
Man, this engine is just too powerful.
Keep your eyes on me, alright?
- Keep your eyes on me.
- P'Three,
- Oh, right...
- watch the road.
Damn, this car is fast.
Let's go.
Go.
Whoa, you're driving with one hand?
Wow!
I'm an expert on this map.
I'm a pro. I've played it
since I was a kid.
Wait, where'd you go?
- I'm right here.
- Oh.
I've never lost a match in my life.
Now, press the buttons as they light up.
Just smash them real quick.
Hit them fast, okay?
If you're ready,
let's go!
Ouch, Soh!
Why does my hand...
Why can't I feel anything in my hand?
Is this the end
of my career as a player?
Hey, P'Three!
I'm definitely gonna break the record.
But it's almost at the highest.
Whoa.
I definitely wouldn't want
to mess with you.
Of course. You wouldn't.
Hey, want to give it a shot?
- Let's go.
- But I've never tried this.
Yeah, go for it.
I think it might be broken.
I... I think so.
Shall we try a different machine?
Okay.
Is this machine broken?
I'm sorry, P'Three.
I couldn't get the hang of it.
Hey,
no need to worry about it.
Gaming should be fun, man.
If you lose, you just play again.
Come on, let's try again.
I'm serious this time.
- Is the gun too powerful, P'Three?
- Yeah, it is.
- Yay!
Uh...
There's something in your hair.
Right here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's everywhere.
It's everywhere?
Wait...
P'Three,
this is so cute.
Go for it.
Anyway, can I borrow some tokens
from you?
I only have one left,
and I don't think it'll be enough.
I'm all out of them, too.
And I don't have any cash.
I'll go hit the ATM first.
Wait here, okay?
Just join our activity,
and you'll get tokens for free!
Hey, kids.
Give it a try. I got ten tokens!
- It's for real.
- Go for it.
♪Birthday but with me♪
I'm not really into freebies, though.
But since you want them,
I'll get them for you.
P'Three...
Come on, go, go, go!
Let's do this.
The rules are simple.
Just keep dancing
until the song is over.
You got it.
Don't worry. I've got this.
Dancing is a piece of cake for me.
Look at my hips. Watch my moves.
Ready? Let's do it.
Even better, if you play as a couple,
you'll get a special bonus
of twenty tokens.
You definitely don't like dancing.
Ten is enough anyway.
Come on, I'm ready.
I'll dance, too.
Whoa.
It's twenty tokens, you know.
Alright, let's hit it.
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪It always happens to me
every single time♪
♪Is this how it feels?
Huh? Is that right?♪
♪Thinking of me, aren't you?♪
♪(Thinking of me, aren't you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪It happens to me every single time♪
♪The more it's like this,
the more certain I am♪
♪Mm, that's right♪
♪(That's right, that's right)♪
♪The more it's like this,
the more certain I am♪
♪Mm, that's right♪
- Here are your twenty free tokens.
- P'Three, the game's over.
Sir, here you go.
Thank you.
Whoa, twenty tokens?
Yes, twenty.
If you hadn't joined me,
we would've only gotten ten.
- The game is over. Please step down.
- Oh, we can go now?
Wow, twenty tokens.
- Thanks.
- Let's go for the claw machine.
I thought you'd be too shy.
I thought so, too.
I was hesitant and scared at first.
But now, I feel like
I've unlocked something.
Thank you, P'Three,
for taking me out
to do something this fun.
Playing games with you
really is a lot of fun.
Then come play with me again.
But...
about joining B.S. Brothers,
I'm not sure at all
if I'll be good enough.
And I'm not even sure
if I'll fit in with the others.
I'm just not sure about anything now.
If you think you're not good enough,
I'd have to disagree
because the person
who beat me in that match
definitely doesn't have trash skills.
I can guarantee that.
As for whether you'll fit in or not...
Well...
If you think it's too hard,
just think of it as a game.
A super tough level
that you have to clear.
I believe that if it's about gaming,
you can definitely beat it.
Just like when you got up there
and danced with me.
So, while we're at it,
let's make a bet.
Look. If I win this plushie,
you have to join B.S. Brothers.
Deal. Let's bet.
Come on.
There it is.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh...
I'm just showing you it's there.
Is this machine rigged?
It's literally stealing my money.
What the hell?
I thought you said
games are supposed to be fun.
It's a real blast.
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
This is it.
Hey, hey, hey!
Blow on it.
Go.
(Game over)
As promised...
I won't nag you about this anymore.
Wait, P'Three.
I still have one token left.
Come on.
I really want to
play on the same team as you.
Come play with me.
Hey, P'Three!
Whoa, whoa!
- Whoa, wait!
- P'Three!
I got it.
But...
I have two conditions.
Sure thing.
Tell me as many as you want.
I'll agree to anything.
First,
every time we compete,
I get to wear my bear head
while playing.
Second,
if I feel like I can't do it
and want to withdraw,
please respect my decision.
Of course. No problem at all.
Welcome to B.S. Brothers, Derpy Kid.
Ready to meet the legends
of B.S. Brothers?
There he is. The first one.
Meet Cher, or "Laem"
as everyone calls him.
The Comet Mage.
He plays Mage,
dealing devastating burst magic damage.
Next up...
She's Preaw, the Lady General.
She plays Carry
and is the attack damage carry
the team can't live without.
This guy...
Jack,
or the Lone Wolf.
He plays as a Dark Slayer Laner
specializing in pushing
and keeping the enemies on their toes.
And this one right here.
He's P'Toobtub,
the strategist.
He plans our every single move.
And as for me, the King of the Jungle.
A Jungler,
the backline diver
with insane farming that enemies fear.
And here are the legends
of B.S. Brothers!
Hello.
My name is Soh.
Or...
It's okay, Derpy Kid.
You can think of one later.
You're done talking?
Hey, Jack.
Help me out with the cooking.
Move it.
Got it.
Hey,
Preaw.
Why didn't you call for help?
How can you carry
all these boxes by yourself?
P'Three!
Are you just going to
stand there doing nothing?
- Come on, there are three boxes.
- Watch your mouth, dude.
Why did you have to say it like that?
Is there anything I can help with?
Nothing.
Are you okay, P'Three?
You derpy kid.
Be more careful.
(We are B.S. Brothers)
I'm okay now.
My friends are just silly like that.
You'll get used to them before long.
Is it that obvious
that I'm super nervous?
Crystal clear.
Like it's written on your forehead.
(We are B.S. Brothers)
- Numb2r, Numb2r!
We're number one!
Well...
Look at this. What a mess.
Man, who wrote this?
Where's P'Three?
He should be in the cafe with P'Toobtub.
Just think of it as a game.
A super tough level
that you have to clear.
I believe that if it's about gaming,
you can definitely beat it.
Just like when you got up there
and danced with me.
So how did he manage
to trick you into this?
He didn't.
He didn't trick me.
You don't have to be so polite.
We're probably the same age.
Right, P'Laem?
Yeah, right.
Being in B.S. Brothers,
you just gotta chill.
No need to be so polite or anything.
Yeah.
Just say, "Preaw, you dumbass!"
- Whoa, whoa.
- Just chill.
- You got it, P'Cher!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, Soh, look at this.
She's a total psycho Carry.
- What are you guys doing?
- You want this?
- Stop, you psycho Carry!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- You're gonna get paint everywhere.
- Bring it on!
- No, no, no.
- Take that!
Uh, Preaw did it.
No, P'Laem did it.
- Hey, what? I didn't.
- Well, you dodged!
You guys are so dead.
- Hey, I'm out!
- Get back here!
- Wait! What?
- P'Jack, I'm not with them.
- No, you are. Head in the paint!
- So you want this?
- Grab him! Put his head in the paint!
- P'Jack, I didn't do anything.
- Grab him! Hey, no!
- Man, you're the culprit!
- Soh, move out of the way.
- Hey, don't move!
- This has nothing to do with you. Move.
- Stay right there. No, stop!
Stop it!
Preaw, hey.
Come on.
Bring it.
P'Laem, come here!
Get him! Get him!
Hey, you ready?
What should we do with the newbie?
- Let's give him a proper welcome!
- Don't mess with him!
Stop messing with him.
Oh, you think this is funny?
- You're getting it, then.
- Hey, P'Three!
Laughing, huh? You think it's funny?
Jeez, what are you guys even doing?
Why the hell are you splashing me?
P'Jack, come here! P'Laem, P'Jack!
- Take this.
- Hey, what?
We're a mess.
P'Toobtub really worked me to the bone.
He kept me painting that wall.
Forget about gaming.
Well, well.
I'm curious to see
what P'Three's boy's got.
Think you're pretty hot stuff, huh?
Come on, let's play a couple of games.
- Come on.
- Yeah, okay.
- Let's do it.
- 05...
805?
- 884.
- 805...
- 884
- 80588...
884.
Let's pick our heroes.
Let's go. Let's go!
Whoa, you guys actually know
what you're doing.
Of course. We're pros at this.
Do your job, Jungler.
(Abyssal Dragon has been defeated)
Soh, where are you going?
You're on the wrong side.
I'm on my way.
Support, you're not tanking
any damage. Faster.
I'm being dove!
I can't hold them off anymore.
The inner turret!
(The Blue Team's tower
has been destroyed)
They've got Blade of Eternity.
Ugh, I can't do this anymore.
We lost in the league, and now this...
Man, I'm starving.
Let's go grab some food.
I'm heading home.
Catch you later.
I'm beat today.
Exactly. He made me paint so much
I'm getting jacked.
Look at this. Look.
- I'm out. Noodles sound good.
- What?
Thought we'd play a couple of games.
The noodle lady
won't wait forever. Noodles!
I was just getting started.
- What is wrong with you guys?
- Catch you later, P'Three!
I'm so hungry.
So this is the newbie?
I don't see what the hype is all about.
Yeah.
Three, is the kid you brought
really up for this?
Come on, give him some time.
I'll take care of him.
Make sure you do.
What? Feeling down already?
You scared me, P'Three.
How did you know...
Because you're Derpy Kid.
You're not exactly subtle.
Don't stress about it. Let's go.
I'll drop you at the train station
when we're done tonight, okay?
Okay?
- P'Three...
- Yeah?
Actually, you don't have to drop me off.
I can make my own way back.
What? Who said I'm dropping you off?
I'm...
just going to pick some things up.
Yeah.
Look at you.
I'm kidding.
Of course I'm dropping you off.
Since you're so down like this,
how could I let you go home alone?
P'Three, do you remember
what I told you?
I said if I can't handle it,
I'd ask to withdraw, remember?
I remember your conditions.
I don't think I'm cut out
for the Pro League.
But...
even if you haven't clicked
with the team yet,
you seem to be opening up more.
That alone is a big achievement.
Any better and you'd have to be me.
I'd just hate for you to give up now.
If you still want to keep fighting,
I want to help you
unlock your own achievements, too.
Let's clear this level together, Soh.
(Why are you tagging us right now?)
Hey, I need your help with something.
(You're a Pro League player, Soh.)
(What do you want us to help you with?)
Help me practice RoV.
Watch out for the ambush in the Jungle.
Hold them off.
Take the tower. Now.
Nice work up top. Push it. Push.
They lost their inner tower.
Looks like they're setting up a gank.
Three of them in the bottom lane.
(Dare to rematch, you bullsh*tters?)
(Newbie, big mouth, trash, noob)
Who the hell did this?
Just wait until I find out
which little brat is behind this.
Is it those backseat gamers
who have beef with you, Laem?
You do love pwning those brats.
I don't think so.
(Newbie)
Don't read those things.
Just look at me.
Look, they even left their tag
on the wall.
Jeez!
Should we call the cops on them?
No need.
Those backseat gamers are pathetic.
Yeah, I'm with P'Toobtub on this.
This doesn't need the police.
Three, where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm going to...
deal with them myself. Damn it!
- Let's go, Laem. Come with me.
- Let's go, yeah. Let's do it.
- Why would you bring that chair?
- Well...
- Go!
- Come on.
- Give me the key.
- Alright, move it.
Wait up!
Kids, why the hell did you do that?
I'm an only child of my parents,
not your kid.
Don't blame us
for teaching you a lesson, then.
Don't go crying to your dad
about it, either.
Is that what you did all the time
when you were a kid?
Is that why you think we'd do the same?
You've got guts, Pod,
challenging a Pro League team.
I don't care how good you are
as long as you have
such dead weight on your team.
That's what you think, too, isn't it?
You just haven't said it out loud.
Go on, say it.
Exactly.
What are you talking about?
Nobody's thinking anything like that.
Yeah, right now,
our team might not have
quite gelled yet...
But when it comes to
crushing toxic brats like you,
it'll be a total piece of cake.
We'll see about that.
How about this? Let's do a best-of-five.
And if we win...
You have to repaint P'Toobtub's cafe
and make it look as good as new.
And apologize to us, too.
- Deal?
- Fine.
But if we win,
you have to leave the team
and let us join B.S. Brothers instead.
Is that a deal?
Deal?
Deal.
- Let's show them what we've got.
- Yeah, bring it on.
(The Blue Team's tower
has been destroyed)
(Infinite Slayer has been defeated)
Sh*t, it's an ambush.
(The Red Team's tower
has been destroyed)
Keep pushing. Push it.
- Nice!
- Nice.
(Infinite Slayer has been summoned)
(Vanguard is advancing)
- Wrap it up!
- They're dead.
(The Red Team's tower
has been destroyed)
- Alright.
- Hey, hey, hey!
You're f*cking legendary, my Derya MK12.
Hey, hey, hey!
Keep your end of the deal, Pod.
I'm sorry.
What? I didn't catch that.
Say it again.
I said I'm sorry.
What more do you want, P'Laem?
You shouldn't just be
apologizing to me.
You need to apologize to everyone
for tagging P'Toobtub's wall like that.
Do you have any idea
how exhausting it was to paint that?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, P'Toobtub,
for tagging the wall.
And...
I'm sorry
for looking down on you, P'Soh.
It was an honest mistake.
That excuse again.
I'll forgive you guys,
but don't you go
doing this to anyone else.
They would've called the cops on you.
- Come on, we already said we're sorry.
- We're sorry.
I didn't mean any harm.
We practiced so hard
for that audition, though.
You never got back to us
after you said you'd call, right?
- Yeah.
- Then you just went and picked P'Soh.
But he is legit good, man.
Yeah, he is.
Sh*t, you guys play like trash.
Look, you are just kids.
If you want my advice,
you can be subs
for B.S. Brothers for now.
And if you improve,
I'll let you play in the big leagues.
- Really?
- For real?
- You mean it?
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.
- We're glad to be on the team.
- Look forward to learning from you.
Look forward to playing with you.
Yeah, give it a try.
Let's give them a chance.
Gotta give people a chance, man.
I'll give it my all.
A large mookrata set is here!
Look, you go serve the drinks.
Hey, can someone
grab a tray for the pork?
I'll go get it.
Alright.
- Here's the extension cord.
- Finally found the stove. Took me ages.
It was right there in the storage.
Here. Use this for the sauces.
P'Toobtub, what do you want to drink?
Get me some toilet water
with two ice cubes.
Toilet water with ice?
Go drink it over there.
(Dare to rematch, you bullsh*tters?)
(Newbie, big mouth, trash, noob)
(Only got in
'cause they were short-handed)
With the weather this nice,
let's get some exercise
before hitting the mookrata.
Hurry up, come on.
Move it.
- Go on, move over.
- Put it down. Put the paint down.
- The paint is right here.
- Hey.
How can you paint
all of this by yourself?
- I'll cover the black paint.
- We'll all help you.
It's all over.
Come on, don't just stand there talking.
- The job won't finish itself.
- You won't stop talking.
Got it?
You're getting the paint all over me!
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, newbie, refill the paint.
Everyone, cheers!
That was so satisfying!
I know they were just some kids,
but how long has it been
since our team won?
- Exactly.
- Right.
I didn't think
you'd be this serious, Soh.
You look all quiet and innocent,
but you're an absolute beast.
You're a beast.
Well, you all worked so hard
to finish painting the wall.
If all your hard work went to waste
because of me,
I would have felt terrible.
That's why we had to win.
Soh, what shirt size do you wear?
Judging by your build,
you're not that big.
I'll get you a team jersey.
Thanks.
Our team used to be
just a bunch of chubby guys.
- Hey.
Well, look what you feed us.
Look at all this stuff.
Here, Soh, I grilled this just for you.
Chicken breast is good for you.
Go ahead, have some.
- Hey!
What's up with that?
How could you do this?
You used to be feeding me.
Yeah, and look at you now.
Man, I should file a property claim.
Exactly.
Because that spot next to him
used to be ours.
And why are you whining, too?
Guys.
Actually, I have an idea
for renovating P'Toobtub's cafe.
I think...
the cafe should have
more food and lounge areas.
When delivery riders come
to pick up or drop off food,
they'll have a place to wait.
Plus, we'd attract customers
who aren't just gamers.
Hey, that's a great idea, Soh.
I'm sold.
Thanks a lot.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Your cafe has been around forever.
It really needs a renovation.
For real.
It's like your cafe's
still stuck in the Numb2r era.
Is it cooked yet?
It's taking forever.
Uh...
Anyone want more pork?
See ya.
Hey, how are you getting home?
I'm thinking of calling a ride.
It's late. The Skytrain
must have stopped running by now.
How about you stay at my place?
You still haven't been able to quit,
have you?
What the hell are you doing here now?
I've always liked coming here.
You should know that by now.
Do you think
I'd believe someone like you?
Then why do you think I came?
Because of you?
Is that it?
Put on the slippers.
Go take a shower.
You can barely keep your eyes open.
Okay.
There's no place to put it, so...
I just tossed it on the bed for now.
Thank you.
You helped me unlock my achievements.
Did me just standing here looking cool
really help you that much?
I'm really happy
that you brought me into B.S. Brothers.
You've worked really hard, Derpy Kid.
Keep it up.
This was only the first level.
Want to take a shower?
Yes.
P'Three!
I forgot to bring my clothes in.
Could you grab them for me, please?
P'Three, why aren't you
wearing any clothes?
Why are you coming in?
I'm just bringing you your clothes.
What kind of dirty thoughts
are you having?
Shouldn't you go
put some clothes on first?
I'm gonna do some laundry.
Or do you think...
I'm going to do something to you?
Huh?
Are you sure you're giving this to me?
I am.
After all, it's the first plushie
you managed to win
with your own hard work, isn't it?
I feel like I've just
unlocked an achievement.
I've literally never won one before.
Well, well.
Did the claw machine expert
from earlier already leave?
Hey, watch it.
You've barely joined the team,
and you're already giving me attitude?
Thank you, Derya MK12.
Go on, get yourself home.
Let me know when you're home.
Got it,
Mr. Thr33Gamer.
- I'm leaving.
- See ya.
♪Telling myself, "You'll be fine,"♪
♪'Cause trouble finds me every time♪
♪By PROXIE♪
♪I never wanted trouble in my way,♪
♪Yet somehow it keeps finding me always♪
♪I'm just out here doing my thing,♪
♪Goofing around,
worrying 'bout nothing,♪
♪Then luck's gone cold,
and love brought pain,♪
♪I've learned my lesson,
no more love again♪
♪Yeah, I know,
I said that last time, too♪
♪My friends went,
"We've heard that from you"♪
♪Even my mom said,
"Here we go, déjà vu"♪
♪Love keeps chasing me
though I never ask it to♪
♪I don't know why fate keeps testing me♪
♪It's as if this was meant to be♪
♪A thousand thoughts
keep running through,♪
♪But all I ever think about is you♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
♪Rain wherever I go,
lights go out at home,♪
♪Seems like misfortune
won't leave me alone♪
♪Almost broke my leg
as I ran out of luck♪
♪'Cause I just fell in love,
I guess that sucks♪
♪I'm Player One,
will you be my Player Two?♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪