As the son of a major CEO,
excelling in both academics and sports,
Naoya ruled at the very
top of the school's hierarchy.
But I'm the only one
who knows the real Naoya.
Constantly bearing the pressure
from his parents and everyone around him,
the expression he shows only to me
is so incredibly precious.
Lick it clean.
Understood.
You really do
whatever you're told, don't you?
If I told you to kiss me,
could you do that too?
To make you even more addicted to this,
To make it so you can never leave me,
That's right.
I'm the only one he has.
"The Servant Prince"
(Episode 3)
Hey, Takaaki.
Good work today.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, my fever's gone down.
Dinner?
Yeah, I used the tofu from the fridge.
Do you want some too?
Sure.
Sorry for the wait.
Thanks.
This is the first time
I've had your cooking.
Now that you mention it,
I think it really is the first time.
Let's eat.
This is really good.
I'm glad.
It's seriously delicious.
Thanks for the meal.
Glad you liked it.
What's this all of a sudden?
Sorry.
Do you have any idea how much
I've been craving you until yesterday?
Yeah.
You looked so cute wanting me,
so I pretended not to notice.
Huh?
You really have a twisted personality.
Just let me hold you like this.
Hey, Takaaki.
I...
I'm planning to get a part-time job.
Huh?
I looked around online today.
You see, that Grisa Building.
A restaurant inside is hiring right now.
I sent in my resume
and they got back to me right away.
It's close by,
and it seems they're really short-staffed.
I see.
I know I should probably
find a full-time job,
but I'll treat this as practice for
getting back into the real world.
Got it.
I'll go wash the dishes.
You taking on longer shifts is a huge help.
So, we're counting on you.
Great.
Here you go.
This is your uniform, Goto-kun.
I'm expecting great things from you.
Understood.
Sorry to keep you waiting, party of two.
Right this way.
Welcome. Please have a
seat and wait a moment.
Maybe it's because the upper floors
have offices and a hotel,
the customer base is pretty diverse.
That guy is the most
efficient one here, right?
His customer service,
his movement,
and the way he supports his coworkers...
I see.
- Excuse me.
- Please wait just a moment.
It looks like they really
are severely understaffed.
I'm Goto Naoya, starting work here today.
Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mori, the floor manager.
Ah, from yesterday...
I'm Harumoto Nana, a part-timer.
I'm Suzuki Hiroki, a part-timer.
Since it's your first day, you'll be training
while helping out with the lunch rush.
Harumoto, make sure to show him the ropes.
Got it.
We've been packed lately,
so it's great to have you here.
We really appreciate it.
We couldn't handle it all on our own.
We're counting on you, Goto-kun.
Understood.
Sorry for the wait.
Here is the spicy tomato pasta.
And the side salad.
Enjoy your meal.
- Welcome. Party of two?
- Yes, two.
Right this way.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, how can I help you?
What kind of ingredient is the Ise lobster?
The Ise lobster is a delicacy...
Wow, Goto-kun.
He hit the ground running.
Ouch...
Enjoy your meal.
Hey, you there.
Yeah, you.
Yes?
Move me to that table over there.
I'm very sorry, sir.
That table is already reserved.
Don't give me that.
It's been empty
since before I even got here.
We sincerely apologize
for making you feel uncomfortable.
You are more than welcome to make
a reservation before your next visit.
That's enough, stop it.
Excuse me.
Good work today.
Good work.
Goto-kun,
we really owe you for earlier.
You handled that complaint perfectly.
Seriously.
I had no idea what to do.
But you handled it so calmly.
That was amazing.
We definitely learned a lot from that.
Thank you.
It was nothing.
We're counting on you again tomorrow.
Understood.
I feel like I'm fitting in
better than I expected.
I've always lived my life
as the CEO's son.
Naoya-san, as expected
of the president's son.
You're truly outstanding.
Everyone has such high hopes for you.
Please let us follow you
for the rest of our lives.
Let's build a truly great company together.
Those sycophants,
in the blink of an eye,
turned their backs on me.
Ruining the company.
What a useless piece of trash.
As expected, relying solely on his parents'
coattails, he can't do anything right.
No one has ever truly
looked at me for who I am.
But working just as an ordinary
'Goto Naoya',
Thank you for coming.
We hope to see you again.
It is surprisingly fun.
Looks like things are going well.
It's going alright.
If you have some spare time,
could you help me out a bit?
Huh?
I've been so busy lately.
It'd be great if you could pre-check
the documents submitted to me.
Is it okay for me to look at them?
Yes.
Hmm.
Ah.
There's a typo here.
Huh?
You're right.
By the way, this form,
wouldn't it be better
to revise it like this?
True.
Become a full-time employee?
Mori-san is planning to leave.
I was thinking it'd be great if we
could leave the floor to you, Goto-kun.
If it's you, Goto-kun, I can leave it
in your hands with peace of mind.
I'd be thrilled if you'd
seriously consider it.
Okay, thank you.
I'll think about it.
This seasonal fruit cake
is also highly recommended.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
A full-time employee, huh.
I never even considered it before.
Excuse me, I'm here to meet someone.
Understood.
You're the guest who reserved
the private room, correct?
You...
Right, I need to show him to his seat...
If it isn't Naoya.
Look at you dressed like that.
I wondered where you'd scurried off to.
To think you were in a place like this,
doing menial work even a monkey could do.
But I guess this just proves
this is all you were ever capable of.
Sir,
I am very sorry.
I will show you to your seat.
Mori-san, I'm fine.
No, you look terrible.
Go take a break in the back.
Please, hurry up.
Understood. Right this way.
I apologize for not recognizing
that was your son earlier.
No.
I don't consider him my son.
At his age, it turns out that he's
only capable of such lowly work.
His mother, who died early,
was also a vulgar woman.
Blood doesn't lie.
How can you say that...
That's all in the past.
I guess I was just young
and reckless back then.
She was nothing but a
pretty face and a nice body.
I hear you have a son
with a very bright future.
That's the son I have with my current wife.
Yuma joined our company this year.
That's certainly something
to look forward to.
He looks to be about my age.
Do you have any regrets in life?
Excuse me.
President Goto.
About the redevelopment project...
Oh.
Goto-kun.
Are you holding up okay?
Mori-san.
It's been a while since
we've had such a difficult customer.
I'm so sorry about my father.
Oh, he really took me by surprise.
He completely treated me like a commoner.
A commoner...
I heard your mother passed
away when you were young?
He even told you that?
Yeah.
My mother was exactly what
my father would call a 'commoner.'
What a stubborn piece of work.
Get out of my sight.
Get out.
It's fine.
And because of that,
I wanted my father to acknowledge
my abilities no matter what.
Even though it was just a pipe dream.
I'm still single at my age.
Not that I regret it,
But if I had a son like you,
you would absolutely be my greatest pride.
Thank you for bailing me out today.
Goto-kun.
I'll see you tomorrow, right?
I'm on the schedule.
The last time I had a meal with my father
was at an unexpected matchmaking dinner.
Thank you all so much for taking the time
out of your busy schedules to be here today.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
I hear Mika-san and Naoya
graduated from the same university?
Yes, we did.
Even from the same department.
Is that so?
Then you two must have a lot to talk about.
Well then, we'll leave you two to it.
Yes, let's go.
Naoya, you know what to do.
These kinds of situations
always make me so nervous.
Yeah, they do.
I was in the international
relations club in college.
What about you, Naoya-san?
Oh, I wasn't really in any clubs.
That makes sense.
After all, you had already decided
to take over your father's business.
I could feel my body slowly turning cold.
No matter how hard I tried,
If anyone found out I was moaning
in the arms of another man...
I would be nothing but
a disgrace to my father.
President.
We still haven't heard back
from Goto Construction.
Is that so?
If they cancel the contract...
That's to be expected.
If anything, they're the ones
who are going to be in trouble.
He's not back yet?
The lights aren't even on. What's going on?
I didn't realize it was already dark.
Did something happen?
I messed up at work.
Messed up?
Hey, hold me.
You can do whatever you want to me.
I got it.
What are you doing?
Hold still.
It's hard to massage you like this.
Didn't you say I could
do whatever I wanted?
I don't care about that.
Just hold me already.
You can be as rough
as last time, I don't mind.
Takaaki.
Look...
This isn't like last time.
Didn't you say you were done
using me to punish yourself?
It's times like this
when you tempt me so easily.
That's not what I meant...
I'm sorry.
What happened today?
I ran into my father
at my part-time job.
I see.
Naoya.
Do you have any idea?
Being here with you right now,
just how incredibly happy I am?
Yeah.
Because I still have you by my side.
Ah, Takaaki.
That feels so good.
I love you.
Naoya.
Instead of always focusing
on what you don't have,
you should cherish what you do have.
Takaaki.
I love you.
(Next Episode)
It's been a while, brother.
If I can't control the things I want,
[Naoya Goto's banking passbook]
and keep them tied to
me, I get incredibly anxious.
Can I come over to your place today?
I'm sorry.
Cancel the rest of my schedule.
The thought of having to let you go
is what hurts the most.