A servant like you has nothing to lose!
My love has dignity too.
Focus on your study and forget everything.
[11 Years Later]
This is Captain Phobthee Munkongphak,
a representative from army's Artillery Division.
Nice to meet you,
Prince Tinnakorn.
Why didn't you stay to watch the show?
It isn't because of the show reminded you of our past, is it?
That's why you can't stand watching it.
I told you that I forget all about it.
Oh, hey.
Do you want to try it?
I don't think so, I don't want to break your camera.
You're so great.
You can write and you can take photos.
I want to be good at something like you.
Oh dear, why do you want to be like me?
I should be the one who's jealous of you.
You have everything; the look, the noble title
and your perfect date like Prince Tinnakorn.
Is everything okay?
Hi, Siri.
There you are.
I got caught up at work so I was late to the show.
Well, who is this?
Chat, this is Ms. Janthorn.
She's a journalist from Lok Siam newspaper.
A journalist from Lok…Siam?
It's you!
You've constantly dragged my name through the mud in your paper!
Give it to me! Give it to me now.
- It's mine.
- Let it go.
- Give it to me.
- It's mine.
- Let it go.
- Give it back to me.
- Let it go and give it to me.
- It's mine.
- Janthorn?
- Did you take a photo of me? Give it to me.
- Give it to me.
- It's mine.
Let me see, what photos did you take?
What are you doing?
Didn't you know that she's a journalist from Lok Siam newspaper?
They attacked the government
and royal family members like us.
I'm writing only facts, I didn't attack anyone.
What facts? You're such a smart mouth.
You're jealous at someone like us.
Give it to me!
Judging from your action,
I think you deserved all those bad words about you.
You bullied a woman in broad daylight.
Phob!
You're taking her side?
You lowlife scumbags!
People like you
have never done anything to benefit the nation!
You're useless!
You're speaking as if
you own a nation.
This land is not reserved only for royal family members.
It belongs to everyone
who gave their blood and sweats to the nation,
including servants
like us.
Noble people who take advantage of
and tyrannize people in lower status deserve to be called useless.
- Phob!
- Chat, let go.
People are watching you.
You're not ashamed of that?
Are you alright?
I'm sorry about my brother's behavior.
If there is anything broken, please let me know.
I'm happy to be responsible for that.
Nothing is damaged.
You're nothing like your brother.
How are you going back home?
Can I give you a ride?
So you can see the doctor and check if you're hurt.
It's okay.
Phob can give me a ride.
I'll stop at his place for dinner first.
How long have you two been close friends?
We've been friends since
Phob left Varakulvatin Palace for a while.
Phob and his mom lived in Ayutthaya
but one of the noblemen scammed their rental.
His hand got slashed so bad.
Where is my money?
It's not time to pay yet.
Oh my goodness!
No! Don't break my things!
Don't break them! Oh my!
Stop! Don't hurt my son.
- Phob, are you okay?
- Mom!
- Phob!
- Where's the money?
I'll get you the money, don't hurt my son.
Here, take it all. You can have it all.
Don't hurt my son! Please!
That's it.
Let's go.
Phob!
How are you?
- His hand got slashed?
- That's right.
When he filed a complaint,
they falsely accused him and he almost went to jail.
Auntie Nual struggled so hard to helpher son
and her valuables were all sold.
That's why they moved to Bangkapi
and met me.
He was struggled that bad?
Yes. Good for him that he is an excellent student.
So he pass the test to be a soldier and won a scholarship to France.
I heard from Princess Ruethaisiri that when he lived in the palace,
you two were close, right?
I guess we both are his best friends.
I don't think so.
You were with him when he had a hard time in life.
Instead, I was the one who gave him the hard time.
So tasty.
Everything is so good.
Let me help you.
Your cooking skill has never changed, still so good.
You're such a sweet talker, always.
I should cook a beef spicy salad for you.
Please? Thank you.
Now you're talking nicely.
You look so tense, what is on your mind?
Are you thinking about Prince Tinnakorn?
Nonsense.
Why would I be thinking about him?
I can tell
that you two were close once.
He is a conservative
and we are progressives.
You two were friends who stand on the different sides,
it must be so awkward.
You can't go soft on him.
We still need insight info from Prince Tinnakorn.
Do you understand?
I know.
I will go to see him tomorrow
and I will get it done.
Hey!
You went to see Prince Tinnakorn?
Phob.
Why do you need to see him again?
Mom, I told you. It's just for work.
The military needs to help him with the Phra Nakhon's celebration.
Are you sure about that?
Don't you worry.
Prince Tinnakorn
will be engaged to Princess Ruethaisiri.
He forgets about me,
all about me.
There is no bonding left between us.
What about you?
Did you forget about him?
Phob.
You need to forget
what hurt you.
Your wish
can never come true.
The sky is high and the ground is low.
We are living in a different world than he is.
It doesn't have to always be like that.
What do you mean?
Chat?
About the soldiers' reimbursement that Phob asked you,
you took care of it, right?
It's all done, Dad.
Good.
Don't embarrass me again.
Janthorn's article
encouraged people to speak up what they used to be afraid of.
The wind is on our side.
We need to start our mission on the celebration day as our original plan.
We can't make a mistake.
We need to know the schedule of all royal family members, in every detail.
We need to know what places they will visit,
when they will visit and who will be around them.
If you want a schedule, then it is easy.
Like we discussed earlier,
Phob was close to Prince Tinnakorn.
He grew up in the palace.
It's time for Siam's transition.
You're our hope.
Yes, sir.
[M.C. Tinnakorn Varakulvatin - His Majesty's Principal Private Secretary]
What?
You're asking for the royal family member's schedule on the celebration day?
Why is it related to your job?
I need to know
so I can provide protection to all of them.
Provide protection?
From who?
Do you believe that
someone would be dissatisfied and they would start to protest?
It is possible.
People are in distress
people are stuggling to live.
In the meantime, some noble people
focus on organizing fancy parties and neglect those who are beneath them.
This is considered as take advantage of
people living in lower status.
All of us are not the same.
You ived in Varakulvatin Palace,
- and it gave you life.
- That's right.
I remember it so well.
The place gave me life
but it took something from me.
It got destroyed to pieces.
Where are you going?
Why are you trying to avoid this subject?
What's wrong?
We used to be even closer than this.
Are you sure you want to forget all about it?
That's right.
I don't remember a thing.
Your past
could mean nothing to you.
That's right.
You should forget about it too.
It meant nothing.
If you forget all about it,
do you want me to remind you?
Let me go.
If you want me to let you go,
your voice needs to be stronger than this.
This one is pretty.
I know, right? I think so, too.
I like this bright blue.
Thank you so much
for accompanying me to pick our the fabric.
We are just two old ladies,
where we are going and what we pick out
are so outdated.
Who are you calling 'old ladies'?
I'm still young and fresh.
I can walk smoothly.
I can get up and sit back down easily.
I will get you! I will get you good.
Stop with your funny comments already.
We're not at our palace, okay?
I need to look over there.
- Where is it?
- They're so pretty.
- Aum.
- Yes, ma'am?
Phob and Tin
were so close when they were young.
Why did Phob leave the palace?
It's because of Phob's mom,
I mean…Captain Phobthee,
resigned to sell her products out of the city.
Then we lost touch with her.
They were so close
why did they
lose touch all of a sudden?
Good question, ma'am.
Right, in the middle of one night,
Phob sneaked into the palace to meet Prince Tinnakorn.
But his father forbade
all of us to talk about Phob the next morning.
Before Prince Tinnakorn left to study in the UK,
he asked me to bring Phob
a letter when he was in Ayutthaya.
What letter?
I can't read so I wouldn't know.
If I can read, I'd read the letter already.
I was just kidding.
Why did you ask?
If you forget all about it,
do you want me to remind you?
Let me go.
If you want me to let you go,
your voice needs to be stronger than this.
I baked some breads
but I was too clumsy, I dropped them.
Hi, Phob.
I didn't know you were coming.
I just feel like they're not so close anymore.
That's why I'm asking.
Oh my goodness, my princess.
Excuse me, ma'am.
People are stuggling to live.
In the meantime, some noble people
focus on organizing fancy parties and neglect those who are beneath them.
This is considered as take advantage of
people living in lower status.
Your Highness,
you are still the same.
You're a lightweight and you still like to drink.
I'm not a good drinker like you are.
You can drink all night and you feel nothing.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing to me?
Janthorn told me that after you left the palace,
you and your mom had to struggle to live.
A nobleman scammed your rental,
you lost everything and almost went to jail.
Is that why you hate us so much?
That's right.
We struggled to live.
But the most painful experience
wasn't the fact that I almost went to jail,
or lost everything,
it was that letter.
Phob?
Every letter
on paper
was so cruel and it cut me deep.
I wanted to burn the letter.
But I couldn't
because it was the last thing
that you gave me.
It reminded me of
how stupid I used to be.
I'm sorry for causing you pain.
But I..
I still meant every word I said in the letter.
Both of us should forget everything.
I can forget it.
But you need to prove to me
that you forget all about it as well.
Prove how?
Are you back, sir?
Oh my!
What bit you?
Look at that, your neck is red.
A mosquito.
Just a mosquito.
You poor thing, it must be so painful.
Phob and his mom lived in Ayutthaya
but one of the noblemen scammed their rental.
His hand got slashed so bad.
When he filed a complaint,
they falsely accused him and he almost went to jail.
Auntie Nual struggled so hard to helpher son
and her valuables were all sold.
You were with him when he had a hard time in life.
Instead, I was the one who gave him the hard time.
Your Highness? Sir?
There is an update from the group asking for the regime change?
I heard that many parties are involved,
including the military,
law graduates, civil officials,
and journalists.
The coordinator is a soldier from Artillery Division,
he is close to Kitti.
I am Captain Phobtheee
from Artillery Division.
I am representing the division and I'm here to ask for clarity
about pension payment for junior rank soldiers.
I don't care who they are,
if they wish to overthrow the regime, they will face with death penalty.
- Aum?
- Yes, sir?
Has Tin left for work yet?
I haven't seen him.
Is everything okay?
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness!
Let's go.
Tin!
What's going on? What?
I saw you and Phob last night, on Charoenkrung Road.
What?
What did you see?
I saw you get out of Phob's car.
What did you do in his car?
I met him by chance.
What is it?
You two met by chance?
Why did you get in his car?
There was nothing.
We need to work together.
Listen to me.
He is a bad person.
He didn't mean well to us.
He didn't care about Dad, he didn't care about me.
He was a servant who happened to do great in his career.
That's why he is arrogant.
Therefore, you can't be around him, you hear me?
He will ruin your reputation,
and our family's reputation.
The only person who is ruining the family's reputation is you.
You should worry more about yourself.
Don't worry about me.
I was just worried about you.
I'm worried that he could hurt you.
In your eyes,
I must be a really bad brother, right?
No! Hey!
You have a date with Tinnakorn, right?
That's right.
Dad?
What if I didn't want to marry Tin?
Why wouldn't you?
His dad and I had an agreement.
What if he didn't love me?
It doesn't matter if he loves you or not.
Our family needs to be bonded with Varakulvatin.
You're a woman, you will have to marry and have children.
Why did you think about it too much?
I have a friend.
She's a talented woman, she can do so many things.
She can make a living independently.
That's absurd.
She is a commoner.
Of course, she needs to work hard to make a living.
You were born in a royal family.
Your duty is to maintain your pride.
You have to marry Tinnakorn.
You?
Hey! What are you doing?
I missed you.
Do you miss me?
Stop doing something crazy.
Something crazy?
- But last night…
- I was drunk last night.
You were drunk?
That's right. I was drunk.
Just drunk.
I used to be drunk like this when I was a kid.
You should know it well.
We are not drunk right now,
we should prove it
to see if you really have no feeling for me.
What? You said he just went in.
Why is the door locked?
Siri, I'm inside.
I'll open the door for you.
Hi, Phob. You're here, too?
Siri, how are you doing?
I hope that we will get another chance to discuss more about this.
I'll see you later.
Thank you.
Hello? Are you here for a cup of coffee?
Are you here by yourself?
I was supposed to be here with Tinnakorn
but..
he's busy.
If that so,
can I join you instead of him?
Sure, with my pleasure.
Is something bothering you?
You can tell me.
It's about my friend.
She has a fiancé.
But it seems like her fiancé falls in love with someone else.
We can punch his face.
He's a player who hurts a woman's heart.
We can't do that. Well…
he is a really nice guy, but they're not in love.
Also,
my friend only see him as a brother,
and nothing more.
If they aren't in love to start with,
why were they engaged?
It's about suitability.
Their parents took care of it.
Arranged marriage couple?
I think when two people are not in love,
they won't be happy together.
That is so easy. We can just…
let him be with a person that he loves.
She shouldn't try to keep him around.
You're right about this.
I feel so much better now that I talked to you.
Well,
can I buy you a cup of coffee as my way to thank you?
Sure, thanks.
Enjoy yourself.
Hello, are you here by yourself?
Welcome.
Sir? How long have you been here?
Right, Sakchai..
- About the money…
- Oh, come on.
We're friends, you can just pay me
when you have enough money.
Actually,
I have something important to tell you.
What is it?
Well,
I heard that a company owned by British people
is looking for new investors
to invest in mining business in Krabi.
Really?
Of course.
I rushed here to tell you this.
If you can invest in the company,
I think we will be so rich.
They will provide 30% of dividend yield
per month, sir.
That much?
Think about it,
if you become a major shareholder of this mine,
you will be well-known and well-respected.
You will bring great reputation to your family.
Great reputation to the family.
I don't have that much salary.
- And I still to pay…
- About that…
don't you worry.
I have a plan for you.
I heard that your ministry is about to do budget planning?
Did you and Phob talk about something else besides work?
Why did you want to know?
My people suspected that
Phob could be a part of the group wanting a regime change.
Are you sure?
There is no evidence.
Did he say something suspicious?
I'm not sure.
We didn't talk much.
Anyways, you have to be cautious.
If he is acting suspiciously,
you need to tell me.
Yes, Dad.
Forward, march.
[Ministry of Defense]
Your Highness.
Are you here to watch the drill?
The celebration day is right around the corner.
I need to check for preparation,
in case someone plans to stir something up.
Your division showed great strength in marching,
I guess Captain Phobthee should take credit for it.
They should have been marching with better form.
The soldiers look so exhausted,
and it could be from delayed pension payment.
It's just a little bit late.
You shouldn't use it as an excuse.
An economic recession happens across the world,
even the noble people's salaries got cut.
Their salaries got cut but they have their own assets
to spend for the rest of their lives.
For junior rank officials,
it could be their death or alive situations.
Many of them need to take care of many people.
It'd be better
if you care about your people.
The noble people have money
because they have been working hard for generations.
We are not robbing anybody.
It's true that you're not robbing anyone,
but you can live like this
because people in this country are working
so hard to pay taxes.
That's why Rattanakosin has been flourished for 150 years.
It's true that people pay their taxes.
Bur our Kings guided the nation
and Siam has never been colonized by anybody.
Also, Siam's honor can compete with other civilized nations.
We have never been colonized.
But we lost to extraterritoriality.
Siamese needs to attend Western courts.
I don't think that looked good.
That's fine.
People have freedom to express their ideas.
They need to fulfill their duties to the fullest
and organize the celebration to show our pride.
We are all Siam's officials.
We need to keep in mind that
if we didn't have royal family members with great vision
to grant scholarships to commoners to study,
many soldiers around here
would have been just a person with no future.
Therefore,
they shouldn't be ungrateful to the country.
Did you have any idea what you just said?
I said that truth.
Did you know that if someone heard you,
they could misinterpret of what you said?
You could be in danger.
Are you worried about me?
You need to lead the army there
and arrest all important royal family members.
If they invade our area, shoot them all.
Captain Phobthee have led the soldiers.