[Kim Hyeonseo as Sung Ho]
[Jung Myeongcheol as Yoo Sehyun]
[Kim Seonghyuk as Kwon Hyukjae]
[Jung Hyunwoong as Kim Minho]
[Sin and Love]
[Episode 4]
Right.
No.
Something's off about
Sehyun and Kwon Hyukjae.
I knew it.
[Sung Ho]
[I...]
[Whenever I see you, I waver.]
Why is there only one cup of milk?
[Got it.]
You look tired.
Did something happen?
I'm fine.
I just didn't sleep well.
Don't act tough.
Are you sure you're OK?
Well,
Minho told me
you rushed out at noon.
It's a personal matter.
I met a friend.
A friend?
Yoo Sehyun?
Yes, well...
We were high school classmates.
We just chatted a bit.
Haven't you...
heard about the Gangnam Palace case?
Rumors are just rumors.
Yoo Sehyun isn't that kind of person.
What are you talking about?
Whether he is or not,
you're a cop and he's a suspect,
you know?
You two shouldn't get involved.
I'm busy.
Let's talk later.
Gosh, damn it.
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
Goodness,
you're boring.
Got it.
We'll talk later.
Did you come looking for me?
Sung Ho,
it's dangerous here.
I'm here to help you.
How are you going to help me?
Kwon Hyukjae
knows about our relationship.
You're in danger here.
I'm not the only one in danger.
You're in danger too.
He's not someone to be trifled with.
Besides, you just
came back from the US.
How can you
even help me?
Do you want to be
stuck in such a life forever?
I said I'll help you.
What's wrong with such a life?
This is
the life I chose.
Sung Ho,
don't come to me again.
Or I'll call the police.
How long are you going to run away?
I said I'll help you!
Let's have a drink together.
Yeah?
That's a first for me,
Mr. Yoo.
Let's have dinner together tonight.
Sure.
Let's go.
Our dear Mr. Yoo,
have a drink.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
I-I was wrong.
Sung Ho!
Why are you here?
Don't touch him.
Stop.
I said, stop!
Don't touch Sung Ho.
Come at me.
Let's go.
Let's go!
I'm not leaving.
You're hurt!
Better than you getting hurt.
Officer Kwon,
you saw that, right?
Ultimately,
Sung Ho lost his cool
because of Yoo Sehyun.
And Yoo Sehyun
has completely fallen
for Sung Ho.
Gosh, what is this?
Hmm?
Minho.
Once a person
has something they want to protect,
they will definitely break,
you know?
Yoo Sehyun will eventually do as I say
because of Sung Ho.
And Sung Ho will
abandon his principles
to protect Yoo Sehyun.
Then, they'll both be doomed.
Do you understand?
Why'd you let yourself get hurt?
Sung Ho.
Are you OK?
I'm sorry.
I crossed the line
just now.
Leave.
And don't ever touch Sehyun again.
Sung Ho.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Dragging you in
and pushing you away,
it's all my fault.
I know.
What?
I know who forced you to push me away.
And I know who did this to you.
You didn't want to abandon me
but to save me, right?
I wanted you to hate me.
Only then
could I push you away.
Because I
didn't want to see you
get hurt anymore.
But why did you...
You fool.
Why endure it alone when I'm here?
Aren't you scared?
I am.
But I'm more scared of losing you.
I'm so scared.
Scared that you'll
get hurt again because of me.
Nothing else matters.
Even if I lose everything,
having you by my side is enough.
Sung Ho.
Can I kiss you?
Does it still hurt?
No.
As long as I can feel your touch,
it can never hurt.
[Sin and Love]