[Adapted from Che Ye Liu Xiang's
novel of the same name]
Xiao Fan, I'm going to stay here
with Lv Qing for a while.
So... I'm afraid you'll have to move out.
Let's get to know each other. I'm Li Wen Xi.
Who is Li Wen Xi?
He's Lv Qing's childhood sweetheart.
Do you know what your most valuable trait is?
It's that you're sensible.
Oh.
Big Bro.
The soup in the pot
will be ready in half an hour.
I...
I'll be leaving now.
It's the middle of the night,
and you're crouching by the door.
- Auntie Lin.
- Aren't you at school?
Auntie Lin.
The dormitory closed early.
I didn't make it back in time.
Why were you out so late?
Xiao Fan.
Let me tell you.
You and Lv Qing are at the same school.
Even though Lv Qing has graduated,
there are still many alumni at the school.
You must behave well at school.
Don't embarrass Lv Qing.
I understand.
Yeah.
I've embarrassed him.
Xiao Fan.
Come sit here.
You're graduating soon, right?
Yes, Mr. Bei.
Do you want to get a bachelor's degree?
I don't want to study anymore.
If you don't want to, then don't.
Starting work early isn't a bad thing.
I'll be going now.
Wait a moment.
Regarding Xiao Fan's job...
I think we should respect his decision.
He is a man of his own mind.
Bye-bye.
Xiao Fan.
Here's the number for your new workplace.
Since you chose to start working early,
do work hard.
The Bei family will treat you well.
Hello.
I'm Lu Xiao Fan.
I'm here to report for duty today.
Xiao Fan, you're here.
Come, have a seat. Come on.
Come over here.
I've been waiting for you.
Come, sit.
Okay.
Xiao Fan, work hard.
I have high hopes for you.
Bro, you haven't been back in so long.
You didn't even come visit me.
That annoying Lu Xiao Fan
watches DVDs in the living room every day.
He whimpers late at night.
It's so annoying.
You should find something to do too.
I'll go back once every few weeks.
I'm busy. That's all.
[Two years later]
[Xiao Ping Calling]
Xiao Fan. What's the emergency?
Can't you call after work?
Big Bro, didn't you page me?
Mom booked a train for next week.
Remember to go pick her up.
Mom is coming to Yunjing?
Have Old Wu pick her up.
I think he's a steadier driver.
You haven't thought of coming home in ages.
By the way, Mom specifically said
she wants to see Lv Xin.
Mom wants to see Lv Xin too?
What's wrong?
Can't a mother-in-law see her daughter-in-law?
Return tickets are hard to come by.
Book one as soon as possible.
She's taking a plane?
It's not easy for Mom to visit Yunjing.
We should let her enjoy herself.
Fine. I'll pay for the ticket.
But you'll need a letter of recommendation.
Just have Old Wu book it.
Does the Bei family need
a letter of recommendation to book tickets?
Oh, right.
Mom said she's bringing the little one along.
To let her see the world.
Okay, I understand.
All right. I'll hang up now.
Be sensible.
Auntie Lin.
Is Mr. Bei not home?
Mr. Bei?
He's at a meeting out of town.
He won't be back for half a month.
Is something wrong with your family again?
My parents are coming to Yunjing.
Then just host them normally.
Don't trouble Mr. Bei with everything.
Lv Xin.
- Lv Xin.
- What?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Help me take this inside.
You're here!
Sir.
Any new releases lately?
Sure. Plenty. Which one do you want?
What's that one?
A martial arts film.
Brigitte Lin is cross-dressing.
I'll take that one.
I like Brigitte Lin, too.
Besides Brigitte Lin,
no one can play Lian Ni Shang well.
It's a pity Lian Ni Shang
had a humble background.
If she hadn't fallen for
Zhuo Yi Hang from a noble family,
she wouldn't have ended up like this.
What a pity.
- I'm off, sir.
- Okay.
Take care. Come again.
- Auntie Lin.
- Oh.
Xiao Fan.
You're back so late.
I didn't save any dinner for you.
It's okay, Auntie Lin.
Go and get some rest.
I'll leave you to it then.
- Hello?
- It's so convenient with a workplace phone.
Have you arranged for Mom's meal with Lv Xin?
I'm working on it.
Is it so much trouble for Mom
to see her daughter-in-law?
Geez.
Don't worry.
I'm at work. I'll get it sorted.
Who are you trying to kid?
With that job of yours,
what could be so urgent?
Who is it?
It's me.
Big Bro.
Long time no see.
What is it this time?
Does your family need money again?
Or is your brother unhappy with his job again?
Or something else?
My mom said she wants to visit me in Yunjing.
Can't you just host them yourself?
She also wants to see Lv Xin.
Maybe you could give her a call?
Fine. I got it.
Big Bro.
Are you really not going to eat?
I'm not hungry.
Then...
I'll get going.
I'm going to stay with Lv Qing for a while.
[Two years ago]
I'm afraid you'll have to move out.
Big Bro.
I'll get going.
See?
He's even afraid to face me.
How can he have the courage or capital
to face your mother?
You know better than anyone
how your mother treated me back then.
You want to know his reaction too, right?
Will he cry?
Will he... fight for it?
You're too proud to ask him yourself.
Is he... simply looking for your help?
It's for the best.
Rather than waiting for your mother
to find out and take action.
It's better to break up sooner.
I'm really curious.
Why did you fall for someone like him?
Aren't you being a bit too nosy?
Our only connection now
is that money in Gangcheng.
I can help you with your goal now.
I'm the one helping you.
Give the information from the old man
directly to Li Wen Xi.
Let him handle the overseas operations.
It's a partnership.
In Gangcheng, there aren't many companies
that can buy out your mother's shares.
I don't want to be controlled by my mother.
Wait a second.
Regarding Xiao Fan's job...
I think we should respect his wishes.
He is a man of his own mind.
Is that section chief easy to get along with?
I need to give him a little nudge.
He's timid.
Deliver the two cartons
of cigarettes in the trunk for me.
We can't let the relationship sour.
This is our new
deputy section chief, Lu Xiao Fan.
From now on, please support him in his work.
If he adjusts well, let him stay there for now.
As for other matters...
Two years.
Two years is enough to get
my mother's shares out of there.
We'll talk about matters again then.
Bottoms up!
It's your birthday,
but all the drinks are coming my way.
Isn't that Lu Xiao Fan?
He fled quite quickly.
Thank you for taking care of me, Big Bro.
I'm very grateful to you.
Did you tell him?
I just wanted you to experience
what it's like to have one on each arm.
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
[Two years later]
[Year 1992]
Isn't this Xiao Fan?
Want to join us for some high-end abalone?
Your brother is here, too.
Zi Yang, I'm busy, so I won't be going.
All for nothing.
My dear Young Master Bei,
how did you get tangled up with him again?
I didn't.
Look at you.
You went to all that trouble
to finally stop
being controlled by your mother.
And it turns out it was all for Lu Xiao Fan.
Fine.
Stop being smart.
What are you trying to say?
You've helped him a lot,
both openly and secretly, these past two years.
In your heart,
he's no longer just a pageboy, right?
If you were worried about your mom
harming him back then,
you could've just told him directly.
I want to go buy a cake.
Today is Xiao Fan's birthday.
So, you do know how to coax him.
They say a rabbit doesn't eat
the grass near its burrow,
but you're even going back for old grass.
I really don't see
what's so charming about Lu Xiao Fan.
Of course you don't.
When I was little,
we had a nanny named Mrs. Zhang.
I was very attached to her.
I would only eat her cooking.
One day, when she came upstairs
to bring me food,
the spoon fell on the floor.
She picked it up and handed it back to me.
I was thinking, if I were her own child,
would she have gone to the trouble
of going downstairs to get me a new spoon?
Are you saying
Lu Xiao Fan would get you a new spoon?
Now, my spoon won't fall on the floor.
Fine, fine, fine.
Here we go again.
Don't tease him anymore.
Lu Xiao Fan takes things too seriously.
Come back.
Big Bro.
Why are you back?
They gave me an extra one,
so I brought it back.
Big Bro, can you say "Happy Birthday" to me?
Happy birthday.
Wait a second.
There.
Happy birthday to you.
All right.
Blow out the candle.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Big Bro.
This cake is as delicious as always.
The rest of the movie isn't that good.
Big Bro, why don't you watch
the international news?
It's fine.
I can watch the tape anytime.
It's okay.
No, really. I'll stop it right now.
I said, I want to watch it.
Get back here.
Tomorrow, make me some porridge.
[Bei Lv Qing: Call when free]
Why did you take so long to call back?
I was at the office.
It wasn't convenient.
I'm at the supermarket.
What do you need? I'll get it all at once.
I bought scallions, ginger,
and garlic last time.
And then... get half a chicken.
And a fish, anything that's fresh.
Get some leafy greens, too.
Buy whatever you want to eat.
Oh, right. Get some eggs, too.
Okay, I got it.
Just buy whatever you like.
Go to my place and wait for me.
I'll be back soon.