Kazumi.
You're awake?
Feeling okay?
Yeah, much better now.
Sorry, it's your day off.
It's fine.
I made porridge. Want some?
Yeah.
Darn, the weather's perfect
for a date though.
Once you're better,
we'll go wherever you want, Himari.
Okay.
Thanks.
Time to eat.
Oh, wait.
It's hot.
I can eat by myself.
Come on, just let yourself
be spoiled at times like this.
Come on, open wide.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Good.
Want some fruit too?
Yeah.
Be right back.
- I didn't have a mom around, remember?
- Yeah.
So when I had a fever as a kid,
my dad fed me porridge like this.
I'd get so happy.
You know, Kazumi,
I think you'd make a great father.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
Your parents must be wonderful people too.
After all, they say children take after
their parents.
Are you okay?
Oh, sorry, my hand slipped.
Be careful.
I didn't have a mom around, remember?
When I had a fever as a kid,
my dad fed me porridge like this.
Family memories, huh?
As for my family... It was falling apart.
- You're going to that woman, huh?
- Shut up!
Who do you think pays the bills?
My father had an affair.
My mother blamed my father,
and he just doubled down.
From that day on, there was no peace at home.
All I could do
was protect my younger brother, Koki.
After my father's affair came to light,
my mother became emotionally unstable.
I mediated between them
to keep fights from breaking out.
You won't betray me, will you, Kazumi?
That was my role in this family.
But no matter how careful I was,
I'd stumble in unexpected ways.
Are all men like this?
My mother,
who was hostile to anything sexual,
lectured me about how vulgar
and dirty such things were.
And yet the urges still welled up.
It's for your own good, Kazumi.
You understand, don't you?
Yeah.
You really are such a good,
understanding boy.
I'd smile without thinking.
Compared to you, Koki's just...
Koki... Koki!
Are you running away again?
- Mom's worried about you!
- Get off me!
Stop pretending to be a good brother.
It's gross.
That naive thought
that I was doing it for my brother...
Everything was terrible.
I ended up hurting everything
that matters to me.
Apple bunnies...
But after meeting you, everything changed.
For the first time,
I was able to love someone.
I want to stay by that gentle smile forever.
I shouldn't touch you
with these filthy hands.
If I did, I'd make that smile vanish.
But if someday,
someone else is going to pluck you,
I want you to bloom by my side.
That's how I feel now.
You haven't told her much
about yourself, huh?
If it were me, I'd tell her everything.
I can't leave Himari alone.
[Vextos]
Can I get your answer
on the Fukuoka business trip soon?
I'm sorry. I'm still undecided.
They're asking for you specifically.
And if you pull this off,
I can push for your promotion too.
What is there to hesitate about?
I'd rather see through
the current project with Yanami.
We'll have Shibasaki take that over.
Nihei will support her.
He's only in his second year,
but he's very capable.
He is capable, but...
Yanami is quite a difficult client...
Trust and delegate to your colleagues.
That's necessary for a leader.
I want to entrust you
with the Fukuoka project.
You'll live up to my trust, won't you?
You really do eat with such joy.
I'm fully recovered now, thanks to you.
Don't overeat and get a stomachache.
Then I'll have you take care of me again.
Oh, right.
There's a place
I want to take you to, Kazumi.
Oh? Where?
It's called Hamagasaki Beach.
I went there once and it was amazing.
I've been wanting to go there with you.
How about next Sunday?
Wanna go?
Sunday, huh?
Do you have plans?
Sorry, I actually got a sudden request
to go on a Fukuoka business trip.
My manager practically begged me,
and I couldn't say no.
Oh, a business trip?
When is it?
This weekend, for two weeks.
My manager said
it might even lead to a promotion.
But I was worried
you'd feel lonely while I'm gone.
That's amazing! It's a great opportunity!
I'll be fine.
Don't worry about me. Go give it your all!
I see.
Then let's go to Hamagasaki Beach
when I get back.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
All right then.
You'll be taking over my project, Himari.
Nihei will be supporting you,
so do your best together.
And have Ando and the others
help with the materials.
Got it. We'll all do our best.
Thank you.
Okay, let's finish eating
and I'll hand the work over to you.
Okay! Let's eat.
Well, I guess that's just how it is.
I wonder why...
Sometimes I feel like Himari's so far away.
Two weeks, huh?
It'll fly by, but still... I'll miss him.
They're quick to respond over there,
so try to reply within the same day.
But this is a big chance.
I want Kazumi to do his best.
He's supported me so much.
I'll do my best too, and support him!
- Thank you.
- Sure.
All right.
Man, what's going on with this?
What's wrong?
Well, it's jammed, but I can't tell where.
I'm good at this. Let me try.
I think it's here.
Oh, I found it.
I can't reach it.
Let's see here.
Let's see...
What's up?
Something got stuck in the back.
Here, try using this.
You sure? Thanks.
I got it!
Good work.
You really helped me.
- It's nothing.
- I'll do the rest.
- Oh, got it. I'll toss this out.
- Thanks.
What about your chopsticks?
- It's fine. I got a spare pair.
- Really?
Oh, right.
There's something I wanted to mention.
- What is it?
- We're taking over Hojo's project.
So, with this, I want you to...
Don't tease your elders, rookie.
Scary...
- I'm fine.
- Thanks, Nihei. I'll take care of Himari.
Good work.
Have I always been this jealous?
Hello.
Hey there.
Taking a break too?
Shibasaki was explaining the work
you're handing over to us,
and we wanted some coffee.
I see.
A sudden business trip sounds rough.
And to Fukuoka, no less.
If it were just work and good food,
I'd go in a heartbeat.
But I'm not great at inserting myself
into already established relationships.
Really?
But you're good at controlling people,
aren't you, Hojo?
What do you mean?
For the record, that's a compliment.
You slip into people's hearts
and give them what they want to hear,
to steer things your way.
I could never pull that off.
You make me sound like some kind of villain.
That's not what I mean.
But...
You shouldn't do that to Shibasaki.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're on break too?
Yeah, just taking a breather.
I made one for you too.
Thanks, Nihei. You're such a capable junior.
Thank you.
It's because I like you.
Huh?
You don't have to answer now.
Anyway, let's get back to the handover.
Wait, what?
You're being loud.
He deliberately stirred things up, huh?
Now that you've met Yanami,
is anything on your mind?
I'm just nervous about
whether I can fill your shoes.
You'll be fine, Himari.
Just call if you need me.
You can even call to complain
in the middle of the night.
Thanks, but I'll be okay.
I can be reliable too, you know.
I know you can.
When in trouble, there's Lady Himari!
So your business trip is in two days, huh?
It's only two weeks.
It'll fly by.
Let's go on a date once everything's done.
You're taking me
to Hamagasaki Beach, right?
Right.
Since it'll be after you come back,
that's in three weeks.
I can't wait.
Yeah. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm hungry.
Since it's late, let's grab food
instead of going back to work.
Sorry, I've got things I need
to take care of back at the office.
I see.
Here. The key to my apartment.
Huh?
Grab some stuff from your place.
Since you'll be visiting more often,
make it so you can stay over whenever.
Why do this all of a sudden?
Is it too soon?
No...
I'm so happy.
So, what did you tell him?
Tell who?
Nihei.
That was just a joke.
He's probably just messing with me.
But what if he was serious?
Then of course I'd turn him down.
Because I have you, Kazumi.
Yeah.
I'll be going then.
I'll come back as soon as I can.
Wait for me.
Okay, see you.
Nihei confessed to her
in front of me on purpose.
Is it really okay
to leave Himari alone like this?
[Hojo]
Coming!
I'm home.
Sorry for intruding.
Just say "welcome back".
Welcome back.
Come in.
Oh, nikujaga?
Yeah, it's still cooking though.
Thanks for waiting. Here you go.
It's rolled dashi omelets.
Yeah, you said you like it, right?
Himari never lies.
- Let's eat.
- Let's dig in.
The fact that she said she loves me,
and that she'd turn down
Nihei's confession...
I understand that objectively.
It's so good!
Glad to hear that. Eat as much as you want.
Try this too.
Thanks.
Himari.
I love you, Kazumi.
I love you too.
And yet, the unease won't go away.
I know.
This is fear.
Kazumi?
That kinda hurts.
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Once again, the thought that
I may break something precious to me...
makes me feel despair.
Here we go.
Feels like a solid team.
That's when I fell for you.
Am I not good enough?
Don't you trust me?
You don't need to change, Himari.
You won't answer me, huh?