If you forget all about it,
do you want me to remind you?
You can't go soft on him.
We still need insight info from Prince Tinnakorn.
You went to see Prince Tinnakorn?
My people suspected that
Phob could be a part of the group wanting a regime change.
Are you sure?
Are you here to watch the drill?
I need to check for preparation,
in case someone plans to stir something up.
Mr. Phobthee.
Mr. Phobthee!
Phob!
What is it?
- Did you hear what you just said?
- It was the truth.
The economy is going downhill and people are struggling.
Instead, aristocrats do nothing about it.
Everyone is trying to save the country.
That is from your perspective.
But in my perspective,
it should have been done better,
not waiting until people are dying from starvation.
You need to stop talking!
You do know that people could misunderstand you
if they just hear what you said, don't you?
You could be in danger.
Why are you smiling?
Hey,
do you care about me?
As a colleague.
Right,
I haven't received the schedule of royal family members who will attend the event.
Where are they staying at?
I can provide them protection.
I told you that it wasn't your job.
I saw the reaction of Kitti and Phob today,
it was obvious of what they had in mind.
They could be planning for the regime change.
Dad?
Actually,
Phob asked me
about the schedule for all royal family members.
He did?
Did you give it to him?
I haven't.
It wasn't his job.
But Dad,
I think perhaps he just felt oppressed
that the country was in trouble,
we're facing economic recession,
I don't think he would do such thing.
Tinnakorn,
I need your help.
Okay?
The regime change?
You dream big, you filthy slave.
Do you remember our conversation
before you left to study in England?
Before I left for England?
Before you left,
you said that you'd talk to our fathers about our marriage.
I remember it well.
I remember it, too.
If you don't want to marry me….
You don't want to marry me either.
I know
that you don't love me.
You love someone else.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
We don't love each other like that
and we shouldn't be bonded by marriage.
The problem is that
I can't talk about this topic to my dad.
He never listens to me.
I understand.
I will talk to my dad and our elderly relatives about this.
Tinnakorn,
even though we wont' be engaged anymore,
I still love and care for you.
If something is bothering you,
whatever it is,
please know that I will always be here for you.
I will listen and help you through it.
Thank you, Siri.
I'm so lucky to have you as a lovely sister,
who always means well and understands me.
Hi, Phob.
Janthorn.
Are you here for the garden festival?
That's right, I want to put it in the news
so I asked Phob to take me here.
Phob, please take care of Tinnakorn.
Follow me.
You look so happy today.
Unlike the other day, you looked so gloomy.
I'm happy because of you
for giving me advice the other day.
Wait,
I thought a friend of your friend
had that problem.
Well, a friend of my friend wanted to say thank you to you.
Have some cake, it's delicious.
How is it? Delicious?
Yeah.
Why are you leading me here?
What do you want?
What are you doing?
What? You asked me about what I wanted.
This is what I want.
Not this.
It's about this.
A schedule about
all royal family members' arrival during the celebration.
Why did you change your mind?
You said that you wanted it for protection plan.
Now that I gave it to you, it'd be over.
And you should stop messing around me already.
Phob!
Prince Chatthorn?
Oh, you still remember me?
I thought you would forget about me.
You're a Captain's mom now.
And you might forget who you used to be.
I'm grateful for all of your family members, I never forget any of you.
You never forget?
Why was your son
so ungrateful to all of us?
He is trying to destroy pride and honor of me and my people.
What do you mean by that?
What did Phob do?
How could you ask me that?
- Your son…
- You found out about Phob and your brother?
Huh?
Phob?
And Tinnakorn?
I tried to stop my son
from being around Prince Tinnakorn.
He could taint the prince's reputation.
What did he to to my brother?
He did something to Tin that night, didn't he? What did he do?
What did he do? What did he do to Tinnakorn?
Tell me! I said tell me! Come on!
Let her go! What are you doing to my mom?
Phob!
Mom!
You took care of what I asked, right?
I did.
If he is a part of the rebellion,
we will find out that day.
Dad!
About Phob's big attempt to transform the nation,
don't you worry a thing.
I handled it already.
How did you know about this?
What did you handle?
I heard about what you and Tinnakorn said,
so I threatened Nual and she passed out.
- I don't think he would…
- How much did you say to her?
I didn't say anything much, she just passed out…
Chat!
You're not helping and you're causing more troubles!
You're so good at stupid things!
Why did you hit me? I was just trying to help.
You? Helping?
If you hadn't done anything,
it would have been better for us.
Now they know about plan
and it was all ruined because of you.
I started to wonder
if you really were my son.
Or someone switched you at birth with a calf!
That's why you're so stupid like this!
Get the hell out of my face! Go!
I don't want to see your face anymore. Go!
Chat.
Dad is still furious, please don't be mad at him.
How could someone like me
be mad at anyone?
Chat.
I'm stupid like a buffalo
I shouldn't have been born as his son.
But..
you shouldn't have hurt Nual like that.
You would just make it worse.
Are you blaming me even more?
That's right.
I'm not you.
- No!
- I did everything wrong.
Since I was young,
I can never be good at anything.
I wasn't a good student.
I couldn't be as good as you were.
Do you know
how much I am jealous of you?
Dad loves only you,
he praises only you.
And me…
I'm not good at anything.
Stop talking like that.
Don't ever think like that.
Stop thinking like that.
You're also his son.
Dad loves you.
Dad loves you, okay?
Not true.
Trust me, he loves you.
And I love you.
You hear me?
Dad loves you, I love you, everyone in this house loves you.
We all love you.
You understand?
If you're not stop crying, I will tell Ruethaisiri.
Will you stop crying?
Good boy.
She has suffered from heart disease.
When she was terrifed about something,
her heart works harder than usual.
And it is dangerous.
I'd suggest her to rest
and avoid hearing news that could upset her.
I understand.
Thank you.
What the hell is wrong with you?
- Huh?
- What do you think?
Do you know who I am? Do you?
You're Prince Chatthorn.
That's enough.
Stop it.
Phob?
You slave!
How dare you do this to me?
What did I do?
I'm here to help you.
Why are you all still standing here?
I'm sorry.
Please go.
See?
I'm here to help you, really.
Therefore,
from now on,
you need to behave, okay?
Don't mess with my mom ever again.
Come on.
Nual! Pleae don't get up, please.
Prince Tinnakorn?
Nual, I…
I'm here to apologize.
I'm apologizing for my brother.
I'm really sorry.
Your Highness,
please don't do that, I'm not worth it.
Did my brother
say anything to you?
He said that
Phob was likely
to ruin your reputation.
Did he know about this?
No, he didn't.
It's not that.
About that,
besides about Phob and I,
did he say something else?
Something like..
Phob's work?
Or
what is his plan?
Did he say anything?
No, I don't think so.
Your Highness,
from now on,
I will stop my son
not to be around you anymore.
It is entirely my son's fault
to cause all the mess.
He was ungrateful for your family.
Instead, he tried to
- ruin your reputation.
- It's not his fault.
Not true. It is his fault.
It is Phob's fault.
He dragged the sky to stoop to his level.
He tried to run away from me.
He really did.
It was me.
I pulled him closer to me.
And it was me who left him.
I caused you and Phob to leave the palace.
I pushed both of you to struggle in life.
I'm sorry. Please don't be mad at me.
Oh my goodness, please don't say that.
You know what?
When I saw that
Phob became Captain, I was so happy for him.
I was happy to see that
he was the same talented man that I knew.
When I learned that after he left the palace,
he struggled so much in his life.
I wanted to praise him
for his effort that he refused to give up.
He is a soldier with bright future.
I will never cause him any damage.
I will never let him
ruin his future because of me.
My sources received the schedule of royal family members
and it is the same information that you got.
It is trustworthy.
The royal ceremony will take place in the first couple of days.
I think we should start our plan the next day
when they arrive and gather up at the theater,
according to their schedule.
It will be easier to control them.
I agree with your plan.
Phobthee, you need to lead our team to that place
and detain important members for negotiation.
There will be no royal family members stay in that place.
Our people will stay there and wait for the fight
against the ungrateful traitors.
We are digging up the pond
and now we are waiting for fish to catch its bait.
[April 7, 1932]
The royal ceremony in the first couples of days
turned out to be so marvelous, Your Highness.
People looked so happy and they enjoyed the ceremony.
I hope it stays this way until the end.
Did you hear what the King said the other day?
When people are happy in the country,
the country will remain its peace.
Our country
has been a peaceful nation for 150 years.
I hope that Siamese people will continue to live happily like this forever,
with no traitors to ruin the peace of the nation.
The important members are gathering up in one place, right?
Yes, sir.
My sources reported that if they'd start the mission,
they would send someone to detain the members first.
If that's the case,
the leader should be a person who is close to Kitti,
Captain Phobthee.
If they break in, you can shoot them all.
Dad?
That's not what you said to me.
You said that if
Phob was involved with this, you'd get him out
and you'd help him.
If he started it, I needed to kill him.
Tinnakorn, you can't go soft on him.
When you reach the destination, tell them to let me know.
Excuse me,
did you see Capt. Phobthee?
He led the soldiers out of this place already.
- He's gone?
- Yes, sir.
Phob!
If they break in, you can shoot them all.
Your Highness?
Phob.
Are you okay?
You didn't ride in the car with the soldiers?
They're done for the day
so they are travelling back to their camps.
What about the protection for aristocrats at the theatre?
You didn't do it?
About the security plan,
the civil officials all agreed that
we should postpone our mission, not to do it today.
There are many people attending the celebration.
It could lead to a bloodbath situation.
I'll tell them to abort the mission.
The Royal Guard has taken over the protection.
It's okay.
It's alright.
I am here with you.
I thought I would never see you again.
Phob!
Phob, you slave!
Go to hell!
Phob!
Your Highness!
Phob, are you okay?
I am not dreaming, am I?
You are dreaming
and you will wake up soon.
Chat is here.
When will Tinnakorn be back?
I don't know either.
It is getting late.
I haven't seen him since after the ceremony. I didn't know where he was.
[Operating Room]
How is he?
He is doing fine.
The bullet grazed his arm, it wasn't lodged in.
I healed his would and it stopped bleeding.
He passed out in the beginning because
he was terrified and stressed out.
Excuse me.
Phob.
Phob, don't leave me.
- Your Highness?
- Phob, don't go.
Your Highness.
I'm here. I'm standing right here.
I'm right here with you.
It's fine.
It's going to be okay.
Your Phob is right here with you.
And I won't leave your side, ever.
Dad, I don't think we should report a missing person to the police.
Tinnakorn will come back soon. He might get drunk somewhere.
Tinnakorn is not like you.
He won't get too drunk to go home.
There must be something happen to him.
Phob?
You should go.
I'm fine.
Tinnakorn?
What happened to you?
- What did you do?
- Dad!
- What did you do to my son?
- Please, no.
Please, don't hurt him.
No! Dad!
Dad!
Why don't you ask your other son?
Who really hurt Prince Tinnakorn?
Phob! You shut up!
Chat? What is going on?
I got ambushed yesterday,
Prince Tinnakorn saw it so he shieled me from the bullet.
He saved my life.
You did that?
Huh?
Chat? Did you try to kill him?
He is lying, don't believe him.
You're still denying it until now?
This is so typical you,
you're such a coward, so useless.
Phob! You slave!
What is going on?
You two used to live together.
I'm sorry, Your Highness,
for causing you some troubles.
I should get going.
What the hell did you do?
Can't you just stay still?
You want to go to jail?
Have you ever thought that
if Phob went to the police, what it will effect me?
He attacked me first.
He told his guys to hurt me.
You expected me to do nothing?
And let that slave stomp on my face for free?
If you hadn't come to him first,
if you hadn't hurt his mom,
he wouldn't have attacked you like that.
You are always causing troubles.
You are always ruining the family's reputation.
Why are you blaming me?
I did all of that
to teach them some lessons.
So he would be scared and stopped the plan to transform the nation
and transform the members of royal family like us.
You've never seen anything good in me.
I have never seen it because you have none!
Chat!
You are so useless to me!
You're such a disgrace to me.
You're so full of troubles.
What had I done so wrong in my past lives?
Why do I have you as a son?
If I only had Tinnakorn as my only child,
I wouldn't have had any bad headache for the rest of my life.
What is going on?
Why did Chat become such a cruel person?
I wonder the same thing.
Prince Chatthorn never liked Phob.
But I don't think he would hate him enough to kill Phob.
It was more than that.
Did you see Vasin
and his reaction to Phob?
They acted as if they were enemies for such a long time.
In the past,
Vasin adored Phob.
And Phob
used to respect Vasin so much.
Your Highness?
Before Phob left the palace.
Prince Chatthorn said that Phob sneaked in to see Prince Tinnakorn.
After that,
Prince Vasin forbade us from mentioning Phob.
Do you think it would be related?
How are you feeling?
I'm fine, just a scratch on my arm.
Why did you have to risk your life like that?
I tried to protect Chat,
protect our family.
If something had happened to Phob,
Chat would have been in big trouble.
Are you sure about that?
It wasn't because you still have feeling for him?
And you could die to protect him?
My feeling
really doesn't matter here.
When the celebration is over,
Phob and I won't see each other again.
Then I should leave you to rest.
Dad?
The celebration went smoothly and nothing happened.
It meant that Phob had nothing to do with
the regime change's team.
Can I ask you
to leave Phob alone?
Stop monitoring him.
We also should stop messing with him.
We won't be in touch with him again.
Can you do that for me?
Fortunately, we didn't start our mission during the celebration.
Otherwise, it would be bloodbath uprising for sure.
We can't sit on it for too long.
The longer we wait, the longer we give them time to plan.
I think we shold take more time.
We need to think and plan carefully.
We still need information from all sources.
Especially from you,
Phobthee.
You need to be around Prince Tinnakorn.
The schedule from the royal secretary was useful to us.
But the celebration was over.
I don't think our path will cross again.
Don't worry about your path with him.
Give me a month,
I will find a way to send you
to work with Prince Tinnakorn
in Royal Palace Office again.
You feel bad for having to lie to Prince Tinnakorn again, don't you?
During the celebration,
- Prince Chatthorn tried to shoot me.
- What?
Are you okay?
Phob!
Prince Tinnakorn was there to save me.
He took a bullet for me.
Janthorn.
He saved my life.
And now I have to use him again.
I know
- that you two were so close.
- Janthorn.
I am so grateful for Prince Tinnakorn.
He has never looked down on me even though I was only his servant.
He made my life in the palace
so happy and peaceful
from his kindness.
Look what I have to repay him,
I'm a traitor.
I betrayed him and I used him.
Phob, listen to me.
I understand that we put you in a tough position.
But what we are doing right now
is nothing personal.
We are trying to transform the nation.
We are doing this for people's rights
and their freedom.
- But I…
- Listen to me,
about the royal family's schedule,
I will ask my sources to look for it.
If we can get one from my sources,
you don't have to get anything out of Prince Tinnakorn.
But if I can't get one,
we need to rely on you.
If he knows what we are doing,
he will hate me for sure.
You said it yourself
that he has never looked down on anyone.
He is a man with great vision.
I believe that when the day has come,
he will understand and forgive you.
The archives for 150th anniversary of Rattanakosin celebration?
Yes, Your Highness.
The army sent me to work with the royal secretary department
so that the archives will be accurate and complete.
How is your wound?
I feel so much better.
But it's been only a month.
And…
many members of royal family are staying in Hua Hin, aren't they?
I don't think there is anything urgent going on.
You should have taken more days off.
Even they are not staying in the city,
there are still papers from various ministries that I need to care for.
You're right.
When are they coming back to the city?
Are they staying at Klai Kangwong Palace for long?
Why do you want to know?
I should know their exact schedule
so I can speed up on the archives when they return.
This way, I don't have to disturb you when you're working.
Captain Phobthee?
Why are you here for?
The prince and I are not strangers.
I don’t have to visit him because of work merely,
perhaps I can visit him when I miss him.
The army sent
him to work with me
about the celebration's archives, Dad.
You need to leave.
You have to leave!
Just go, get out of here!
Why can't I run away from you?
You're coming back, what did you expect me to do?
How can I forget about you?
The sources reported that the soldiers from our side were arrested.
They will spill the members of this movement for sure.
We need to do something to transform the nation soon.