[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Alright, thank you.
Everyone thinks this job is
clipboards and signatures.
Actually, it's surveillance.
And luckily, my co-supervisor
sees everything.
The living, the dead,
and the slacking.
Thank you.
[ROS SNORES]
[SNORES]
[CACKLES]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[GROANS] Hmph!
[MOANS] Hmm.
Tess! Stop it!
I'm sleeping!
Stop messing with me!
[TESS] Hey, Ms. Ros! Your break
ended ten minutes ago!
You know,
if you weren't dead,
I'll shove my foot down
your throat.
Hi, Ros! Break ended at 9:05.
[SIGHS]
Noa,
can you please tell your mom
to stop doing that to me,
or I'm going to spill all
her dirty little secrets!
You're always late.
And your feet
are full of callous.
I thought my tickling powers
would go to waste.
[ROS] Hey, Tess!
You heard me, right?
Mom said, she'll stop.
Okay.
Good.
[GASPS]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Want a snack?
Yes, please.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[GROANS IN PAIN]
I'm sorry, we didn't know
we had another
overflow patient
being brought in.
Jane Doe?
Listen, lady. I just
rolled the beds, okay?
All I know is that she
collapsed in the grocery store.
Hi, I'm Noa.
How can we help you?
Dear, it hurts.
I can't take it anymore.
My stomach hurts.
Don't worry,
we'll take care of you.
Do you have an ID?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Sorry,
I don't have one right now.
Uh-oh, TNT vibes.
That's okay.
Do you have an address?
Uh...
12 Greenhills Subdivision.
Yep, that confirms it.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ma'am?
There's no subdivisions
here in America.
Is she stupid?
My intestine is in pain!
I'm not deaf!
It's fine.
Let's move her to...
Room 511.
Huh? Why are you
putting her in my room?
Noa? A word.
[ROS] I need to tell you
something important.
Come here!
Noa, don't trigger
the silver alert yet.
That's protocol.
How's her family supposed
to find her?
Do you know what they
do to people with no papers?
Especially with an accent
as thick as that?
I'm not breaking the rules.
[GROANS] Ugh!
Excuse me, ladies.
Can I ask you a question?
No, we're not talking to
ghosts here, you crazy person.
Go back to work!
Okay, Ros, don't gaslight me.
I know what gaslighting is.
That's the same tool I
use making you all believe
I can only speak Spanish
and my real name is Atzin.
Wait, your real name
is not Atzin?
I definitely don't like secrets.
They don't care if your
name is James Ingram.
Just mind your own business. Go!
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH] Don’t tell
me to mind my own business!
When you tell me
not to do something,
I’m gonna do it anyway!
I’ll show you what
a real chismosa is...
Whatever!
Where am I again?
Minding your own business?
Ah.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING,
FADES]
Can you at least tell me
anyone's phone number?
[TESS] Oh, is that so?
You brought her here so that
I can be your Tagalog tutor?
What is your...
No, no...
phone number?
I failed as a mother.
Alright.
- Maybe we can start with...
- [GROANS]
- [PHONE THUDS]- Oh!
[GROANS IN PAIN]
What is it? Where's the pain?
Flip phone?
[CHUCKLES] It's like 1997.
You're not helping.
Whatever happens,
don't call them.
[GROANING IN PAIN]
Excuse me.
[JANE] Sir.
Bruh.
- You're ward five, right?
- Yup.
It says you're off today.
Is Noa making you come in
on your mandated rest day?
Well, yes.
Actually, she's a...
She's a slave driver.
[JANE] What?
Yeah.
Not on my watch.
You go be with family.
Touch grass.
I don't care. Just not here.
Family...
If I see you in here,
I'm writing you up.
It's payday.
Live a little.
Right... right.
[INHALES SHARPLY, SIGHS]
- Uh...
- Go live a little.
[SIGHS] Yeah, of course.
[BRIGHT UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRIGHT UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFS]
[MUSIC FADES]
[TESS] It's a miracle.
Dr. Morris answered their phone.
We needed the order.
Plus, she's a little altered,
so UA should let us know
if this is infection-related.
[ROS] Hey!
What's urine got to do
with confusion?
UTIs are the most
common reason
why older folks become
suddenly confused.
Ah,
so that's why Tess is always
nagging me to get a urine test.
Hey, Tess!
If I become a ghost,
you better watch out!
I'll tear your hair off
one by one!
[PHONE RINGING]
Answer it.
[SIGHS] She practically begged
me not to contact anyone.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Then respect her wishes.
Why would you listen to Ros?
Maybe her family
is worried for her!
Maybe that person
knows her family.
[PHONE RINGING]
[ROS SCOFFS] That's not
a contact.
That's a warning.
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Welcome!
OMG, Dolce.
I used to have one,
but it ran away.
Either that,
or I left it at CVS.
- Either way, respect.
- Where is she?
Hi, Beatrice?
- Yes.
- She's resting right now.
Thank God, we were so worried.
(In Tagalog) See? I told you,
it's a good idea to call them.
The boss can also
call the family members.
Is she your mom?
- Yes.
- No. She's not.
But she's like family.
Is she okay?
What happened to her?
She's okay. We gave her
medication for the pain,
but we're gonna need
full consent for a CT scan.
A CT?
Yeah, it could be
something serious.
We can't afford that.
Girl, I know the perfect
pawn shop for your bag
if you need some extra cash.
Oh, foot in mouth?
I'll go take my break now.
Yeah.
- [PRAYING IN SPANISH]
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh...
- [EGG CRACKS]
- my god.
I didn't see anything.
I am just...
uh, looking for my lunchables.
Uh... [STAMMERS]
it's fine. You can look.
[SIGHS]
If I look, legally,
I have to report it.
I don't know to whom.
But still,
that did not look right.
I'm doing
what my grandma used to do.
She was a faith healer.
And I'm a Christian,
so I'm used to
the whole golden rule thing.
What?
Don't judge others
and get judgmental karmic acne,
or whatever.
Right.
What are you
doing that for, anyway?
Haven't you ever wanted
to communicate
with the ghosts in this ward?
[SCOFFS] Did Camille tell you?
I ghosted that guy from Tinder.
He looked nothing
like his profile picture.
Never mind.
Wait, like ghost ghosts?
Because I know how to
open someone's third eye.
[QURIKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHISPERS]
What? Is that true? Really?
- [MONITOR BEEPING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Go watch the kids.
- Okay.
We were so worried about you.
- I doubt that.
- Ros!
No, Noa.
You were not
supposed to call them.
That's what she asked for!
We follow protocol.
Do you even know what
these people have done to her?
Who the hell
do you think you are?
If she did not collapse
in the grocery,
nobody would ever know what
you have been doing to her!
(In Tagalog) I just wanted to
take a little break,
before I go back to...
She's just making up
an excuse.
- That's not true.
- Tell them.
Tell them how much you're
getting paid to be their maid.
- But she's like family.
- Liar!
This is labor, and she's abused.
- Ros, go outside.
- Don't even bother.
- Now!
- No!
- What is...
- I'm so sorry, folks.
Ros!
- [ROS GRUNTS]
- [NOA SIGHS]
[NOA] Ros!
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BRIGHT MUSIC FADES]
[NOA] Ros!
Ros!
Please give us a minute.
You don't hurl accusations
at patients like that.
Just because she's old
doesn't mean she's confused.
It's not our place.
This is all your fault.
You shouldn't have called them.
Trust me, Ros.
I can't break any more rules
than I already have.
How about you trust me, huh?
Your mom may be
a pain in my ass,
but she well knew
enough to listen.
I may not have your degrees,
or your straight A's.
But I have been there.
I have been there!
- Ros!
- [TESS] Noa!
Shhh!
Let's listen.
[NOA SIGHS]
I'm listening.
[ROS TAPPING]
When I came to America,
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I was desperate to send money
to the Philippines.
Desperate for my son.
He's special.
I was a caregiver
in the facility.
This Filipino sponsor
seems so nice.
And you know,
I have this sense of gratitude.
But then it became nonstop.
Every day.
Every hour.
Seven years.
With no day off.
Why didn't you just leave?
How could I?
She kept my passport.
I'm so sorry.
Not until I saw the flyers
of the Filipino Workers Center
here in LA.
Led me to the consulate.
Then the FBI got involved.
I couldn't even make a call.
She said long distance
was too expensive.
I can't talk to my son.
I can't even listen
to his voice.
It hurts.
You don't know how lucky you are
that you've been born here.
We...
we bleed just to get here.
Ros.
I'm so sorry
you went through that.
[ROS SNIFFLES]
[ROS EXHALES]
Noa.
I don't need your pity.
Especially you, Tess.
I don't pity you, Ros.
I hate you most of the time.
But...
I always respect you.
Is she saying something?
She loves you
more than she'd like to admit.
Oh.
So, what do you suggest we do?
It's not like you have
those consulate contacts
on speed dial.
What if I do?
I wouldn't know what to say.
Uh...
you think...
you can hold them long enough?
[WHISPERS] I have a plan.
[TESS] Wow.
Now she has a plan?
I don't know. I don't know.
I get it.
It's so hard to trust.
It's always just been you two.
I'm not asking for forever.
Noa.
Just this once.
Hmm?
Okay.
I'll follow.
You lead.
(In Tagalog) Hey, Tess.
You heard that?
I'm being a good girl here.
So don't you dare
use magic on me
with your unspecified
ghostly powers.
Just three hours.
Okay.
[WHISPERS] Okay?
Three.
[DOOR OPENS]
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WAVES CRASHING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
When do we get the results?
Oh, you can go.
Oh, here they are.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Our Consul General from
the Philippine Consulate General
of Los Angeles,
ConGen Adel.
[MUSIC FADES]
And that lady over there,
our PWC representative,
Ms. Malou Villacisneros.
The President of SIPA,
Ms. Kimmy Maniquis.
[SCOFFS] What is this?
This is so cool.
It's like a mafia movie,
but like, with good people.
We're here to assist Nanny Linda
in coordinate support
from the Philippine government
for a distressed citizen.
Wow, you can do that?
Yes, of course. We are mandated
by the Philippine government
to promote
and protect the welfare
of every Filipina
wherever they are.
- Wow!
- Mm-hmm.
And the lady over there,
Miss Malou,
our PWC representative,
is here to help find
Nanny Linda's
closest living relative.
You can't do this.
I'm going to sue all of you.
She's not even a citizen.
I'm actually here
to help out with that.
Mario Salgada, MTS Law.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
You cannot do that.
You don't get to intimidate
staff and patients here.
Step back.
Now.
Actually, as her counsel,
I'll be filing criminal
and civil complaints.
We are here to advocate
for Nanny Linda.
Mm-hmm. And I'm sure
Nanny Linda will be
more than happy to sue you
for 30 years of unpaid labor
for three generations
of your family,
not hers.
Ooh, girl, you are in trouble.
You might want to pawn
that bag now.
I totally know a place.
Hi.
It's time to roll you over
to Imaging now.
(In Tagalog)
But that's expensive, right?
There are some nice people here.
They are going
to take care of that for you.
(In Tagalog) Ma'am,
we have a surprise for you.
We've found your
relatives on social media.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINDA WHIMPERING]
[LINDA INHALES, SNIFFLES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINDA CRYING]
[LINDA SNIFFLES, CRYING]
[LINDA SNIFFLES, WHIMPERS]
[LINDA SNIFFLES, WHIMPERING]
[WHEELS ROLLING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DISINFECTANT SPRAYS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[DISINFECTANT SPRAYS]
I asked everyone
at the nurse's station.
I even texted Camille,
George, Grim...
No luck.
Lapis lazuli.
It's supposed
to open someone's third eye.
- How do you know that?
- ChatGPT.
No one had it,
so I ordered one for you.
[JOSH GASPS]
Wow, that's--
that's very nice of you.
If Noa's taught me anything,
this job is about people,
not just the work work.
Hey, um...
W-Would you be down
for dinner sometime?
Maybe ghost hunting?
I'll bring snacks.
And holy water.
Y-You have my number?
Yeah, saved.
I just couldn't spell your name.
Oh. Real name's Josh.
You're, like, totally blowing
my mind.
Well, Josh is too approachable.
Well, text me if
anything starts floating, Josh.
[JOSH CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHOOSHING]
Where did you go?
Did you think I wouldn't notice
that you did a side quest?
Day off.
Day off?
Then what are you doing here?
Don't you know
how to enjoy yourself?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Immortality.
It's lonelier than I realized.
[GRIM INHALES]
Now I understand why
you're so close to each other.
The hourglass moves too fast.
Wow, do you have
a translation for that?
[GRIM CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[TESS BREATHES DEEPLY]
[FABRIC RUSTLING]
[GRIM INHALES]
[TESS] I think...
You're not here
to tell me anything.
[GRIM CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
You should be thankful that
I'm here, not because of you.
It's another excuse
for your daughter to hate me.
What a shame.
I really thought
it would end well.
That is neither
good nor bad, Tess.
It simply is.
[TESS INHALES]
Maybe...
I should be the one to tell her.
She might be asleep
in front of the computer again.
Don't worry.
I gave her some extra time
to say goodbye.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
[TESS GASPS IN AMAZEMENT]
You know...
You're not
as bad as I thought.
[WHOOSHING]
[GROANS]
Mom, I'm still sleeping.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[GROANS]
[WHEELS ROLLING]
[NOA GROANS]
Oh.
You're back
from imaging already?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
No! No, no, no, no!
[CHAIR SWIVELS, THUDS]
[NOA EXHALES]
- He did this.
- He said you would say that.
He also told me
how hard you're fighting
to keep your mom here.
[NOA SCOFFS]
He's really trying
to piss me off.
I don't think spite
is their purpose, dear.
Because you can't keep her here
for the rest of your life.
She's all I have.
There are more people out there.
There are a lot of people
waiting for me.
Exactly!
We just helped you!
They were going to fly you back
to the Philippines
to see your family.
I've been sick for a long time.
I think you already know that.
[NOA SIGHS]
[NOA BREATHES DEEPLY]
Don't cry.
You know what?
You've given me more than my
whole 30 years here in America.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
That's not fair.
When did life become fair?
When were we given
this kind of miracle?
That's what you gave me.
You and Ros.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You can't stay?
What for, dear?
I've lived a long life.
I've been suffering
for a long time.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[NOA EXHALES, INHALES]
- There's nothing I can do?
- Be happy for me.
My dream is to serve
my family in the Philippines.
And because of you...
We can stop this
from happening to others.
Goodbye, Noa.
Thank you for my happy ending.
Please hug Ros for me.
And please check
her blood pressure
from time to time.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINDA INHALES]
[WIND BLOWING]
[EXHALES, CRIES]
[SNIFFLING, WHIMPERS]
[SNIFFLES, CRYING]
[SNIFFLES, WHIMPERS]
[NOA CRYING]
[KNOCKING ON WINDOW]
[SNIFFLES, EXHALES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SHUTS]
Did you hear?
[NOA EXHALES SHAKILY]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[NOA CRYING]
- [PATS BACK]
- [NOA CRYING]
[NOA WHIMPERING]
[NOA SNIFFLES]
We're still going to sue
those a-holes, right?
- Come here.
- [NOA CHUCKLES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[NOA BREATHES DEEPLY]
(In Spanish) What are you doing?
(In Spanish) Oh my god!
G-Grandma!
(In Spanish) You couldn't wait
until I was done?!
(In Spanish) Oh, please.
You act like
I haven't seen those before!
So many times!
[GRANDMA CHUCKLING]
(In Spanish) But, how are
you here?
Is this because of my rituals?
(In Spanish) Oh, you missed me
so much.
Uh, honestly...
I regret not remembering
everything you taught me.
(In Spanish) Well...
Sometimes it's better
to let things stay dead.
If you really want this,
it means you miss me so much,
you wanna see dead people.
(In Spanish) Oh, grandma...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Granny... Why now?
(In Spanish) If I've
learned anything...
It's the more the merrier.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
(In Spanish) Thank you, grandma.
[GROANS]
[LIQUID PLOPS]
[LIQUID PLOPPING]
[SCREAMING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]