Tak Sungwoong.
That's the man Jahyeon loves most.
A lover she couldn't forget
even if she died.
even if she killed him.
Could he have killed him for Oh Jahyeon?
No.
Rather than saying Koryoin Kim died
because the drug bag in his stomach burst
was intentional,
it's more like a coincidence.
But why was his body dumped?
Could it be because they
mistakenly thought they killed him?
But,
why on earth would Director Tak
help Oh Jahyeon?
Didn't she say they love each other?
Can you understand it just based on that,
Prosecutor Ju?
Don't try to understand it.
The harder you think,
the less you'll understand.
Love is inherently
ignorant and irrational.
Fasten your seatbelt. Let's go.
Where to?
To find Tak Sungwoong.
[Prosecutors' Office]
[Room 703]
[Chief Prosecutor Tak Sungwoong, Room 703]
Director Tak, I'm Ju Taeseon.
Come in.
I was just about to call you.
That Supervisor Lee Chaeha...
what do you think about transferring him
to a different department?
Having Lee Gilyoung's son
investigate Oh Jahyeon
makes me feel uneasy.
Oh?
Ah, hello.
Why are you here?
W-Well...
What are you doing?
I... I just wanted to drink some water.
Prosecutor Ju and I went out
for fieldwork and I suddenly got thirsty.
I used this cup...
It's fine.
I grew up in an environment
without so many rules.
The water here tastes better.
I'll be going now.
Goodbye. Please go ahead.
[Park Siwoo]
[Kim Yunsik]
[Kwak Seunghwan]
[Because of inheritance?]
[Koryoin Mr. Kim overdosed on drugs]
[Found in a small room
on the second floor]
[The Last Abandoned Mine in Danhyeon City
To Be Turned Into a Casino]
[Led by Ohsong Construction, 'Danhyeon Land' Integrated Resort (Casino, Hotel, Theme Park) to be built—
Officially secures $400M in foreign investment]
[Casino Industry's First Female Executive…
Pledges "Transparent Operations, Regional Co-Prosperity"]
[Danhyeon City "Casino Owner Murdered";
the suspect is his driver, Lee]
[The Prosecutor's Proposal]
[Prosecutor's Office]
What's going on?
Haven't gotten off work yet?
Where's the paper cup?
I've already passed it
to the National Forensic Service
and asked them to compare it
with the DNA in the glove.
You told them to contact you
as soon as the results are out, right?
Yes.
Prosecutor Ju.
You hope it isn't Director Tak, right?
I completely understand how you feel.
Don't make wild guesses,
and don't project yourself onto me.
Even if you stop the investigation here,
no one will blame you.
I won't stop.
Why?
You have nothing to do with any of the cases.
No matter what the final result is,
you will lose Director Tak.
It's for the truth.
I'm afraid that if you started this
because of me,
it will end up hurting you.
I'm worried.
So what if you're worried?
What are you going to do?
You're just an investigator,
not a prosecutor.
How do you plan
to investigate this case alone?
And I'm not doing this because of you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Doubt everything and uncover the truth—
that's what a prosecutor does.
So don't be arrogant and boss me around.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Lee!
Mr. Lee.
I'm late, aren't I?
Sorry.
No, I just got here too.
Sorry for taking up your weekend.
I just thought you might be busy
with work all weekend.
You and Prosecutor Ju
have been super busy lately.
And you're often out in the field.
It's pretty much the same.
People like Oh Jahyeon
should face their doom.
What?
She's making you super tired.
Indeed.
By the way, where are we going?
Follow me.
We still have some time before the movie.
This is the best place to relieve stress.
Give me your phone.
Huh?
Hurry up.
[Slide to power off]
Oh?
Don't think about work today.
Just have fun.
Here.
Let's go!
Here I come.
Please.
You can do it.
Isn't it cute?
Yeah, so cute.
Here.
Do you want to try?
Why did it suddenly start raining?
I know, right?
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
It's so cold.
The doors are closing.
Do you want to have dinner
before you leave?
I'm a good cook.
After all,
I've lived alone for a long time.
[I'm worried. Did something happen?]
[I always feel like I'm causing bad things to happen to you,
and it makes me very anxious.]
I'm worried. Did something happen?
A-Ah, let's eat next time.
I'm afraid I have to go back first.
Okay.
Got it. See you on Monday.
The doors are closing.
Seems like you had a good time.
Were you waiting for me?
Why didn't you answer the phone?
I was with Mr. Song.
Did he stop you from answering my calls?
Well, not really.
Then what was it?
Did you do something
I shouldn't catch you doing?
No.
We just went to the arcade.
Is that so?
Go back and rest.
Huh?
Aren't you going in with me?
Let go of me.
This hand that was just waving happily
at another man—
I don't want it holding me.
I'm leaving.
I'm afraid if we talk more,
all the happiness you are feeling
will vanish.
No, it won't...
Look at you. Your face is frozen.
I'm leaving.
I've wasted enough time.
Mr. Lee, you're not in your dorm.
[Mr. Lee, you're not in your dorm.
Why aren't you answering?
Contact me when you see this.]
Why aren't you answering the phone?
Contact me when you see this.
[02:12 Missed Call 02:25 Missed Call 02:38 Missed Call
02:38 Missed Call 02:50 Missed Call 02:50 Missed Call...]
I always feel like I'm causing bad things to happen to you,
and it makes me very anxious.
[I always feel like I'm causing bad things to happen to you,
and it makes me very anxious.]
It makes me feel very uneasy.
I'm waiting at your door.
[I'm waiting at your door.
Please answer the phone. Please.]
Please answer the phone. Please.
Did he wait for me for 3 hours?
I'm leaving.
I've wasted enough time already.
I told you to go.
Why follow me here?
If I had known you were coming,
I wouldn't have gone out with Mr. Song.
Did you follow me here just to say this?
I'm not interested in the fun
you share with Mr. Song,
so just leave.
I don't want to.
My patience today
was already exhausted
while waiting for you.
When I found out you were
having fun with Mr. Song,
I even used up tomorrow's patience quota.
I'm much less patient
than usual right now.
So get lost.
Prosecutor Ju.
We didn't have any official business
to meet today.
Why on earth did I go to your place?
I'd love to tell you
I don't know why I did that,
but actually, I do know the reason.
As for you,
do you know why you came here?
Yes, I do.
You have to hold back
like you normally do,
especially today.
If you want to leave,
turn around and go now.
I told you, didn't I?
I have run out of patience today.
I don't plan on being gentle
with you today.
Dry my hair properly.
Are you really bossing me around
to dry your hair?
Are you jealous because
I went on a date with Mr. Song?
Lee Chaeha, let's get things straight.
Sorry.
You are not jealous.
Date?
Are you two dating?
Uh, no.
Do you have trouble sleeping too?
Yeah.
More often than not, I still can't sleep
even after taking medicine.
Prosecutor Ju,
are you upset about Director Tak?
No.
I actually feel more at ease.
What?
S-Sorry.
Turn your head away,
before I turn around.
Wasn't he like a father to you?
And such a person became a murder suspect.
I suddenly had this thought.
Maybe Lee Gilyoung...
isn't the real killer.
Thoughts like this...
Prosecutor!
What is all this?
I'm organizing the case.
[Gambling addiction] [An intersection with the perpetrator] [Probability of an accomplice?]
[Why Danhyeon City?] [A client who pays well?]
[Oh Jahyeon's husband, Kwak Seunghwan] [Died 19.10.16]
[No way to prove the suspicion]
The death of Oh Jahyeon's husband—
the cause of death is
a heart attack.
[Heart attack. No external trauma. No drugs detected in the autopsy performed 12 hours later.
Cremation took place right after. Because of property division?]
Did Oh Jahyeon's husband die?
Yeah.
He had no external injuries
and had no drugs detected.
[Autopsy performed after 12 hours]
The autopsy was conducted
12 hours after death.
Very clean, right?
That was the first thing Oh Jahyeon said
after the inspection. And...
[Oh Jahyeon's regular OB-GYN]
[Died 19.10.19]
What happened 3 days later was...
The murder of Granny Park with an awl.
Ransacking marks were deliberately made,
and it was an overkill with 20 stabs—
a vendetta.
[A change in the murder weapon?]
A change in the murder weapon?
The culprit confessed, didn't they?
It's exactly the same.
I'm here to turn myself in.
In these two cases,
the suspects' former occupations were...
[Granny Park's case: surrendered suspect]
[Koryoin Kim's case: surrendered suspect]
When I was young...
I was a retired miner.
Both miners.
[Koryoin Kim]
The case of Koryoin Kim's dumped body.
[Cause of death: meth overdose,
excess nicotine detected, drug dealer]
[Needle marks found on neck and arms]
The cause of death was a meth overdose.
Needle marks on the neck,
and excess nicotine was detected.
And a glove dropped at the scene.
He didn't even return the room key.
When I saw him leaving
with a suitcase that day,
I should have known.
His whereabouts after
he entered the country couldn't be traced.
Now we
agree that the Koryoin died
while smuggling drugs with his body.
Then in your opinion,
where in Danhyeon City could you buy
such a large amount of drugs?
Casino World.
Do you know where most people
from miner families in Danhyeon City
work?
It's Casino World.
That's exactly why the Coal Mining Association
brought in the casino in the first place.
Do you see it now?
The connection
between all the cases.
[Oh Jahyeon's husband, Kwak Seunghwan] [Died 19.10.16]
Oh Jahyeon's husband.
[Oh Jahyeon's regular OB-GYN]
[Died 19.10.19]
Oh Jahyeon's regular OB-GYN.
[Koryoin Kim] [Died 26.01.07]
The same kind of drugs as Oh Jahyeon.
The casino director.
[Casino director]
Oh Jahyeon.
It seems these 3 cases
are all related to Oh Jahyeon.
Three cases?
Isn't there 1 more?
A murder case
related to an awl and the casino.
The starting point of all these cases.
[Kang Woosung] [Died 11.01.21]
The murder of casino boss
Kang Woosung with an awl.
[1 million won check found in Lee Gilyoung's house
-Stolen? Or a reward?]
The killer was a high school classmate
of Oh Jahyeon and Kang Woosung.
[Lee Gilyoung]
The Lee Gilyoung case...
Are you ready?
Yeah.
That day at Kang Woosung's house,
his son was sleeping.
He was a senior in high school.
According to his statement,
he was a light sleeper
and heard the door opening and closing—
4 times in total.
And the sound of the passcode lock
being pressed—
2 times.
I'm not drunk. I'm not.
-You're drunk.
-I'm not drunk.
One more drink.
Hey, wait, wait. One more drink.
Hey.
Why drink so much
when you can't hold your liquor?
Thanks for the bonus.
Get some rest.
I'm leaving.
I'm not drunk.
The first 2 sounds of the door
opening and closing
and the first sound of the passcode lock
were probably Lee Gilyoung
bringing his boss, Kang Woosung,
home and then leaving.
And the second sound
of the passcode lock and
the third sound of the door
opening and closing...
Was the killer entering the passcode
to enter the house.
Right.
And other than his family,
the only person who knew
the passcode was...
His driver, Lee Gilyoung.
The reason the son, who was home
all along, didn't hear his father scream
is because the killer
attacked from behind.
Kang Woosung didn't even
have the chance to scream.
They knew each other.
Even though the killer
used the passcode to enter the house,
they knew each other,
which is why Kang Woosung
didn't put up a fight.
The first strike pierced his neck,
but it continued.
One time.
Two times.
Three times.
Four times.
He was stabbed
15 more times.
Overkill.
A vendetta.
Did the killer really use this?
Could it be like Granny Park's case,
where the murder weapon was switched?
There's no way to verify that.
There's no documented evidence
of the size and marks
of Kang Woosung's stab wounds.
Do you think this was
an accident or intentional?
I'm not sure.
But one thing is certain.
Lee Gilyoung's DNA was found on this.
But you saw Han Soojin's case.
If someone wants to,
forging this kind of evidence is nothing.
Lee Chaeha, we're not here
to prove Lee Gilyoung's innocence.
As a prosecutor and an investigator,
we're just reviewing
one of the many related cases.
Yes, I understand.
I'm also talking about possibilities
based on past cases.
Okay.
Since it's not the real murder weapon,
it was left here so blatantly—
why is that?
"I killed him. Come catch me."
Is it a provocation, or is it...
A signature?
What if we assume
this is a serial killing?
Even though the killer
hid the real murder weapon,
he still wanted to show off.
"Look at me. I did this."
If that's true,
then the killer must still have
the awl used for the murder,
keeping it as a souvenir
for a sick sense of superiority.
Prosecutor Ju,
let me go see Kang Woosung's son.
Why would you go see him?
Are you going to tell him,
"I'm the son of Lee Gilyoung
who killed your father"?
As an investigator.
Whether you reveal
your true identity or not,
it's mocking to him.
After all, he'd probably want to kill you
the moment he sees you.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
What's written in the statement
should be everything.
He couldn't even speak properly
due to the shock.
He couldn't remember anything
for a while.
Yes.
[Casino director]
Do you really think Oh Jahyeon
is involved in this case?
She must be connected in some way.
Ever since she was kicked out of Ohsong,
she's been trying everything to get
her hands on the casino hotel project.
But...
[Kang Woosung]
she hit a wall with Kang Woosung.
20 billion.
That's the profit Ohsong could make
from the hotel bidding.
Although she couldn't return to Ohsong,
she got the position of casino director.
Whether as an investigator
or as Lee Gilyoung's son,
there are 2 things to solve
to prove Lee Gilyoung's innocence.
The sound of the door passcode, and
the DNA.
It's the National Forensic Service.
I asked them to compare the DNA
on the glove
with Director Tak's DNA.
Answer it.
Hello, this is Supervisor Lee Chaeha.
What?
It doesn't match?
Right. The DNA results don't match.
However...
Got it.
Thank you.
I'll contact you again.
What's wrong?
What did they say?
They said it's a father-son relationship—
between Director Tak
and the DNA detected on the glove.
Director Tak's child...
He has a son.
Did he drag his son in to kill someone?
No.
That child's DNA
couldn't possibly match his.
That child is
from his wife's previous marriage.
She had a boyfriend
she dated since high school.
She got pregnant in her 20s,
but later had an abortion.
No matter how my dad tried
to break them up, it didn't work.
He has a son he hid.
A son he hid?
They have a son—
Oh Jahyeon and Tak Sungwoong.
[The Prosecutor's Proposal]
[Next Episode]
Should we go to your dorm today?
Isn't the soundproofing there quite bad?
Yeah.
Are you two dating?
Huh?
What's going on, Mr. Lee?
Are you having an office romance?
With whom?
You said you hated office romances
the most.
Are you two-timing?
When did I...
Oh Jahyeon and Tak Sungwoong have a son.
I'll give each of you one secret
that you're keeping from each other.
Lee Chaeha is Lee Gilyoung's son.
Then whose son could he be?