‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎Sergeant Kim. Put down the gun.
‎Let me go!
‎Just calm down.
‎Calm down.
‎You promised me my freedom
‎if I completed this mission.
‎-You said that the last two times.
‎-Just calm down, okay?
‎You can't discharge him.
‎Discharging someone like him
‎is unthinkable.
‎If the North finds out he's still alive,
‎his existence alone
‎will cause a diplomatic crisis!
‎Captain Kang!
‎You're not the only one here.
‎Sit down.
‎He's a tier-one wanted fugitive
‎in the North anyway.
‎Why don't we extradite him?
‎If we make a deal with the North,
‎we can get something out of it.
‎It'd be better to eliminate him.
‎I share everyone's concern
‎that it'd be dangerous
‎to allow him back into society.
‎We should take this chance
‎to get rid of him first.
‎Discharge him.
‎He's done enough for South Korea.
‎Before every mission,
‎we promised him his freedom
‎in exchange for completing it.
‎We've gone back on our word
‎multiple times.
‎Fortunately,
‎the North believes he's dead.
‎Let's consider his service record
‎and grant him a discharge.
‎General.
‎Of course,
‎this isn't the only reason.
‎There will come a day
‎when we'll have to use him again.
‎Until that day comes,
‎we'll keep 66 alive.
‎That'll be all.
‎You're dismissed.
‎Just wait and see.
‎You'll come to regret this decision.
‎EPISODE 7
‎Hey, it's the spy.
‎Hey, spy!
‎Congrats on getting discharged!
‎Hey, 66!
‎Hey, 6 times 6 is 46!
‎-It's 36, dumbass.
‎-It's 46, dumbass.
‎-You dumbass.
‎-6 times 1 is 6, 6 times 2 is 12,
‎6 times 3 is 18, 6 times 4 is 24,
‎6 times 5 is 30, and 6 times 6 is 46.
‎Why the long face? You're discharged.
‎Yeah, you look like a private
‎who had his leave canceled.
‎You're supposed to be the happiest person
‎in the country right now.
‎Why did you come here?
‎"Why did you come here?"
‎We came to congratulate our underling.
‎Congrats on becoming
‎an official South Korean citizen.
‎Hey.
‎I brought this for you.
‎Take a big bite.
‎That way, you'll get a fresh start.
‎-Here.
‎-He's not being released from prison.
‎Or are you trying to be funny?
‎There's no difference
‎between this place and prison.
‎Come on, take a bite.
‎There you go.
‎This is the taste of freedom.
‎Good, right?
‎I'll keep in touch.
‎Where are you going?
‎We need to have a party!
‎A grilled pork belly party!
‎Leave him alone.
‎He's in no mood for a party.
‎How about the two of us?
‎All right.
‎Then go change.
‎Then you go get a haircut.
‎He always has to have the last word.
‎THE LATE IM YU-JIN
‎She's asleep.
‎Support her neck with your left hand.
‎Will you be okay on your own?
‎Min-ji, I'm here.
‎Let's go home now.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎Dad?
‎Dad!
‎Wait here.
‎Min-ji.
‎I'm here.
‎Let's go home now.
‎Dad…
‎Look at him show up
‎after we did all the hard work.
‎Jeez, late as always.
‎Hey, take your stinky sock.
‎It doesn't stink.
‎Don't move.
‎Unless you want me to blow his head off.
‎Lay down your weapons.
‎Hold your aim.
‎What are you doing?
‎Drop your guns!
‎I'll count to three.
‎-One.
‎-No, don't kill me!
‎Drop your guns right now!
‎Everyone, drop them! That's an order!
‎Lay down your weapons.
‎Lay down your weapons!
‎-Two.
‎-He just counted to two!
‎Two!
‎-Drop your guns!
‎-Hold your aim!
‎You're the vice minister
‎of National Security,
‎and you're ordering soldiers
‎to drop their guns?!
‎What are you doing?
‎Shoot him now!
‎We can't, sir.
‎The vice minister is being held hostage!
‎-You want to die, bastard?
‎-Tactical team leader!
‎You'd better make the right call!
‎Everyone, drop your weapons!
‎The vice minister's safety comes first.
‎That's right! Well done!
‎Good job!
‎Drop your guns!
‎Drop them!
‎Drop your guns right now!
‎Hey, Mole Cricket.
‎He said to drop your gun.
‎Oh, right.
‎This is live ammo. Drop your gun.
‎Drop it.
‎There you go.
‎All right.
‎Everyone, drop your weapons,
‎come over here,
‎and get inside the square.
‎Hurry up.
‎I said hurry up!
‎What are you doing?
‎You punk.
‎Oh, I forgot. Hey.
‎-Hold this for me.
‎-What?
‎Dad!
‎Dad.
‎I'm here now, so don't worry.
‎I'm sorry I'm late.
‎Why won't you get inside the square,
‎you mole rat?
‎Oh, your pride won't allow it?
‎Okay, fair.
‎Stay right behind me.
‎Listen up.
‎This isn't just any Claymore.
‎This one reacts to sound and movement.
‎It's my masterpiece.
‎And it's very sensitive.
‎Try moving if you're curious.
‎You made us do all the hard work.
‎Focus.
‎It's not over yet.
‎The sensors are working.
‎You know what happens
‎if you so much as move a finger, right?
‎Boom!
‎Hey, how are we getting out of here?
‎My Rock or Die…
‎Hey, Mole Rat.
‎Hand over the car key.
‎I know you have a car. Give me the key.
‎Man, that jerk…
‎Hand it over, damn it!
‎Okay. The hero gets to drive.
‎-Man, I'm busy.
‎-I'm sorry, sir.
‎In any case!
‎When I hit the switch,
‎it'll arm the Claymore.
‎Ready?
‎Hold on. This isn't enough.
‎Everyone, hands up.
‎Hands all the way up!
‎Arms against your ears!
‎That's it.
‎Good.
‎Green light, red light.
‎What the hell is he doing?
‎Hey, there it is! Run!
‎Here we go!
‎Hold on.
‎An unidentified car is coming out.
‎Hey, zoom in.
‎What the heck?
‎Wait, those people…
‎They'll move out of the way.
‎Hey.
‎-Seriously?
‎-Hold on.
‎Turn off the engine and get out.
‎Hey, your co-workers seem serious.
‎They're your co-workers?
‎Everyone, get out!
‎Let's get out.
‎Shooting at your co-worker, huh?
‎What a scary bunch.
‎Put down your gun right now!
‎You promised to surrender
‎once you found your daughter.
‎Don't tell me you forgot.
‎I'll keep my promise
‎once Min-ji's safety is guaranteed.
‎There's no safer place than the SMD.
‎I don't think so.
‎Please just listen to him!
‎Drop your guns!
‎Don't worry. I'll keep my promise.
‎Lower your gun.
‎Bring the Cheonsan Unit commander
‎to my house.
‎How could you damage a perfectly good car?
‎Not that it's mine.
‎-Get in.
‎-Side mirrors are important, you know.
‎How am I supposed to change lanes?
‎Don't worry.
‎He's a man of his word.
‎CHEONSAN GROUP RESEARCH CENTER
‎Open the gate.
‎Open it!
‎Open the gate right now!
‎Hurry!
‎Let's go.
‎Gosh, what a nice guy.
‎We could've just rammed through.
‎Have a good day!
‎Dad.
‎Jin-cheol, step on it.
‎We can take a breather.
‎Dad.
‎Min-ji's calling you, man.
‎Yeah, Min-ji?
‎What is it? Are you okay?
‎Are you hurt?
‎Where does it hurt? Tell me.
‎No, I'm okay.
‎But I don't think you are.
‎How did you get so hurt?
‎I'm okay. I'm totally fine.
‎Fine, my foot.
‎-Your dad got shot earlier--
‎-Hey.
‎Just drive.
‎It must've been so tough.
‎Why would you say that?
‎Look at you.
‎You must be hungry.
‎Let's go eat.
‎-Jin-cheol, let's go eat.
‎-Sounds good.
‎How can we eat at a time like this?
‎You really are my dad.
‎Well, of course, I'm your dad.
‎You must've been so scared.
‎I'm sorry I didn't get there sooner.
‎I won't ever…
‎No, Dad.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I'm sorry for making you worry.
‎I'm sorry for the things I said.
‎No, Min-ji.
‎I'm sorry.
‎What was that? Did Min-ji's stomach growl?
‎How long has it been since she's eaten?
‎Now that you two have had your reunion,
‎let's go eat something.
‎It's on me.
‎-What was that for?
‎-Because you're cool.
‎Can I eat anything I want?
‎Over there!
‎Let's go.
‎GEUMBI EEL
‎Man, I'm hungry.
‎Min-ji, hurry up. I'm starving.
‎Oh boy.
‎Let's have some eel.
‎Yes, sir.
‎The vice minister
‎isn't answering his phone.
‎I think something happened.
‎We spotted someone infiltrating the SMD
‎about 30 minutes ago.
‎We believe he took the girl.
‎Who was it?
‎I'm not sure because he's far away,
‎but based on his build and attire,
‎I think it's her dad.
‎Her dad?
‎Bring both of them in.
‎I'm going to witness the end myself.
‎Understood, sir.
‎As a fellow parent raising a daughter,
‎I ask that you find it in your heart
‎to forgive us.
‎There's nothing better than eel
‎for middle-aged men like us.
‎I couldn't be happier.
‎Don't you agree, buddy?
‎Right, I couldn't be happier eating eel
‎while looking like an absolute mess.
‎-Jeez, my back.
‎-Look ahead.
‎By the way, Min-ji,
‎I noticed that you ate as much as we did.
‎Yeah, I saw you eating
‎three pieces at a time.
‎Kim, you'll need to make a lot of money,
‎seeing how much she eats.
‎Thanks for the meal.
‎-I wanted to eat more but held back.
‎-What?
‎-We ate all the eel they had.
‎-Really?
‎Yeah!
‎Thank goodness they ran out of eel--
‎What the heck?
‎That jerk doesn't know how to drive.
‎-Uncle!
‎-He bought you eel. Let it go.
‎Don't get mad at me.
‎That driver's the one at fault.
‎You should've kept a safe distance.
‎Hey, I bought you eel,
‎and this is the treatment I get?
‎-Dad.
‎-What the…
‎Hey, it's blocked.
‎-Dad.
‎-It's okay. Don't worry.
‎Guess I won't be getting home
‎any time soon.
‎Looks like they know tactics.
‎They're not with the SMD.
‎I'll just get out this way.
‎Just wait. Min-ji's here.
‎Min-ji, don't be scared.
‎It's like getting roadside assistance.
‎That's right.
‎-This should be fun.
‎-It's okay.
‎What do you mean?
‎What?
‎What do you mean by fun?
‎Are they trying to export us or what?
‎Who knew it'd be so hard
‎to get Min-ji home?
‎Min-ji.
‎Are you okay?
‎I'm okay.
‎I'm your daughter, aren't I?
‎What are these bastards up to?
‎What are you doing?
‎Trying to get out.
‎Just stay put for now.
‎This is when the hero takes charge.
‎Hey.
‎Do they really have to make me
‎get out like this?
‎Can you even get out?
‎I ate too much.
‎Hey, push me out!
‎Can you get out?
‎Jeez, you're too bloated to be a hero.
‎Hey!
‎What are you playing at, huh?
‎Hurry up and get on with it!
‎I'm a busy man.
‎What's this?
‎It's gas!
‎-Han-soo.
‎-It's gas!
‎My skin is fine.
‎I think it's just sleeping gas.
‎Just wait a second.
‎Hey!
‎-Hey!
‎-Min-ji.
‎-You cheeky little punks.
‎-You're going to fall asleep.
‎It's better not to fight it,
‎so just sleep.
‎I'll be right next to you, so don't worry.
‎Okay.
‎I once went a month without sleeping.
‎What about Uncle Jin-cheol?
‎He's out there. Will he be okay?
‎-They're trying to capture us alive.
‎-He'll be fine. He likes gas.
‎-Don't worry about him.
‎-Kim!
‎Hey, Kim.
‎Hey, let me in!
‎Hey!
‎Open the sunroof!
‎The sunroof!
‎Hey, Han-soo!
‎Open the sunroof! I'm getting sleepy!
‎But Min-ji's in here.
‎I get that, but let me… Hey!
‎Just take a quick nap, hero!
‎Han-soo! Sung Han-soo!
‎The sunroof!
‎Han-soo!
‎Han-soo…
‎You jerk, I knew you'd pull this on me…
‎Check on them.
‎They're asleep.
‎Get them out.
‎Take the girl and her dad
‎and kill the rest.
‎Hey, it worked. It actually worked.
‎You bastards.
‎I almost died…
‎I almost fell asleep!
‎Get them.
‎There's…
‎There's still time…
‎The sun…
‎The sunroof!
‎Jeez, I slept like a baby.
‎I need to wake up.
‎I think I held out for five minutes.
‎Oh man.
‎Jeez, I'm old.
‎My body isn't the same anymore.
‎Got any water?
‎Hold on.
‎Oh, there you are, Min-ji.
‎You must be cold.
‎I'm pretty sure I struck your face.
‎Get some sleep.
‎Get plenty of rest.
‎You're in your growing phase.
‎Lead vehicle, move out.
‎Hey, you know what?
‎You've got speed but no power.
‎This is how you do it!
‎Get him!
‎Hey, hold on.
‎Min-ji.
‎Min-ji!
‎Your punches tell me you're a veteran.
‎Which division were you in?
‎Do you know who I am?
‎Does any of that matter?
‎You'll be dead soon anyway.
‎Karambit, huh?
‎I see you trained overseas.
‎Where did you serve?
‎Which unit?
‎Delta Force? Green Berets?
‎Which one?
‎Hang on.
‎Hey, you can't hit me
‎when I'm not looking.
‎I'm not taking a single hit
‎from here on out.
‎Bring it.
‎By the way,
‎if a soldier pulls out a weapon like that,
‎it means they're ready to die.
‎Rock and roll.
‎It's not over yet!
‎Not yet.
‎There it is.
‎The look of a man
‎who met someone stronger than him.
‎Your legs are shaking, aren't they?
‎And you've got the chills, right?
‎-Please spare me.
‎-That's why…
‎That's why…
‎you should never mess with…
‎middle-aged men with glasses!
‎Just who the hell
‎are these bastards?
‎Is he the same guy
‎who got on his knees in front of us?
‎Dad!
‎He seemed like
‎an ordinary middle-aged man.
‎How?
‎What the heck?
‎Who the hell
‎are these middle-aged men with glasses?
‎Rock and roll.
‎I didn't get hit. I blocked everything.
‎Hey, aren't you guys tired?
‎Doesn't it hurt?
‎Okay.
‎Come at me again. Oh, wait.
‎I'll come to you.
‎Let's stop, guys.
‎That's enough.
‎Let's stop.
‎-Is Min-ji okay?
‎-Seriously.
‎You'll wake her. Open the door.
‎You always show up
‎right when everything's over.
‎Why me?
‎Why am I the only one
‎doing the hard work?
‎Is Min-ji okay?
‎They're from Juhak Construction, right?
‎Kim isn't going home, is he?
‎I have to go though.
‎-Why?
‎-The water purifier guy is coming.
‎I've already rescheduled once.
‎I can't do it again.
‎Don't worry.
‎I told you I'd take care of it.
‎I'm sorry.
‎Don't say you're sorry.
‎Just say thank you.
‎Everything is taken care of, so…
‎Sir.
‎What is it?
‎I think they took down Chief Nam.
‎What?
‎Are we here already?
‎Hey, what's this place? It's really nice.
‎Watch Min-ji for a bit.
‎What are you going to do?
‎There's something
‎the parents need to settle.
‎I'd expect no less from you.
‎See you.
‎What is this, a parent meeting?
‎Yeah, with hardcore parents.
‎Hey, let's turn the car around.
‎Okay, do it.
‎Let's turn it around.
‎I said go ahead and do it.
‎You're in the front, so you do it.
‎Is it faster if I go around,
‎or if you come up front?
‎I fought a lot, okay?
‎Rock, paper, scissors.
‎When I heard Nam was taken down,
‎I thought you used
‎some sort of trap or trick.
‎But you didn't.
‎You have incredible skills.
‎Are you ex-special forces or something?
‎An attempted cover-up and a kidnapping…
‎Aren't you ashamed as a father?
‎I did what I had to as a father.
‎You and I are the same.
‎I'm sure you weren't
‎in your right mind either,
‎trying to find your daughter.
‎You used your abilities to commit violence
‎and probably killed people in the process.
‎So tell me.
‎Were you ashamed as a father?
‎I'll make you an offer.
‎How about we bury the hatchet…
‎and you come work for me?
‎Would 100 million won a month be enough?
‎You got on your knees for your daughter.
‎Are you going to let your pride
‎get in the way?
‎You need money to raise a child.
‎Being an incompetent parent is a crime.
‎Having kids
‎when you can't provide for them?
‎That's no different from animals breeding.
‎That's not parenting. It's child abuse.
‎Think carefully
‎about what kind of dad you will be
‎for your daughter.
‎I don't think you get it yet.
‎I'm doing you and your daughter a favor.
‎One phone call,
‎and I can make all of this go away.
‎Or I can make it
‎so you never see your daughter again.
‎On my way here,
‎I wondered what I should do about you.
‎Now I know.
‎For Min-ji's sake…
‎I'm going to
‎end you.
‎What?
‎Oh jeez, what kind of parent meeting
‎are they having?
‎That's right. Just run.
‎It's the only way you'll survive.
‎Hey, Kim. Take it easy.
‎Why should he?
‎Dad!
‎Min-ji.
‎Dad.
‎Don't do it.
‎If you want to live…
‎beg for my daughter's forgiveness.
‎With all your heart.
‎I'm sorry.
‎I apologize
‎on behalf of Hye-ri.
‎As a fellow parent raising a daughter…
‎I beg you to forgive me.
‎As a fellow parent raising a daughter,
‎I ask that you find it in your heart
‎to forgive us.
‎Turn yourselves in.
‎Both you
‎and Hye-ri.
‎Even the smallest sin of a parent
‎turns into a mountain of burden
‎for their child to carry.
‎Min-ji.
‎Let's go home.
‎Okay.
‎Let's go.
‎4 HOURS LATER
‎Everyone, get down!
‎Get down!
‎Psych!
‎Park Jin-cheol…
‎Park Jin-cheol, you damn pig!
‎I wonder what will happen.
‎Whatever the outcome is,
‎today will be the last time
‎Agent Kim sees Min-ji.
‎DOWON LAUNDRY
‎HAPPY BIRTHDAY
‎Here you go.
‎Are you disappointed there's no cake?
‎It went bad, you see.
‎It's okay.
‎You must be hungry. Let's eat.
‎Those soldiers outside
‎are waiting for you, right?
‎Yeah.
‎It's because of me, isn't it?
‎Because you tried to rescue me.
‎-No, it's not.
‎-Don't lie.
‎It is.
‎They're taking you because of me.
‎Can't you just run away?
‎Don't think about anything else.
‎I know you can easily escape.
‎Dad.
‎Min-ji.
‎You see,
‎I came from North Korea.
‎I used to live
‎a very dangerous and rough life.
‎But everything changed
‎after I met your mom.
‎I thought maybe someone like me…
‎could live an ordinary life.
‎What kind of person…
‎was Mom?
‎She was warmhearted, strong,
‎and beautiful.
‎Just like you.
‎I knew I took after her.
‎I made a promise to her…
‎the day you were born.
‎I promised to leave
‎my painful past behind…
‎and just live as your dad.
‎It was tough at times
‎because you gave me a hard time.
‎But you know what?
‎It made me so happy
‎to watch you grow up.
‎But now…
‎we have to say goodbye.
‎When can I see you again?
‎I don't know.
‎It might
‎take a long time or maybe…
‎-We might never--
‎-Come back.
‎I'll wait for you.
‎You'll come back.
‎You're my dad.
‎You're not just anyone's dad.
‎You're ‎my‎ dad.
‎So I know you'll come back.
‎You think you can wait for me on your own?
‎Of course.
‎And I'm not alone.
‎To be honest,
‎there were times
‎when I felt like I was alone.
‎I didn't have a mom,
‎and I transferred schools so many times
‎that I had no friends.
‎I thought about that a lot
‎in the cold storage warehouse.
‎But then I remembered you and thought,
‎"Oh, that's right."
‎"I'm not alone."
‎"I bet Dad's worried about me."
‎I missed you so much
‎that I found the courage.
‎And I knew you felt the same way.
‎You're not alone.
‎You have me.
‎That's why you came to get me.
‎Min-ji.
‎I'm okay. I promise.
‎I'll be brave and wait for you on my own.
‎Right.
‎Here.
‎What's this?
‎It's a belated birthday gift.
‎Sweetheart.
‎Happy birthday.
‎And…
‎I love you.
‎I…
‎I love you a lot too, Dad.
‎I have something for you too.
‎Here.
‎Kids these days
‎give this to their parents.
‎It came out well, right?
‎You look pretty.
‎Why are you crying?
‎Don't cry.
‎You look ugly when you cry.
‎Come on, Min-ji. Let's eat.
‎Okay.
‎Eat up.
‎Thank you for the meal.
‎By the way, what's wrong with the fridge?
‎Oh, Uncle Jin-cheol used the door
‎to catch someone.
‎There was a thief in the house.
‎Eat slowly.
‎If you eat quickly,
‎you'll have to leave soon.
‎Okay, okay.
‎Forget it.
‎Those won't work on him anyway.
‎Did you receive the terms of my surrender?
‎You'll guarantee Min-ji's safety, right?
‎Don't worry.
‎I'm a four-star general
‎of the Republic of Korea.
‎I'm counting on your word.
‎Goodbye, take…
‎What are you doing?
‎Arrest the ones sleeping in the car!
‎Wake up, Mr. Sung Han-soo.
‎-Get out.
‎-Hold on.
‎-I'm coming.
‎-How did you get out?
‎Was there an explosion?
‎-Gosh, it's gotten chilly.
‎-Oh, I farted.
‎You have to be careful.
‎Hold on.
‎Receipts for the eel
‎and everything else we've eaten.
‎You had wild eel, you jackass?
‎Oh, right.
‎He spent the cash.
‎Goodbye, then.
‎Let's go.
‎I left the motorcycle
‎at Ju Gang-chan's house.
‎Go get it. It's yours.
‎Goddamn it.
‎Thank you for your hard work.
‎Oh, sorry about that.
‎Happy birthday, Min-ji.
‎This is expensive,
‎so take good care of it.
‎Dad…
‎I'm Lee Si-young, the managing partner.
‎GYUDAM LAW FIRM
‎MANAGING PARTNER LEE SI-YOUNG
‎I trust this will remain confidential.
‎Even our own legal team
‎is unaware of this.
‎Don't worry, sir.
‎But I suggest getting your daughter
‎out of the country first.
‎Don't worry. I'll take care of the police.
‎Damn, the price of gold these days
‎is no joke.
‎NOTICE OF PERSONNEL ACTION
‎AGENT NAME: JUNG SANG-A
‎RANK: GRADE 6
‎Demoted by one rank.
‎Be grateful that this is the extent
‎of your disciplinary action.
‎I'm sorry, sir.
‎DRY CLEANERS FOR SALE
‎PLEASE CALL THE NUMBER BELOW
‎DOWON LAUNDRY
‎I wonder what happened to Kim.
‎Jin-cheol.
‎Are you okay?
‎Yeah.
‎He should be okay too, right?
‎Are you sleeping?
‎How the hell can you sleep?!
‎GEOSEONG KOREAN MEDICINE CLINIC
‎Next month's high-level inter-Korean talks
‎have been abruptly postponed.
‎No official explanation has been released,
‎leading to widespread speculation
‎about the cause.
‎Some point to internal issues
‎in the North…
‎I don't have much to offer,
‎but please help yourself.
‎The government
‎will monitor the situation closely
‎while continuing its diplomatic efforts
‎to resume inter-Korean talks.
‎What if we quietly
‎take care of him on our end?
‎He's already been discovered by the North.
‎They won't let it slide.
‎How do we explain
‎that we've been hiding him
‎all these years, sir?
‎The general was the one
‎who granted his discharge.
‎I trust he'll take
‎decisive action this time.
‎DIPLOMATIC VEHICLE 905-17
‎We have orders to transfer you.
‎We will follow protocol,
‎so please cooperate.
‎BETTER DEATH THAN ENEMY CAPTURE
‎Are you awake now?
‎I have
‎so many questions to ask you.
‎Welcome home…
‎Number 66.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎It's been a while, 66.
‎What's the mission?
‎He'll do anything
‎to see his daughter again.
‎I only want one thing.
‎Let me be the one
‎to finish him off.
‎Track Kim's location.
‎Don't forget who has your daughter.
‎Protecting the people I care about
‎is more important…
‎I thought you should say
‎your final goodbye.
‎…than killing my enemy.
‎Subtitle translation by: