You have two weeks
to make her fall for you.
Like she's counting down
the time she has with Piang.
I love you.
I lost a family member.
She was my twin sister.
So I don't deserve to be happy either.
Let's break up.
So why, when it comes to us,
are you the one letting go?
Have you ever felt anything for me?
This is my answer.
Song doesn't love me back, Grandma.
I give up.
I give up, Grandma.
Do you love me?
Please don't stay silent.
Song, What's wrong, my dear?
Have you been drinking?
May I come in, my dear?
Grandma, what's wrong?
You don't seem like yourself,
so I wanted to ask
if there's anything you'd like
to tell me, my dear.
No.
I just need some time.
Please give me some time, Grandma.
Song, you know
you can tell me anything.
Okay.
Then I won't push you.
I'll give you all the time you need.
But, I'd like to send someone
to keep you company, my dear.
Can I sleep with you?
Get some sleep, Piang.
It was just a bad dream.
Could you check on your sister?
She hasn't eaten since yesterday.
I have a meeting this morning, Grandma.
I'll get going.
Is your work really
more important than your sister?
Maybe you should
ask yourself that question.
At this point,
what you want or how Piang feels,
which matters more.
I'll get going.
I'm going to the café, Grandma.
I haven't been there since the accident.
I wonder how it's doing.
Are you sure you're okay?
I am.
I don't want my sadness
to ruin everything.
Besides, working makes me feel worthy
and love myself more.
So I won't have to chase
anyone's love again.
I'll get going.
Here's our signature drink.
Are you tired?
Your matcha latte is ready.
Please give it a try.
Hey!
Didn't I tell you I'm allergic to dairy?
Why did you put it in?
If something happens to me,
I'll sue the hell out of you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm the café manager.
I sincerely apologize for this mistake.
We'll take full responsibility
for the damages.
With such an idiot working here,
you're going to get someone killed!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Piang, are you okay?
You're soaked. Go clean yourself up.
Go on.
Thanks.
Piang's back. Don't worry.
Mm.
I thought you said you were okay.
I really tried.
But I can't do it.
I know.
Come on. Have a seat.
Hey.
It's okay if someone doesn't love you,
because you still have Mudmee,
and…
you have me too.
Grandma.
I've played a part in
what happened to you.
But you have to understand
everything I did
was because I truly
wanted the best for you.
I understand.
But none of this is your fault, Grandma.
It's because of Song.
If she loved me
and was willing to fight beside me,
I would've never given up.
I know.
That's true.
I should thank you
for opening up to me so honestly.
I never thought
I'd hear those words from you.
Well,
you should thank me,
because it wasn't easy for me to say them.
Grandma,
I'll do as you said.
I'll get over her
and become the old Piangrawin
again as soon as I can.
You don't have to rush.
Just let it be.
Give yourself time.
It's okay if you fall apart
a little longer.
Really?
Seeing you hurt this much,
I guess I have to stop forcing you,
and your sister too.
I guess it's time
for me to let you both feel
what you truly want to feel.
Grandma, thank you.
I'm hurting with you now, Neung.
You don't have to hurt alone anymore.
Is this really Song, my little sister?
You love that woman, don't you?
I'm sorry.
I promised myself
I'd never love anyone again.
I didn't want to be selfish,
finding happiness after you were gone,
while you left with so much pain.
Are you suffering like this
because of me?
No.
It's because of me.
I still can't let go.
Then stop doing this to yourself.
Stop holding on,
and stop running from your heart.
In life, we don't get many chances, Song.
When we find someone we love,
and they truly love us back,
we should hold on to them tight.
And…
Please be happy for your big sister.
Can you do that?
You promised me. Don't let me down.
Neung.
In life, we don't get many chances, Song.
Please be happy
for your big sister.
Well, that's a satisfying sound.
Very refreshing.
-Grandma.
-Song, come here, my dear.
If you want a drink, I'll drink with you.
I may not know
what you're going through right now,
but more importantly,
the two of us, grandmother
and granddaughter,
will get through this together.
Come on, help yourself.
Whichever bottle or flavor you like,
feel free to pick one.
Go ahead.
I'm not drinking anymore, Grandma.
Huh?
Why not, my dear?
I dreamed about Neung.
She gave me a reality check
and made me realize
how I should face what I'm going through.
Poor you.
See?
Neung must be worried about you,
just like your grandma is.
Grandma.
All right, enough.
No more drama.
Instead, help me out.
I went through
all the trouble of lining these up.
So let's have a drink-off.
Let's finish them all.
I can't be bothered
putting them back on the shelf.
-Okay?
-Really?
Since you asked so directly,
I'll be honest. The answer is no.
The truth is,
I've been craving a drink for days.
Come on, let's finish these together.
Pick any flavor
or any drink you like, be my guest.
Come on.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Another one.
Coming right up, boss.
You got it.
Undefeated.
I need to talk to you.
Are you asleep?
I'm sorry for saying that.
So your grandma
has finally accepted you and Song.
Yes, but what does it matter
if Song isn't interested?
I'm not chasing her for love anymore.
I love myself a lot more now.
Really?
Yeah. If we ever get back together,
I'll make her chase me instead.
I'll teach her a lesson.
But then again,
that'll probably never happen.
You never know.
When I came in,
I think I saw her watching you.
Where?
Where's Song? Song!
Song, where are you?
You said you'd make her chase you,
but the second you heard her name,
you ran off instead.
Don't joke like that. I'm already sad.
I'm not joking.
I really saw her.
If Song comes to win you back,
make her work for it.
I'm going to the restroom.
I'M SORRY FOR WHAT I SAID.
I REALLY LOVE YOU.
Oh, Song.
I'm sorry for what I said.
I really love you.
Hey!
Why didn't you come in?
I'M SORRY FOR WHAT I SAID.
I REALLY LOVE YOU.
Damn.
I'll be right in.
Mon, get over here.
-Sorry.
-What's going on?
-Look at this.
Tell me your plan.
Sure thing.
I guarantee this is going to be fun.
Let's do it.
Everyone, this is Piang. I need your help.
126 FOOD
Hello, Ple.
Mm.
What are you doing? Am I bothering you?
Not at all. What's up?
What do you think of Piang's plan?
I was going to help her. What about you?
I'm going to help her too.
But, are you okay with seeing me again?
Of course.
I can separate the two.
Okay.
But I think when we're around everyone,
we should pretend we're still together.
Why?
If Piang and Song find out
we've broken up,
they'll feel bad asking us for help.
I think
we should wait until their plan succeeds,
then tell them when the time is right.
Mm.
Then it's settled.
Is that all? I'm hanging up.
But, Ple…
Is your dad still harassing you?
Not anymore.
Okay.
I'll hang up then.
I'M SORRY FOR WHAT I SAID.
I REALLY LOVE YOU.
Shit.
-Yes, Boss.
-Song.
Piang's been in another accident.
What?
Piang.
How did Piang fall down the stairs, Boss?
Piang…
She's still heartbroken over you.
She wasn't paying attention.
Why was she moved to
a recovery room already?
Did the ER doctor examine her thoroughly?
Well…
Yes.
But don't worry.
I've taken over Piang's case.
If anything comes up,
I'll take care of her myself.
I see. But aren't you a cardiologist?
I am.
-My head…
-Piang.
My head feels like it's going to explode.
Piang.
Namking, what do we do?
Mud.
Namking.
What's going on?
Who are you?
My head…
Piang suffered a head injury not long ago.
Now that she's hit it again,
even though it wasn't severe,
it can still cause symptoms like this.
Medically, it's called
post-traumatic amnesia,
which is temporary memory loss
after an accident.
The patient remembers almost everything
except certain events
or certain people they've forgotten.
Temporary?
So she'll remember me again?
Mm.
Yes.
But you'll have to be patient.
Though if you want my advice,
don't wait for her.
Why?
The day she confessed to you,
you turned her down.
That means you don't love her.
So why wait?
This is your chance
to let her go for good.
Thanks for the advice.
But I'll wait for her.
And I won't just sit around.
I'll do everything I can
to help Piang remember me again.
I'll get going then.
Okay.
You really don't remember me?
I'm the one you loved,
the one you always chased.
No way.
Piangrawin would never. I just sit here
and people hit on me every day.
I'd never chase anyone.
But I'm telling the truth.
Not long ago, you told me you loved me.
And I…
I…
What?
I love you too.
All this time,
I was in denial.
I never admitted my feelings.
So why now?
Because I already lost you once.
That's when I realized
how painful it is to live without you.
I don't want to lose you again.
Here.
Look.
You wrote this to me.
It's delicious.
But the chef is even sweeter.
I'd love to taste more.
Whenever you're ready, just let me know.
Ew.
That's way too flirty.
By the way, what's your name?
My name is Song.
Song.
I don't think I love you.
I probably just watched too many K-dramas
and wanted to copy them.
Piang.
Ploy, Ple.
-Namprow.
-Hi.
When did you all get here?
I came with Ple.
I brought you some fruit and snacks.
Thank you, Namprow.
Does your head still hurt?
It does, but I'm feeling much better.
You'll be better soon.
Thank you.
Do you need anything else?
You look like a lost puppy, Song.
Ready?
Our mission starts now.
Song.
Why do you look so down?
Don't tell me you've given up.
I haven't.
I'm just thinking.
I don't give up that easily.
Hey, did you and Piang ever
share any special moments?
The good or bad kind?
Good kind, of course.
Yeah.
Why?
I think we should recreate those moments
to trigger her memory.
It might work.
I agree with Namprow.
Um…
But will she go along with it?
We'll just have to lure her in.
Don't worry.
We'll help you.
Fighting!
Piang.
Piang, Ple and I
are going on a trip next week.
We'd love you to come with us.
Would that be okay?
Of course.
Ever since we helped you
at the matcha café,
we haven't had the chance
to travel together.
Please come with us.
By the way,
is Song coming too?
She is.
Song was one of the people
who helped you at the café.
She also created
your café's signature drink.
Really?
I don't remember that.
Hang in there, Song.
Mm.
We're all staying in the same room?
That's right.
Why waste money on separate rooms?
Where are Ploy and Ple staying?
They can't make it after all.
They just texted that something came up.
You must be tired from the trip.
Why don't you soak in the tub first?
I'll bathe you.
No, thanks.
I'm an adult. I can do it myself.
What are you doing?
We've been here together before,
and we slept like this.
Can you stay still for a while?
Keep your hands like this.
Don't move them down.
Otherwise, I'll stop.
And…
you have to endure it
until I'm satisfied.
Get out.
Who do you think you are,
ordering me around?
Don't get the wrong idea.
Just because I share a room with you,
doesn't mean you get to do this.
Listen carefully.
I'm not that easy.
Piang.
I'm sorry.
I never thought you were easy.
Everything I did
was only because I wanted you
to remember me.
Please stop trying.
Can't you see?
I'm only missing memories of you.
Maybe it's because the time
we spent together
was the worst time of my life.
I admit it.
I treated you terribly back then.
But…
I really don't want you to forget me.
I want you to remember me.
So you'll know
I'm not the same Song anymore.
The one who was stubborn
and kept running from her own heart.
I'm a new Song now.
Someone who's ready to make you happy
and ready to love you
with no conditions.
Do you really love me?
I do.
Then say it five more times.
I love you.
I…
Wait.
You…
Ding-dong!
You got played.
What do you mean?
I never had amnesia.
I staged everything to get back at you.
Because if I hadn't,
I would've never heard you say,
"I love you."
What about the others?
They were in on it too.
Wait.
You can't get mad and run away again.
We've been chasing each other long enough.
If you leave again,
there won't be another chance.
I'm not running away.
I'm just thinking
about how to punish you.
What's taking you so long?
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED
Mission accomplished.
The two of us helped Song and Piang
find their way to each other.
So why, when it's our turn,
are you letting go?
Let's fight for us together.
The pain you're going through now…
You've already survived it once.
Don't let it hurt you again.
Ple, are you trying to kill me?
You little brat!
Are you trying to kill me?
Ple, is something wrong?
About my father…
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to report him.
That's the right thing to do.
As for us…
I've… made up my mind too.
Everything you said was true.
The two of us
kept helping other people fall in love.
But when it came to us…
No.
It was me.
I chose to let go of your hand.
Seriously?
When you weren't by my side,
I felt so lonely.
I kept telling myself,
"It'll be better tomorrow."
But when we met again,
my feelings became even clearer.
I realized how much I need you.
Really, Ple?
You didn't seem to care about me.
Ever since I called you,
even when we met at the hospital,
you ignored me.
Yeah, I was putting on an act.
I'm terrible at being honest.
You know that.
Ploy.
Will you come back to me?
By the way, how many drinks have you had?
Why?
I just want to make sure
you're not too drunk
to know what you're saying.
Ploy.
Come back to me.
How could I not?
I've been waiting for this.
The view is beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
Once we're married,
we can come here more often.
What?
Are you proposing to me?
Then… where's the ring?
I don't have it.
Then why are you getting my hopes up?
Actually, I already have a ring.
I just didn't bring it with me.
I think
before I put the ring on your finger,
I should ask your grandmother first.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
Oh.
Hey, Piang.
Come dance with me.
You haven't danced with me in ages.
Let me have this dance with her.
If you don't mind,
may I have this dance, Madam?
You can dance?
Yes.
Song.
Oh…
It doesn't look like she can dance.
Song, that's not
how you dance with an elder.
Madam,
I'm sorry for breaking my promise to you.
I really tried,
but I couldn't do it.
I'm in love with Piang.
Very much.
And I'm going to ask her to marry me.
This time, I won't make you any promises.
I'll prove to you
that I truly love your granddaughter.
I won't ask anything of you.
Just don't make her cry again.
Are you finished?
Yes, I am.
So I can get back to
dancing with my teacher.
Otherwise,
people might think
you came to flirt with me,
not my granddaughter.
What?
That's a dance move for couples.
Next time,
if you can't dance, just tell me.
I'll teach you
so you won't embarrass yourself again.
Well…
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
Sorry…
There she is.
Grandma.
Your Ladyship.
Piang.
Oh.
So you're
the woman who stole Song's heart.
Oh, my.
What a twist of fate.
Song, remember when
I told you
I once saved a young woman?
That young woman was Piang.
Wait, wait.
What's going on?
And why are you at my house,
Your Ladyship?
Well, I'm here to ask for
your granddaughter's hand
for my granddaughter.
Who's your granddaughter?
-Right here.
-Huh?
Song Sadanun Warakij.
The heir
to the Warakijaruwongs royal family.
-I'm going to faint.
-Grandma!
Why didn't you tell me
who your family was?
Because I didn't want to win you over
with my status or family name.
I wanted you to accept me
for how sincerely I love Piang.
That's my wonderful granddaughter.
That's exactly how it's done.
So, what do you say?
Will you let your granddaughter
marry my granddaughter?
Sure…
Take her already.
What?
Careful, Grandma. Easy.
Isn't it amazing?
It's so good.
I've never had a girlfriend before.
So, will you be my girlfriend?
Hello, Mudmee.
I'm Kwanrin from 124 KT Design.
I'd like to help plan
your sister's wedding.
Is that really why you're here?
Your name is Kwanrin, right?
Yes.
You remember me?
Of course.
I'm the one who broke you two up.
Would it be alright
if I asked you
to get back together
with my granddaughter?
Grandma.
I want to see both of
my granddaughters happy.
Thank you so much, Grandma.
Mudmee.
I'm sorry
for letting go of you
the way I did that day.
Everything happened so suddenly
that I didn't know what to do.
But today,
I'm here to ask for another chance.
I promise
that no matter what we face,
or what obstacles come,
I won't leave you again.
I promise.
I accept.
Then keep your promise.
Look, I've got a witness right here.
You're the witness,
but you're also the biggest obstacle.
You little…
Let's start over.
Okay.
I look beautiful, don't I?
You look beautiful.
You look beautiful too.
Is this Neung?
You two look exactly alike.
Yes.
We look the same
but our personalities are nothing alike.
Song,
can I ask you something?
What happened to Neung?
And… what does it have to do with you?
But if you're not ready to talk about it…
I am.
We're getting married.
I have nothing left to hide from you.
The two of us…
dated the same woman.
What?
-"The same woman?"
-Yes.
But she was a con artist.
She conned us both out of our money.
She used her charm
to make both Neung and me
trust her completely.
Neither of us
ever suspected her.
I missed you so much.
Have you been waiting long?
We loved her so deeply
and gave her everything.
Then one day,
Neung realized something wasn't right.
Eventually, she learned the whole truth.
I was devastated.
But Neung was hurting even more.
She couldn't move past the pain.
In the end,
she made that choice.
After that,
I kept thinking…
If Neung died in misery,
then you didn't deserve
to be happy, right?
That's right.
Especially when it came to love.
That's one reason
I never wanted to love anyone.
Until I met you
and truly fell in love with you.
That's why I ran from my own heart.
I understand.
If I'd known what you'd been through,
I would've never let you go.
No matter how many times you ran from me,
I'd still stay by your side.
Thank you.
For being here.
Yes.
And I'll stay by your side
for the rest of my life.
Thank you.
Marry me.
Yes.
Thank you.
Isn't this the perfect moment for a kiss?
-Kiss!
Are you ready?
-Mud's over here!
-Piang, throw it this way!
-Mud is over here!
-Three, two…
-That's it!
-Get married next!
Come on, that's it!
-Grandma!
-Everyone, get in the frame!
-Come on, my dear.
-Don't block the camera.
-Okay.
Five, four, three… Okay!
Isn't it winter?
Where's the fog?
It's nighttime.
There won't be any fog now.
I was kidding.
So what star are you waiting to see?
The lovers' star.
You've been watching another series,
haven't you?
Well…
The same one with the wine scene.
So you know it doesn't work now?
True.
I can't see that star.
Where's the lovers' star?
It's right here.
Forget that silly star.
Let's go back to our room.
My hand's fully healed now.
Wait.
Will you dance with me first?
This time, I'll lead.
Of course.
I'd like to see how well
Grandma trained you.
Piang, thank you for loving me.
And for giving me the courage
to be happy again.
I'm so lucky to have met you, Piang.
I'm lucky too
to have met you, Song.
Really?
How so?
I don't know.
Isn't that what I'm supposed to say?
You're so adorable, you little goof.