"Unfold"
(Episode 8)
If Yu Guangming wanted to kill Bai Che,
he wouldn't have gone to all this trouble.
He just wants to clean up his mess
so he has no loose ends.
It's not that simple.
Wake up.
I think I met him twenty years ago.
Back then, Lao Bai rounded up those kids
and locked them in dog cages.
He was burning up with a 104-degree fever.
I was the one who gave him his medicine.
So,
you've always hated
this business of theirs.
Bullshit.
A bunch of filthy kids running around you
all day long.
Who would like that?
But you still couldn't bear it,
so you wanted to help them.
Three years ago,
you knew Lao Bai sent me here.
Why did you keep me?
Bai Che,
do you remember me?
I don't know you.
Of course you don't.
Back then, you were locked in a cage
like a dog.
You were dying of a 104-degree fever.
If I hadn't given you that medicine,
you'd be dead by now.
Let me go!
That's exactly how I
pried your mouth open.
Get a pen and inkpad. Make him sign.
Don't move!
Bai Che!
Zhou Chen!
What is he doing here?
Let Bai Che go!
Don't move!
Stay back!
Back off!
Or Bai Che is dead.
Who sent you?
Someone texted me.
You lunatics who play with human lives
will get what's coming to you.
How much is a life worth anyway?
This city went mad a long time ago.
If not for us lunatics,
where would that little
girl's organs have come from?
Oh, right.
You played a part in it too,
Bai Che.
Shut up!
I'm nothing like you.
And you,
Zhou, the great saint.
Do you really think you're a savior?
That little girl's father
contacted us on his own.
He was in debt,
so he jumped off a building.
You happily went to arrange the transplant.
You saved one life,
but you killed another.
You want to silence us
just because we know
too many of your secrets?
Why don't you check your phone?
Right now, the whole city
is talking about what you've done.
Do you think Mayor
Yu can still protect you?
Do I need protection?
I just want to sell the port and leave.
I never wanted to kill anyone.
But the fact that Mayor
Yu let you find this place
means he doesn't just want to kill Bai Che.
He wants to kill you too.
Do you think selling the port
and giving Mayor Yu a cut
will make him let you go?
You know
far too much.
What makes you think
you can get away scot-free?
How about this?
"Mayor Yu
hired a hitman
to kill the eldest son of the Zhou family."
Sensational enough, right?
Once we kill you
and get this signed contract,
we'll leak the news.
Do you still think we can't
get away scot-free?
Sign it.
Let Zhou Chen go,
and I'll sign.
Bai Che,
don't!
Let him go.
I'll be your hostage.
Zhou Chen,
don't...!
What makes you think
I need a hostage?
The Zhous aren't stupid.
Mayor Yu is begging
everyone for help right now.
Only with me in your hands
can you force the Zhous
to give you a green light
to leave here safely.
Zhou Chen,
don't...!
Don't fucking move.
Tie him up.
Zhou Chen,
I'm not worth this.
Don't worry, I didn't lie to you.
And I didn't lie to him either.
We'll all be fine.
Zhao Lingye,
Cheng Fan betrayed Lao Bai.
He can betray you just as easily.
That's a lie!
I've never thought of betraying him.
Zhao Lingye,
do you dare to deny
that in these three years,
you've never doubted him?
I trust him.
Cheng Fan,
Lao Bai killed my parents,
and he killed your mother too.
Why are you still working for them?
He's not like Lao Bai.
He's different.
If Zhao Lingye dares to kill
Zhou Chen and me today,
he'll kill you tomorrow.
To them, human lives are just tools.
He never loved you.
I didn't want to kill anyone today.
Bai Che!
Stop!
Let me go!
Bai Che.
It's nothing.
I'm just worried about you.
It's going to be very unsafe lately.
Would you...
like to move in with me?
I'm glad
you came to see me.
But next time,
just call me.
I'll come pick you up.
Can you feel it?
Every time he sees you,
it beats a little faster.
(To be continued)