Hey, buddy
Thanks a lot
How much?
How much is it?
One yuan, just one
Thanks
Uncle Daren, off to work?
Afu, you go on ahead
I'm waiting for someone
Okay
See you in a bit
Sure thing
Daren
Am I late?
No, you're not
Put this on first
What is this thing?
This is your work ticket
Wear it and you can find work
Got it
How do I...
How does this go on?
Tighten it up
Okay
What kind of work can I do?
Whatever you're told to do, you do
Fine
As long as it's not illegal
I can do any damn thing
I can take any hardship
Here, eat your breakfast first
A full belly means strength to work
It's still hot!
Don't rush, don't rush
One at a time
One at a time, please
Boss, boss
You can haul heavy loads, right?
Yes, I can
Sure I can
Then you all get ready
Okay, come on
Don't rush now, don't rush
Why are so many people looking for work?
It's like this every day
Some things, you know...
you're better off not knowing
Curiosity killed the cat
I'm afraid you couldn't handle it.
It's a big world, full of strange things.
As long as you dare to tell me
I'll dare to believe it
Alright, once I tell you
you have to keep your lips sealed
I promise
If I break my word
may lightning strike me down
That last one doesn't count
Let's do it again
Eight years ago
after my old man passed away
touching a relic connects my five senses
I can see and hear
what happened to the deceased when alive
I can even feel
their joys and sorrows at that moment
It's kind of
a bit like dreaming
From my view it's like filming a movie
You don't have a fever
So why are you talking nonsense?
Fine, don't believe me
It sounds absurd
but
I believe you
I wonder if it's connected
to when I hit my head back then
Maybe stuff in your brain got jumbled up
and then recombined
giving you superpowers
Are all you art students this abstract?
Because your five senses connect
that's why your writing hits so hard
Come on, man
I graduated in Chinese Literature
Stop doubting my professional skills.
Okay, okay, okay
Just hear me out
Given that you have this ability
you're destined for the funeral business!
You, me
teaming up with my sister
we could definitely make Xiaoxitian huge
All this talk
you're trying to keep me here
I know
your heart isn't in this
I can't wake a person pretending to sleep
nor hold onto a heart that wants to leave
You got it right
Clear-headed as they come, kid
Oh right
Do you have any other powers?
Like what?
Walking through walls
Hypnosis
Telekinesis
Are you crazy?
Friends walk through life together
those days will never come again
One word, a whole lifetime
Kneel
Heaven above,
earth below,
I, Zhou Fang,
I, Chen Xiaofang,
ask not to be born on the same day,
but to die on the same day...
Hey, we don't say that word in our shop.
It really jinxes things.
I won't say it.
I won't, I won't.
But Xiaofang,
you have to promise me one thing.
You have to go before me.
Because if I die before you,
leaving you in someone else's care,
I couldn't rest easy.
I'll go after you.
Why, you ask?
Because you're too much of a fool.
Leaving you with someone else worries me.
No way, you go first.
You go first.
You die first.
Get up, get up.
All right, all right.
Easy now, easy.
What are you two doing this late at night?
Brother-in-law,
I'm just so moved.
I'm not drunk, I can still drink.
Okay, okay.
There's serious business tomorrow.
Head home now.
Right.
Serious business.
Then I'll head home first.
Friends walk through life together,
those days will come no more...
Enough.
He's already gone.
Stop putting on an act.
I'm not acting.
I'm genuinely drinking to forget.
Yiran, I'm getting married tomorrow.
I'm really anxious.
What are you anxious about?
You two know each other inside out.
It's a love marathon.
So what's there to worry about?
You have no idea.
They all say
marriage is the grave of love.
I'm really scared that once I marry,
a family brings a burden,
and Zhou Fang and I will end up in the grave.
Bah, bah, bah, knock on wood.
Bah, bah, bah.
It's such a wonderful thing.
Why go on about all this nonsense?
Oh, right.
What were you and my brother doing alone?
I didn't even call you two out.
It's not what you think.
We were discussing the five-sense link.
Chen Baixi!
That mouth of yours...
He, he...
The two of us were just saying...
talking about how to pay off debt faster.
Paying off debt?
After all, 200,000 is no small sum.
We said, split it into five payments.
Brother,
do you have feelings for Yiran?
Come on, tell me.
No way.
You know me well.
Impossible.
I know you too well, that's why I said it.
This acting of yours...
Your face is all red.
You've got it wrong.
I've just had a bit too much to drink.
Xiaofang,
listen, tomorrow's a big day.
I'll go with you to the registry office.
Let's get a good rest tonight, okay?
Come on.
I'll go pack up.
I'll grab a bag.
Well then
The two of us guardians
won't be going in there with you two
Go on
Let's go
Here.
This is yours.
And this is yours.
Thank you.
Share in our joy.
Good things come in pairs.
Thank you!
May you two be forever united.
And have a child soon.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Let's go.
You scared me!
You two are way over the top.
Congratulations on your wedding!
Thank you both!
Today you're officially licensed.
We've got to celebrate.
Three-star Michelin, how about it?
Perfect!
You stole our Xiaofang away,
so we're gonna bleed you dry.
Zhou Fang!
Dad.
Uncle.
Hello, sir.
Zhou Fang,
do you even care about me, your father?
When did I ever agree
to you marrying into the funeral trade?
You...
you even dared to steal the family register!
If Wumei hadn't told me,
were you planning to defy me completely?
Didn't you tell me your dad agreed?
Well, obviously he didn't.
I was just so eager to marry you,
that's why I snuck out the register.
Who knew you don't even need it anymore?
Sir.
Why don't we talk somewhere else?
This is a family matter.
It's none of your business.
If you dare go through with this wedding,
I'll disown you as my son.
Then disown me.
We're already legally married anyway.
You little brat!
How dare you!
Mr. Zhou.
There's no need for this, come on.
Don't think I can't rein you in.
I'll freeze every one of your cards.
Let's see how many days you last.
Even if you freeze all my cards,
I'm still going to marry Xiaofang.
You...
Dad
What'll it take
for you to leave my son?
Name your price.
Sir, this really isn't right.
Dad, this won't work.
Xiaofang is not like that at all.
Fine then.
You.
On this card,
there's a million.
Leave my son right now.
I was only going to ask for 100 grand.
Didn't expect him to be so generous.
A whole million, just like that.
Guess I was still too naive.
Just wait, sir.
I'll do exactly as you wish right now.
Xiaofang! Xiaofang!
Divorce.
You two just got married.
None of your business. I want a divorce.
The faster, the better.
Think it through next time you marry.
This isn't playing house!
There won't be a next time.
Sorry.
Sorry to trouble you.
That was faster than ordering takeout.
Fingerprint here.
There's a 30-day cooling-off period.
If you change your mind, you can withdraw it.
I'm changing my mind right now.
Xiaofang.
Press it, for me.
This...
Xiaofang
I'm dreaming right now, aren't I?
Zhou Fang
From now on
you go your way
and I'll go mine
Let's just leave each other be
Xiaofang
I'll go check on her
It's fine
We're the most fickle
No
It's women
Women are the most fickle
Xu Wumei, just shut up
Chen Xiaofang just loves money
In her heart
this one million
matters more than you
She's not like that
Xiaofang
Sis
What kind of act was that just now?
Do you have any idea
what happens if Dad finds out about this?
Bro
Yeah, I love Zhou Fang
but I love money even more!
Do you have any idea
how many funerals our family has to run
just to earn that one million?
Exactly
You're a little rich lady now
A millionaire!
Who needs a man?
Call that talking her out of it?
Yeah
Score a 30-day divorce cooling-off period
and pocket a free one million too!
Let's go!
I'll go find Zhou Fang.
I'll come with you.
You've gone too far, Zhou Fang.
What were you thinking?
Do you even have a brain?
What kind of problem is this?
This is a matter of principle.
To put it bluntly,
this is marriage fraud, you know that?
Okay, okay, okay.
Sit down first, sit down.
Just sit down.
I didn't mean to deceive her.
I just wanted so badly to marry her.
The way your dad acted today,
if my sister had married into that family,
who knows how badly she'd be bullied.
Good thing they divorced.
How could I ever let her get bullied?
You two are my friends, after all.
Could you at least comfort me a little?
Divorced on my wedding day, seriously.
What did I do to deserve this?
What sin did I commit?
You brought this on yourself.
A dreamy start,
a nightmare ending.
You totally deserve it.
It's a pretty good ending, though.
I'd call it a perfect ending.
Everyone's happy.
Good thing Xiaofang didn't stay with you,
right, Mr. Award-Winning Actor?
Fair enough.
Yiran, you...
How can you be like this?
Comforting one while insulting another.
Brother-in-law,
try to think of something.
Don't call me that.
Xiaofang's always been headstrong.
Once she decides on something,
she usually won't change her mind.
But you two just got divorced.
There's a 30-day cooling-off period.
Maybe things could turn around.
Brother-in-law, you're right.
I still have that cooling-off period.
After all, I just got married today too.
Stop thinking about marriage or divorce
or cooling off or whatever.
You just calm down first.
Deal with your dad before anything else.
Young Master Zhou.
I think, you know,
Yiran's right.
Some things, you know,
are just like these skewers.
Wait too long and they go cold.
Uncle Daren, you're right.
Some things really can't wait.
I'll go back right now and handle my dad.
Here, Uncle Daren.
This is for the meal.
You guys eat, go on.
I won't eat then.
No, no.
This can wait.
It can wait.
Then I'll keep it for you.
Just put it away, quick.
That's too much money.
I know, I know.
I promised to roast him a whole lamb.
Forget the roast lamb, Uncle Daren.
Next time I'll roast you a whole cow.
He doesn't deserve it.
No roast for him.
All right.
Have some skewers.
I don't want any.
Eat up, they're getting cold.
What's wrong with you?
Those Zhous are pushing us around!
I'm going over to the Zhous right now
to demand an explanation.
Dad.
Let me ask you something.
How much savings do you have?
At a time like this,
why are you asking that?
Be honest, how much savings do you have?
I lent your brother 200,000.
So I've got about 300,000 left.
See?
You slaved half your life for 500,000.
Today, one sentence earned me a million.
Oh, you.
This isn't about money.
This is about your marriage.
I won't let you get pushed around.
Dad.
Do I look like someone who gets pushed around?
If I don't push the Zhous around,
they should count themselves lucky.
My child,
you have to remember,
when it comes to marriage,
never settle for less than you deserve.
Don't worry.
As long as your dad's around,
I'll never let you suffer one bit.
Dad, I know.
I'm just afraid
you'll think that I
married in and got mistreated,
and your health isn't good either.
I know.
Our family's in this line of work,
and the Zhous find it unlucky.
I also know I'm old now,
and I'm not good for much.
So I've never meddled in your marriages.
But I do hope
you can both find
someone you truly love.
Dad, don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Dad
Just let me explain
It was wrong to steal the family register
But I have to marry Chen Xiaofang
You're gonna be the death of me
Let's go
Dad
The damn weather forecast
isn't accurate at all
Such heavy rain
Where'd you go?
Coming back this late
What are you doing?
Did you miss me?
You care about me?
I'd better just worry about myself
Being jobless isn't scary
What's scary is staying jobless forever
Here.
It's the same one you lost.
I bought it at the official store.
This model costs over 2,000.
Where'd you get the money for it?
Don't look down on me.
I earned it doing odd jobs lately.
What odd job pays over 2,000 so fast?
I've got two hands and two feet.
I didn't steal or rob anyone.
I'd never do anything illegal.
Use it, don't worry.
And one more thing.
The debts I owe, I'll pay off myself.
Stay out of it.
That bankbook of yours,
I put it under your pillow.
Wu Huilian, listen to me.
Those shady jobs from Auntie Juan,
you really can't take them anymore.
You hear me?
What do you mean, shady jobs?
I'm in great shape right now.
The moment money sees me,
it comes flying straight at me.
It chases after me, you know?
Go take a shower first.
Don't catch a cold.
Wu Huilian
Don't worry
Where'd she go this early?
Did she get conned by some quack again?
Dad
Don't worry
I'll keep an eye on her
She just got out and doesn't know a thing
And she's been out of touch for so many years
I really don't want to deal with her
But, for your sake
I'll grit my teeth and
keep an eye on her, I guess
Can't just let her get scammed, right?
Waking up early ruins the whole day
Something's off here.
Something's off about this Wu Huilian.
Aren't I just asking for trouble?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Where'd you go? Coming home this late.
Went to play mahjong.
Wanted to win some money off them.
But my luck today was just terrible.
Downright cursed.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Wash off the bad luck.
Hold on, hold on.
Wait a second.
You stand right there.
What for?
What is it now?
What's that smell?
You reek of perfume mixed with stink.
It's suffocating!
That damn Zhang Lijuan.
She sprayed that perfume all over me.
Stinks to high heaven.
What are you staring at?
What happened to your hand?
This?
I was playing mahjong today.
Those tiles were huge.
And it was a brand-new set.
The tiles weren't smooth at all.
I shuffled back and forth.
Shuffling really hard.
And ended up scraping my hand raw.
See?
All from shuffling mahjong.
Mahjong tiles made of knives?
Razor blades on the tiles?
Slashed your hand up like this, huh?
Take a look yourself.
Just look at your hand.
You expect me to believe that?
Quit lying to me.
I looked for you all day today.
You weren't playing mahjong downstairs.
I wasn't playing downstairs, no.
I went to play on the old street.
Tell me the truth while I'm still patient.
These past days you leave early every morning.
And come home this late.
What have you been up to?
Just sweep the snow off your own doorstep,
and don't mind the frost on others' roofs.
You won't even let me look after you.
So why bother minding my business?
You sure stick your nose in a lot.
None of your business anyway.
I'll do whatever the hell I please.
Strange guy.
Such a liar.
Let's see how long you can keep hiding it.
Go on
Go, go, go
Go
Go! Get out!
Get out!
Demons and ghosts, be gone!
Go, go, go!
Get away! Get away! Get away!
You scared me!
You scared me too!
Are you possessed by a ghost or what?
Possessed by a ghost? Come on.
I feel something evil following me.
I'm driving them away.
Go, go, go!
The bad energy is heavy this morning.
Let me breathe in some good energy.
Stop breathing it all in!
Save some for me, would you?
I'm taking in some good energy.
There, feeling some good energy now.
Scared me to death!
Wait, wait, wait!
What are you doing?
No way.
You're seeing things now.
That's enough, you worked a whole week.
It's time to take a break.
Rest today.
Rest, rest.
I'm not tired.
I've got tons of energy.
Fine, I get it, I get it.
That's right.
Give me the hat, come on.
Oh my goodness!
Come on, let's go.
You got me all sweaty.
Jumped around till you're hungry, huh?
There's no evil thing at all.
You're just imagining things.
Bouncing around a bit felt so good!
Let's have breakfast first.
What is it?
Your favorite pork and pickle buns.
You're so thoughtful!
What's wrong?
Why do I feel something following me?
Why are you so paranoid?
Come on, let's go.
It's time.
Have a bite.
I already ate.
So this fraud is Uncle Daren!
I've gotta see this.
What are they up to?
Take it easy, take it easy
One at a time
One at a time, okay?
Shandong buns!
Fresh steamed
Shandong buns
Fifty cents each
Six, six, six
How many?
Six
And pickles, twelve yuan
This one
Which one do you want?
This one? This one?
You two are together, right?
Together
Come on, come on
Shandong buns
Shandong buns, tasty and delicious
That job you mentioned last time,
any news on it yet?
They say the materials aren't all in
Who knows how long we'll be waiting
Yeah
Work's so hard to find this year
These days you just can't get any work
Can't find any, can't find any
Boss, I can tie rebar, you know
You interested?
Pay up now
Twelve yuan a bottle
Twelve yuan
I'll take one bottle
Want one? Come get one
Big Shandong steamed buns
Fifty cents each, come on
Fifty cents
Scan it over there
Okay, okay, okay
How many do you want?
Just one
Fifty cents each, right
Handmade pickled veggies
Fifty cents
Handmade pickled veggies, twelve yuan
Fifty cents, fifty cents, fifty cents
I want three
Auntie, one bowl of porridge
Big buns, fifty cents each, want some?
Fifty cents each, right here
Shandong steamed buns
All out
Sorry, we're all out
Come back tomorrow
Two bowls of rice porridge
I want two bowls of rice porridge
Auntie
How much is this?
Five yuan
Give me something hot, will you
Sure. You tired or not?
Come on, come on
Hiring! We're hiring!
Hurry it up
Coming, coming
Come on, everybody line up over here.
Quiet down, quiet.
Quiet!
Listen up to what I'm saying.
You, and you.
Get in the truck.
Go, go, go.
You won't cut it.
A scrawny little frame like yours.
Hauling frozen pork from the cold storage.
Even strong men can't handle it, get it?
Why you little son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
You little bastard, put me down!
Don't let my skinny build fool you.
I'm strong as hell.
What's your name?
Just call me Afu, boss.
You little rascal, you're pretty sharp!
Get in.
Thanks, boss.
Break it up, break it up.
Next time, next time.
Clear out.
Come on, come on.
Hiring workers!
Hurry up, hurry, hurry!
Go, go, go, over there.
Get down, now!
What are you doing?
Come back next time.
What are you shoving me for?
You okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm still hiring here.
Hey, that one.
Don't push! Settle down!
I only need two people, two.
Just two people.
We only need two people
Come on, pick two more
Come on, hire one more
We only need two people
I think I just saw Yiran
No way
This early?
That sleepyhead? No way she's up
Boss, boss
Coming, coming, boss
Count me in, will you
Still got two left
Dried radish
Welcome to Dr. Wu's secret hospital.