The best agent in the agency,
Special Agent Alex.
She figured out the whereabouts
of Mikoy and Chiara Valtrovi.
So you think Agent Alex will find Mikoy?
I think that's possible.
Right at this moment,
the two of them are already in custody.
I have a strong feeling they're okay.
Very much alive.
And when you're young,
you're so in love, like,
crazy in love, like Beyoncé!
La Morte Bianca.
Ouch!
Hello? Anybody home?
Anybody home?
Hey, have mercy on me!
Let me out of here!
Wait. Mikoy, relax, okay?
Relax. Breathe.
That's it. Just relax. Breathe.
Wait.
I've seen this before.
How did Uma Thurman get out of here again?
What is this?
Ouch!
I can't breathe anymore!
Smoky air and polluted particles?
I'm back in the Philippines.
Wait, what happened?
Can you at least debrief me first?
Well, believe it or not,
it was easier to transport
the two of you in coffins.
Sweetheart, you too?
They put you in a coffin too?
But unlike you,
I wasn't being overly dramatic.
Fine, you're the cool, calm,
and collected one.
I'm the one who's always over the top.
It's called emotion regulation.
Don't worry, we have protocols
for situations like this at the agency.
We're actually allowed to use coffins.
And I also gave both of you
strong sedatives,
so you wouldn't get claustrophobic
during the trip.
Thanks for those strong sedatives
you gave us.
I don't even know what's going on anymore.
This.
Since you still haven't signed
the immunity agreement,
you are still considered
enemies of the law.
So you need to wear those.
I remember these!
They're just like the wedding booths
during school intramurals, right?
Sweetheart, this was
how it worked back then.
If you had a crush at school,
you'd handcuff them,
then you'd both go into the wedding booth.
You know what that means.
- So you've been married before?
- No.
Come on, sweetheart, it was just for fun,
and I was still a kid back then.
Little Mikoy?
Very little.
Chiara, please put it on.
Come back again, okay?
Tess!
- What?
- Tess!
- Uncle Pepe.
- You have a visitor.
Who?
That one.
Sofie, come here! What brings you here?
I'm applying for a job.
Oh, dear.
Are you really sure about this, child?
You know this will ruin
your summer vacation.
I'm absolutely sure,
and Daddy already approved it.
Okay. Let me just manage
your expectations first, okay?
Just look at our bakery.
It's very small and not high-tech.
And look at our oven.
Right, Betchay and Angel?
We're always drenched in sweat here.
Are you even used to working in the heat?
Your skin will get all sticky
from the heat around here.
And during summer vacation,
there are fiestas one after another
in the barangays.
I'm telling you, you won't get any rest.
- You won't even have time to sit down.
- True.
Wow. Okay.
I'm not trying
to discourage you, okay, Sofie?
But are you really sure
this is what you want?
Yes, I'm absolutely sure.
I don't care about
the heat or the exhaustion,
and no matter how many orders there are,
I can handle it.
Because a summer job
is exactly what I'm looking for.
Besides, there's no such thing
as an easy job.
My goal is to develop life skills
that I can't easily learn in school.
Well then, why don't you look
for a different summer job?
Right?
One that aligns with those life skills.
Why work here with us?
Good point.
Because I want to work here!
And I also want to spend time
with Mama Tess.
Really! You're flattering me now.
Oh, no, I'm not flattering you.
You know, I've always wanted
to learn how to bake.
And now I finally have the chance.
And the best part is,
we'll get to bond too.
That way, it's like getting
to know my mom better too.
You really are something, kid.
You really will do anything, won't you,
to get what you want.
Tell me about it.
You can never beat Sofie's determination.
All right, hija!
You're officially a baker now!
Oh, my baker!
PINAGPALA
SPECIAL BAKESHOP
Where are we?
And it's part of the immunity agreement
you're about to sign.
And just how safe is this safe house?
Well, it's very safe here.
And it's just the two of you--
Surprised?
Don't worry. It's just us.
We're also joined by Senator Quintin,
who has been helping us with this case.
Senator Quintin, winning as always.
Oh.
Wow.
This is the first time
I've been starstruck by an assassin.
You're actually cute.
And you're handcuffed to your boyfriend.
You two are so cute together.
You make a great pair.
You look like a couple
of tame little kittens.
Now?
Do we still look like tame kittens?
We're not underestimating you.
Because we're willing to cooperate.
I hope you are too.
Didn't I tell you?
Lock your holster
so nobody can grab your gun.
You're so stubborn.
It's already loose.
When we get our bonus, I'll buy a new one.
You just lost beauty points with me.
Turns out you're not respectful.
Take them to the living room first.
Somewhere we can keep an eye on them.
We have to talk about some things first.
Sir. I promise you, sir.
Chiara can help us a lot.
Besides, it's more fun here too.
I'm getting tired of dumplings
and Hong Kong fried noodles.
But for now,
leave us for a moment, La Fornarina.
It's simpler.
Let the bosses
have their discussion, okay?
Oh, wow!
Well, Angelito's shirt
looks so good on you.
Even if it's just a little bit oversized.
Oh.
It's perfectly fine with me.
I don't mind if it's a little big on me.
Besides, this isn't the first time
he's let me borrow his things.
Girl, that's not exactly a flex.
That was my spare toothbrush.
Besides, that's in the past.
Let's not bring up the past anymore.
Let's just forget about it.
All right, all right, all right.
You need to head upstairs
to the kitchen now
because I need to work and prepare lunch!
We have a delivery to make.
Leave that to the kids.
We'll work upstairs. Come on.
- Come on, already. Let's work upstairs.
- Oh, yeah.
Good grief!
Look who's talking. You're the one
telling Mom all sorts of things.
So embarrassing.
Embarrassing? Didn't you see that?
Mom was totally fine with it.
So then, where do we start?
You know, it's not too late.
You can still back out.
Just relax at the resort.
Look how hot it is.
It's perfect weather for swimming.
You know what?
You're a great pretender.
Whenever your parents are around,
you're so nice, like some kind of angel.
But once they're gone, there you go.
It's like you want to kick me out
of your bakery.
Oh, please.
If I'm a great pretender,
then you're a great manipulator!
Look how quickly you got
Mom and Dad to say yes.
Not just this time, but with
so many people in so many situations.
Whenever you want something, you get it.
You're the only thing that's hard to get.
- You're so difficult.
- Because
All right, let's get to work.
We still have 100 cakes
to finish and deliver.
- One hundred? That many?
- Yes.
Can I cut in?
Yes, 100. One hundred. Siento!
So save your little drama
for later, you two!
We need to bake 100 cakes.
So help us God. Let's go. Come on.
Looks like I need to schedule
an appointment with my nail tech.
My nails are starting to chip.
I know what that means when you do that.
That you don't want to talk about
what you did earlier.
What did I do?
He started it.
And you know I hate it
when people underestimate me.
Even so, sweetheart, he's still a senator.
And even if he weren't a senator,
it would still be wrong
to point a gun at someone.
Come on, sweetheart.
What if they have another plan,
and that's why they want immunity?
And what if
they're just making up stories
about having something valuable for us?
You know,
it's true that Chiara has a scary stare.
Very intense.
But those are exactly the kinds of girls
who fall for my charm.
Just give me one or two days.
She'll fall for me, I promise.
Wow, you're really making promises now?
You know Chiara.
She'd throw you off a cliff.
You need to tone down
your violent tendencies
if you want to make a deal
with the agency.
We're here to cooperate,
not to start a shootout.
Well, I have my reasons for doing that.
Go ahead then.
Give me one good reason why you did it.
To show them that even if
we're willing to help,
we remain dangerous,
and we're not easily manipulated.
And if they go back on their promise,
I'll take them out one by one.
To be honest, at first,
I didn't believe them either.
I know Chiara has explosive information
that could change the course
of this entire story.
Looks like she's been blinded
by her love for Mikoy.
She wants immunity because
she wants a future
with the man she loves most.
Whatever information she has,
well, at least we'll be one step ahead
of a bigger and more dangerous enemy
other than the Moravianos.
What is this Concordat?
That is why the Philippines
is very important to the mafia.
Because in this country lies the weapon
that will bring chaos and instability
to the entire world.
Nobody got this weapon, right?
What is that gut feel?
Because I have a feeling
it was a mistake to leave Ben there
to watch over Mikoy and Chiara.
Mikoy and Chiara are missing.
What?