Ouch!
I can’t breathe!
Mom!
We’re not underestimating you.
Because we are willing
to cooperate with you.
And I hope you too.
I guess I was just trying
to get close to you all.
That's pretty rare.
I'm not the kind of senator
who's driven by ego,
who refuses to apologize
when they make a mistake.
Instead of saying sorry,
they even gaslight people.
There!
We're all friends again.
Now we can finally start the real meeting.
What exactly is this Concordat?
The Concordat began in the 1900s.
It's an organization
similar to the European Union.
Like the United Nations,
but for criminals.
But since the Concordat
was created not for peace,
but for chaos,
the unity of nations
became the greatest threat to its power.
AMERICA: UNDER ATTACK AND WAR
Are you saying she's planning
to cause chaos here in the Philippines?
Not just in the Philippines,
but throughout the world.
And here in the Philippines
lies her means to bring havoc
to the whole world.
How?
What's Broken Arrow?
I have broken vows.
The Broken Arrow refers to an incident
that happened in 1965.
It involved an American fighter jet
that crashed into the Philippine Sea
somewhere near the Batanes Islands.
Neither was the nuclear bomb
it was carrying.
And that is why the Philippines
is very important to the mafia,
because in this country lies the weapon
that could bring chaos
and instability to the entire world.
But no one has recovered
that weapon, right?
Like you said, it sank
into the depths of the ocean, correct?
What’s happening?
They seem to be feeling faint.
Let’s check them.
- Go, ask for help!
- All right, okay!
Help! Help!
Help!
Are you saying that someone
already recovered the bomb?
Based on the information I have,
it was accidentally caught by a fisherman,
who later died from exposure.
Wait.
Why wasn't this incident reported?
Actually, it seems that it was reported.
A college professor named Enrico Santos…
…but he vanished and disappeared.
So how did you know all of this?
How did the mafia learn about it?
From what I know, this professor
fell victim to a phishing scam
because he liked dating sites.
And in one of his emails,
he described a radioactive bomb
that he stumbled upon during one
of his community outreach programs.
He knew the value of that information,
so he hid it,
planning to sell it someday
to the highest bidder.
What matters is that it's
a very, very powerful weapon.
And if it falls
into the Concordat's hands,
they will have the capability
to bring chaos to the world.
Tens of thousands
will be killed or injured,
with millions more affected
by the nuclear fallout.
‪Oh, so…
Do you have any idea
where this weapon might be now?
That's where the college professor
was last seen before he disappeared.
But maybe there's
a digital footprint we can use
to find that professor?
There's no trace of him.
That's why La Morte Bianca
wants to control the world,
and that's what the Moravianos are doing.
And I no longer have any information
about their plans or movements.
All I know is,
La Morte Bianca is already
here in the Philippines,
and I'm sure she will utilize everything
just to find that college professor.
Bye.
If we have the same information
as the Concordat has,
what advantage do we have
over them at this point?
That's my great love! So feisty!
We need to stop La Morte Bianca
before she gets her hands on that bomb.
I want eyes and ears
in every part of the Philippines.
Okay, I'm assigning Ben
to stay with you guys
because I know he can watch
over both of you.
There shouldn't be any problem
with you staying under one roof.
How about you?
Maybe you should ask the two of them first
if they even want you
living under the same roof.
Maybe they don't.
Because we don't really need
Agent Alex's protection.
Mikoy and I managed on our own
back in Hong Kong.
We can do it again.
Chiara's pretending,
but she's clearly falling for my charm.
I told you, I'm so magnetic.
Like a refrigerator magnet.
Jealous.
That's because you have no love life.
Okay, well, the meeting's over now, right?
I need to go to the nail salon,
and I need a massage.
I got a stiff neck
because you put me in a coffin, right?
What, are you keeping us
as prisoners here?
I don't understand why you're surprised.
This was the deal.
This was not part of the deal.
We have lives and families.
We asked for immunity in exchange
for the information I gave earlier.
We are doing this to first verify
the information you gave us.
We still don't have
mutual trust in each other.
Why? This place is fine.
You have plenty of room to move around.
I understand, sir.
Actually, whatever the agency wants
is fine with me.
We're okay with it.
I just hope there's a swimming pool
to cool off our hot heads.
What am I supposed to do now?
Well, you've already completed
one day of internship?
Basically, you'll just keep doing
what you've been doing.
What, put boxes on the motorcycle again?
I don't want that anymore.
I want the hard part.
I want to experience
baking a torta. Come on.
It will be our baby.
What baby are you talking about?
Our torta baby. That's what I meant.
Come on. We're going to make it together.
I don't know what kind of terms
you're learning these days.
That's from being on your phone too much.
Come on, teach me.
No, I can't.
We have too many orders.
I don't have time for lessons right now.
Please, just one?
Do you want me to kneel here?
Do whatever you want.
I'm really going to kneel. Here I go.
Sofie, what are you doing?
You're wearing shorts.
What if you get hurt?
You won't teach me.
You're so persistent, Sofie.
Fine then, sift this, this dry mixture,
so we can finish faster.
Here.
Not like that!
- Why?
- That's wrong.
You told me to sift it.
Like this. There, this one, like this.
But hold it more gently.
Don't grip it too hard.
Then, there, go ahead. Put it in.
That's it. Now slowly. Okay.
So finally, we're going to bake our baby!
Will you stop calling it a baby?
If Mom and Dad hear you,
they'll get the wrong idea.
So?
Come on. Help me with this.
Didn't you say it was too heavy
for you the first time?
I've got it.
Or we can do it together.
Okay.
Oh, for heaven's sake!
We have so much to prepare,
and all you do is fool around?
I’m telling this to Miss Tess.
You're the one who hasn't been here.
Me?
Sorry, okay? I'm here now.
What else is missing? I'll do it.
Here. This one.
Miss Betchay, come on.
- Teach me how to do it.
- Go ahead and pour that for me.
- Let's mix it.
- Pour it like this?
Mix.
- Then what?
- Go ahead.
I need to inform the President about
this radioactive material in our country.
Because we're not dealing
with a crime syndicate.
We have to verify and cross-check
all the information
Chiara gave us earlier first.
We need to know for sure
whether that bomb really exists.
What if Chiara is just
pulling the wool over our eyes?
Pulling the wool over my eyes?
I'm already bald.
No.
I'm not laughing because I'm bald.
I'm laughing at everything
that's happening to us.
There's a nuclear or chemical bomb
we need to find.
What if we end up finding
the Sex Bomb Girls instead?
- Oh my God.
- But you're right, comrade.
Every day I pray that
none of this would happen.
If there's one thing
we should be grateful for,
it's that we can still
do something about it.
We have to do everything we can
to stop La Morte Bianca's plans
from succeeding.
You're right, comrade.
Don't worry, you'll have all my support.
- Thank you, comrade.
- See you!
You know, Chiara isn't the only one
who needs to chill out.
Sir Norberto does too.
He's just being careful.
That's why he made those decisions.
I thought you trusted me?
Yes, I trust you.
But just because I trust you
doesn't mean everyone
in the agency will too.
Imagine all the resources
the agency had to deploy
because of your Hong Kong stint.
Everything could have been prevented
if you'd gone to the agency
from the start.
That's exactly why we did what we did.
I don't easily place my trust
in authorities either.
More often than not,
there's a mole inside the agency.
I like those.
Women with beauty marks,
especially on the cheek.
I don't really have a preference.
As long as she's kind,
can cook well, and loves dogs.
- You know--
- That's not the kind of mole I meant.
Maybe this is the first time in history
that there isn't a traitor
inside the agency.
Okay, we need to take our leave.
We still have a lot to do.
Just a reminder.
Okay?
Sianong.
I'm just going to the kitchen.
I've been thirsty for a while now.
You know, sweetheart,
this feels like my sister's house.
There are cameras everywhere.
There's only one way to find out
if this really is my sister's house,
like you said.
Chiara, Mikoy, please proceed
to the confession room.
Why does that voice sound like that?
It's definitely my sister.
You're right. Let's go.
Sis?
Sis!
There it is!
I knew it!
There's really no safe place
in my sister's house.
My whole life, I've felt
like I was trapped.
It's like I just traded
a steel cage for a birdcage.
We're still not free, Mikoy.
What's your problem? Does your back itch?
This car was just washed.
- No, it's not that.
- Then what?
I just have this feeling.
I don't know, maybe I'm starting
to catch your gut feeling thing.
What gut feeling?
Because I feel like
it was a mistake to leave Ben there
to watch over Mikoy and Chiara.
Think about it, on his very first
appearance at the hospital,
they got past him right away.
What?
Don't tell me, Bok, you're the one
falling for his charm now?
Wow, for the second time around!
Idiot.
I'm just saying people change.
Besides, who knows? Maybe
Senator Quintin sees something in him
that we simply don't see.
Wait.
There. I covered it up.
That should do it.
And then we'll get scolded again.
That's okay.
We can't always keep conforming.
We can rebel too, in our own little way.
- I'm so stressed right now.
- Really?
I have an idea.
What is it?
It’s Ben.
Mikoy and Chiara are missing!
What?
Do you want us to put you in jail?
I already talked to General Norberto.
Because of what you did,
he’ll send someone over
for you to be with.
Someone who's not addicted
to staying up late,
but addicted to the gym.
Who?