Are you saying that she will make
chaos here in the Philippines?
Not just in the Philippines,
but in the whole world.
It could be a nuclear bomb
or chemical bomb,
it's just a very, very powerful weapon.
So that's it?
Chiara has been excommunicated?
She's no longer family, that's it?
You did nothing?
You let Isabella make a decision
for our daughter?
It's always about the Moraviano!
You're Chiara's father.
Okay? We need to protect our daughter.
Believe me.
And we are powerless
against La Morte Bianca.
Wherever she may be right now.
Let's think about our survival first,
before our daughter.
You're pretty good at escaping.
Of course, I learned from you.
- From me, really?
- Yes.
Didn't you use to sneak out of school?
You were always climbing walls.
Huh? No way!
Do I look like someone who cuts classes?
I never cut class.
Wow, look at Mr. Pinagpala!
Of course, who else?
I've always been a good boy.
You know, sweetheart,
this is real freedom.
Just eating ice cream
while walking around.
Then talking about our past.
You know?
Reminiscing. Like this.
It's definitely easier to escape.
When no one is chasing you.
And when no one says,
"What do you think you're doing?"
Or when no one says,
"Just a reminder,
don't do anything stupid."
Wow!
You sound exactly like Agent Alex!
You know, I think
that Ben guy is already awake.
And he probably told Agent Alex
about what we did.
So I'm sure that any minute now,
their vehicle will arrive,
and stop right in front of us.
And Sianong will be the first to speak.
"Would you rather be locked up in jail?"
"We can arrange that."
Then Agent Alex will say,
"Do you think this is funny?"
"You're ruining everything!"
Would you rather be locked up in jail?
We can arrange that!
See?
I told you!
We just went out for ice cream.
There wasn't any at the safe house.
That's why we went out.
Yes.
Do you realize that because of this,
the agency will trust you even less?
We're sorry, we were already heading back.
You just got here first
because you have a vehicle.
Come on, let's go.
- Let's go back together.
- Get in.
Yay!
Are you making deliveries?
I'll come with you.
There's only one motorcycle.
That's our delivery vehicle.
So what's the problem?
I'll just ride with you.
Huh? No, just stay here.
Come on, this isn't new to you.
You used to ride with me before,
now it's my turn to ride with you.
Give and take, right?
Come on already!
If we're riding together, let's do it.
Get going already,
so the tortas will still be warm
when they're delivered.
Hurry up.
Come with us.
- Be careful.
- I'm definitely coming.
Come on, they're waiting for those.
- Hey Angelito, take care of her.
- Wait, wait.
Ouch.
There!
- Take care.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
- Okay.
Hold on tight!
Take care.
‪PINAGPALA
‪SPECIAL BAKESHOP
Tess, you can come out now!
Hey.
Are you sure they're gone?
Absolutely sure.
I knew it!
You left on purpose earlier, didn't you?
Pretending you had to prepare lunch.
What an excuse.
Well, of course. If I stayed by the oven,
how would they ever get some alone time?
I don't know with these kids.
They even have to keep
their relationship hidden from the public.
Anyway, let me change the subject.
Is it true we have an order of 100 today?
No, Tess. It's only around 30.
I was just teasing the kids.
The order of 100 is tomorrow.
I just wanted to see them
work under pressure.
So how many
are we really delivering today?
Ten of those, and we still have
fifteen torta cakes to bake.
There are five more in the oven.
What are we waiting for?
Come on, let's get to work!
- Let's go.
- Hey, where's Angel?
How many chances have you been given,
yet the result is always the same?
How many times are you going
to let the force down?
Huh?
You keep talking about
letting people down.
Like you've never made mistakes?
You caught them anyway.
Besides, you did it first.
And when did I do that?
When you ghosted me.
You're still stuck on that, man?
I thought you'd moved on.
Didn't you say you already found yourself?
You're not the one she loves.
You're not the one she wants, okay?
Then who?
And she wants you?
Do you want me to put you to sleep again?
Thank you!
You even have a tagline!
Wasn't I great?
See? I look like a legitimate
member of your bakery staff now.
Bechay taught me that.
- Very good.
- Really good!
Thank you for this!
My fiancée's favorite
is your special torta.
I'm meeting her family later.
Can I come with you?
What do you mean come with us?
Are you a relative?
You don't even know
the people who'll be there.
I know, but…
I just want to know
how meeting the family works.
No.
Sir, you're all set.
Just give this to your fiancée and
please ignore everything
this one just said.
All right, thank you, Sir!
You know,
you really love ambushing
random strangers.
Why? I'm just curious.
What's wrong with that?
Besides, isn't that how we first met?
When I ambushed your room.
Hey, let me sleep.
I've already spoken to General Norberto.
And because of what you two did,
he's sending someone to work with you.
Yup.
Someone who's not addicted to
staying up late, but addicted to the gym.
Someone who can't be
put to sleep so easily.
Because he's tough as nails.
Who is it?
If you're really into burgers,
which tastes better?
Wrong!
Neither is wrong!
Because they're both delicious!
Oh.
Mom just sent a text.
She said the orders are already done.
She and Betchay finished them.
The 100 orders?
No.
There were only 30!
Bechay just made a mistake
writing it on the calendar,
the 100 orders are actually for tomorrow.
Oh… I thought they finished all 100.
So, should we head back to the bakery?
Huh?
Oh.
Wait, wait. I think
I just had a better idea.
Why don't we stay here for a while?
Show me around your town.
Come on, let's spend some time together.
You know, let's spend
time with each other.
You know?
That's not a good idea.
Let's go back to the shop.
Why not?
Just look at how beautiful the weather is.
Why don't we take a walk?
Relax and reflect?
Because I'm starting to feel things
that I shouldn't be feeling.
What are these feelings
you shouldn't be feeling?
Huh?
Can you read my mind?
Of course not!
What am I, a mind reader?
It's just that I've noticed you've been
holding your chest for a while now.
So what exactly are you feeling?
Nothing. None of your business.
You're in love with me already,
aren't you?
Come on, admit it.
No way! You're so full of yourself!
Come on, let's go home.
Get on. If you don't,
I'm leaving you behind.
All right, all right. I'm getting on.
- Come on.
- There you go again.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
I got this.
Okay.
Hey.
What happened?
Is it broken?
I think the battery died.
So that means we can't use it anymore.
Looks like it.
To help us with
high-stakes investigations.
And because of your impressive
professional background,
the state is offering to commute
the remainder of your sentence.
In exchange for what?
If I cooperate with you,
can you guarantee that
the Moraviano will be brought down?
In that case,
if this is the only way
I can get justice for Jepoy,
count me in.
And he has a background
in forensic accounting.
So we can use his expertise
to map out their financial network.
Oh! Just like the Al Capone case!
Where the mafia boss was caught,
not because of the people he killed,
but because of tax evasion!
Exactly!
It always leaves a trail behind.
You think you're the only one? Me too.
Me too! I love money as well.
Cocoy, aside from your work at the agency,
your job here is also
to keep an eye on Mikoy and Chiara.
They seem to have a strange condition
that makes them want to
run away all the time.
What time is she leaving?
She didn't say.
Mi amore, behave.
She shouldn't feel
that you don't like her.
But look at how she gives orders,
it's like she has no plans
of ever leaving.
Bianca!
Can I ask you something?
Hold on a second.
Bianca.
Boss, I heard she's staying here?
Maybe I can stay here too,
so I can get more exposure.
But the house is already
pretty close to here.
Are you okay with walking?
It's only about, 20 to 30 minutes away.
That's close?
Yes, it's not that far.
Just think of it as exercise.
Is that okay?
You know, haven't you noticed?
Maybe this is the universe's way
of giving us some alone time.
Just the two of us.
Taking a walk together.
Right? Can you imagine it?
Fine.
I agree.
If you tell me the latest update
about my brother Mikoy.
You thought I forgot?
You said you still had
something to tell me.
Angelito.
I'll be honest with you.
I'm sorry, but…
I really don't know anything
about your brother.
I have no updates.
But let me explain, okay?
Okay, go ahead and explain.
The thing is, you know that
your brother's case is
pretty confidential.
So, you know,
even Dad and the people at the agency,
they don't tell me anything.
But I can assure you that
they're trying to save your brother,
and they won't let anything happen to him.
Yes.
Sweetheart,
what's his problem?
Why does he keep staring?
Who?
You know, that's how it is
when a bunch of strangers
start living in the same house.
They observe each other.
Checking each other out, you know?
Figuring out your weaknesses
and your strengths.
Oh, right.
What do you want me to call you?
I'm the Bisdak Heartthrob of Cebu.
As for Cocoy, I think he's the
Smart Buff of…
wait, Cocoy!
Where were you born?
Guimaras. Why?
Nothing, thanks.
Then Cocoy is the Smart Buff of Guimaras.
See? What about you?
The Pretty Femme Fatale of Prague?
There you go!
Sweetheart, that suits you perfectly!
And you? What do you want us to call you?
Just call me Asian Cutie.
That's a new one.
Asian Cutie.
Thanks for the reassurance.
I needed that right now.
You know, if what you're going through
is weighing heavily on you,
you can share it with me.
It's not that heavy.
Mom and Dad are sharing
the burden of worrying about my brother.
So, how are you two?
Well,
there hasn't been a single night
that we haven't prayed
for Mikoy and Chiara.
That they're safe and okay.
I can't help but wonder,
why did all of this have to happen?
But at the same time,
I understand.
I mean,
Mikoy loves Chiara.
That's what love is like, huh?
Oh, yes.
You can say that again.
Why?
Have you never been in love?
How did the topic end up on me?
Nothing, it's just that, you know…
I'm just curious about you,
I still want to know more about you.
So, were you mad at me when,
you know, I lied?
I already knew from the start that
you were just making up stories
about your brother,
that you didn't actually know anything.
That's just part of who you are,
being playful.
Being your Sofie self.
If you're not playful,
that's not you.
You're really full of charm!
You know what,
let's commemorate,
let's commemorate this day!
Let's take a photo!
Of course, I'm ready.
Here.
Wait, wait, wait.
There, this is perfect for posting.
Wait,
you've been taking pictures
for a while now,
what's that for?
I'm going to post this in my
"A Day in My Life" on Fishbook!
Right?
Wait, wait, wait.
I just remembered a saying.
That when a moment is perfect,
it supposedly deserves a perfect kiss
when the 3Ps are complete.
What are the 3Ps?
You don't know that?
- Listen carefully.
- Okay…
Just like now.
Um…
What about the perfect person?
Maybe, right?
- You're just distracting yourself, huh?
- Yes!
What else are we supposed
to do here, sweetheart?
We need to adapt to our new environment.
So I'll just wait around
for the next safe-mates to arrive here.
Whatever that is,
it ain't me.
What are you doing?
Why do you have a suitcase?
This? It's not mine.
It's Agent Alex's.
Really?
The alluring babysitter of G.A.G.O.
Although we don't need a babysitter,
because Cocoy is there to watch over us.
Didn't you tell him a while ago?
Hey, I'm still here in case you forgot.
Actually Ben, you're out because of
what happened earlier.
You're evicted already?!
Come on! I didn't even give you a moniker.
Agent Alex, here are the documents
that you asked me about earlier.
Work already?
You're such a workaholic.
So I hope you two behave
while I'm working.
I'm just replacing the bulbs.
Let me help you.
No, it's fine.
Uh, can you just turn it on?
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
Why don't we raid the camp
of La Morte Bianca?
Unfortunately, Chiara, here you'll
experience waiting and more hiding.
We need to wait to
align with the law enforcement agency
before we make a move.
Otherwise, there might be a misencounter
with another police department,
or even the military.