Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
(Any activity I could do alone…)
(I snapped my fingers,
and there was no more of that, Lookpeach.)
(Because anything you could do alone…)
(we could do it together.)
(Or with even more people.)
And the giant bear and the panda
lived happily ever after.
(This is more than a dream come true.)
I just got up early to take a bath.
We’ve been glued to each other
for almost four months.
A little time apart won’t kill us.
You’re wrong.
It’s three months and 22 days.
-You’re still counting?
-Seven hours…
and six minutes.
P’Kian.
9,687,960 seconds have passed.
Not a single one went by…
without you in my heart.
Lookpeach.
That’s how much I love you.
A new tie?
What’s this?
My heartbeat spelling out your name.
Lookpeach. Lookpeach.
Why are you wearing a suit
and tie at home?
Honestly, I like you better without a tie.
What are you doing?
Just take it off.
I just want to give you what you like.
I’ll have my men throw out
every tie I own.
Just don’t.
What are you going to wear
when you go back to work?
How about we cancel
the six-month vacation…
and make it a lifetime honeymoon instead?
I don’t want to spend a single day
away from my Lookpeach.
We can’t.
If we quit our jobs,
how are we supposed to make a living?
Actually,
if we only count my personal assets,
separate from ARSENI’s,
and live a little frugally…
say, under a billion per year…
What?
It might sound like a hard life,
but we should be able to get by
until we’re sixty.
Assuming that’s the average
human lifespan.
Totally doable, right?
And in the next life,
we’ll build a life together again.
Gosh, P’Kian.
Oh.
I meant a billion for me…
and another billion for you.
What do you think?
Could you live with that?
We just go to work
then come home
to each other every evening.
It’s not like we’ll be apart forever.
But if we’re already together,
why be apart at all?
Let the single people…
live their lonely little lives.
Rise and shine, stubborn one.
Did you reject all the pillows
just to use my chest as one?
What’s on the menu today, Chef?
Fried egg and rice,
served with a direct hit to your heart.
What are you all doing up so early?
You cooked?
What’s the occasion?
3.33?
What’s that supposed to mean?
It’s our wedding anniversary.
3 months and 33 days.
Wouldn’t that just be
four months and three days?
How is that an anniversary?
Everything counts.
It’s a nice number.
You keep track of every little thing.
Careful, they might just become ordinary.
The kids are here.
So you’re all taking Dad’s side now?
Don’t ever say “ordinary” again.
It hurts, baby.
Aran, say that again.
You want me to help promote a restaurant?
(The Italian restaurant Mr. Thee gave me.)
(Tawan came up
with the idea of renovating it.)
(It’s almost finished.
So we want to start promoting it.)
Hmm.
Is it going well?
(It is.)
(While we were closed,)
(our regulars kept asking
when we’d reopen.)
I meant you and Tawan.
How are things between you two?
He’s like a different person now.
(I can hear the smile in your voice.)
I have Mr. Thee to thank
for giving me the restaurant.
At least I have something
to keep me busy while I’m on hiatus.
So?
What do you say, Peach?
Will you do the shoot for me?
(Think hard.)
(I expect a good answer.)
Actually,
Mr. Thee and I agreed to
take a six-month vacation
after we got married.
Whoa! Six months?
(Yeah.)
He wants to take me
on a honeymoon trip around the world.
We’ve already been
to more than 20 countries.
What?
20 countries?
(Hold on, Peach.)
(Haven’t you only been married for,
like, four months?)
Four months and three days.
Right.
It’s all good then.
I understand.
(I’m really sorry.)
Maybe next time, Aran.
I don’t want to break the promise
I made to Mr. Thee.
(No worries.)
Once the restaurant’s finished,
let’s have a meal together.
I’ll send you the contact info
for a photographer I know.
Thank you.
What are you doing?!
P’Kian, what would you say if…
I wanted to go back to work?
Work?
P’Kian.
How many times must I repeat myself
before you understand?
As long as you’re under ARSENI’s roof,
you’ll never know hardship.
So stop thinking about going back to work.
A lone wolf finally got a taste of honey,
and it’s only been six months.
A whole six months.
It’s only six full moons.
Is that really too long for you?
Long enough for me to almost forget
how to hold a camera.
Perfect.
Then you don’t miss it that much.
P’Kian.
It just…
breaks my heart
to be apart from you, Lookpeach.
I want to get back to shooting photos.
Shoot my photos.
You’ve got the handsome and perfect model
right in front of you.
Why photograph anyone else?
It’s not the same.
How is it different?
If I wait until the six months are up,
all my connections will be gone.
Then we’ll make new ones.
How?
I’ll invite the whole industry
to travel the world with us.
Turn it into a networking trip.
The whole world will be your studio.
But we’ve already been
to more than 20 countries.
Who said our next destination
has to be a country?
Huh?
It’s our honeymoon, after all.
Where do you think we should go next?
Don’t tell me…
Tickets to the Moon.
P’Kian!
It’ll just be absolute chaos.
Ow!
Take it seriously, P’Kian.
You’re holding back.
How will I handle a real opponent
if you keep going easy on me?
I told you,
under my protection,
you’ll always be safe.
What are you,
the amnesiac heroine in a soap opera?
Ow!
I know you can protect me,
but I want to be able to protect
myself too.
Now take it seriously.
Maybe I love you too much.
I treasure you more than anything.
I just can’t bring myself
to throw you to the mat.
Whatever.
If you won’t take this seriously,
I’ll find a new sparring partner.
You can’t.
Why not?
I’d be jealous.
Jealous of what?
It’s just a sparring partner.
How could I let someone else
hold you like this?
Just seeing people look at you
makes me want to gouge their eyes out.
Imagine them holding you like I am.
They wouldn’t live to tell the tale.
But if you’re not taking this seriously,
I’ll really find a new sparring partner.
I’m sorry.
One, two, three.
Did I hurt you?
I’m sorry.
Was I too rough?
I lost.
But my heart nearly shattered.
Nailed it.
Got a great teacher.
Not a teacher.
More like a husband.
What? What’s with that look?
I’m really your husband,
reserving you for eternity.
This man was born just to love you.
Whoa, whoa~
Sneaking up behind me like that,
aren’t you afraid it’ll go off?
If you shoot me,
I’ll die without a single regret.
But I will go to prison for murder.
More importantly,
I can’t live without you.
Don’t say that.
Because death is the only thing
I can’t outrun.
But don’t worry, Lookpeach.
If I leave this world first,
I’ll wait for you somewhere
in the Milky Way.
There are millions of planets
How will we ever find each other?
We will.
But before that…
there’s something I need to tell you.
Don’t lose yourself
just to make me happy.
Hey.
You want to go back to work,
don’t you, Lookpeach?
Why did you ask me that, P’Kian?
I’ll send you the contact info
for a photographer I know.
KEY VISUAL SHOOT INQUIRY
MAGAZINE COVER SHOOT
MY APOLOGIES. I’M NOT TAKING PROJECTS
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
A falling leaf hasn’t even touched
the ground yet,
and we’re already about to be apart.
P’Kian, we agreed on six months.
Let’s stick to our promise.
But I’m the one…
breaking my promise.
I might be pretty busy with work,
but I promise I’ll take good care of you.
Whatever you want to do,
wherever you want to go, just tell me.
I’ll make it happen.
If you like working,
I won’t get in your way.
I’ll let you live your life.
How long will this honeymoon phase last?
For as long as I breathe.
I never forget the promises I make to you.
And I’ll keep them.
Every single one of them.
You don’t have to do that much for me.
Actually…
I’ve been thinking about it for a while.
Now that Aran’s offered you a job,
I think it’s time I did something.
Thank you.
It’s because…
I’ve finally got a grip, Lookpeach.
Say goodbye to the over-the-top mafia boss
you used to know.
So, when does Aran need you?
If you don’t mind,
could you give me just a few—
He wants me to start immediately.
The day after tomorrow, if possible.
(Seriously, Peach?)
He said he wanted to keep the promise
he made to me.
He knows how much I like to work,
so he’s letting me go back.
(Ah!)
He also said I’m his heart.
He doesn’t want me
to lose myself for his sake.
How sweet is that?
Why don’t you just ask Mr. Peach
for a little more time, sir?
Tell him you’re not ready.
A man keeps his word.
Once he gives it, he stands by it.
Stand tall and face the consequences.
But if you’re really not okay with this—
I knew this day would come.
I just never imagined it’d hurt…
hurt me this deeply.
What’s wrong?
What’s that look?
Nothing.
I’m perfectly fine.
Totally.
Should we turn off the light?
Mm.
Wait.
Can I stock up on hugs in advance?
You’re going back to work
the day after tomorrow, right?
Actually, I just got off the phone
with Aran.
I have to check out the location tomorrow.
Huh?
Tomorrow?
Sweet dreams.
I love you, P’Kian.
I… I love you too.
P’Kian, when are you going back to work?
The day my heart is strong enough.
Can you not go, pwease?
Is it too late to change your mind?
Don’t be such a baby.
Or do you want to come to work
with me today?
It’s okay.
Let’s leave a little room
in our hearts to miss each other.
Then let go.
Wear my perfume today,
so it’ll feel like I’m always with you.
Just pray my heart doesn’t shatter
before you make it home.
Mongkol,
tell me the good things
about long-distance relationships.
(The good thing about being apart)
(is that it makes you
miss each other in full force.)
(It makes your reunion
feel even more special.)
(You can tell me how long
you’ll be apart from your partner,)
(I’ll give you more tailored advice.)
Maybe… eight hours.
(Eight hours would not normally be
considered a long-distance relationship.)
Don’t worry.
I’ll take good care of our children
while you’re away.
We’ll be half a world apart,
but I hope our hearts stay close.
I’m only going to Bang Na.
That’s hardly half a world away.
You two, take good care of Dad.
Of course.
Mork and I
will take good care of Dad for you.
Don’t worry, Mr. Peach.
Leave everything here to me.
Mr. Mok. What a pleasant surprise.
Just so you know,
ARSENI has a strict no-rehire policy.
Mr. Thee…
How did that mad dog Rome
ever let his prey slip away?
Still got him in my jaws.
What kind of fool would let him slip away?
-Uncle Rome.
Mr. Thee, the team told me you’d…
Ahem.
I only asked you for one thing,
and you still can’t do it?
Thee, the team told me—
Ahem!
My dear friend Mok,
fix the way you address me,
or I’ll have Rome…
deal with you for every word
you get wrong.
Mr. Thee.
That’s one.
Dude.
Let’s go with ‘dude,’ sir.
Keep going,
bud.
The ARSENI team told me
you, my dude, cut your vacation short
and you’re coming back early.
That’s right, buddy.
But…
ARSENI Hong Kong
still hasn’t found you a new assistant.
So I volunteered to help
cover that for you,
buddy,
until then.
How self-centered.
Always get everyone dancing to your tune.
Did I ever so much as utter a word
asking you to come back?
Damn it, Kian.
Please, don’t fight.
Let’s do this.
I’ll look after you, dude,
until we find you a new assistant, sir.
As for you, Mr. Rome,
we’ll stay here with them.
It’s settled.
Hey.
You really don’t want to get paid?
It’s fine, Aran.
I haven’t touched a camera in months.
This is good practice for me.
It’s Mr. Peachayarat Lee after all.
He only works to socialize, huh?
So how are you?
How’s married life?
Good.
Actually, I think…
it’s really good.
I think
it’s filling something
I was missing in my life.
I don’t need anything else now.
I wake up next to him.
I go to bed beside him.
We eat every meal together.
You’ve changed a lot.
I haven’t changed.
I’m just
experiencing something I never had before.
Yeah, yeah.
Why are you asking?
Thinking about getting married?
Oh, come on.
I’ve never even thought about it.
Still not sure?
I don’t know.
Maybe I’m still young.
I haven’t really thought that far ahead.
Are you calling me old?
I didn’t. You did.
Come on, Aran.
I’m not shooting for you anymore.
Easy, easy.
That looks good.
Nice try changing the subject.
Need anything else, Mr. Peach?
Thanks, Tawan.
If you need anything, let me know.
Uh…
Move it a little to the left.
Thanks.
Why are you smiling?
-What?
-Why are you smiling?
No reason.
I’m just proud.
He’s my trainee.
So he’s been promoted
from roommate to trainee, huh?
Peach!
Just keep shooting.
Tawan’s proven himself
time and time again.
When are you finally going to give in?
My heart’s already softened.
It’s practically melted.
But I don’t know.
Things are so good right now.
So good I don’t even
want to move forward or backward.
You got fired
with ten years’ worth of severance.
If I were you, I’d leave everything behind
and travel the world.
That’s an interesting suggestion.
Leave everything behind, huh?
Everything except me.
If you’re the exception,
then it’s not really everything.
Make me your exception.
Mr. Rome.
Because you’re the exception
to every rule.
What are you doing?
I’m sorry for upsetting you,
but I can’t leave Mr. Thee.
At least not for now.
You really think…
that’s enough to make me cave?
Thank you.
For the past two months,
I haven’t fallen in love with you
over and over again…
because I never fell out of love with you
in the first place.
Très bien.
P’Kian, did you really have to do all this?
I’m celebrating
my 99,999th beautiful minute with you.
With every passing minute,
my love for you only grows.
P’Kian.
What?
There are so many people here.
Anyway…
our private rooftop is ready
for our 100,000-minute celebration.
Dad.
My teacher said I have a talent for art.
Dad, you look sad.
You’re missing Peach, aren’t you?
If you miss him, why don’t you call him?
Hello?
Oh, Lookpeach.
It’s not like I called
because I missed you or anything.
I’ve finally gotten a grip.
If you didn’t miss me, then what is it?
Marn had art class today.
She drew this really beautiful picture.
Take a look.
That blue-and-green bear is pretty cute.
Right?
So you called just to show me the bear?
You’re sure you don’t miss me?
Mm.
That’s all.
Okay.
That’s all, then.
I’ll get back to work.
I miss you, P’Kian.
Wow, your photography’s amazing.
What about you?
When are you going to model for me again?
I broke my contract with ARSENI.
I’m probably blacklisted by now.
Who would dare blacklist
the company owner’s partner’s little bro?
Wow.
What a flex.
I’m kidding.
All right.
If you’re happy with the photos,
I’ll start editing them
and upload the files later.
Sounds good.
Let’s do that, yeah?
Okay.
Oh, hey.
Why don’t you stay for dinner?
It’s on the house.
I don’t think I can today.
Someone’s waiting for me at home.
Here.
Thank you both so much.
LOVETHEE 1
BANGKOK
Whoa!
Let me make it up to you.
Dinner’s on me.
We can invite Mr. Thee and Lookplub too.
Call it an after-wedding dinner.
You really don’t have to, Aran.
Yes, I do.
We missed your wedding.
The least I can do is treat you to a meal.
Honestly, it’s okay.
We kept the wedding small.
Just family.
Hold on.
What’s that supposed to mean?
Am I an outsider?
You were the one who said
I’m like your little brother.
Then I’m bringing my whole family
to your restaurant, okay?
I should get going. See you later.
Okay. Bye.
See you, Tawan.
Have a good night, Mr. Peach.
You okay?
Seeing how kind Mr. Peach is to you
just makes me feel even worse.
I was such an idiot back then.
Don’t think like that.
No one thinks so.
Peach isn’t angry with you anymore.
Good boy.
My Lookpeach.
Look at you with that big, fat smile.
I missed you so much,
my heart almost burst out of my chest.
Lookplub.
Why didn’t you tell me
you were coming home?
I wanted to surprise you.
Instead, I ended up
as mosquito food out here.
Well, I’m home now.
Everyone’s here tonight.
It feels warm.
How was the trip with Mr. Mok, Rome?
It was great.
But it ended too soon.
We got called back.
Once Thee finds a new assistant,
you guys can get back to your vacation.
Vacation’s over.
Over?
The schedule for the grand meeting
has been announced.
Europe’s nice.
I like the weather there.
Asia’s boring.
I’ve lived here my whole life.
What about you, Mok?
Just asking though.
It’s not like we actually get to choose.
If Mr. Thee gets to choose his own path,
then you can—
No.
Honestly,
I think Kian’s job
is even more boring than Dad’s.
Why do you look like you don’t believe me?
The three of us grew up together.
But…
When Mr. Thee was transferred to Thailand,
you seemed so against
the decentralization strategy.
Why do you seem okay with it now?
I don’t get it.
Because it’s Kian.
Yes?
I was upset with Dad then
because he split us up.
That’s all.
Huh?
People always say
I’m decisive, just like Dad.
Kian’s gentle, just like Mom.
What about you?
Do you think so?
So Mr. Rome’s being transferred
to the other side of the world?
It all depends on Dad.
There’s no way to know.
I’m going back to work tomorrow.
I’m interviewing a new assistant.
Dad found you a new candidate?
The sooner I find a new assistant,
the longer Rome and Mok
can enjoy their lives
before the grand meeting.
Mr. Rome would be so happy
to know how much
his big brother loves him.
Don’t you ever tell him.
He’ll never let me live it down.
They should be here any minute, sir.
Good morning.
I’m Mira.
I’m ready to be
your new assistant, Mr. Theerakit.
I owe you an apology, Mr. Thee.
No one told me
your new assistant was a woman.
I’m a woman.
Is that a problem, sir?
Here’s the thing.
Being his assistant means
helping with ARSENI’s business…
and looking after his safety.
I hope you understand
what I’m saying, Ms. Mira.
Never mind.
I don’t care whether
my assistant’s a man or a woman.
Besides,
I told you already, Mok.
This is my turf.
I’ll be safe.
Even so…
I brought some food—Ow!
Ow!
Don’t!
She’s my partner’s little sister!
My apologies.
It was pure instinct.
I’m sorry, ma’am.
Feeling a little more at ease now, buddy?
You’re absolutely pathetic.
That’s rich coming from you.
You were getting eaten alive
by mosquitoes the other night.
Lookpeach.
Have you made up your mind
about the new assistant?
Can’t you at least
give me some time to decide?
I want Mok back.
Mr. Rome.
We… should get going.
Please excuse us.
If you two want more time together,
stop pretending
to sleep in separate places.
Don’t sneak into my house
in the middle of the night like a thief.
At this point, it’s public knowledge.
805.
Good thing he brought it up.
You can just move in with me tonight.
I’ll help.
708, lead the way.
(The big boss is coming to Thailand
to attend the meeting in person.)
(I don’t know what’s going to happen,)
(but this meeting is different.)
(I’m sure everything will work out.)
(No matter what happens,)
(know that
you’ll always have me, Mr. Rome.)
Mr. Rome.
What’s going on?
Where’s Mr. Rome being transferred to?
He’s not being transferred.
Rome’s going to be ARSENI’s next leader,
taking over from Dad.
Okay.
Mok called back.
They’re together,
but Rome isn’t ready to see anyone yet.
Knowing they’re safe is enough.
Don’t overthink it.
It’s been a long day.
Come here.
Let me give you a hug.
I feel like I’ve failed.
Everything I’ve done all this time…
none of it worked.
It’s selfishness.
I’m forcing Rome to carry a burden
that should’ve been mine.
P’Kian.
I’m a terrible big brother,
aren’t I, Lookpeach?
Don’t blame yourself.
I’m sure Dad and Mr. Rome
don’t see it that way.
Being ARSENI’s leader isn’t easy.
It’s a thousand times harder than
being sent to run a branch.
But I believe that
if Mr. Rome doesn’t want it,
Dad won’t force him…
and will give him
the same freedom he gave you.
Dad’s ARSENI
is like a tiger raised to be a warrior.
Too fierce.
Too dangerous
to be released back into the wild.
So someone has to keep that tiger in check.
It’s either Mr. Rome…
or you, right, P’Kian?
I can face anything
as long as you’re by my side.
I’ll do whatever it takes not to lose you.
I know that.
Better than anyone.
P’Kian.
I…
I’ve finally gotten a grip, Lookpeach.
Let’s save that
for when it really matters.
♪ L'amour est un oiseau rebelle ♪
♪ Que nul ne peut apprivoiser ♪
Phew!
Well? How was that?
Did I sing nicely?
Want me to give it a try?
Good idea.
♪ L'amour est un oiseau rebelle ♪
♪ Que nul ne peut apprivoiser ♪
Let’s try that again.
♪ L'amour… ♪
♪ Laaa… ♪
♪ L'amour est… ♪
♪ L'amour est un oiseau rebelle ♪
♪ Que nul ne peut apprivoiser ♪
Can you ask Dad for me, Kian?
I want to stay here with you and Mok.
Hi. Want to come in with me?
Hey!
I did something for Mr. Thee.
You prepared a surprise for me?
All my time belongs to you.
We’re both going to work.
And we’ll see each other this evening.
Then let me get a refill first.
Lookpeach, what would you say
if Dad’s position ended up being mine?