"Blue Lips"
(Episode 1)
Brother Mo.
The usual?
The usual.
Thanks.
Something on your mind?
Nothing's on my mind.
Just bored.
Came to listen to some music.
Are young people's
ears that bad these days?
The new singer I hired...
What do you think?
Handsome, right?
Don't mind how loud his singing usually is.
So many of these customers
come here just for him.
It's him.
Xiao Teng.
Late again today?
Overslept.
You can't run a business like this,
slacking off all the time.
You can't go on living like this.
Just getting by.
Taking it one day at a time.
You...
Defend! Defend!
Don't rush, don't rush.
Give me a second.
Just a moment, almost done.
Hold on a second.
Almost there, almost there.
Almost done.
Just let me finish this round.
What do you need?
A box of Vandacon.
Five-pack or ten-pack?
Five-pack.
Four hundred and fifty.
Hey, kid.
This is the fourth time
you've bought Vandacon from me this month.
If you're really having trouble,
I suggest you go see a doctor.
Taking this too often
has major side effects.
It'll ruin your health.
Stop lecturing me.
You're young now.
But when you get older,
and reach my age, you'll regret it.
Ending up like you
is definitely something to regret.
You've got a sharp tongue.
What's his name?
Wu Shixian.
"Why should the sad zither have
fifty strings [sounds like Wu Shixian]"
"Each string, each strain evokes but
vanished springs." [A Tang dynasty poem]
Interesting.
"Let me fall into the
bottomless abyss."
Such depressing lyrics.
Does he usually
sing songs like this?
Drinking and flirting to this kind of music
doesn't seem quite right, does it?
Well, they're young.
Look around the bar.
Besides you,
who else is actually here for the music?
They just want some background noise.
Can I request a song?
For him?
Three hundred.
I'll support your business.
I'll request 'Pink Memories'.
Sure.
Wu Shixian.
Someone requested a song.
Who requested it?
It was requested by that Mr. Teng.
Hey, kid.
This is the fourth time
you've bought Vandacon from me this month.
When you get older,
and reach my age, you'll regret it.
It's him.
You want to hear a song?
Just you wait.
Here we go.
This kid is pretty interesting.
Turning a sweet song into a sad one
is a real talent.
Does he perform here every day?
Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays.
Why?
Are you going to become a regular fan?
With a character like him,
I'd love to hear him sing every day.
Quite interesting.
Brother Mo.
You're back.
A'Heng,
get me a whiskey.
Waiter,
I'd like to request a song.
I want to request 'Love Sale'.
Alright.
Xiao Wu,
do you have a grudge
against that older guy?
He seems to be targeting you.
Who knows?
He's a psycho.
But honestly,
the guy might be a bit tacky,
but he's pretty amusing.
Xiao Wu,
Sister Liu asked if you're free tonight.
She wants to treat you
to a late-night snack.
Just food?
Or is there
something else to it?
If you ask me,
Sister Liu isn't even that old.
If I were with her,
I'd save myself twenty years of hard work.
Get out of here.
Look at Xiao Wu's league.
He's popular with both guys and girls.
Well,
then I'll go turn her down.
Xiao Wu,
it's a full house tonight.
Give it your best.
You got it.
Sister Liu didn't come today?
Hey,
I'm just a singer.
With people who just hang around bars,
there's no need to get upset.
Peace brings prosperity, right?
I'm going to tune my guitar.
Wu Shixian,
someone requested a song for you.
Are you messing with me on purpose?
No, I'm not.
How many times has it been?
What kind of songs are you requesting?
What do you want?
I paid for the request.
You're the singer.
It's not like I'm asking
you to sing for free.
You...
Just tell me which song you don't know.
I only requested popular songs.
I don't know any of them.
But those songs of yours...
But what?
I paid money.
Of course I'll request songs I like.
Should I request what you like instead?
Am I right or am I right?
Like hell you are.
What?
In front of everyone,
you're going to assault a customer?
And a paying customer at that?
Do you want to get fired?
Xiao Wu,
are you okay?
"Waiting for a millenium"
What's wrong with him today?
I don't know.
If you don't know how to smoke, don't.
You worry too much, old man.
It's your body.
Health is what matters most.
Bullshit.
I'm in perfect shape.
In perfect shape, yet you buy Vandacon?
If you don't want to host at Blue Moon,
why don't you consider another job?
Mind your own business.
Fine.
What are you doing?
Off work, Xiao Wu?
See ya.
Hey, Mom.
Did the fruit I sent you arrive?
Yes, I got it.
Eat it while it's fresh.
Let me tell you,
and don't think I'm nagging.
Stop staying up so late.
Don't always smoke, drink, and play games.
The holidays are coming up.
You're coming home this year, right?
We'll see.
Seriously,
what exactly are you doing in Jinzhou?
You haven't come home in years.
You're almost thirty years old.
You're not a kid anymore.
Can't you just come back to Fengzhou
and find a decent job?
It would be so nice if you found a partner.
Look at your classmates.
Maybe they aren't wildly successful,
but at least they've settled down.
But look at you.
Never at home,
Hello?
And you don't even have a girlfriend.
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Mom?
Hello? My signal is bad.
Hello?
I'm hanging up.
Honestly, this kid...
Driving so fast!
Are you crazy?