Stop apologizing.
So you two become loving.
I remember you two were always bickering.
Why do you fall for a guy like me?
I just like you.
I don’t need a reason for it.
He kissed me.
I’m still thinking about what happened.
If you’re still thinking about it,
doesn’t it mean that you…
I’m not sure.
Did they tell you where they were going?
But if it bothers you, you should talk to them.
Do you want to have a meal with me?
Sure.
Do you want to come to my room
to play games?
(At one point in our life
when dreams are shining all over the sky.)
(We can’t even choose
which dream we should reach for.)
(Sometimes, you find your dream
in a boring class in school.)
from advice from your best friend.)
(When we have a dream,
we know that it’s not easy to achieve it.)
♪ When the sky clears after the storm ♪
♪ We start our journey together and move on ♪
(Many people give up along the way.)
♪ Every story we go through
turns into a memory ♪
(Many people achieve their dream.)
♪ That reminds us
how far we have come along ♪
(Many people achieve their dream.)
♪ That reminds us
how far we have come along ♪
(For someone,)
(They can only dream of it.)
Can’t you let me sleep a bit more?
Is he home?
Honey.
Will I get to eat breakfast today?
Stop teasing me.
Get your dad away from me.
Where do you want me to go?
Can’t you take the laundry out?
Why? Are you feeling shy
because of our son?
Go take the laundry out.
I miss you.
Why would you miss me?
Here is your rice.
Why won’t Dad have breakfast with me?
He already ate. You can go ahead and eat
Bummer
You woke up this late.
Are you expecting your dad and me
to wait for you?
Fine.
Mom.
Yes?
You called me,
and why didn’t you say anything?
When Dad tried to win your heart,
what did he do?
So my son wants to be in a relationship,
don’t you?
No, I’m just asking.
I don’t want to know anymore.
Your dad often patted me on my butt.
Huh? What do you mean?
Have you never heard this?
When you like someone,
you want to tease them
Can you stop joking?
You seem to be serious about it.
I guess you must want to be in a relationship.
No need to be shy.
You can tell me anything.
Ask me.
Why are you talking about me now?
Your dad did what other guys do
when they hit on a girl.
He took me out on a date
and went to see a movie.
He bought me my favorite food.
But friends also do that, don’t they
That’s nothing special about it.
Mister Romeo.
It hurts.
Yes, you can go to see a movie
or eat out with your friend.
But it’s different
when we go with someone we like.
How?
Of course, it’s different.
Otherwise, we wouldn’t call them
our special someone.
What do you mean
when you said it’s special?
I’ve never seen you have so many questions
when you ask me about your homework.
Mom.
You, little rascal.
I can’t explain the feelings to you.
You have to experience them yourself.
But I believe when that day comes,
you will know it.
Hey.
Why did you smack my butt?
You need to notice
if that person pats on your butt.
Aren’t you going to eat your breakfast?
No. I’m going back to bed.
Did he finish his breakfast?
No.
Honey, I think he’s dating someone.
Really?
Ko Song.
I need to give the food to my mom first.
Alright.
If I have feelings for him,
I hope an orange falls from the tree.
Come on. Fall down.
This is it.
Fall down.
It’s coming.
Come on.
Nothing.
It’s good that it doesn’t fall down.
Orange.
Yeah.
Ouch.
Ko Song.
I thought you would catch it.
I got a few for you.
Well done, Ko Song.
What’s going on?
What?
Why did you call me?
Nothing.
I just want to call you.
Really?
Yes.
Why? Can’t I call you?
It’s just strange.
How?
It’s odd.
Are you suspecting me?
How dare you?
Okay.
Ko Song.
Yeah.
I want to eat oranges again tomorrow.
I’ll bring them.
I want to eat dough sticks at the market, too.
I’ll go with you.
After that, I have to buy plants for my mom.
I’ll help you.
I also want to eat ice cream
at the shop near August’s house.
Sure.
We can ride our bike there.
I also want…
Orange.
I’ll do everything you ask me to do.
Okay?
Fine.
I got it.
Thank you, Achi, for buying us ice cream.
You can order more if you want.
Don’t give him ideas like that.
Too late. I’m milking it.
August, wait for me.
Ko Song.
Yeah.
When did you start to eat lime ice cream?
I want to try something new.
I can’t eat oranges every day like you.
Ko Neung, you really like oranges.
What would you do if you don’t get oranges
from Ko Song’s house?
I can’t help it. They are delicious.
You’re going all out
when Achi said it’s on him.
I’m holding back.
If I weren’t, I’d order five more.
Do you want more?
Stop it, Achi.
I’m asking you.
Achi, I’m just being sarcastic.
You are so naïve, little boy.
Achi.
Does your chauffeur have to wait for you here?
Yes.
My mom told him to wait to take me home.
Is he the Terminator?
No, he’s very kind-hearted.
It’s like he always keeps an eye on you.
It would be hard for you to date.
Only fools choke on ice cream
No, I got brain freeze.
Since it’s school break.
Do you want to take a trip and
stay at my mom’s beach house in Hua Hin?
Do you want to go?
You can say no. It’s okay.
Of course, we want to go.
Achi, you are taken aback, right?
Look at his face.
Of course, we will go.
What is this?
Ko Song, you also play along with them?
How can you do this to me?
I’m hanging out with them for too long.
Then…
Let’s say cheers
Sure.
Come on.
One, two, three.
Yay!
We are going to Hua Hin tomorrow.
I know that.
That’s why we hurried back home to pack our bags.
It means that we won’t get to eat
dough sticks at the market
or buy plants for your mom.
We didn’t get to eat ice cream together.
We can do that after we get back.
The plants that we want to buy
will grow a little bigger.
What’s wrong?
A beach trip is more fun
than going to the market.
We will get to spend time together
when going to the market.
We will spend time together on the trip.
But it’s just the two of us
when going to the market.
I…
Follow me.
Huh?
Didn’t you say you want to spend time together?
I’m making up for it.
Do you want to do it or not?
If not, you can go home.
I’ll put my bike back at home.
Hurry back.
Ko, I want to eat oranges.
But you already ate them this morning.
Oh.
You are not only the big guy
in the neighborhood,
but you can also order the orange tree
to do what you want.
Yes, Boss Ko is the real deal.
Here.
My hands are busy. I’m holding the book.
One more.
- Feed me properly.
- Okay.
Is this a gate or a wall? Why is it so tall?
Ko Song, his house looks like a village.
Hold on, everyone.
Why?
Step closer.
I’m going to take a picture.
Right, take a picture. Come on.
Make a pose.
Ready? One, two, three.
You look good.
Wait here. I’ll be right back.
August.
Don’t you think that your shirt color
will hurt other people’s eyes?
I was going to warn you
when we were at home.
You are so lame.
Don’t you know this is Y2K style?
I thought you wanted to be
a motorbike taxi rider.
Are you afraid people won’t know
that you’re a basketball athlete?
Why don’t you carry a ball too
You look like a fake basketballer.
This is my style. Don’t look down on me.
You look like a motorbike taxi rider.
Where is your motorbike?
That’s enough. Stop bickering.
Ko Song, why did you stop them?
It’s getting fun.
Your outfit.
I think you should do this.
It’s okay. I can do it myself.
It’s okay.
This is it.
You look great.
Where is Achi?
How would I know? I’m standing with you.
Yes, Boss Ko
Damn.
Wicked.
It looks so cool.
Are you ready?
I’m ready since I was born.
Let’s go.
We arrived.
I want the ride to be a bit longer.
Uncle, can you take us on a ride?
He’s acting cool.
I saw you dancing to Ricky Martin’s song.
You are getting overexcited.
You are living in a beach town,
but you act like you never saw the sea.
Augar, why do you have to ruin the mood?
When will we get to ride on a Wolk again?
Idiot, it’s called Volkswagen.
It sounds the same.
Idiot.
Let’s put our bags inside.
Sure.
Come on.
Are you that happy?
I’m happy
because we came on this trip together.
Can you two stop flirting?
Let’s take the bags inside and go to the beach.
I want to kick your butt, August.
I’ll show you the bedroom.
Hua Hin, here I come.
Augar, you’ve got to become an athlete.
Of course.
Go, go. Augar, Go.
Don’t push me.
Augar wins.
Guys.
Achi’s chauffeur is over there.
Should I pretend to get cramps?
Good idea, Achi.
Please help us.
Achi is having cramps.
This way. Hurry up.
Don’t splash me.
Stop it.
No.
Uncle.
♪ Every time that we meet again ♪
♪ Something grows a little more each day ♪
♪ The closer we are,
the more I feel the love I’ve waited for ♪
♪ Might not be too far away at all ♪
♪ Even when winter fades I’ll still wait on ♪
♪ Till the final raindrop falls,
hope is never gone ♪
♪ As long as I have you holding my hand
as we walk on ♪
♪ I fear nothing if this season has you ♪
Aren’t you feeling hot?
No, it’s breezy here.
We should go inside.
You are wet. You may get sick.
Later.
Fine.
This reminds me of the first time
we went to the beach together.
It was dark then.
We only saw lights from the boats.
But right now, it’s bright,
and the view is wide-open.
Close your eyes.
Time flies so fast.
Soon it will be our last year in high school.
Time really flies.
I don’t like it.
Why?
I don’t know.
I have this sinking feeling.
So…
What are you going to do after graduation
I have never thought about that.
What about you?
I’d probably study in a med school.
Then I should attend the same school as you.
A med school?
Why?
Do you think I can’t attend a med school?
Aren’t you afraid?
If you are a med student,
you have to study with a dead body.
You have to stay in a hospital at night.
It’s dark and silent.
Then…
can I study as a patient?
At least, I would be under
the care of Dr. Kanin Siritara.
Nonsense.
Come on, it’s getting cold. Let’s go inside.
Why are you patting on my butt?
It’s covered with sand.
Don’t pat on my butt.
But it’s covered with sand.
Ko Neung. Ko Song.
We have a problem.
What is the problem?
The house is big.
But we have to take a shower outside.
Right.
Why does the bathroom
have to be broken now?
I’m cold.
Ko Song.
It will splash on my face.
It won’t.
Shampoo shouldn’t touch our face.
Water.
What?
It gets in my eyes.
It gets in your eyes?
I’ll help you. Wait a sec.
I’ll wash my hands first.
Hurry up. It gets in my eyes.
Stay still.
You look like Son Goku from Super Saiyan.
What does he look like?
What?
Is it better?
Yes.
Ouch.
Ko Song.
It got into my mouth.
Ko.
Give it to me.
Charge in!
It gets in my eyes.
Put your hair down.
Nasal irrigation.
Ko.
Damn, this is powder.
August.
Do you know how to grill meat
Of course.
My grilling skills are guaranteed.
I got an A for boy scout class.
His words sound scary.
I want to taste the food that August cooks.
I’m a better cook than him.
Really?
Then I’ll eat it a lot.
Yes, you need to eat a lot
because you are so small.
Small like this?
Small like this.
What are Ko Neung and Ko Song doing?
They probably complain
while taking a shower.
You two can’t tell them
that I broke the faucet.
Otherwise, I’ll hit you
Fine, brother.
I won’t tell them.
I’m back.
Is he smiling?
I’m as surprised as you.
When we rode the banana boat,
his face was expressionless.
I think he feels comfortable with us now.
I’ll let you guys cook.
Thank you.
What do we have for dinner?
Will we finish it all?
Uncle, please join us for dinner.
I need to get a plumber to fix the faucet.
You need to lift the handle
to turn on the faucet.
But you turn the handle so hard
that it’s broken, Augar.
I’ve got to go.
I…
Augar!
Uncle barely says anything,
but when he starts to talk, he talks a lot.
Ko Song, catch him.
I won’t let you get away, Augar.
Where are you going?
August, why are you helping them?
Take off his clothes.
When you grill meat,
don’t flip it too often.
Here is freshly cooked rice.
Hey.
Ko Song.
Who taught you to cut pork like that?
You’re clueless.
Cut it like this. Get it?
Try it.
Do you finish washing the vegetables?
Yes.
Let’s go.
Wash it again.
Augar, why did you rush me?
Don’t splash the water.
I think I would get to eat your finger too.
Be careful.
He must be hungry.
He’s eating without saying a word.
Why doesn’t Uncle join us for dinner?
He said he has to check the plumber’s work.
The plumber might be sloppy.
He will eat later.
We should save some food for him.
He’s doing a lot for us.
August.
Your friend has grown up
Now, he thinks about other people.
In the past, he ate everything
without thinking about anyone.
Boss Ko has grown up.
We need to celebrate.
Yay!
Are you having fun?
I’ll poke you.
Why can’t I become more mature?
You can, but I’m not used to it.
Ko Song.
Do you want to get smacked?
Do you want to try me?
Why did you take the photo
without telling me?
I want to have proof
that you became a better person.
Damn, you guys.
You gang up on me.
It’s good that you want to improve yourself.
It will help you find your goal.
I’m curious
what our lives will be like in the future.
I told you I wanted to be an expert on manga.
Now, I've grown up.
I have so many questions
What are they?
Do I really like it?
Won’t people think my dream is nonsense?
You don’t need to care
what they think about your dream.
It’s good that you respect your dream.
People see me as a smart student
who gets good grades.
When my parents ask me
what I want to do in life, I can’t answer them.
Will adult life be as stressful
as many adults say?
When we were young,
we wanted to be an adult.
But now, it’s scary to be an adult.
It’s hard to say.
Augar, you are the only one
who doesn’t have this problem.
You know what?
I’m not even sure
if I really want to be a basketball player.
Basketball is something
my dad has been teaching me.
It’s just something I’m growing up with.
To be honest,
I’m suck at studying.
If I don’t work hard on playing basketball,
I would have nothing I’m good at.
It’s normal to not know what you want to do.
But I already chose my path.
Don’t you think it’s scarier?
What?
The one who started this serious topic
is Achi again.
That’s right.
You again, Achi.
This is so you.
Let’s forget it and dig in.
Dig in.
An army marches on its stomach.
We are so unlucky.
We spin the bottle and end up on dish duty.
Luckily, it’s you.
If I did it with August,
we would be fighting
and end up breaking a dish.
I thought you wanted to do it with me.
Are you sulking?
Augar, my hair is now wet.
Sorry.
I think you really love basketball.
How did you know that?
We’ve known each other for two years.
I see that look in your eyes
when you play basketball.
What look?
You look determined and full of happiness.
Why do you know me so well?
Because I’ve been watching you.
You’ve been watching me?
Yes.
Since when?
I don’t remember.
Can you tell what I’m thinking right now?
Augar.
You’re getting too close.
So you can see what I’m feeling.
Augar, stop teasing me.
Okay, I’ll stop teasing you.
Why are you patting on my butt?
(Maybe what my mom said is true.)
(Why did I get so shy when he did that?)
(Am I…)
(…falling for him?)
(Didn’t you say you wanted us
to go back to being friends?
(Why are you sending me mixed signals?)
(If this gets stronger,)
(will I be able to hold it back?)
Guys.
Let’s write a postcard.
Sure.
When did you become a romantic guy?
What?
I haven’t said whom I will write it to.
You don’t need to say it, but I already knew
What?
Let’s pick a postcard.
You can write to whoever you want.
August, what are you writing?
Augar, it has to be a secret.
Let’s go back to the van.
Where did you go last night?
It’s so quiet that we can hear the wind
Yes.
Do you think…
the stars we see here look the same
as when we watch them at home?
Theoretically, they are barely different.
We almost can’t tell the difference.
Do you know the name of the stars?
I don’t know everything, Orange.
I don’t know their names.
But I know.
Do you see the star that is over there alone?
Yes.
That’s August.
Because it likes being alone.
Here.
These are the Augar constellation.
They stick together
and look like a basketball ball.
Where is Achi’s star?
Let’s say every star in the sky is his.
Because he’s rich.
He can own all of them.
Then there’s no star left for us.
There’s no star for me.
I’m not good enough to be a star.
There.
That one is yours, the biggest one.
But that’s the moon.
For me,
the moon is you, Ko Song.
When I turn off the light in my room,
a light slowly shines through my window.
I see you every night before I fall asleep.
When I have a problem,
you are always my light.
My life without you,
it is so dull.
I…
That’s how I really feel.
♪ “I love you” I never said ♪
♪ I kept them, thinking you felt the same ♪
♪ But you left without a word ♪
♪ Kept thinking, if I’d said them first ♪
♪ Things might've turned out better ♪
♪ Distance only makes me think it over ♪
♪ What should be said
if we again meet each other ♪
I mean it this time.
Are you crossing the line?
You crossed it first last night.
♪ Will say "I love you" ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
(Don’t look at me with those eyes.)
♪ No more watching from afar,
letting chances go ♪
(Don’t look at me with those eyes.)
♪ No more watching from afar,
letting chances go ♪
♪ Will say "I love you" so you know ♪
(Let me mess up your hair, little boy.)
♪ To make this worth the wait after all ♪
(I suddenly think of you.
I wish you were here.)
(Thank you for coming into my life
and bringing light to it.)
(You don’t need to be a star.)
(You can be my sun.)
♪ To make this worth the wait after all ♪
- So we are dating, right?
- Please join the group of the faculty
you want to study in.
- So Tle is also choosing
to attend a med school like Ko Song.
- I think so.
- Don’t you worry about being apart from him?
- Ko Song, after we graduate from school,
will you leave me?
- It’s okay.
- I promise that we will see each other.