"Blue Lips"
(Episode 2)
What are you doing?
You saw everything.
Why didn't you save me?
A'Heng.
Brother Mo.
Looking sharp today!
The usual whiskey?
Yeah.
Give me the same drink as him.
Are you all by yourself, handsome?
I'm not a young man anymore.
I'm an old man.
You're so funny.
You're clearly so young,
and so handsome.
This drink is so strong!
Why is a girl like you
drinking something so strong?
A'Heng.
Get her a Long Island Iced Tea.
It's on me.
Thank you, handsome.
You seem to be in a bad mood.
Did you just get dumped?
Then you're actually quite lucky.
If a breakup is the most
painful thing in your life.
A man with life experience...
is exactly my type.
Want to talk about it, handsome?
Maybe I can help.
Forget it.
Alright.
For this next song,
I'd like to dedicate
it to a friend of mine.
Coincidentally,
he's right here tonight.
He is...
that gentleman over there...
having a drink at the bar.
Okay.
As for him,
he suffers from chronic
erectile dysfunction,
and his marriage proposals always fail.
Today,
marks his tenth rejected confession.
Let's give him a round of applause,
to cheer him up,
shall we?
Yeah!
So he can regain...
his faith in love.
Let's also wish this...
Mr. Teng,
a smooth love life.
And let's also wish...
his adult toy store a booming business!
Yeah!
Alright!
Go for it!
I wish you all...
a great night,
and drink to your heart's content!
Bottoms up!
Cheers!
Brother Mo.
It's fine.
He probably...
won't be coming back here.
Better if he doesn't.
Boss,
give me a box of Vandacon.
The 5-pack or the 10-pack?
The 5-pack.
That'll be 450.
What's wrong? Is something up?
Boss,
this medicine...
does it really work?
Why don't you take one,
and wait for it to kick
in before you leave?
Xiao Teng,
you're famous around here now.
Why didn't you tell me
you had this problem?
You have so many pills over there,
haven't you tried them yourself?
As for him,
he suffers from chronic
erectile dysfunction.
Never mind.
I don't want it anymore.
I...
Brother Mo,
why did you...
come here?
Why...
can't I come?
No, I mean...
Well...
Did you think...
I'd go into hiding...
just because I was embarrassed?
No.
You're a bigger man than that.
I know.
I'm not that thin-skinned.
Otherwise, how could
I run that kind of store?
Where is...
the resident singer today?
Why is no one singing?
He's drinking with the customers.
Drinking?
I'll drink later.
I still have to sing.
That's not how it works.
How about this?
Finish this glass,
and I'll let you go.
I'll do it myself.
Drinking so fast...
You're drinking like a beast!
This is already the second round.
Looks like tonight is going to be rough.
I have things to do.
When are you going back to your store?
Why?
Do you want to buy more Vandacon?
None of your business.
Then what about last time,
when you spread rumors about me in public?
Are we just letting that go?
I already said it.
What are you going to do about it?
Maliciously defaming someone...
with false statements.
Do you know what that's called?
It's called slander.
You've already caused
me emotional distress.
And you think saying 'I already said it'...
settles it?
Then what do you want?
Why are you drinking so much today,
and still taking Vandacon?
None of your business.
You can't take Vandacon after drinking.
You'll blow up.
Hold on.
Take this.
What is this?
A special...
sober-up pill.
Is it poison?
You expect me to just take it?
It'll save your life.
Take it or leave it.
Xiao Wu,
the customers over
there want you to go over.
If you take this,
this month...
and next month,
I won't dedicate any
songs to embarrass you.
It's just a pill.
In broad daylight,
he can't get away if something happens.
You'd better keep your word.
What did you give me?
Let me tell you,
we're closed today.
Don't look for trouble.
It's written on the door.
Don't you know why I'm here today?
How should I know?
Shouldn't you be looking for some girls?
Why come here?
I didn't dedicate any songs to you today.
Who pissed you off?
Is it because of that sober-up pill?
Do you think I'm stupid?
My young friend, I was trying to help you.
You can't take Vandacon every day.
And besides,
you can't drink while taking Vandacon.
That Indian miracle drug I gave you...
Indian miracle drug
Drinking doesn't affect its efficacy.
It works incredibly well.
And it lasts a very long time.
How long?
Three days.
You mean...
I have to stay like this...
for three days?
Theoretically, yes.
You old bastard!
I'm going to kill you!
Is it really that strong?
Let me tell you,
the priority right now
is to solve the problem.
You should go find some girls,
not come to me.
You old bastard!
Where's the antidote?
It's not an aphrodisiac.
There is no antidote.
Just take care of it yourself.
Or find someone to help you out.
Where am I supposed to find a girl?
What's wrong?
Out of four girls,
you didn't like a single one?
You have such high standards.
I told you, I only drink with customers.
Why don't you go handle it in the restroom?
We're both men.
I don't need to teach you how, do I?
You think I've never
dealt with this before?
Tell you what.
I have some... hardcore videos here.
They're yours.
Take them home and handle it yourself.
Okay?
No way.
Why not?
Hurry up! I...
Right now, I...
I really need to pee!
I have to go to the bathroom!
Got it.
This is a case of...
youthful vigor...
mixed with alcohol.
It's a bit tricky.
No.
You have to help me solve this.
I already told you,
there's no other way.
How about...
we go to the ER?
There is no way I'm going to
the hospital for something like this.
Do you understand?
Then there's nothing I can do.
Say that again!
Let me tell you,
a gentleman uses his words, not his fists.
I'm telling you,
if you don't fix this for me today,
I'll wreck your shop!
Let me tell you,
if you intentionally damage property
worth over five thousand,
you could face prison time.
You don't want to end up
behind bars at your age, do you?
Nonsense!
I'll fix it!
I'll fix it for you, alright?
Hurry up!
Well...
I'll go get things ready.
Wait here for a second.
What?
Why haven't you taken them off yet?
Who takes off their
pants in the living room?
You want to go to my room?
That's not a good idea.
It'll make a mess everywhere.
Too much trouble.
It's such a pain.
We're both men.
Besides, you can't hold it anymore, right?
I have what you have.
Come on.
Wait!
What is that?
A catheter.
To help you relieve yourself first.
This...
does this work?
Of course it works.
People in hospitals with urinary issues
all use this.
When you get old,
you'll have to go through this anyway.
Just think of it as an early rehearsal.
Does it hurt?
No idea.
Might tickle a bit.
Have you used one?
No.
If you've never used it, why
the hell are you using it on me?
Fine.
Then we'll head to the hospital in a bit.
Don't step on my cat.
This kit costs sixty yuan in total.
I won't charge you for labor.
Just remember to pay
for the materials later.
You're taking advantage of me!
You old dog!
Well said.
Wait, wait, wait!
I... I was wrong, okay?
Just wait.
Have...
have you ever done this to anyone before?
I'm not a urologist.
How would I have the
chance to do this to anyone?
You're using me as a guinea pig!
You're already in this state.
Why are you being so picky?
Either wait for it to burst,
and I'll call an ambulance,
so everyone on the bar street knows
why you got hospitalized.
But...
what if you put it in the wrong place?
There's only one place.
How could I get it wrong?
At most, it'll scrape a bit of skin.
Just take some anti-inflammatory
meds and you'll be fine.
But...
what if you break it?
No, no, no.
You... you...
find another way.
Try something else.
Go to the hospital.
No, that won't do either.
Don't you run that shop?
Shouldn't you have plenty of ways?
Well, as for ways...
there is one,
but it might not be any
easier than a catheter.
Are you sure you want to try?