"Blue Lips"
(Episode 3)
What are you trying to do?
Is this the solution you talked about?
To put it simply,
men and women are the same.
In your situation,
it can be resolved by ejaculating.
Stop, stop, stop.
Don't say another word.
I don't understand
any of this medical stuff.
Just tell me
what I need to do.
Simply put,
that method.
I've tried it,
but I couldn't get it out.
That's because your technique is bad.
Leave it to me.
You...
Wait.
Why do you have an umbrella?
It's a preventive measure.
Just in case you get it on me later.
Otherwise,
I'll be scarred for life.
You're going too far!
Young man,
you know nothing about the
wonders of the human body.
In a moment,
you'll realize how
brilliant my decision was.
Come on.
Relax, relax, relax.
It's my first time doing this, too.
Now!
So?
Much better, right?
I think...
it's a bit better.
That's good.
We'll continue in a bit.
We have to continue?
Of course.
Even if the drug doesn't last three days,
it'll still be effective
for over ten hours.
But since you
just finished one round,
drink some water to ease it.
We'll go for round two in a bit.
Right now,
just hearing the word "water" scares me.
Alright then.
Take a break.
I'll be back in a moment.
Wait.
I...
I think it's starting again.
No way.
Are you...
Should I say you're too young,
or is this drug just too strong?
This...
Come on.
How does it feel?
Why...
Why are you asking that?
What's happening?
It's getting hotter and hotter.
I'm cold.
Then I'll take off the raincoat.
He isn't wearing gloves.
Are you feeling any better?
Once I recover,
I'm going to beat you
to a pulp.
We'll talk about that when you're better.
By the way,
what was your name again?
My name is Teng Mo.
Teng Mo.
I...
I'm so scared.
Tell me,
am I going to die?
Nobody dies from this.
Alright.
Why don't you
get up and take a shower?
I have no strength left.
Teng Mo,
am I ruined?
Why would you say that?
It seems like
it won't go down.
It hurts.
Repeated friction on
human skin causes pain.
Change your clothes first.
Is there really no other way?
Do you trust me?
Teng Mo,
help me.
Is it warm?
Can you make it quick later?
I still need to go home.
Then why don't you close your eyes?
Why?
Because if you can't see me,
you won't be annoyed.
I'm not...
I don't dislike you that much.
Have you ever tried
kissing a man?
Did you feel anything?
It was too brief.
I don't know.
Again?
These sleeves are so warm.
Can I draw close to
you for a moment?
I wanted to prank someone else,
but ended up pranking myself.
You little wolf.
Impressive.
Didn't I decide
not to drag others into this?
Have you used it?
No.
If you've never used it, why
the hell did you give it to me?
Fine.
We'll go to the hospital in a bit.
It doesn't matter anymore.
It's over.
Feel free to look around.
Do you want this one?
Which of these is better?
This one.
It's our best seller.
How much is this?
Thirty. Scan the code.
Thirty. Alright.
Take this.
This month
and next month,
I won't request songs that annoy you.
How was yesterday?
It was alright.
He sang really well.
Would you like to request a song?
Wu Shixian,
someone requested a song.
Why buy Vandacon if you're healthy?
If you don't want to host at Blue Moon,
why don't you consider finding another job?
Xiao Wu,
Xiao Wu.
Your guitar.
Here.
Buying medicine?
Vandacon again?
Have you thought about
trying another medicine?
Fine.
Never mind.
The usual, then.
Four hundred and fifty.
Lately,
why haven't you been coming to Blue Moon?
Didn't I promise you?
If you took that medicine,
I wouldn't request songs
that annoy you for months.
Even if you don't request songs,
you can still come for a drink.
I don't usually drink much.
Well,
you could request some normal songs.
I thought you didn't want me there.
Blue Moon isn't my house.
So, you do want me to go?
Suit yourself.
Who cares?
A'Heng.
Brother Mo!
It's been a while since
you visited Blue Moon.
Whiskey as usual?
Actually, no.
I'll have a Long Island Iced Tea today.
Sure.
Here you go.
Iced tea.
Not bad.
Request a song?
Someone already requested one.
This song is really beautiful.
What's it called?
Let me tell you a secret.
What is it?
The song is called "Let
Me Tell You a Secret."