This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
[Present]
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
[Flaming Chains of Love]
[Surat Thani]
[Akanee Crushing Plant]
[Akanee Oil Palm Plantation]
[Akanee Fisherman’s Wharf]
Ladies and gentlemen, it’s time for the honorary award–
Rattana Narai Award for the year 2026.
It’s an award given to those who have tremendously contributed to the benefits and well-being of Surat Thani.
And for this year, our committee has unanimously agreed that this award shall go to…
Mr. Akanee Watinwanich from the Akanee Empire.
Thank you.
On this occasion, would you please kindly say a few words to all of our guests?
I believe many of you here might only see how successful I am now.
How the Akanee Empire has expanded extensively.
But for me and the Akanee Empire to be where we are today,
I’m telling you–it’s not easy at all.
Every step I took was filled with obstacles…and those who wished to get rid of me.
I’m not afraid! I’ve won this auction for the mining concession fairly and legally.
I don’t care if anyone doesn’t want to play by the rules.
Let’s go.
Master, look out!
[Gunshot]
This way! Quick!
Believe it or not, I used to get assassinated just because I got in the way of some powerful people.
I almost couldn’t make it out alive.
But I still stand firm in my morals, and never will I bow down to any misconduct.
And that is why our Akanee Empire
is able to stand firm and become formidable today. Thank you.
[Applause]
[Guest]: Mr. Akanee, this way please. Can I take a picture with you?
Thank you.
[Guest]: Thank you.
[Akanee]: Thank you. My pleasure.
Thank you.
[Guest]: Congratulations.
[Akanee]: Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yod.
Yes, Boss?
Has Roong arrived in Surat yet?
Yes, I already sent someone to pick her up and take her to the main house.
Good. I’ll move my little one to live in the main house so that she can help look after my business.
Whoa! Will Young Master agree though? Even Miss Wanna doesn’t get to stay there.
It’s not for her to decide. Fai has never slept at the main house anyway.
Also, she hardly helps me look after the business.
Only God knows why she keeps avoiding me.
Just for the time being[whispering].
Fine, answer me–have you seen her today?
Do you know where your Young Master is right now?
Smile, huh?
[Watinwanich No. 4]
[Young Master]
Here, the Master’s woman you’ve asked me to look into.
Is Dad seeing a girl his daughter's age?
He has rented a flat for this girl and even paid for her education until she finished college.
People in the neighbourhood say he comes to visit her every week.
[Phone ringing]
Yes, Paen?
Young Master! The Master just brought his girl into the main house. She is moving in.
What?
[Paen]: Finally, Miss! You’re just in time.
I’m about to take her bags upstairs.
[Paen]: Over there, Miss. Look!
Paen, throw them away!
Yes, Miss!
What are you doing?
Throwing away trash, obviously.
Bring my little one’s bags upstairs, right now!
- Yes, Master.
-Throw them away!
Okay, Miss.
I said take them upstairs!
[Paen]: Yes!
- [Akanee]: NOW!
Yes.
I’m going.
You have no shame calling her your little one.
I already told you not to bring any of your women into this house.
I don’t care how many girls you’re seeing.
But this house isn’t a place for your chicks.
Seriously, can’t you just calm down a bit?
Then why didn’t you keep your words?
This is Mum’s house. You have no right to bring your new lover here!
I never said I’ll bring my new lover here.
If she’s not your new lover, then who the heck is she? Where is she?
There she is.
Do you remember her?
No.
That’s Kaphrao.
The bloody Guinea Pig!
Do you remember me now?
[We all have someone we remember from our childhood.]
[Kaphrao and I are like that. E
[the annoying rascal pest called Kaphrao.]
[I also will never forget Buffalo Fai who always picked on me]
[and did a number on me. Ten years isn’t too late for revenge.]
This is Kaphrao.
She’ll live with us here. Think of her as your little sister.
Kaphrao, this is Fai.
Look after her and play with her, okay?
Kaphrao, always listen to your sister.
Dad said she’s the daughter of a worker who just passed away.
She doesn’t have any parents now so he has to take her in.
But to adopt her as his own daughter?
What if she’s actually his mistress’ kid?
Listen to me, Fai.
You should stay away from her.
She’ll take everything from you.
Do you understand?
Fai…
When will you stop following me?
But I want to play with you.
But I don’t want to play with you.
Wait for me, Fai. Big Sis, please wait. Fai!
Go away! I don’t have a younger sister!
Fai. Fai. Fai.
Geez, I said leave me alone!
[Kaphrao]: Fai. Fai.
[Fai]: Leave me alone!
[Kaphrao]: Fai, it hurts!
[Akanee]: Kaphrao!
Serve you right!
- It hurts. It hurts.
- Are you okay, sweetie?
[Akanee]: Where does it hurt?
[Kaphrao]: Here.
Fai, why do you always pick on her?
If I see you do it again, I’ll give you a smack!
But I don’t have a younger sister. I don’t like the Guinea Pig!
Fai! Fai!
Does it hurt here?
Please don’t be mad at her, okay?
[Akanee]: I’ll fix the wound for you.
- [That annoying brat.]
[She only came here to steal Dad’s love from me.]
[Akanee]: There, there! All good now, right?
Come, let’s go inside.
Bring your toys too.
This one is for Fai. And this one is for Uncle.
Thank you, my dear. Let me have a bite.
It’s terrible.
Don’t listen to her.
Let me try it.
Wow, it’s so good! Well done! Give me a peck.
[In his eyes, whatever she did pleased him.]
[Akanee]: Can you feed your uncle too?
[But whatever I did was wrong.]
Let me play it too.
I don’t want to.
But I want to play it.
It’s mine. I’m not giving it to you.
Fai!
Serve you right! You should’ve given me when I asked you nicely.
Why did you break it then?
You didn’t give it to me when I asked you nicely.
But it’s mine!
Fine, you want it this way, huh?
It’s mine!
[We always fought like cat and dog, until one day…]
I’m not giving it to you!
But I want to play it!
I’m not letting you play it!
But I want to!
No, you can’t!
Then you can’t play it too!
Should we play together?
Do you want to play with me now?
Yes, but you have to listen to me.
Okay, follow me then.
[Worker]: Mee! Mee! Got packages from the wharf!
Come here, quick!
Let’s play hide and seek. But you have to be the seeker first, okay?
[Kaphrao]: But…
[Fai]: You can quit if you don’t want to.
I’ll do it.
Then, get in there.
It’s dark. I’m scared.
You said you’d listen to me. If you chicken out, then let’s not play together.
I’ll do it.
Get in there then.
I’m scared.
Are you going to do it or not?
Turn around and close your eyes, then count to twenty.
1, 2, 3…
Slowly.
4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11…
How could she disappear? There were so many people there?
Fai! Where were you playing with your sister earlier?
I played hide and seek with her on the truck.
But when I went back, the truck was gone.
Probably the fish truck. But we don’t know which one.
It must have gone far now. Damn it!
Kaphrao! Kaphrao!
[Worker]: I’m sorry, Master. I didn’t mean it.
[Worker]: I’m sorry.
[Akanee] Kaphrao!
She’s ice-cold. Why is her body so cold?
Kaphrao. Let’s go!
Will she die?
[Akanee]: Yod, open the door!
[Yod]: Yes, Boss!
Stay with me, Kaphrao. Quick!
Let’s go!
[Akanee]: Hurry up, Yod!
[Yod]: Young Master!
[Akanee]: Hang in there, Kaphrao.
- Let’s go, Yod!
Yes, sir!
Luckily, we found her quite fast. Otherwise, she might have been dead.
Do you know that?
You really went too far this time. I have to punish you.
Dad, I didn’t mean it.
Turn around now.
I said turn around!
Remember, don’t ever do that again.
- Dad! It hurts!
- [Akanee]: Don’t you dare do that again!
[Fai]: It hurts!
[Akanee]: Don’t do it again!
[Panee]: Stop it!
[Akanee]: Don’t ever do that again.
[Fai]: It hurts!
[Akanee]: Stop bullying your sister!
That’s enough! She’s just a child.
You’ve always spoiled her rotten, that’s why she’s like this!
I didn’t mean it.
You didn’t? How many times was it already?
She doesn’t like Kaphrao.
They don’t like each other.
This is all because you force them to live under one roof.
Fine! If you hate her that much, I’ll raise her somewhere else.
You will never see her again!
My dear. Does it hurt? My sweetheart.
There, there. It’s all right now.
[Kaphrao]: Long time no see, Buffalo Fai.
That side piece he’s been keeping and even paid for her college is you?
Yes, Kaphrao already graduated.
So, I want her to stay here to help with my work.
Are you saying this Gremlin will take my job?
But you hate coming into the office.
And you never come to the meeting.
So, I have to find someone who’s willing to work.
But I’m not okay with her!
I can’t help you with that.
I know you don’t want to work with me.
You’ve been avoiding me.
From now on, if you have anything to talk to me–just tell Kaphrao.
And if there’s anything I want to talk to you about, I’ll also let Kapharo know.
Okay?
No, not okay!
It doesn’t matter.
I’m not asking for your approval anyway.
Fine!
I’ll let this Gremlin work here.
But she can’t stay in this house no matter what.
And don’t you dare call me Sister.
I’m not your sibling!
Please don’t mind her.
Her mother passed away when she was little. I buried myself in work after that and hardly had time for her.
And all Aunt Panee did was pamper her.
I understand.
About the place to stay, I can go live at the worker’s cabin.
I don’t want Fai to hate me even more.
No, don’t do that. I want you to stay here as my own niece–not my employee.
Please. I want to start from there so that I could learn about work along the way,
and make friends with the workers too.
It’ll be easier for me when I have to deal with them in the future.
Okay, if that’s what you want. I don’t want to force you.
Thank you, Uncle.
Then, after we finish eating, I’ll ask Yod to drop you off at the cabin.
And tomorrow, I’ll give you a tour around the empire myself.
Sounds great. I’ll be waiting early in the morning.
I’ll pick you up tomorrow.
Let’s eat.
Yes.
Here, the crispy omelette. It’s a must-try.
- Thank you.
- You’re welcome.
Is it good?
Oh, this one is the best. It’s really hard to come by.
I never thought Ak would bring this girl back into the house again.
I completely forgot about her.
I didn’t even recognise her when we met at first.
But will you be okay if that girl will be working here?
Absolutely not. But I can't say anything much to Dad now.
Ak might see her as a niece but it doesn’t change the fact that that girl isn’t his biological kid.
Besides, she’s all grown up now.
What if she tries to seduce him for his money?
I don’t think so. Dad probably isn’t into someone that young.
It’s better to be safe than sorry.
You must keep an eye on her. Understood?
Be careful, or else she might soon become your stepmother.
If that’s the case, then she’ll have to go over my dead body first.
It’s this one.
Thank you so much, Uncle Yod. I can take it from here.
Are you sure you’re going to stay here?
Yes, I’d get to make more friends too.
Up to you then.
I’ll bring you a bicycle tomorrow.
The office is quite far. You’d better ride a bike there.
Thank you.
I’m off then. Call me if you need anything. My house is next door.
Oh, about the key–I already put it in the lock over there.
Thank you again, Uncle Yod.
Sure you can handle it?
Yes.
See you then.
Bye.
Who is it?
Hi there!
Hello.
I’m Bua. Young Master has sent me to stay here with you.
Stay here with me?
Yes. She said you’re a girl and came here alone so she’s worried.
More like to spy on me.
Well then, I’m going in.
It’s even bigger than my house on the island.
Hey, it’s all right. Relax–feel free to be yourself.
Okay.
Do you work here, Bua?
Yes, my house is on Young Master’s private island. My dad is a fisherman.
But since I want to have a boyfriend, and there aren’t so many people on the island; I figured it’s better to be here.
I see.
Listen, Miss, if you want to know anything, you can always ask me.
I might come from the island but I know everything about everyone here.
Oh, and I’ll take this room then. It’s still empty, isn’t it?
By the way, I’ll go shower first–feeling all sweaty and really need a shower right now.
I’ll talk to you later then. Good night. Talk to you later. See ya!
Finally, I get to work here where you used to, Dad.
Please cheer for me.
That one is Yellowstripe. I’ll show you.
They’re sorting out fish since fishes often come in various sizes and types when we unload them from the boat.
This one is Indian Mackerel. We put them in one category.
This one is still fresh.
Overall, that’s what we do here at the fisherman’s wharf. Let’s go see the office next, shall we?
Okay.
Let’s go.
I’ll explain everything to you.
It’s mainly here, the palm plantation, and the mine. Let’s go talk in the office.
My main businesses are fisherman’s wharf, oil palm plantation, and mining.
For today, you can just take a look around first.
Then, you can tell me later what you want to do and where you’d like to work.
Or if you don’t like to stay outside because it’s hot, you can just work in the office.
I’m so lucky indeed. My employer even lets me choose my own position.
Well, it’s a privilege for my little one.
I’ll give you a tour around the mine some day soon.
Yes, Uncle. I’ll do my best at work to make it worth the tuition fees you paid for me.
My dad said we are deeply indebted to you, so we should be grateful and repay the kindness.
It’s actually your dad whom I’m indebted to.
Yes?
I promise I’ll take good care of you just like how I treat Fai.
It’s all right, Uncle.
I’m just a worker’s daughter. You’ve done a lot for me already.
Okay!
Go take a look around first.
Yes.
I’ll teach you what to do later.
[Worker 1]: Look, that’s the Master’s new chick.
[Worker 2]: Really?
[Worker 1]: Yes! They were acting so lovey-dovey a minute ago.
Miss Phrao! Miss Phrao! Wait for me.
Has the Master left?
Mhm.
Why are the workers looking at me like that? Is there something going on?
Hmm, they’re probably excited to see the Master’s new chick.
What?
People at the wharf and plantation have been talking since yesterday that the Master just brought a new chick into the house.
That’s why Young Master was so furious and kicked you out to stay at the worker’s cabin.
What?
And this morning, he even took you around being all cuddly and lovey-dovey in front of the workers.
That’s not true!
Aww, are you sure?
Of course! Uncle and I are nothing like that.
If Fai hears about this, wouldn’t she eat my head off?
I guess it’s too late now.
What?
She already knows.
What did you just say, Auntie?
Our workers are talking that Kaphrao is your dad’s mistress.
That’s right, Miss. I saw it with my own eyes this morning that he was holding hands and being all touchy with Miss Kaphrao.
Don’t tell me he’s planning to let her take over his business.
Where’s that Gremlin right now?
Damn! Too bad I missed it.
You jerk! Don’t you have eyes?
Sorry, I just need to talk to you.
Then why cut me off? Can’t you drive like normal people? What if I got killed?
Well, you’re still alive–can even bark at me too!
What do you want?
Why did you come back?
I’m here to work–to repay Uncle’s kindness.
Who would believe you? I know you’re itching to get your hands on my dad’s money.
Why on earth would you ask then?
But actually, that’s a good idea.
I won’t have to work so hard that way. Why couldn’t I think of it earlier?
Disgusting! Shame on you!
You said it first.
If I get to be the mistress here, that means I can boss you around, Buffalo Fai!
I’m warning you, if you try to seduce my dad for his money–I’ll never let you live in peace!
Oh, I’m so scared.
Guinea Pig!
Shh! Call me Mummy so that you’ll get used to it.
Come on, say it loud and clear.
Sorry, forgot to tell you I’m a black belt.
Does it hurt, my daughter?
Mummy will fix it for you.
Dad! That bloody Guinea Pig just hurt me!
Is what she said true?
[Kaphrao]: Yes, Uncle.
See? Just fire her. I don’t want to live under the same roof with her!
Is that all?
I still doubt it.
Why would the Little One hurt you with no rhyme or reason?
I only did it to protect myself.
Are you saying I started it?
She deliberately drove her car to cut in front of my bike.
Luckily, nothing serious happened.
Guinea Pig!
You can check the footage on her dashcam, Uncle.
Fai, do you have anything to say for yourself?
You’re always unfair! If you’re going to take this Gremlin’s side, then don’t waste your time asking me.
You never take your own daughter’s side anyway.
Apologise to her.
No way! If you feel so sorry for her, then say it yourself!
Fai. Fai!
Fai! Fai!
Stop right now!
Don’t you feel embarrassed acting all childish in front of her? Fai!
I’m sorry she did that to you.
It’s my fault I didn’t raise her well.
That’s why she’s being so troublesome.
It’s my fault too, Uncle.
Hey, don’t try to influence her.
You’ve always been like this since little–keeping quiet no matter what she did to you.
When I found out and wanted to punish her, you wouldn’t let me. I knew that.
But now I think I can handle her.
I’ll try to avoid clashing with her as much as I can.
I know you’re a good girl, Little One. Please be patient with her.
Yes.
She’ll grow up soon.
Actually, she’s all grown up now.
But her personality is still unpleasant as ever.
Exactly!
Paen, get me something to eat! I’m hungry!
Yes, Miss!
Here you go.
I don’t like basil leaves! Throw it away!
Huh? Okay, Miss.
Paen, bring it back!
Not again.
Holy shit!
Is it okay?
[Yod]: That’s good. Carry on.
[Yod]: I’ll leave it to you then.
[Yod]: Hi, Miss Phrao.
Hello.
I heard you don’t seem to get along well with Young Master?
I really don’t get it.
What’s gotten into her head to have such a filthy thought?
It’s understandable if she doesn’t trust me.
But how could she not trust her own father?
I really wonder how she grew up.
Master is very popular.
Despite being a widower, many girls are lining up to be with him.
He’s actually very loyal.
After his wife passed away, he has never been with anyone except Miss Wanna.
Miss Wanna? I’ve never met her.
She lives in a small house at the back of the plantation.
Master had tried to bring her into the main house but ended up having a big fight with Young Master.
So, Miss Wanna had to live in another house instead.
From then on, father and daughter have become estranged.
Young Master hardly goes to the main house.
She mostly sleeps at Miss Panee’s house.
Wouldn’t Miss Wanna misunderstand me then?
Don’t worry. She’s generous and open-minded.
Please excuse me.
Thank you.
Are you busy these days? You haven’t come here for a while.
Yes.
Kaphrao has just moved in so there are many things to take care of.
I also heard about the rumour. It must have given you a headache.
I suppose you don’t believe that rumour, do you?
Of course not. I’ve been with you for so many years now.
I know what kind of person you are.
I don’t think I’ll ever find anyone as understanding as you.
Despite what Fai did to you, you still–
I’m happy to stay in my own place like this. Please don’t worry.
Yes.
But I still don’t understand why you want Kaphrao to live here?
I love Kaphrao like my own daughter.
I want my two kids to become close.
Once Fai finally sees Kaphrao as her little sister, I’ll be able to die in peace.
Want to have some?
I’m all good.
Hello, Miss Panee.
Don’t you know it’s rude to keep someone older waiting this long?
I really don’t know you’d be here, Miss Panee. Why don’t we go inside first?
No need, I’m only here to say what I have to.
I don’t know why you came back here.
But I’m warning you, don’t ever cause my niece any trouble.
Ak might be fond of you, but I’m not.
I know my own place.
I’ll try to stay away from her as best as I can.
That’s good.
I don’t want to waste my time talking to you.
Goodbye, Miss–
Dad, why does everyone here hate me?
[Door knocking]
Why? Are you surprised to see me?
Buffa–Fai!
Yes, it’s me. Who else do you think?
Or are you expecting my dad or one of the workers?
Disgusting! I just didn’t expect you’d come.
Why didn’t you call first?
This house is also my property.
I don’t need anyone’s approval to come here. Move!
Hey! Get out! What are you doing?
Checking if you’re planning something evil, or arranging your bed for my father.
Nonsense!
That’s my room!
From now on, you must come to Aunt Panee’s house to eat with me every single day.
So that you won’t have time to seduce my dad.
No! Eating with you? Just a thought of that makes me want to puke.
I’ll just puke on your face!
But that’s an order!
Listen, first, you’re not my boss. You don’t have the right to tell me what to do.
And even if you’re my boss–which is absolutely impossible–
you can only tell me what to do at work. If it’s not work, then dream on!
Fine! You said it yourself.
Morning, Miss Phrao! Come eat something first, come on.
Where are you off too?
Master said Uncle Yod will come take me to the mine.
Oh, really? Don’t forget to apply lots of sunscreen then.
It’s boiling hot as if you were in hell there.
Is it that hot?
Yes, I used to ask Young Master to let me work there because I wanted to be surrounded by strong and muscular men.
But once I got there, I’d rather stay home on the island.
Have it. Eat all you like.
[Phone ringing]
Yes, Uncle Yod? Okay, I’ll be waiting outside.
Yes.
Uncle Yod is coming. I’m heading out then.
- Okay.
- I’ll have this then.
Sure, take some more.
Thanks, this is fine.
- Hey, Miss Phrao!
- Yeah?
Don’t forget to put on sunscreen. It’s extremely hot there, trust me.
Okay!
Why are you here?
To take you to work, of course.
What?
My dad already agreed to let you work with me.
From now on, you’re my assistant.
Trying to please me?
I’m going to officially help you at work. No more dragging my feet.
Are you serious?
I’ll do anything you assign me to do and attend every meeting, but only on one condition.
What condition?
You have to let Kaphrao be my assistant.
Come on, I know what you’re thinking. Aren’t you going to give me a chance?
Fine, I’ll trust you this time.
Deal?
Deal.
Am I your friend or what?
Here, have some more.
From now on, you have to do whatever I say because I’m now officially your boss.
You’re plotting something evil, aren’t you?
No! Why would you think that? All I have is sincerity.
Get in the car.
Young Master!
Young Master.
Are you going to take Miss Phrao to the mine yourself?
Yes, is there a problem?
No, Miss. Actually, she can come with me since I have to go to work there anyway.
I also plan to show her around the mine to learn some work.
That’s all right, just leave it to me.
You can go take care of something else. Don’t worry about her.
Okay, Miss.
Stop standing like an idiot there. Get in the car!
Why do you want me as your assistant if you don’t like me?
And you even volunteer to take me around the mine.
You’re not planning to kill me and dump my body there, are you?
Good idea. Thanks for your suggestion. Why couldn’t I think of it earlier?
Don’t you dare mock me.
I just want to show you around the mine and give you a 101 mining lesson.
But I don’t want to know it.
Only speak when I ask you to. Don’t try to cozy up to me.
What faculty did you graduate from?
Hey, I’m asking you!
Oh, you’re talking to me?
It’s just us here. If not you, then who the heck I’d be talking to?
I thought you were talking to your imaginary friend.
Answer me!
Accounting.
Unbelievable, you don’t look like someone who’s educated.
And you don’t look like someone who has brains.
You agreed to let Kaphrao work with Fai, does that mean you trust her?
Not at all.
I think Fai is definitely planning to fire Kaphrao.
But I trust Kaphrao that she can handle Fai.
I’m afraid those two might end up strangling each other first.
Well, let them be.
Fighting each other might make them become closer.
Just wait and see. I’ll make those two love each other like real siblings.
Need a little booster.
What’s so funny?
You, of course.
Can I have more?
[Akanee Crushing Plant]
Can you have it inspected?
I think there’s a problem with the brake. It feels squishy and doesn’t stop well.
Yes, Miss.
Take care of it for me then. I’ll wait in the office.
We blew up that mountain earlier.
Then, we’ll put those stones into the crushing plant.
After that, we’ll sort them out into different sizes just like what you see there.
Wow! It’s huge.
Where you’re standing now is called the office building.
It’s for keeping records and documents like a list of clients who buy rocks from us, or vehicles coming in and out of the mine.
I can’t believe you’re really teaching me some work.
I told you.
I need to go through some documents first.
You can go look around or explore the place however you like.
Damn it!
What?
The dump truck tickets are with Uncle Yod. What to do?
Why are you looking at me?
Can you go get it for me?
I have some work to finish off here.
Get it from where?
Behind that mountain over there.
What? Hang on, how do you expect me to go there?
They already took my car for a brake inspection. I guess you’ll have to walk there.
Walk?
[Next Episode]
Young Master said if you can’t finish it today, then you’re not allowed to go home.
Fine! This is a piece of cake!
[Fai]: Is that girl still working?
[Yod]: Yes, are you sure you want to leave her there alone, Young Master?
[Yod]: It’s quite dark and deserted around there at night.
Well, she chose it herself.
It’s not like I’ve forced her to stay back so late.
I’m really curious what makes you change this much?
It’s you.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]