[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Every July, the hospital resets.
New residents, new chaos,
same nurses doing
damage control,
so July doesn't kill anybody.
Ugh.
Do you need a hand?
Nope, I'm doing great.
All on my own, thank you!
Yeah, okay, I'm such a bad guy,
daring to deliver your mom
eternal peace.
[NURSE] Paging Dr. Godwin.
Please come to Room Five...
You know, I don't think
she's going to be okay.
I can...
[SNIFFS]
I can smell her time
running out!
[NOA] Shut up!
I don't have time for this.
No time? Hmm?
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[WHISTLING]
[ELEVATOR THUDS]
Hm? Huh?
[GRIM] Oh, look at that.
Now we have all
the time in the world.
No one can escape
their fate, Noa.
Sorry, Grim.
No one's dying on my watch.
[BELL RINGING]
[SIGHS]
Hi, Phineas.
Another new one.
And why are you
making that face?
With your history
of panic attacks,
keep that paper bag nearby
and you'll be
out of here in no time.
Thanks, Doctor.
But my son's getting
his first school award.
- Can't miss it.
- Oh, and you won't.
Hey, Doc.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Excuse us.
Hey, Doc.
I looked at her records.
I think we should order
more tests-- [STAMMERS]
Nurse, just increase the
dose of her anxiety meds.
Yeah, but what if
it's something--
Those are my orders.
[DOOR OPENS]
Yes, Doc.
- [SIGHS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
What are you doing?
I'm checking.
Did you say something?
[SIGHS]
Finny, did these feel like
any of your other attacks?
Well, yeah. I couldn't breathe.
My chest got so tight.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I really just thought
I was going to die.
Anything else?
[SIGHS]
My back.
It's like someone
stuck a knife in it.
But it's better now.
The pulse is thready.
Wait, what are you doing?
This isn't tracking.
Wait... But the doctor said,
I'll be fine.
- Just give me a second.
- No, stop it.
- No, you're scaring me.
- I just need a second.
Listen to her, dear!
- No, I need to make sure.
- I said stop!
Dear, let it go!
[SLOW, DEEP BREATHING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Whoa, whoa. Blink slower.
Those eyelashes
are causing a draft.
I am expecting a
high-profile company.
Relax. Not every moment
is a close-up, Princess Sarah.
Should I clap too for every
progress note so you feel seen?
[GASPS]
- Here he is!
- Whoa, whoa, what now?
The Director Marty is here.
And he's here for me!
- Who?
- [MARTY] Camille.
Darling, long time no see.
- [CAMILLE] Hi.
- [SMOOCHES]
Hey, hey! You better
put that down,
or I'm going to turn
that into suppository.
Ros, this is the Director Marty.
He's a legend. I'm menopausal.
So what?
Don't worry.
This will be private.
That's what that
asshole said too.
Now my nude is a wallpaper
in some groupchat.
Ros, wait.
Excuse me.
What?
Get us a private room.
Private room? Try HIPAA.
- Ten dollars.
- 30.
Twenty dollars.
I'll prep your room.
- [SQUEALS]
- [TELEPHONE RINGS]
Run the symptoms again.
Maybe you're overthinking.
I'm not.
- Grim said...
- He's a liar.
Patients downplay things.
Then talk to them.
She's already filed a complaint.
Then get help.
Her attending isn't answering.
Well, he's still a doctor.
No. He's just a resident.
You're smart, dear.
But the clinical eye,
it takes decades.
I have a third eye.
- Does that not count?
- Wow.
She's funny now.
Okay, Miss Know-it-all.
With all of your experience,
what do you think it looks like?
Half my patients with aortic
dissections were misdiagnosed.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
So I wait...
She dies.
Here's your return
of the comeback.
For the art.
But this HIPAA thing,
will it be a problem?
Not at all.
[KEYPAD CLACKS]
[CLOCK TICKING]
Dear, you're risking everything.
For what?
A life, Mom.
[CLOCK TICKING CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY] Not again.
Not on my watch.
Ready to give your
audience your all?
I'll save her.
- Whatever it takes.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
- [SHUSHING]
- Good morning, everyone.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
That was weird.
Hey, can we...
Look, I know I'm not
supposed to be talking to you.
But there's something
you should know.
What?
Who told you you
shouldn't be talking to me?
My girlfriend.
But that's not the point, Noa.
People are talking,
and it is not good.
They're saying that
a patient is complaining
about you harassing her,
and going against
Dr. Lee's orders.
I'm trying to save her life.
Dude, I knew there was no way
that you were just going
to break the chain of command
like that or something.
Noa, 30 minutes, your office.
We have a certain
doctor to deal with.
Good morning.
Hmm.
You've come such a long way.
Downward.
Before, you were unreachable.
Hold still, please.
Now?
Beggar level project
in a hospital like this?
[KNOCKS]
Is it okay if I grab
something from here?
Do you know her?
Get out!
[WHIMSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Everything happens for a reason.
Babe, I'm not talking to her.
Why do you think I'm
jogging on my break?
[WOMAN] I know
you're talking to her.
Oh, that's why you vanished.
No one invited you, dude.
I gotta go, babe.
- [WOMAN] Bye.
- Yeah, but this is fun.
[PANTS, GRUNTS]
- What are you, an Olympian?
- No.
I'm not watching naked
men fight for glory again.
- Beat ya!
- What?
- Okay.
- Are you good?
I don't like liars
or cheats, okay?
That's what Noa says.
Why? Is she talking about me?
[SCOFFS] Sycophant.
Look, I'm not the one
who took my flowers
and tried to give them to her.
Then challenge me.
Like the Olympians.
If I win, you drop
the silent treatment.
Didn't think you cared
about what people thought?
I don't.
I just hate unfinished business.
Deal?
- Deal.
- Alright then.
Whoa, whoa! Let's keep
the pants on for this one.
Are you sure?
- Pretty sure.
- Alright.
One, two, three, go.
[CHUCKLES]
Did you check the vitals
for this patient?
- Yes.
- Okay, what about for her?
Insubordination is
grounds for termination.
Slow down, doc.
Excuse us.
Jane.
As I responded to your emails,
we do not fire someone
over a single verbal complaint.
Don't ever mention
the troponin test.
I'm sorry, Dr. Lee.
I don't accept your apology.
Here's what I do accept.
Nurses take vitals.
That's her scope.
I'm not firing someone
for doing her job.
- Thank you.
- However,
you will receive
a formal write-up.
You undermined a physician
in front of a patient.
I need better from you.
Your team needs better from you.
That's all?
I don't get a say in this?
You do, but in this lane,
the call is mine.
[SIGHS]
Just remember, when this
blows back, it lands on you.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry for how that looked.
Don't be sorry. Be sure.
If you're going to break ranks,
you better be
damn certain you're right.
I can't just sit here and
listen to someone die.
He's wrong.
There's something
you're not saying.
And if you lie to me,
I can't protect you.
If the hospital finds out
about this,
you'll lose your license
forever.
It's nothing.
Thank you, Jane.
[JANE] Noa.
One last thing.
Your mom would have been proud
seeing you fight for
that patient like that.
[SILLY MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
Seventy-three?
- That was seventy-one.
- [GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
There she is.
Our brave survivor.
Ready for your close-up?
Well, I can't stay long.
My son's getting an award.
Perfect.
Motherhood guilt.
That's our emotional arc.
Here's $100 as agreed.
- Oh, thank you.
- Let's do BTS.
You're discharged.
So we can use you now.
Right, Camille?
Let's move her to this chair.
Oh, okay. Hold on.
[GROANS]
- [CAMILLE] Oh!
- [GROANING]
- Are you sure you're okay?
- It's my back.
This hundred will
make me feel better.
At least I will have
enough for a congrats gift.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Camille, put your hand
on her back.
- Okay.
- Like you care.
- Oof...
- Oh, did that hurt?
It just... it moved.
Chest to back.
It's weird, right?
Cut!
Be sadder!
Let's try this again.
Action!
Director, I can't.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[FINNY BREATHING HEAVILY]
Camille.
One more mistake...
This is over.
Do you understand?
[SIGHS]
[FINNY GROANS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
Dear, don't.
[NOA] She's dissecting.
We're out of time.
You guys, where's 503?
- She's not in her room.
- I can look it up.
She's been discharged.
No, she's taking a walk
with Camille.
[NOA] What?!
She shouldn't be!
Huh?
W-Wait! Wait!
[SOFT, TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop!
Do you want us
to get kicked out of here?
Keep rolling.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Finny?
Okay.
What is she doing here?
Finny, I need you
to stop moving.
I know you want to see your son,
but if you walk out
those doors right now,
you increase your chance
of dying every hour.
[CRYING]
Director.
Kiss my well-toned ass!
Get out!
Excuse you!
Are you talking to me?
[ROS] Hey!
She may be too demure
to kick your ass, but I'm not!
You have ten seconds to get out
of my ward, Director Dumbass!
Out!
[NOA] Stop talking.
Slow breaths.
- Camille.
- I'm on it!
Rapid response to 503!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYS]
We're here! We're here!
One, two, three, four,
I declare a thumb war.
This is getting sad.
Don't act all high and mighty.
You're the one...
who stole my flowers,
and ruined my relationship.
You're the one
who wrote Noa's name.
Boop! 5-0!
Denial's always easier, huh!
I was distracted!
Out of the way!
[NOA SIGHS]
I'm sorry, Mom.
[WIND WHOOSHES]
Don't be.
Just trust Jane.
[JANE] Noa!
I've been looking for you.
How's Finny?
She'll live.
What I can't explain is
who ordered the troponin.
Noa.
You've crossed the line.
Nurses don't order tests.
I'm sorry.
What would possess you
to do that?
You can't say
"based on your clinical eye,"
because this is new to you.
Mom, please help me.
I'm sucking so bad right now.
Do not go there.
Do not use her
to get me to look away.
Tess isn't here anymore.
What if I told you she was?
Don't make this day any crazier.
She told me that every day
after nursing school,
she'd see you
eating lunch by yourself.
Not until she convinced a bunch
of Filipinos to invite you over.
Okay, yeah...
Well I wasn't the nicest person
when she was
my clinical instructor.
She could have told you that.
I hate secrets, Jane.
I hate not knowing stuff.
But Mom?
She never talked about work.
- Not until she--
- [STAMMERS]
Nurses hallucinate
from overworking.
Don't do this to yourself.
When you were
going over resumes...
Did my resume keep
popping up on your screen
until you recognized my name?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I know you checked
my address with Mom's.
That's her fault.
She taught me
how to use computer.
How'd you...
Mom saw you cry
in your office every night
during the pandemic.
But when she passed,
you cried so hard that
you vomited into your N95.
Don't do this to me.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know you still talk to her.
In your office.
Especially on nights
when you stay late.
You sit there and talk to her
like she's still right
beside you.
Because in those moments...
She is.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATH HITCHES]
Is she here?
Right now?
[EXHALES SHAKILY]
Tess.
[SNIFFLES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
You are still a pain
in my ass, lady.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Every Friday night...
We used to take
one shot of tequila.
- Just for the tea.
- I didn't tell her that part!
She told me to trust you.
It was her experience
and clinical eye that...
...helped me save Finny's life.
[EXHALES]
You were right.
But the system does not allow
for this.
You have got to swear to me.
And you, too, Tess.
That you will remember
that we are nurses.
She's right. She's right.
We do right by our patients,
but we do not diagnose.
Not on our own.
You trust your team
to figure it out.
You trust me.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
It won't happen again.
All that mentoring, and
this is what you remember?
Tequila?
[GROANS SOFTLY]
["THE DENIAL SONG"
BY JADE RICCIO PLAYING]