AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
-Min-ji.
-Hey, what a great house!
It's nice and big.
What are you talking about?
It obviously looks small.
Min-ji, come inside. It's dangerous.
-I'd say about ten…
-Come in!
Well, maybe eight people could live here.
Move some boxes already.
EPISODE 5
Hey, why didn't you mention
there was no elevator?
If I'd known, I wouldn't have come.
You can go now.
Really?
Since you have a hired hand here,
I'll just take off.
Where do you think you're going?
Stop whining.
Go downstairs and move some boxes.
What kind of athlete
can't put any muscle into it
and only moves the light stuff?
If I had any muscle,
I would've become a weightlifter.
What did you say?
Taekwondo isn't about strength.
Get out of my way already!
You can't pivot, can you?
-Jeez.
-You're all muscle and no brain.
You need to use your head.
Move out of the way
before I throw this at you.
Gosh, it's cold.
This is so good.
Thank you, sir.
Sure thing. Come by again.
-Okay.
Who wants to go to the playground?
-Me!
-Me too!
But I have to go to my academy class.
Did you just move here?
Yeah.
Want to come to the playground with us?
You lift this one.
Move this fridge.
Min-ji.
What is it?
Min-ji!
-What's wrong?
-Where is she?
Min-ji!
Min-ji's gone.
-Min-ji!
-Where did she go?
Min-ji!
-Min-ji!
-Kim Min-ji!
Min-ji!
-I'll go this way.
-Okay.
Min-ji!
-Hide your toes, hide your nose
-Hey.
-Here I come
-Where are you going to hide?
-You go this way, and I'll go that way.
-Hide your toes, hide your nose
Here I come
-Good luck.
-Hide your toes, hide your nose
Here I come
Hide your toes, hide your nose
JEILWON SENIOR WELFARE CENTER
-Min-ji!
Let's keep looking.
Come on.
Min-ji!
I'm sorry,
but have you seen this child?
No, we haven't seen her.
Thank you.
Hey, Kim!
-Yeah?
-Any sign?
No.
Let's head back home.
Maybe she's back.
-All right.
-Come on.
Min-ji!
Have they all left?
Is anyone here?
I'm locking up now.
CURRENTLY AWAY
Excuse me!
Over here!
-Is she home?
-No.
Where did she go?
I went to the apartment complex,
but she's not there.
My goodness.
She was right here.
Why didn't you keep an eye on her?
Goodness gracious.
-Did you check the park?
-Jeez.
-Min-ji!
-She was literally right here.
Kim Min-ji!
She was right here.
Daddy!
Min-ji!
-Hey!
-Min-ji!
Daddy!
-Hey!
Where did you go?
I looked everywhere for you.
Are you okay?
I was playing hide-and-seek
at the playground.
I couldn't open the door to get out,
but I didn't cry.
Goodness, Min-ji. You're so brave.
Thank you.
It must've been hard to find this place.
Min-ji told me where to go,
so it was easy.
She's very smart.
There's the fish-shaped bun stand,
the post office box,
and the red house.
Min-ji needs to hit the books.
-She'll be successful.
-That's right.
Have her study to become a doctor or judge
so she can help us out later.
Jeez, that's all you can think of?
From now on,
you can't go off on your own, okay?
It's okay.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
-I'm sorry.
-Thank you.
It's okay.
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
Hey!
Open the door!
Wait a minute. What's going on?
She's alive?
What the hell?
Hey!
Hey, kid!
Stay in there for a second.
Hold on.
What the heck?
Who the hell are you?
I'm sorry. Please.
I'm sorry.
Why isn't he answering? Damn it!
Hello?
Boss, this is Seok-jung.
We're almost there. Where do you want us?
Hey, did you bring the guys?
Yes, I brought all of them.
Go to the office.
Sang-man and Gang-min aren't answering.
Got it, boss.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you going this far over some girl?
Did Ju Gang-chan send you?
Ju Gang-chan?
No?
Then who are you?
Are you a cop?
Tell me.
Where's Min-ji?
The cold storage warehouse.
She's frozen in there.
Go take a look.
I said go take a look!
Cold storage warehouse?
My Min-ji…
Look, all we did was move her
after Ju Gang-chan's daughter called us.
She was dead from the start!
If…
Min-ji is really dead…
I'm going to…
kill all of you.
That crazy bastard. No, I refuse to die.
Nothing beat the MG42 during World War II.
"Hitler's Buzzsaw."
You've seen Saving Private Ryan, right?
The Germans used it
to spray everyone in Normandy.
Man, 1,200 rounds per minute
back then is insane, isn't it?
At 1,200 rounds per minute,
how many rounds is that in a second?
How many rounds is that? Huh?
Did you learn arithmetic?
That's 20 rounds per second.
That's no joke.
It's such a shame
we can only see it in museums now.
-Isn't it a shame?
-Not really.
Are you still doing the math?
Man, what a mess.
Why are you acting sentimental?
I have to say,
life was easier
when I was just ironing clothes.
It would've been easier for Agent Kim
to live an ordinary life too, right?
I mean, he was the easiest guy
to push around.
Sometimes, I wasn't even sure
if he was really 66.
Well, I'm still not sure.
If I were him,
our deputy branch manager would've been
found dead somewhere a long time ago.
The M249 is the most similar to it,
if anything.
Of course, it uses 5.56 mm NATO rounds,
and it's more compact,
so some say it lacks firepower.
But at 1,150 rounds per minute,
it's still pretty sweet.
Tell you the truth, I own a few myself.
Want to see them sometime?
Aren't you curious?
Hey, don't underestimate it
just because it's compact.
It's modular, so you can run
whatever attachments you need,
which is why the M249 is great.
We've located the director.
All units move out,
except for the HQ escort vehicle.
Everyone's done for the day, huh?
Well, in that case,
this is the end of today's lesson.
You guys should go home too.
Get it together.
That bastard's back.
What now?
Holy crap, he's coming! What do I do?
He's coming again!
Oh no.
All right!
I made it!
Good job.
Are you there? What happened?
I think something went down, boss.
What?
I think Sang-man is dead,
and I don't see Gang-min at all.
Don't tell me Ju Gang-chan…
No, it's too early for him to be there.
Hey.
Find Gang-min and bring everyone
to the cold storage warehouse.
Yes, boss.
What the hell was that?
-Hey, follow me.
-Yes, sir.
What the hell did I do so wrong?
I'm sorry.
What?
I swear I just did as I was told.
Take me to the cold storage warehouse.
You can die after that.
Wait, wait…
What kind of SMD director
can't even swim?!
Jeez, I'm crashing.
What took you so long, trooper?
You should've kept up with cardio.
What are you doing here?
I came to throw you a stick
in case you were struggling in the water.
Or at least a rock.
You little…
How did you know I'd be here?
Your route was obvious
once I assessed the wind,
current, and terrain.
I knew you'd come to the cliff area
to elude the SMD agents.
If you'd gone down any farther,
the rapids would've swept you away.
And across the water are thorn bushes.
-Okay, I get it. I don't care!
-The only place
you could've come ashore
with that dead weight
was here.
Of course, you have to be at my level
to figure out the exact location.
Oh, it's working.
What happened to the SMD agents?
Don't worry.
I sent them home safely.
You probably went on about that
1,150 RPM fire-rate gun again.
How'd you know?
Here.
Drink this.
What's this?
The way I see it,
you won't make it at this rate.
You need to drink something like this
to stay healthy and keep up.
You said Myeongpo Port, right?
All right, move out!
Hold on.
These guys will keep coming after us.
Let's split up.
Don't you think
we'll need weapons too?
Weapons?
Please don't kill me.
-Sir!
-Huh?
Hey! Why did you get here so late?
You're dead meat.
Hey, get this guy!
I don't have time for this.
Bring it.
Kill him!
Hey, kid.
You'll freeze to death
if you stay in there.
How much longer do you think
you can hold out?
You haven't frozen to death already,
have you?
Hey, you can't die.
Get it together.
What's your name?
Dad…
Hey, kid. How about if we make a deal?
I'll let you go.
Think about it.
You and I have nothing against each other.
We don't know each other.
All I did was follow orders
and bring you here
because I thought you were dead.
Right?
Are you listening?
If you promise
not to tell anyone what happened,
I'll let you go, okay?
So just trust me--
You're lying.
You killed the security guard.
You'll kill me the second I step out.
You think I'm stupid?
Well, I suppose
you're not a snot-nosed little kid.
Still, I hoped you'd agree.
Fine, go ahead and freeze to death.
I guess I'll just wait.
Damn, why aren't these bastards here yet?
Shall we go?
Where is it?
Over there. It's right over there.
Did you find your daughter?
What a shame.
You'll probably never see her again.
You fucking son of a bitch.
Go back to where you came from.
You've gone soft.
Cut the crap.
Do exactly what you did…
when you killed my brother.
Your brother?
How much longer?
We're 20 minutes away, sir.
-Tell Nam to head over there first.
-Yes, sir.
All units proceed to the destination,
except for the lead vehicle.
We'll secure the area and stand by.
Seriously, man!
I think my ears are bleeding!
-I can taste blood!
-Turn it off!
Just enjoy it!
Hey!
Try to hold out… Are you listening?
Hey, you guys try to hold out
until I get back!
-Don't get scared and cry! Got it?
-Just go already.
Rock spirit!
What's that lunatic even saying?
Your brother?
What do you mean?
You killed him.
I'm talking about Number 66.
Are you…
Gang Seong?
Yeong Gwang!
-Gang Seong!
-Yeong Gwang!
-Go back! Right now!
Don't leave me behind!
-Yeong Gwang!
-Wait for me!
I promise to succeed
and come back for you!
-Stay alive! You have to survive, okay?
-Yeong Gwang!
-Wait for me, Gang Seong!
I'm not the one…
who killed your brother.
CRUSH THE PROVOCATIVE SCHEMES
OF THE SOUTH KOREAN PUPPETS!
Enough.
Take it.
I'm giving it to you out of pity.
You keep losing to me,
so I was wondering
if it's because you don't eat enough.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
You bastard.
Don't you have any pride?
There's no such thing as pride
between friends.
BETTER DEATH THAN ENEMY CAPTURE
Tomorrow's finally the day.
I'm going to make it back alive.
They said if we complete this operation,
they'll give us a house
and find our family.
Family, my foot.
I can't even remember my own name.
Kim.
Your last name is Kim.
What did you say?
Do you remember when we first came here?
After getting beaten up for months,
I forgot my own name.
But for some reason,
I never forgot that your last name is Kim.
Isn't that funny?
I was so scared that I forgot my own name,
but I still remember your last name.
Kim…
Don't forget me.
You're my only friend.
If you forget me too…
there'll be no one left to remember me.
How can I forget my nemesis?
I'm 73, the Republic's pride and joy.
And you…
You're 66, a pile of dog crap.
Hey, 66!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, 66.
Get it together.
Let's get out of here.
Forget it.
Unless you can attach…
my leg.
Let's get out.
This is it…
for me.
You have to live.
I'd rather pull the trigger than survive…
and be taken as a prisoner.
I won't let you die alone.
We'll die together.
Don't die.
Think about why…
we endured that hell.
It was to survive.
I need you to do one last thing for me.
No matter what happens…
promise me…
you'll survive.
Drop your gun! Hands on your head.
Dad!
Don't you have any pride at all?
Why did you have to grovel and kneel?
Is it because Hye-ri's dad
is a powerful man?
I'm so ashamed.
I feel so angry, frustrated, and pathetic.
Why did you even have me?
Min-ji.
DAD
I'm sorry for making you feel ashamed.
But a parent's pride doesn't matter
when it comes to their child.
Min-ji,
you're my pride.
I won't die, Dad.
I'm going to survive and make it home.
What now?
Seriously? Now it's pouring rain too?
You've got to be kidding me.
It's just one thing after another, huh?
Jeez.
Boss!
Gang-min!
Hey, Gang-min.
What's wrong with you? What happened?
A guy
claiming to be that girl's dad came and…
What? Her dad?
What are you talking about?
Why would her dad show up here?
Hey, Gang-min.
Is he dead?
Hey, Gang-min!
That's more like it.
This is how it should be.
You held out pretty long,
didn't you?
Hey, kid.
Why are you hiding?
Come on out. It's time to go home.
Oh, I see.
Are you letting me know where you are?
Should I fall for your little plan or not?
Let's say
I head over there…
Then you'll try to run!
Or you'll come up from behind!
Hey.
Stop playing games and come out.
Does it look like I'm messing around?
If you come out now, I'll let you go.
I'm done going easy on you!
Bullshit.
Hey, you're alive.
Where are you going? Come here.
Come here!
You almost had me fooled.
Don't bullshit me!
Whatever you say,
you're still nothing
but a traitor to the regime.
You think I'll believe anything you say?
You can believe me or not.
That's your choice.
But all of us…
were discarded.
Have you thought about it?
I still don't understand.
Why do you people need me?
To be honest,
I think it's a waste
to throw away talent like yours.
I haven't seen anyone else
who can go toe-to-toe with Park Jin-cheol.
In fact, you're probably the only one
from the North who can.
This is your last chance.
If you continue to hold out,
we'll have no choice but to end you.
The North may have discarded you,
but you still need to find a way
to make a life here.
Don't you agree?
"Discarded"?
What do you mean by that?
Didn't you know?
You were all used as bait.
It was your bureau's second-in-command
who leaked the intel
that you were infiltrating that day.
He used you guys
to get rid of the director general
and to take his position.
"Second-in-command"?
DIRECTOR GENERAL RO TAE SIK
DIRECTOR GENERAL RI EUNG RYEONG
I'm talking about Ri Eung Ryeong.
Thanks to your comrades
getting annihilated,
the director general was cut loose,
and Ri Eung Ryeong swooped in to take it.
"Stay alive."
"You have to survive, no matter what."
Gang Seong!
Stay alive!
You have to survive, okay?
Yeong Gwang!
Those were 66's…
No, those were Yeong Gwang's
last words to me too.
So…
stay alive.
Leave the past behind…
and live as Min-ji's dad.
-Start searching.
-Yes, sir.
We should at least talk to him.
Min-ji.
I'm here, Min-ji.
Min-ji?
Min-ji!
Min-ji…
Min-ji.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm scared.
Min-ji…
is alive.
Min-ji!
Kim Min-ji!
Min-ji.
Min-ji!
Kim Min-ji!
Min-ji.
Min-ji!
It's me! Min-ji!
Spread out and search.
-Yes, sir.
-Director!
-Are you okay, sir?
-Sir.
Get off me!
-What about Kim?
-He's currently at Myeongpo Port.
What about the other two?
Sung Han-soo was already gone.
As for Park Jin-cheol,
he surrendered, but…
He surrendered?
That makes no sense!
The thing is…
It does make sense.
He escaped during transport, you see.
What? Escaped? You little…
What the hell are you guys doing?
You can't do anything right.
Let's get going for now.
-Director.
-Yes, sir.
Here.
Why do you have that?
I found it on the side of the road.
Where's my cash and credit cards?
What's this?
TRANSACTION APPROVED
1,673,000 WON
What? 160,000…
Wait, 1.67 million won?!
Those bastards!
That's actually not bad for them.
Hey, Han-soo.
It's Jin-cheol.
Sorry, it took me a while
to unlock the phone.
Hey, have you heard of
germanium bracelets?
Not sure if they're effective though.
Man, these red snow crabs are huge.
I stocked up on some combat rations.
We need to eat before we fight.
Take that germanium bracelet and stuff it.
How can you eat at a time like this?
-Whose number is this anyway?
-Oh, this?
I took this phone
from one of the SMD agents.
Call me on this number from now on, okay?
Just answer the phone when I do.
Okay, okay!
He nags too much.
DEOKJEON SERVICE AREA
MYEONGPO MOTORCYCLES
Ma'am.
Are you sure you're okay with selling it
for this price?
It's fine.
My husband used to ride this
back in the day.
He's too old for that now.
I'll just buy some good beef with this.
Hold on.
-Yes?
-You're going to ride like that?
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Bye.
Boss!
Boss.
It's so cold here.
We're screwed, boss.
Boss.
Boss!
Hey, the kid.
That little rat.
Hey, go find her.
-Find her.
-Yes, sir.
Our guys…
Grab him.
Open your mouth.
Wait!
Please help me!
Please!
The chairman left you
with his final orders.
You'll take the fall…
for killing that girl.
And then I die too, right?
Where's the body?
Body?
What body?
That one?
Where is it?
You're screwed.
There's no body, dumbass.
That girl
is still alive.
She's still alive. Find her!
-Yes, sir!
-Finish up here, then join us.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, lackey.
Do you know
what life tastes like?
Sweet?
Bitter?
Nope.
Guys like you who act tough
may see life as sweet or bitter,
but for thugs…
life tastes like blood.
Over here!
Please stop the car!
Please!
Min-ji!
HANGMAN 10-RO
NATIONAL HIGHWAY 87
The rain's coming down hard.
MR. KIM
Hello?
Hangman 10-ro, Poseung-eup.
National Highway 87.
Track the CCTV footage
from ten minutes ago.
What?
It'll show Min-ji's whereabouts.
Mr. Kim.
The only way this ends is by finding her.
So call me once you've tracked her.
Please, Sang-a.
What kind of bullshit is that?
How can we trust that bastard?
Agent Kim is going out of control
to find his daughter.
Once he does,
he'll turn himself in.
What, you think he's crazy?
He knows exactly what will happen
if he turns himself in.
He's a man of his word.
Shut up, you punk!
I'm sorry, sir.
Sir.
I think they have a point.
I agree, sir.
Agent Kim's movements
have been centered around his daughter.
What's the matter with all of you?
Any dad would naturally…
It's only natural, isn't it?
So, his daughter is his weakness.
Look for Kim's daughter right now.
We need to take her hostage first.
Sorry?
Yes, sir.
Take her hostage?
Codename 66
entered Myeongpo Port at 23:01.
CODENAME 66
Subject who appears to be Kim Min-ji
sighted at 23:34.
Subject entered the road in question
at 23:45.
It's that car, right?
You sure she got in?
Yes, she did.
I'll track her location right now.
155D 9884
Thank you for giving me a ride.
Thank you so much.
You haven't found her yet?
We can't find her anywhere.
The lead vehicle just passed by here.
You mean the chairman?
We're en route to the villa.
Understood.
Mr. Nam will join us shortly.
The rain stopped.
Jung.
-Do you know what hojae means?
-Excuse me?
Doesn't it mean a good thing?
That's right.
Any factor that provides a good advantage.
It can also mean "good material."
I'll remember that, sir.
An unexpected advantage…
This is proof that Hye-ri
is blessed with good fortune.
She just delivered herself right to us.
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
Where did you take my daughter?
I love and cherish Hye-ri so much,
no matter what mistakes she makes.
Let's just go through them.
Effective immediately, we're initiating
an emergency alert protocol.
Is he trying to start a war or what?
They're both after Min-ji right now.
Fire!
You want to have a shootout?
I can make it
so you never see your daughter again.
You can shoot him
and claim it was an accident.
Min-ji, I'm here.
Let's go home now.
Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim