I don't have any classes today.
[Kim Yunghui: Let's meet up tonight
Senior: It's time to trust your abilities]
Thank you.
Since we both have free
time, wanna go somewhere?
Huh?
Let's eat first and head out.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
What?
Uh...
Yeah
I trust you.
What?
I knew about Kim Jaehyun.
The day my brother died,
there was a strange man beside him,
telling him it'd be okay
and pushing him forward.
By the time I turned back
around, he was already gone
I tried to track down that stranger,
but I didn't even know his name,
and there wasn't a single
trace of him anywhere.
Then...
that stranger was...
Yeah. It was Kim Jaehyun.
We crossed paths by chance,
but I recognized him instantly.
And sure enough,
the people around Kim Jaehyun
started disappearing one by one.
If the same thing happens to you too...
Don't worry
I'm not letting Kim Jaehyun
hurt anyone ever again.
Okay... I'll trust you.
Isn't that Kim Yunghui over there?
Huh?
Ah...
Do you wanna head in first, hyung?
I had something I wanted
to talk to Kim Yunghui about.
Hyung!
Oh, you're here.
Where's Hyunjun?
He went in first.
Ah...
Did you... think about yesterday?
What?
Can't you just take me instead?
That's...
I like you.
So I want to help you.
I don't expect you to feel
the same way about me
I just want us to stay good friends.
That's all.
I'm okay with that.
You're back?
Yeah.
Hyung.
Hm?
How do you think you'd
feel if I disappeared?
What kind of question is that?
I was just curious.
I'd go wherever you are.
I'm not going anywhere.
Hey!
I need to talk to you.
About what?
Not here.
What, you trying to threaten me out here?
I'm staying here, just like you wanted.
But let me ask you one thing.
Do you seriously not feel any guilt...
for what you've done to all those people?
Wow, guilt?
Why?
You want me to feel bad or something?
I see.
Got it.
You piece of shit.
Wait... don't tell me.
Guess you don't know the
underworld's biggest taboo.
I already lost my immortality.
The moment I fell in love
with a human, it was over.
What?
Oh, right.
And one more thing.
Did you know you were
wanted in the underworld?
What the...
[- Hyung, I think I found the infamous
fugitive - You found the fugitive?]
[- Yeah, I'm sure of it... If I alter the
ledger and take him instead... what happens?]
[The original ledger can't be
changed. Once your evidence is verified,
we'll issue you a special warrant
ledger. Upload the evidence]
The one whose name
is written in this ledger...
open the path to the
underworld this instant.
How did you...
Your name has been
called, and your time is up.
No...
No!!
[Yeomra]
You who restored the
balance between life and death,
you have earned the right
to return to the underworld.
Come back home with me.
I've fallen in love with a human
I want to grow old with him in
the human world and die by his side.
And if I die here,
I'll see you then.
You foolish child. This
chance will never come again.
And even if you regret this choice,
it can never be undone.
I won't regret it.
"Fix the Error!"