[Episode 12]
I'm late. I'll take a penalty drink.
I just closed up and saw you from over there.
Li, this is Dragon.
Hello, Dragon.
You can drink!
Looks like Mr. Chen won't drink this glass.
Will you?
No problem.
Dragon, don't make things hard for her.
Excuse me, a bottle of Chinese Baijiu.
We're all out here to have a good time.
Why make it like this?
Dragon, I'll drink this one.
Excuse me, another bottle.
Coming right up.
Dragon, your turn.
Hey, bring some water.
[Lijing Hotel]
Yi.
Lean here first. Bo, go call a car.
Yi, didn't think you'd drink for me today.
Are you okay? Why don't I take you home?
Thank you for today. Go home first.
I...
Li, your car's here.
Maybe you should head back first.
Yi, Li's car is here.
Why don't we take Yi home first?
We've got him. It's fine. Don't worry.
No need. Your brother is waiting
for you at home.
Yong, Bo, take good care of Yi.
Almost there. Hang in there.
What now?
Should I take you to my place for the night?
I'm going home.
Home? Isn't she at your place?
Home.
Careful.
Bye. It's fine.
Look at you, drinking that much.
Are you going to throw up?
I'll open the door.
What? We're almost home. What's wrong now?
I can't go back. I need water.
We're almost home.
You'll have water once you go upstairs.
No. I smell awful. I want water.
Okay. Sit here for a bit.
Hang in there. I'll go buy you water.
Boss, two bottles of mineral water.
- Here.
- How much?
Two yuan.
Aunt Wang, give me a beer.
Get it outside yourself.
Miao Jing.
Bo, what a coincidence!
Thanks.
You drink now?
Work pressure is high in big cities.
Want one? My treat.
You...
What?
Nothing.
Yi had too much to drink.
Let's go.
Yi. Lift your head.
Okay. Thanks for the help. I'll take him up.
I thought you didn't care about Yi anymore.
How could I not? He's family.
Of course I'll take care of him.
Add me. I changed my old phone number.
- Here.
- Okay.
Let me.
- Can you manage?
- Yes.
Try to push yourself up a bit.
- Go home early.
- Sure.
Thanks.
Careful.
That's true. It feels chilly.
Right? Right.
Right.
Okay, still alive.
What are you doing?
Come here.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't go in.
Why can't you go in?
Because...
you're home.
If you're home, I can't drink.
I can't get drunk.
I can't be like Chen Li Bin.
That's bad.
[What kind of person do you hate most?]
I'll be back tomorrow,
before your scores are out.
Pinky swear.
No changing it for a hundred years.
If you break it,
we'll never see each other again.
Don't you get it yet? None of this is real.
Aren't you tired of playing house?
Miao Jing.
Miao Jing, are you up?
Take it for a test drive.
The handling is excellent.
Look, don't let that little scrape bother you.
I'm telling you, seriously, under 60,000 yuan,
this is the best value you'll find.
Qian, are the things ready?
What took you so long?
I had them ready ages ago.
Hold on.
- Li!
- Coming!
How is it? Spacious, right?
Listen, I'll have Li take care of you first.
When I come back, I'll keep showing you around.
Give me a minute.
- Let me check the mileage.
- A little over 20,000 kilometers.
- Over 20,000 kilometers?
- Its main selling point is its agility.
How many kilometers has it actually done?
- What about this one?
- This one?
This is a Volkswagen Polo.
It's equipped with a 1.6-liter turbo engine.
Right. The original price was 80,000.
Based on what you're looking for,
between this and the Volkswagen,
we'd say the Volkswagen suits you better.
Because it's a small car, right?
If you're interested,
we can sit down and talk in detail.
- Let's go.
- Okay, this way, please.
This way, ma'am. Please.
The round table over there.
The car we just looked at is a compact model.
It can fit into any small parking space.
It'll be very convenient for your commute.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
And this one is available now.
You can drive it away right away. No waiting.
What about fuel consumption?
Are all the papers complete?
The papers are all complete.
Insurance is good for another 20 months.
The mileage is under 20,000 km.
Can the local plate be transferred to my name?
My household registration isn't local,
so I'm worried it may be complicated.
Well...
There's a new model of your old lock cylinder.
I found one for you specially.
What's going on?
- This car of ours...
- You're being so mysterious.
Nothing.
around 30,000 to 100,000 km.
No, what is this?
- What's the deal? Why so mysterious?
- Nothing. I just ran into an acquaintance.
- Give it to me. Thanks.
- I'll give you a discount.
No need. Thank you.
Come to me if you need anything.
Okay.
Mr. Wang, how does it look?
Did you talk about price?
50,000 yuan.
Teng City. Long-term stay?
Yi.
What took you so long?
Tell me.
Say, someone arrives in a new city
and immediately buys a car and gets a plate.
What does that mean?
She's planning to stay long-term.
Otherwise,
no amount of money would cover the taxis.
I saw Miao Jing at the car market.
Miao Jing?
Didn't she just come back for vacation?
Nothing she says now is true.
Then why don't you just ask her?
I feel like she's pretty easy to talk to.
I don't have her contact information.
[Miao, Add Friend]
[Block]
[Add Friend]
Are your hands useless?
You two live under the same roof.
You'd have to add me sooner or later.
I'm helping you.
[Hi.]
- Check, please.
- Okay.
How much?
Ten yuan.
Exactly.
[Who are you?]
You didn't add a note when you added her?
Didn't you say you weren't cooking anymore?
Yet you made all my favorites.
Go wash your hands. Eat first.
Where did you go today?
A bar.
Dressed like that to a bar?
Who are you trying to fool?
This beef tastes too gamey, and it's too salty.
Your cooking got worse.
I saw you at the car market.
If you're just here on vacation,
you can drive my car.
Why did you suddenly want to buy one?
Were you following me?
I was getting my car fixed.
You just saw me at the car market,
and now you're cooking for me, all smiling.
You're fishing for how long I'm staying.
Chen Yi, are you scared of me,
or are you avoiding me?
So you never planned to leave from the start.
I finally came back.
Of course I can't leave that easily.
Miao Jing, we're not children anymore.
- Living together like this is not right.
- Oh, by the way,
the window latch in my room is broken.
Can you fix it?
And the bathroom always smells.
It makes me uncomfortable.
You should replace it too.
And every time I sit on this sofa,
it digs into me.
Doesn't it bother you?
One order of fried noodles.
Sure.
[I hurt my hand,
you come back and wash the dishes.]
What are you two now?
I still need to observe for a few more days.
I never said I came back because of you.
I'm hurt.
I'm not lying. I'm really hurt.
The skin broke.
If I'd come back any later,
it would've healed.
I'm used to living more comfortably.
This place is small.
It can't compare to Hai City.
If you feel wronged,
go back as soon as you can.
Don't worry. I won't let myself suffer.
She could have just called a repairman,
but Miao Jing insisted you do it yourself.
If she wants to pick a fight, let her.
When I saw her that day,
I almost didn't recognize her.
She's changed too much.
That sweet girl is now in studded leather.
I need to find a way to make her move out.
Could you find an excuse to stay at my place?
I'll find her a nicer compound.
Either way, get her out first.
Please don't.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
It's mainly that I have a girlfriend now.
You've been through so many major things.
Why are you still scared of one girl?
Five yuan.
Miao Jing, pour me a glass of water.
Yi, something happened at the billiards hall.
What happened?
Didn't we have a fire inspection days ago?
Now they say the observation windows
in our private rooms are undersized.
They demanded to see you,
or they'd call the police.
Yong is panicking at the shop right now.
Our observation windows were installed
by the previous owner.
There haven't been any issues for years.
He's obviously trying to cause trouble.
Miao Jing. I'm heading out.
Boss.
Boss, have a seat.
Stay still!
Yi.
Mr. Chen, you're a hard man to meet.
How about we play a couple
of rounds and talk while we play?
Dragon, with all this backup today,
I don't think you're here to play pool.
You're straightforward.
Then I'll get right to it.
Have you thought about buying in
like we discussed?
I remember making myself very clear last time.
There's nothing to discuss.
Don't reject me so quickly.
Well, the observation windows
aren't the right size, are they?
It's not a huge problem, but
if it gets reported up the chain,
the rectification will be a hassle, right?
I can admit the observation window issue.
But Dragon,
your recent actions won't be easy to explain.
So you're choosing the hard way.
You're all alone,
and we've got powerful backing.
Why make this difficult?
First, pay compensation
and settle this privately.
Then back off and keep your hands off my turf.
Second, you report me to fire safety,
I'll report you to property management.
Neither of us gets an easy life.
Third, you know me.
Sometimes I don't play nice.
Don't do anything rash.
Don't you know I've got a powerful backer?
I only know your heart is racing right now.
- Don't be impulsive!
- My goodness.
This is lively.
Mr. Zhang. Save me.
So this is that powerful backer behind you.
Pull me up.
Remember to pay compensation.
I called to invite you, and you wouldn't come.
I happened to pass by.
Thought I'd come in and see you.
Pass by?
Then my place is truly honored.
Interested in a game?
I twisted my wrist. Can't play.
All right. I won't disturb you, then.
Let's go, Li.
What happened to that billiards hall?
Are they in trouble?
The owner grew up here. He's gang-connected
and used to do business out of town.
He disappeared for years,
and only came back recently.
Where did he go?
Who knows? Probably didn't make it big.
Then why come back acting like a hooligan,
hiding in the old town and refusing to move?
Everyone gets a paid day off today.
Go home and get some rest.
What's wrong? You're not happy about a day off?
Go on. Hurry. Don't hold me up from closing.
Move it. Come on.
Are you hurt anywhere else?
No. I'm fine, Yi.
Disinfect it yourself later.
Don't worry.
Bo, I saw a woman looking around outside.
- Could she be with--
- It's fine.
Clock out.
All good?
Then I'll head back.
- Call me if you need anything.
- Okay. Bye.
Bye.
You're back.
Here.
When did you come back to Teng City?
Why are you asking that?
I just thought when you were at Kuangxia,
you were also following Zhang Bin.
Why does it seem like you're not close anymore?
I left Zhang Bin back then.
Really?
Who've you been with these past two years?