Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
Again, you're running from me.
Following you around
is making me lonely.
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby.
Told me not to love, but I already fell.
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well.
Baby, I’m crush on ya.
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart.
Hello there, my darling.
If you were a laundry,
I'd be your Rinse Charming.
Ready for love,
I have two shoulders for you to lean over,
Even though they feel heavy,
carrying my own beauty (Yep)
I know, I'm just your type, aren't I?
You're so hot like fire (Huh?!)
Because my heart burns for you (Right!)
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love.
Baby, I wanna tell you something…
I love you!
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
Lin Mingyue
and her fiance
have arrived in Thailand.
If I had to guess,
they're using a hideout in Thailand
for illegal drug deals, as usual.
My hotel
is being used by the mafia
to transport drugs?
How could that even be possible?
Well, it is now.
I'm not seeing him anymore.
Who?!
I don't want you to get in trouble
because of my career path.
Thank you
for getting hurt for me.
Can't I come with you?
I'm going back to mine,
so go back to yours.
Please don't worry, Deputy.
We've made a secret deal with the hotel.
What the hell is this?!
Fu!
Moo!
I told you not to make the wedding so flashy!
But I wanna get married!
Did I ever get to have a real one?
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
We're at the scene of a sting operation
targeting major international
drug trafficking syndicates,
who used a luxury hotel
in the heart of Bangkok
as a base of operations.
We'd like to express
our appreciation to the hotel
for its excellent cooperation
with the law enforcement officers.
We've also learned that the hotel's owner
reportedly went undercover
to assist officers in infiltrating the network
in order to apprehend the suspects.
Well, well, well, if that isn't
straight out of a Hollywood detective movie.
Moo,
why are you here?
I told you that
you didn't have to come, right?
Fu!
Tell me.
Why didn't you do as I said?
You're undercover, aren't you?!
Moo!
Fu!
I leth you to dove.
I love you... to death.
Fu! Stay with me, alright?
Fu!
Please stay with me.
Don't leave me!
Fu!
Moo...
Our first kiss in a hospital...
Aren't you happy, Moo?
Surprise!!
Fu, is this the time to be messing around?
We have to pay Ryan a visit.
He's doing fine now.
I requested the best doctor
to take great care of him.
Fu!
Who are you?!
Moo!
Fu!!
Fu...
Fu, don't do this.
Stay with me!
Don't fall asleep, Fu!
Don't fall asleep!
Stay with me.
Ow...
If Mr. Fu wasn't here...
who'd fire those cheesy pickup lines...
right?
Why am I here... just to suffer?
Please stay with me.
Don't leave me!
If you're done over there,
call an ambulance for me...
You're cleared for discharge today.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Ryan,
for risking your life for me
and the one I love.
That's why you got hurt like this.
It's always been my duty, Mr. Fu.
Don't worry about me at all.
Besides, it was just a graze.
It missed...
my heart brimming with joy by a mile.
"Heart brimming with joy," Ryan?
"Heart brimming with joy..."
Mr. Fu!
Moo!
Jang, you're here to visit, too?
Uh...
Yes.
Ms. Jang has been visiting me every day
while I'm in the hospital.
So we're now...
Together?
Jeez, Moo!
Then...
once you're discharged,
I think I'll give you...
a two-week vacation in Koh Samui.
I'll reach out to Golden Coconut
on your behalf.
- Let's go with a suite...
- Wow...
with a beach view...
Jacuzzi!
Can I have a room with a jacuzzi too?
- For my right-hand man...
- Ow, ow, ow...
Yes.
For my right-hand man,
there is nothing...
unattainable.
Aw...
Thank you so much.
And you too, Ms. Jang.
You've worked so hard,
so take a break.
Thank you so much, Mr. Fu.
Jang,
I think...
you're gonna need some nice bikinis.
Whoa...
Bikinis...
By the way, what have you bought me?
- Ooh, here you go.
- What do we have here?
Ooh!
- It's during my hospital stay.
- What fillings?
Filled with my love.
"Your love."
Filled with you guys' love.
Please.
Congratulations
on the Goldentime project, Mr. Fu.
I was wondering why
this penthouse was never up for sale.
I understand everything now.
Anyway, please feel free
to conduct a quality check
at your convenience, Mr. Fu.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Who is this picture for?
It's for Fu.
Well, well, well. Look at you.
Agent Moo-Moo Romanoff.
You've been
crazy in love with Fu lately.
Thank you, you two,
for staying by my side
no matter what happens.
Well...
it's just the three of us.
I'm also happy
you finally followed your heart,
though
it feels a little strange
having you as my brother-in-law.
The Dong family's eldest son's husband, huh?
I bow to you, Royal Consort.
You'll be the first to get executed.
Hey,
Tai.
I swear, that man of yours
has been staring at you nonstop.
Haven't you noticed?
He looks at everyone like that, doesn't he?
Nope.
Oh?
Are you saying
you're quite eye-catching?
Ugh.
Yu are just really attentive.
He... looks at everyone like this.
"Yu", hm?
You mentioned his name
like you're close to him.
Tian, you fucker.
We're not close.
He just... has that name tag on his shirt.
Alright, alright.
In other words,
if you see him again,
does that mean
you're meant to be together?
Meant to be like this.
Meat to be.
- Yeah.
Isn't that right?
Ridiculous!
Here are your sweets.
It's our new recipe,
and our cafe would like you to try it.
Thank you.
Uh...
Are the sweets the only thing to try?
What if
my friend wants to
have a taste of you as well?
Tian!
Are you crazy?
What?
If you end up liking it,
it might cause some trouble.
Since there's only one piece.
I meant the sweet.
Oh...
Bon appetit.
Damn.
That was so sexy.
Tian!
What do you mean by that?
I'm glad I have shitty friends like you guys.
Oh
I'll say this:
if you're going through a shitty situation,
at least you've got shitty friends like us
who'll support a shitty person like you.
You're the shitty one, Tian.
- You're the shittiest.
- You fucker.
Wow.
Oh, I fucking love you guys,
you shitty friends.
You're the shittiest.
Yeah, you're the shittiest.
- Yeah, you're the shittiest, Tian.
- We're all shitty.
Take this.
Wait... Little Chicken,
don't go yet.
Leave me alone for a day.
I'm studying for an exam,
so don't bother me.
Where did the thing I bought you go?
You're not even using it?
I pre-ordered it from Japan, you know?
I never said I wanted it.
Ouch...
It wasn't cheap
and it even looks like me.
See?
Oh.
I want it even less.
Why would I want a doll that looks like you?
You don't have to buy anything for me.
Why would a monster like you
buy something like that for me?
If you buy something for me,
I'll just throw it away anyway.
I don't want it.
I don't want to see your face.
And I don't want anything
that reminds me of you.
I'm sorry.
For what?
For...
Your wound...
has it healed?
It's too late to ask that.
Tee,
this wound
will heal over time.
But the wound you left in my heart
won't heal that easily.
Your custom rings are here, Mr. Fu.
Every ring has been made with care.
So these are
the shapes of my love.
If the universe falls apart.
This heart of mine will find you.
Even if the sky falls or the world ends
I still... intend.
'Cause my heart only beckons.
For you...
I'm sorry...
Would you like some water?
It's okay.
May all the clouds bear witness.
To the love between us.
That never wavered.
Take my hand.
Stay with me until the end of time.
So will you...
Don't spoil it just yet.
I will...
handle the rest.
The poem you've written
is very beautiful.
Right?
Because I'm.
'Edgar Allan Fu.'
The real deal.
My Moo-Moo.
(MR.FUU WILL SEE YOU NOW)
(Location: GOLDENTIME)
Goldentime...
What does that mean?
What is this room, Fu?
It's our room.
What do you mean by that?
This room is called "Goldentime."
I would like to spend
the most precious time
with the person most important to me.
Do you like it?
The room is very beautiful.
You did really well, Fu.
Anyone who gets to stay here
will definitely have a wonderful time.
What if I told you
the only people who can stay here
are us?
You're about to graduate, aren't you?
Yes.
"May all
the clouds
bear witness
to the love
between us
that never wavered..."
You wrote a poem?
"Take my hand and stay with me
until the end of time.
So will you...
marry me?"
My Moo-Moo.
You're about to
graduate, aren't you?
Once you graduate,
let's get married, alright?
Fu...
What does that mean?
Hmm?
Okay.
Tai.
- Hm?
- Your brother really went all out
building a whole new hotel
just to propose to Moo.
Mm.
But it's just the penthouse,
not the entire hotel, though.
Well, if Moo marries him,
the hotel will belong
to him eventually, right?
Mm... you're probably right.
I'm so jealous of him.
How come I'm not
pursued by a prince, too?!
I don't want to be in school
or work anymore!
I wanna be rich!
Someone as slutty as you
really wants to settle down?
I've retired from being slutty.
From now on,
I'll only find true love.
True love? The hell do you mean?
Like...
someone rich.
A prince
or maybe an oil tycoon.
- That bellboy...
- Huh?
Bellboy?
That's an intense shift there.
Ugh! That's not what I'm saying!
I mean...
that bellboy looks familiar...
I'll be back.
Hey, you!
Hey, hey, hey!
You...
Hi, there.
Do you work here?
See my uniform?
That was a dumb question, huh?
What should I do?
Your shirt is all messed up...
Take off your shirt.
What are you doing?
Oh?
Here's a shirt.
Put it on.
And give me the one you're wearing.
I'll wash it for you.
I thought you wanted to...
Have sex with you?
You're so full of yourself.
We've only met twice,
and you're already thinking about that?
I did, since the first time.
You're just...
Right,
we've already met twice,
but I still don't know your name.
Sure you don't.
You were so obsessed with dirty thoughts
that it didn't occur to you to ask my name.
Whoa!
That's brutal!
Right,
my name is Tian.
What about you?
I'm Mark.
Nice to meet you.
Can't say the same.
You could fall
and get someone dirty again.
Thanks.
Now you won't be a burden to anyone.
Please.
Are you looking for me?
No, I'm just thinking about
whether I should order coffee.
Go ahead. I'll make you one.
Uh...
I'm in a rush.
I don't want to be late if it takes long.
No worries, I finish quickly.
Huh?
I mean... I finish making coffee quickly.
Oh, right.
Oh, but speaking of that,
it's still working just fine.
I wasn't gonna say anything.
Do you still...
want to do it inside?
Uh...
You're soaked.
Do you want my shirt for now?
Oh, it's okay.
Do...
Do you wanna borrow my shirt?
Well, do I have to pay?
It's free of charge.
So, should we get it on?
What did you say?
The coffee, I mean.
Right!
Consider it a thank-you.
Sheesh!
This room is so damn cool, dude!
As expected of Lady Moo.
It's fitting that my brother has been
madly in love with you for years.
Did he propose right in this room?!
Yeah, but...
over in that corner.
Aww!
So does this mean
we should start picking out
our groomsmen's suits, huh?
Are you getting married right after graduation?
I don't know.
We'll see how things go by then.
There's almost a year to go.
Mm, so that means you should get started, no?
Do you want us to help?
Are you gonna help or troll?
Jeez,
my friend finally realized
what his heart wanted
and stopped holding it in.
Yes!
We're gonna throw you
one hell of a wedding you'll never forget.
You're scaring me, man.
- Let me have some.
- Hey, let me have some.
- You've already had a lot.
- Hey.
- Go on then, feed me, Tee.
- Look at me.
You've already had a lot.
- Sit down.
- Tee!
- Little Chicken...
- Hey!
I'm the only one who can call him that!
This isn't the time for that!
You might not be able to
call him that anymore.
What are you on about?!
Just spit it out already.
Jeab
is dropping out!
- Huh?!
- Drop out?!
Yes!
I just overheard him talking to the teacher.
Teacher, teacher!
Tee,
you came running over so fast.
What did you get yourself into this time?
Where is Thawin Suthanon?
Wow, full name and everything?
You mean Jeab?
I saw him leave earlier.
Do you know where he went?
I said that I don't know.
Tee,
where do you think Jeab went?
it's you.
My name is... Jeab.
Ow!
This wound
will heal over time.
But the wound you left in my heart
won't heal that easily.
Hey.
I can stay for a bit,
or they'll deduct my pay
and I won't have enough money
to pay for your drink.
I'm just stopping by.
I'll leave soon.
Mm.
Yu,
thank you so much.
For what?
Thank you for always tutoring me,
and not even charging me anything.
You even had to buy me snacks and drinks.
You're like a little brother to me.
Yes, Yu.
So, don't worry.
Okay.
Jeab!
Wait for me!
Don't go!
Little Chicken!
Jeab!
I thought I'd never get to
say goodbye to you.
Why are you suddenly changing schools
without telling me?
Where are you going? Is it far?
Why don't you ever
mind your own business?
I...
I... um...
Cat got your tongue? Spit it out.
I just don't want you to change schools.
Is it because
of me...
Uh...
Me? Changing schools?
I'm just traveling to Japan.
Huh?!
Go to Japan?
Does that mean
we'll still be together in Grade 12?
Will we be in the same class?
Who would want to be with
a monster like you?
Tee,
just leave me alone already.
Okay, I'm fine with anything
as long as you stay.
Is he your friend, Jeab?
Oh, no.
Is he your boyfriend?
What even is that question?
No.
He's not your boyfriend.
So you're not taken, yeah?
Part-time workers here
receive full welfare benefits,
just like full-time employees.
You don't have to worry
because I'm very kind.
And the owner of this hotel, Mr. Fu,
is very sweet and handsome, too.
This hotel has a lot of handsome men.
Oh, God!
How will I
be able to focus on work?
Thank you, Jang.
I will do my best here.
Oh, and don't let work
affect your studies, okay?
Yes.
Oh, wow...
Hey!
What are you doing?
You're just so cute.
Don't you feel like...
No.
Then,
if I want to wake you up,
what should I do?
Kissing your neck?
Kissing your lips?
Or...
Hey.
If you want to do that,
I can set the alarm myself.
Doing this
won't help.
Then...
Why?
I can use my hands.
Tian,
we're not even that close.
I can't do this.
Mark!
You're such a challenge for me.
How long did it take
to make this hotel feel like home
with one big family living in it?
Where there are siblings,
the elders you look up to,
and someone who would
risk their life for you?
You might not always
understand each other
and fight sometimes,
but you always find your way
back to each other.
I'm happy
to be a part of this family.
When you said that...
my heart truly swelled.
Do you remember
what you told me?
"With love, all is as joyous as ever."
"Without love, even perfection turns bitter."
Did you learn how to speak Chinese as well?
I'm so happy.
If you have a close bond with someone,
even when things are difficult,
you can still feel whole.
But without love,
even if you have everything,
your heart will feel empty.
You translated it better than I did.
I used ChatGPT, Fu.
- Go on!
- Kiss!
Kiss!
Kiss...
Kiss him!
- Aw!
- Wow!
Tee Lek, no peeking.
It's all been truly worth it
after spending so long
trying to win Moo-Moo's heart.
Today, he's completely my Moo-Moo,
standing right by my side
and looking at me
with such gentle, loving eyes.
My Moo-Moo!
Little Chicken.
Tee,
didn't you say you'd stop teasing me?
It's not just that
I like to tease you, Jeab.
I like to tease... oops!
I like your rosy cheeks... oops!
I like you... oops!
- That's right!
Woo!
I like to tease you
because teasing you...
it means...
Tee, you monster!
Get ready,
Little Chicken.
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
(To be continued...)
Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart.
Again, you're running from me.
Following you around
is making me lonely.
Again, you're mad at me,
But why do you have to look so lovely?
Oh Baby.
Told me not to love, but I already fell.
Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well.
Baby, I'm crush on ya.
I need a way to flirt with you, yeah
I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart.
Add another hundred
Even when you're ready to leap,
I'll always be ready to love
I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart