‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎TAEUN HOTEL, JEJU ISLAND
‎Three days from now,
‎the US president's youngest daughter
‎will arrive on Jeju Island.
‎She's coming for a week-long vacation,
‎but we've received intel that a group
‎believed to be tied to al-Qaeda
‎is planning a kidnapping attempt.
‎Turns out, she's refusing Korean security.
‎Something about her privacy, I guess.
‎I reserved a room on the floor
‎right below hers.
‎You'll provide unofficial security
‎until she departs.
‎Welcome. How may I help you?
‎I have a reservation for Room 1306.
‎Please give me a moment.
‎Sir, I'm afraid Room 1306
‎is already occupied by another guest.
‎Who?
‎I'm afraid we can't disclose
‎guest information.
‎Okay.
‎Otter One, wiretap in place and ready.
‎Turn off that damn music, you punk.
‎It's loud!
‎You nutjob.
‎Then I'll take Room 1506.
‎Oh, I'm sorry.
‎I'm afraid Room 1506
‎is also occupied.
‎Location tracking is ready.
‎Should I install this in a vehicle?
‎Then I can turn it into a bunker.
‎SAMGEORI TRADITIONAL SOUP AND RICE
‎-Please sit over there.
‎-Okay.
‎Hello.
‎Goodness, you have lovely hair.
‎-A bowl of blood sausage soup, please.
‎-Sure thing.
‎It's been a while, 66.
‎You're drawing attention to yourself.
‎It's my everyday look.
‎What's wrong with it?
‎You look suspicious.
‎Hey, you look more suspicious
‎with that cap pulled down low.
‎Also, we live in a society
‎that values individuality,
‎so you shouldn't judge someone's…
‎Now ‎that's‎ suspicious.
‎That's not suspicious.
‎That's just a crazy punk.
‎Hey, go sit over there
‎and don't embarrass us.
‎Not here. Go over there.
‎Go sit over there, away from us.
‎Damn it.
‎Hey, don't even look at him.
‎Pretend like you don't know him.
‎Enough with the nonsense.
‎We have a mission ahead, Park Jin-cheol.
‎You need to be careful too.
‎Avoid drawing attention to yourselves
‎until the mission is complete.
‎Go change, both of you.
‎Koreans are known as white-clad people.
‎You're full of crap.
‎-Right back at you.
‎-Double right back at you.
‎-Triple right back at you.
‎-Quintuple right back at you.
‎Wrong. You said "quintuple," dumbass.
‎Yeah, quintuple, dumbass.
‎You were supposed to say "quadruple,"
‎dumbass.
‎-You fish-brained idiot.
‎-It's quintuple, dumbass.
‎-I said, "Right back at you."
‎-Yeah!
‎-You said, "Double right back at you."
‎-Then I said, "Triple right back at you."
‎-Yeah!
‎So what comes after triple, dumbass?
‎Quintuple, dumbass!
‎That's enough!
‎I don't know why
‎you two are on this mission,
‎but since you are, don't get in my way.
‎If you fool around like this
‎during the mission…
‎I won't let it slide.
‎Talk about the pot
‎calling the kettle black.
‎Hey, North.
‎Why don't you stop getting in my way
‎and get lost yourself?
‎How about it?
‎Want me to walk you to the DMZ?
‎What the hell?
‎Getting worked up, huh?
‎Your accent's slipping out.
‎"What the hell?"
‎That's just how the hell I am, dumbass.
‎You son of a bitch.
‎Hey, just let it go.
‎Look at him. He's obviously ignorant
‎and has no manners.
‎"Ignorant"?
‎Hey, white-clad.
‎You're a bigger pain in the neck
‎than he is.
‎What?
‎At least he went through insane training
‎in the North.
‎But what about you?
‎You just jump and break boards in the air,
‎you pale bag of bones.
‎Look at that.
‎Guess this is what happens
‎when you only train.
‎You need to work on your social skills.
‎You talk a lot for someone
‎looking like a long-haired female ghost.
‎Stop destroying property and come outside.
‎-Are those your last words?
‎-Just come outside.
‎Bring it!
‎Rock and roll!
‎I thought he said
‎not to draw any attention.
‎Two is better than one.
‎And three is better than two, right?
‎Are you sure about that?
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎Over here!
‎Please stop the car!
‎Please!
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you for stopping.
‎Thank you for giving me a ride.
‎An unexpected advantage…
‎This is proof that Hye-ri
‎is blessed with good fortune.
‎She just delivered herself right to us.
‎Move to the rendezvous point.
‎Dismissed.
‎1 NEW MESSAGE
‎The vehicle carrying Min-ji
‎has cleared National Highway 87.
‎The vehicle is owned
‎by Juhak Construction.
‎Juhak Construction…
‎Did Ju Gang-chan send you?
‎Look, all we did was move her
‎after Ju Gang-chan's daughter called us.
‎Look at who she takes after!
‎She's got her father in her.
‎Han-soo.
‎Min-ji's alive.
‎Thank goodness.
‎Up there. Let's go.
‎Chief Nam.
‎Mr. Cho isn't here yet.
‎He'll join us
‎after taking care of the bodies.
‎Let's go first.
‎Han-soo, can we go faster?
‎This is as fast as we can go.
‎It can't go any faster
‎with two middle-aged men on it.
‎We got her location!
‎It's 274, Musu Mountain!
‎Get her changed
‎and bring her to the study.
‎Yes, sir.
‎-What are you doing?
‎-Oh.
‎I was trying to call home.
‎Do it later.
‎-Ready to get out?
‎-Sure.
‎This way, please.
‎Take a seat.
‎How are you feeling, Min-ji?
‎Are you okay?
‎I didn't recognize you at first
‎because you were soaked.
‎Oh, yes.
‎I'm fine.
‎What on earth happened
‎for you to be out there?
‎Oh…
‎I'm sorry for fighting with Hye-ri.
‎And thank you…
‎for helping me despite that.
‎No.
‎I asked why you were out there.
‎Oh, I see.
‎The thing is…
‎I don't remember.
‎I found myself in the warehouse
‎when I came to.
‎So I escaped.
‎You found yourself in the warehouse
‎when you came to, huh?
‎Yes.
‎What's the last thing you remember?
‎Leaving the principal's office.
‎What happened
‎in the cold storage warehouse?
‎Did you see anyone?
‎Yes, I did.
‎I saw a man who looked like a thug,
‎but I don't know who he is.
‎I'd never seen him before.
‎Did you talk to him?
‎No.
‎He suddenly came at me with a knife,
‎so I ran away.
‎I heard him yelling from behind,
‎but I couldn't hear over the rain.
‎Is that so?
‎By any chance…
‎can I borrow your phone?
‎I'll ask my dad to pick me up.
‎I can't allow that.
‎Sorry?
‎I can't allow that…
‎because Hye-ri tried to kill you.
‎So what should I do as her father?
‎I don't know anything.
‎I don't remember anything.
‎You're still young,
‎so you're bad at hiding your emotions.
‎You're even bad at pretending
‎you lost your memory.
‎I don't know what you're talking about.
‎I knew all along.
‎From the moment you got in the car
‎and pretended to have fallen asleep.
‎An unexpected advantage…
‎This is proof that Hye-ri
‎is blessed with good fortune.
‎She just delivered herself right to us.
‎I don't know anything!
‎I swear!
‎Let go of me!
‎KIM MIN-JI
‎I love and cherish Hye-ri so much
‎that no matter what mistakes she makes,
‎I'd cover them all up.
‎If you think about it…
‎it wasn't a big mistake, was it?
‎So here's how I'm going to wrap this up.
‎Some thug kidnapped
‎a female high schooler named Kim Min-ji,
‎and they went missing together.
‎Now that the thug has gone missing…
‎all we need is for Kim Min-ji
‎to disappear.
‎No.
‎Dad!
‎Please don't kill me! I'm sorry!
‎Please don't kill me!
‎We anticipated as much,
‎but what should we do?
‎We're not here to pay our respects.
‎-Ram through it.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Three unidentified vehicles
‎have entered the property.
‎Who are you people?
‎Do you know where you are?!
‎If you don't leave right now--
‎I don't give a damn where I am.
‎As you can see,
‎we're here on official business.
‎There's a girl inside, right?
‎We need to take her with us.
‎Sir, unidentified vehicles
‎have entered the premises.
‎Hide her in the basement.
‎Please don't kill me!
‎Please!
‎Search the premises!
‎VICE MINISTER OF NATIONAL SECURITY
‎IM DO-HYEON
‎Goodness, Chairman Ju.
‎To what do I owe your call at this hour?
‎I'm sorry, sir.
‎You're here alone,
‎yet you placed a chair facing you.
‎Looks like you had a guest.
‎You're the chairman
‎of Juhak Construction, right?
‎Mr. Ju Gang-chan.
‎Yes, that's correct.
‎And you're with?
‎Let's just say that I'm a civil servant.
‎You don't seem to be with the police.
‎The NIS?
‎Or maybe the SMD?
‎You know a lot for a civilian.
‎You must be pretty chummy
‎with people in government, huh?
‎Then let's stop beating around the bush.
‎I'm the director
‎of the Special Missions Directorate.
‎I'm looking for a girl named Kim Min-ji,
‎and it turns out she's here.
‎I know everything already,
‎so bring her out now.
‎All right.
‎It's fine that you broke through the gate
‎and barged in here.
‎But I hate cigarettes.
‎You little shit. I was being polite,
‎but you're too dumb to notice.
‎Bring out Kim Min-ji
‎before things get messy.
‎Just how much power does the SMD have
‎that you can just barge in here
‎and threaten a civilian?
‎Hey, Chairman Ju.
‎Do you still not get it?
‎My agents are swarming the whole area.
‎We're here on official duty, you bastard.
‎-Did you find her?
‎-No.
‎-We searched the entire second floor.
‎-She's not in the basement either.
‎What's that?
‎Stop.
‎This is private property.
‎Leave right now.
‎We're on official duty!
‎Who the hell are you?
‎I dare you to shoot me.
‎Damn it.
‎Looks like the SMD beat us to it.
‎What should we do?
‎Well, it doesn't matter
‎who came first, does it?
‎-Let's just go through them.
‎-No.
‎The SMD and Ju Gang-chan
‎are both after Min-ji right now.
‎If we make a rash move,
‎it could put her in danger.
‎Then what, are we just going to sit back?
‎Aren't those the agents who helped us?
‎Han-soo.
‎Let's split up.
‎I think you're the one who doesn't get it.
‎-Yes, Vice Minister.
‎-Hey, you bastard!
‎What the hell are you doing there?
‎-Excuse me?
‎-Get out of there right now!
‎Wait, sir…
‎Get up, you punk!
‎Sorry, sir.
‎He's a damn government official.
‎How much in bribes did he take?
‎Goddamn it.
‎Everyone, pull out!
‎SUNG HAN-SOO
‎All clear here.
‎What the…
‎Why, hello there.
‎I'm here to pick up the laundry.
‎You should really press your suit.
‎Min-ji!
‎Are you okay?
‎Are you hurt?
‎What are you doing here?
‎I temporarily closed the dry cleaners.
‎Are you okay? Can you walk?
‎-Who are you?
‎-I'll tell you later.
‎What's going on?
‎-Come on, let's go.
‎-Let's go.
‎Let's get out of here.
‎Good work.
‎-Get her in the car.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Ms. Kim Min-ji, please come with us.
‎-Who are you?
‎-It's okay.
‎Mister.
‎Who are these people?
‎Mister!
‎See you later.
‎Status report.
‎There are no signs of movement yet.
‎Have them watch our six just in case.
‎-We're heading back first.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Everyone will maintain a rear guard
‎until the lead vehicle reaches HQ.
‎Understood.
‎Excuse me.
‎Thank you.
‎But who are you?
‎Where are we going right now?
‎Let me call my dad.
‎If you don't, I'll get out.
‎Min-ji.
‎Calm down. We're going somewhere safe.
‎-Let me call my--
‎-Hang on.
‎Just a moment.
‎We can't tell you who we are.
‎It's the nature of this job.
‎We operate quietly, out of the public eye,
‎behind the scenes.
‎All clear.
‎What the heck? Where'd he go?
‎Where did they take my daughter?
‎Back to headquarters.
‎Min… okay… worry.
‎What's he saying?
‎-Switch channels.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Min-ji.
‎Can you hear me?
‎Everything will be okay. Don't worry.
‎I'm coming to get you right now.
‎You're okay, right?
‎Can you hear me?
‎Min-ji!
‎We can hear you, Kim.
‎If you so much as lay a finger
‎on my daughter,
‎I'll kill you all.
‎Man, times sure have changed.
‎South Korea is such a free country,
‎seeing how a damn spy
‎can threaten the director of the SMD.
‎I said I'd turn myself in
‎once I find my daughter.
‎What a shame.
‎I don't trust the words of a spy.
‎The more desperate person
‎has to give in first.
‎Finding my daughter comes first.
‎Then let's wait and see what happens.
‎I might as well wait with your daughter
‎in the meantime.
‎Why don't you bring a bottle of liquor
‎as a housewarming gift?
‎All right.
‎I'll have a gift waiting for you.
‎Posturing, huh?
‎My heart is already racing
‎at the thought of his gift.
‎I'm not sure if this is right.
‎I mean, using his kid?
‎Jeez.
‎I need to get it together.
‎I'm an agent.
‎I'm not the owner of a dry cleaner.
‎I might be the owner of a dry cleaner,
‎but I'm an agent.
‎This is driving me crazy.
‎ONCE A MARINE, ALWAYS A MARINE
‎KOREAN MARINE VETERANS FEDERATION
‎Damn it.
‎Taekwondo.
‎I should've snapped
‎that donkey leg of his.
‎Salute!
‎Honey.
‎What brings you here, honey?
‎And what's with that knife?
‎You haven't been home in days,
‎so I wondered if you had a second family.
‎Come on.
‎But judging by the looks of you,
‎I don't think you're having an affair.
‎Come on, I'm not crazy!
‎I would never have an affair.
‎You vowed at our wedding
‎you'd have me shot
‎if I ever cheated on you.
‎All right, then.
‎You will now provide an excuse
‎for not coming home.
‎-Proceed.
‎-Yes, ma'am!
‎You know I always make it home.
‎But Kim's daughter has been kidnapped.
‎You remember Min-ji, right?
‎Wait, why was she kidnapped again?
‎Anyway, I was in lockup
‎and got there late.
‎You see, some bad guys
‎insulted our Da-bin.
‎-What?
‎-They said awful things about Da-bin!
‎I should've really thrashed them,
‎but then the cops came and tased me.
‎I hadn't been tased in a while,
‎so it hurt.
‎So then Han-soo went to help Kim,
‎but ended up in the water.
‎I had no idea he was such a bad swimmer.
‎Anyway, I went to help.
‎But I stopped by the service area
‎and got this germanium bracelet--
‎What about mine?
‎This is yours, of course.
‎But I'm not sure if it's effective.
‎Anyway, after crossing mountains
‎and rivers, I came here.
‎Wait, why am I here?
‎Oh, right! Weapons!
‎I came to grab some weapons.
‎So, to summarize,
‎Kim's daughter has been kidnapped,
‎and you and Sung Han-soo are helping him.
‎Yeah! That's exactly it!
‎Goodness, honey. You're so smart.
‎So I was thinking I should go and help…
‎But it's a bad idea, right?
‎I'm sorry.
‎-Who beat you up?
‎-Husband Park Jin-cheol.
‎Go.
‎Go?
‎I can go?
‎They're your brothers.
‎And it's not like I can stop you.
‎I'm craving ‎tteokbokki.
‎Get some on your way home.
‎Level two spiciness, right?
‎Add cheese.
‎Noted!
‎You smell.
‎Change your clothes or something.
‎Goodness gracious.
‎Do whatever you want.
‎Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
‎I'm not worried about you.
‎I'm worried about the guys
‎you're up against.
‎When will you middle-aged men grow up?
‎I love you.
‎Salute!
‎Jeez, that was a close call.
‎I almost died.
‎Seriously, I almost died.
‎Add cheese.
‎Level two spiciness and add cheese.
‎Don't forget to add cheese.
‎Don't forget level two spiciness.
‎Hey, kids.
‎You've been asleep for too long.
‎It's time to wake up.
‎How've you been?
‎I love the smell of gunpowder.
‎All right, then.
‎Now, who should I take with me?
‎Who should I take?
‎Let's see here.
‎If I take this one,
‎then this guy will be sad.
‎But if I take this guy,
‎then this one will be sad.
‎I haven't slept, so I can't seem to focus.
‎All right.
‎Let's grab a Claymore first.
‎And the M3.
‎Definitely the M3.
‎And the M249.
‎M249.
‎Are you disappointed?
‎All right, then.
‎You're coming with me.
‎Right. Let's go.
‎You know what? Let's just all go.
‎All right, we're going on a field trip!
‎Take us to the top-level
‎security building.
‎Yes, sir.
‎-Take her to the interrogation room.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Situation room.
‎Effective immediately, we're initiating
‎an emergency alert protocol.
‎Where's the tactical team?
‎Have they arrived?
‎They'll arrive shortly, sir.
‎I've watched too many action movies.
‎Why did I get under this car?
‎What's this?
‎Even the tactical team is here.
‎Is he trying to start a war or what?
‎Agent Kim said he'd surrender
‎once he finds his daughter!
‎The director doesn't believe him.
‎Until he sees him surrender
‎and get sent to prison,
‎he won't let his guard down.
‎But this is just…
‎That's how much
‎he fears Agent Kim.
‎GOVERNMENT VEHICLE 8769
‎PARKING LOT
‎EVACUATION ROUTE
‎INTERROGATION ROOM
‎HIGH-RISK MONITORING ROOM
‎MECHANICAL ROOM
‎Wait.
‎The interrogation room…
‎ISOLATION ROOM B, ISOLATION ROOM A
‎DETENTION ROOM
‎INTERROGATION ROOM
‎CLEANING SUPPLY ROOM
‎Ma'am.
‎You still work here?
‎It's been so long.
‎It's me. Don't you remember me?
‎Are you okay?
‎You can breathe, right?
‎Okay.
‎I'm really sorry, ma'am.
‎I promise I'll make it up to you.
‎Mechanical room.
‎Let's see. Where's the mechanical room?
‎Mechanical…
‎Which way do I go?
‎This…
‎Is it this way?
‎This way?
‎OIL GEAR PUMP, GENERATOR TANK PUMP,
‎GENERATOR COOLANT PUMP…
‎How many do I need to make?
‎Got it.
‎Now to the interrogation room.
‎Let's go to the interrogation room.
‎Hello?
‎Where am I?
‎Please let me go.
‎Hello?
‎Are you Kim Min-ji?
‎What?
‎Yes, that's me.
‎Why are you doing this to me?
‎Kim Min-ji.
‎Do you know
‎what kind of person your dad is?
‎My dad?
‎What do you mean?
‎He's just an ordinary office worker.
‎Why?
‎Did he do something wrong?
‎Is that why you're doing this to me?
‎Give me that.
‎Listen carefully, Kim's daughter.
‎Your dad used to be a spy.
‎You know what that is, right?
‎Sir.
‎A notorious one at that.
‎So if your dad's identity is exposed,
‎North Korean operatives come to the South.
‎And that puts us in a very tough spot.
‎But you see, your dad stirred up trouble
‎looking for you.
‎The man who spent over a decade
‎living like a ghost
‎suddenly lost his mind!
‎All because of you.
‎Listen.
‎You and your dad
‎have put me in a very bad predicament,
‎so I need to know what started all this.
‎What exactly happened?
‎Why did Ju Gang-chan hold you captive?
‎What kind of scheme
‎are your dad and Ju Gang-chan plotting?
‎You need to tell me the truth
‎about everything.
‎Do you understand?
‎Ju Hye-ri.
‎It was because I fought with her.
‎Who's Ju Hye-ri?
‎The daughter of the chairman
‎of Juhak Construction.
‎I was fighting with her
‎when I got hit by something
‎and passed out.
‎I think…
‎it was a brick or something.
‎When I came to,
‎I was in a cold storage warehouse.
‎And I barely…
‎I barely escaped from that place.
‎But then Ju Hye-ri's dad took me.
‎Let me get this straight.
‎Kim causes trouble for the first time
‎in over a decade,
‎causing the North to send an operative.
‎And you're telling me all this started
‎because of some kids' fight?
‎Man, that Kim.
‎My dad…
‎was a spy?
‎Sir.
‎The vice minister
‎of National Security is here.
‎What for?
‎I think Ju Gang-chan called him.
‎Damn it.
‎Hide the kid.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎VICE MINISTER OF NATIONAL SECURITY
‎IM DO-HYEON
‎Why is this so tiring?
‎I feel like I'm the only one
‎doing the hard work.
‎Is it just my imagination?
‎Just a little bit more.
‎Where are they taking her?
‎INTERROGATION ROOM
‎I just got here.
‎Where are you taking her, you bastards?
‎You assholes.
‎ISOLATION ROOM A
‎Hey, you!
‎What the hell were you thinking,
‎barging onto private civilian property?!
‎Do you want to get fired?!
‎Where's the girl?
‎Min-ji.
‎Kim Min-ji.
‎Up here.
‎It's me, Uncle Han-soo.
‎Uncle?
‎How did you get here?
‎I'm going to open this.
‎So be quiet, okay?
‎You must've been so scared.
‎Let's go see your dad.
‎That's it.
‎Step on that and grab my hand.
‎One, two, three.
‎Bring her to me.
‎Right now!
‎Goddamn it.
‎Are you Ju Gang-chan's lackey
‎or something?
‎Just how much did you get in bribes?
‎What did you say?
‎What do you want with her?
‎Are you going to deliver her
‎to Ju Gang-chan? What for?
‎Does she know something
‎that she shouldn't?
‎Have you lost your damn mind?!
‎You need to get a grip on the situation.
‎Kim is out of his mind right now,
‎looking for his daughter.
‎If you hand her over,
‎it'll be the end for you and Ju Gang-chan.
‎So just shut the hell up and wait
‎until I get my hands on him!
‎Go right. You have to turn right.
‎To the right.
‎Go straight.
‎Keep going straight.
‎I know it's tough.
‎Just hang in there, Min-ji, okay?
‎-Uncle.
‎-Yeah?
‎They said my dad's a spy.
‎Did you know?
‎Your dad…
‎was‎ a spy.
‎He's not anymore.
‎What do you mean?
‎Then what is he now?
‎I'm sorry, Min-ji,
‎but we really have to get going.
‎Can we talk later?
‎-Okay.
‎-All right.
‎Let's go.
‎What's going on?
‎Alpha Tango 312.
‎-Alpha Tango 312.
‎-What's going on?
‎-Alpha Tango 312. We have a situation.
‎-What do you think? We have a situation.
‎Intruder alert. We have a situation.
‎-Possible intruder.
‎-Where are you?
‎The top-level security building
‎is experiencing a blackout.
‎-Restore power now.
‎-We'll begin the recovery process.
‎Send the recovery team.
‎Be careful.
‎Hold on.
‎It's here.
‎I'll catch you from down there.
‎Uncle.
‎Come down.
‎I'll catch you.
‎It's okay. Just trust me,
‎and lower your legs first.
‎That's it.
‎Slowly.
‎That's it. I got you.
‎It's okay. One, two…
‎ZONE C BUNKER
‎ACCESS DENIED
‎What is it?
‎Min-ji.
‎How good is your acting?
‎Hold it open.
‎Let's go.
‎Hands on your head and surrender!
‎Uncle.
‎Damn it, always a little late.
‎-Hey, Sung Han-soo.
‎-Yeah?
‎Are you the gift
‎Kim said he'd have waiting for me?
‎Well, we prepared a gift too.
‎What do you think?
‎Do you like it?
‎Uncle.
‎What now?
‎Min-ji.
‎If you look to your left behind you,
‎you'll see an emergency exit.
‎On the count of three,
‎I need you to run that way
‎as fast as you can and don't look back.
‎What are you talking about?
‎-What about you?
‎-Me?
‎I'm just going to say hi to those men
‎and then catch up with you.
‎You can't do this alone.
‎All right. One…
‎You can shoot Sung Han-soo
‎and claim it was an accident.
‎Don't kill the girl.
‎Two…
‎Uncle!
‎Fire!
‎Three.
‎What the hell was that?!
‎He's always late.
‎Flashbang.
‎Smoke grenade.
‎Attack.
‎Tactical team!
‎Rally at Zone C bunker!
‎Hey, get in!
‎Nice of you to finally show up.
‎It's okay, Min-ji.
‎Why aren't you getting in? Hurry up!
‎How can we get in if the doors won't open?
‎What are we going to do?
‎Damn it.
‎You're shooting blanks, aren't you?
‎They're blank rounds.
‎Hey, take cover!
‎They're blank rounds! Fire!
‎Hey, Min-ji!
‎Oh, for crying out loud! My car!
‎Hey, you should've brought some live ammo!
‎Why did you bring all blank rounds?
‎They caught on right away.
‎I did bring live ammo!
‎But I can't go around
‎killing my juniors, can I?
‎Jeez, my car, man!
‎This won't do, huh?
‎Here.
‎Choose one!
‎I can't choose
‎because I love both of them!
‎-Choose one.
‎-You want to have a shootout?
‎Hold your fire!
‎Hey, Park Jin-cheol.
‎Now what?
‎You want us to continue?
‎This is a white flag.
‎We surrender!
‎We're coming out, so don't shoot!
‎We're coming!
‎Nice and slow!
‎Slowly!
‎Why are there so many of you?
‎All of you just to catch the three of us?
‎I saved you from drowning,
‎and you shoot live ammo?
‎There's a kid here too, you mole rat.
‎You return to your old stomping grounds
‎after all this time, wreck the place,
‎and expect me to sit back?
‎Take her.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎All of you!
‎Drop your guns!
‎What are you doing?
‎I said drop your guns!
‎Dad?
‎Dad!
‎Wait here.
‎Min-ji.
‎I'm here.
‎Let's go home now.
‎Dad…
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎I'm here now, so don't worry.
‎I'm going to witness the end myself.
‎Just take a quick nap, hero!
‎An attempted cover-up and a kidnapping…
‎We should take this chance
‎to get rid of him first.
‎I'm sure you weren't
‎in your right mind either,
‎trying to find your daughter.
‎Today will be the last time
‎Agent Kim sees Min-ji.
‎Dad!
‎For Min-ji's sake,
‎I'm going to
‎end you.
‎Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim