Hizaki Ainosuke.
A college student who has never
experienced an internal orgasm.
It's not like I'm into guys.
I'm just curious.
I just want to know what
an internal orgasm feels like.
But in reality,
I can't find anyone to try it with.
For my first time, I'd want someone
who is gentle and knows what they're doing.
Is it creepy of me to think that?
Huh?
Are you browsing dating apps
in a place like this?
I ran into a groper.
Give me a break.
Are you okay?
Not really.
Let's go, then.
"Are the Sexy Buttocks Not Good?"
(Episode 1)
Sorry for pulling you
off the train like that.
It's fine.
Thanks for earlier.
Don't mention it.
But you know...
Your screen was totally visible.
You should be careful.
Anyone who knows the app
would recognize it instantly.
Huh?
What?!
No, that was...
Oh, by the way, here.
What's this?
Here.
You see, I have a soft spot for cute boys.
So...
Hit me up if you're interested.
What is up with that guy?
He just handed over his number
so casually.
He's definitely a player.
Just forget about him.
Welcome.
Oh.
Thanks for yesterday.
Two lattes, please.
Sure thing.
Hizaki.
And your first name?
Ainosuke.
So you're Ainosuke.
Why did I just tell him that?
What is wrong with me?
It's almost time for the meeting.
Oh, already?
Here are your drinks.
Thanks.
Talk to you later, Ai-chan.
Thank you, come again.
He's a handsome older guy.
Huh?
Is he?
Is it because I keep
touching my butt?
I want to be treated gently
by an older man, too.
Whoa.
Did I just fantasize
about that guy?
Are you kidding me?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
He's not that kind of guy.
See you.
Ai-chan.
Thank you, come again.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- Ai-chan, about tomorrow's shift...
How long are you going to slack off?
Ah...
Ai-chan, Ai-chan, Ai-chaaan.
- He called my name ten times.
- (He comes in almost every day.)
- Ai-chan.
- (He's definitely playing me.)
Ai-chan, Ai-chan, Ai-chan.
Good work today.
Good work.
Ai-chan.
Are you stalking me?!
Of course not.
I'm just on my way home.
My office is nearby.
By the way, did you find your type?
- Huh?
- The app you were staring at on the train.
That was purely out of curiosity.
It's not like I like guys.
Then why...
Because I want to experience
an internal orgasm.
I see.
Want me to help you?
I'm...
really good at it.
(I'm so easy to lead on.
What is wrong with me?)
Um...
You're so tense.
- Come here.
- (But maybe, this is the start of something.)
Aren't you going to put it in, Okumi-san?
Don't you want to climax from behind?
Today, just focus on
your own pleasure.
Okumi-san...
That felt amazing.
(We'll... see each other again, right?)
(That's what I thought.)
(But I never heard from him again.)
(He just vanished from my life.)
(Was I the only one who thought
something was starting?)
(Not that it matters, though.)
I'm so glad I finally found you.
I'm sorry.
I had a sudden business trip
and forgot my personal phone.
I thought you dumped me.
No way.
Why would I dump you?
Was it because sleeping with
an inexperienced kid is boring?
Or something like that.
And you didn't even want to text me.
Of course not.
I had a great time.
But you didn't even put it in.
Is that what you're worried about?
Sure, if I were just a player,
I would've gone all the way.
But...
You're different.
To be honest,
I felt like I was in trouble.
Because you're just too cute.
Shall we finish what we started?
Can I put it in?
I'm going to fall for you if you do.
You're so cute.
Stop calling me cute.
Want to date until you
get tired of me, Ai-chan?
Oh, crap!
Today is my final job interview!
Wait, no!
I have to go!
Come in.
Excuse me.
Well, you're energetic.
(You're the CEO?!)
(Next Episode)
Are you sure he's not playing you?
Just like a child.
It's both worrying and comforting.
Ai-chan.
Why?
Why were you seeing Teramachi
while you were seeing me?
I...
want to know more about Okumi-san.