I don't know
why he's been getting involved with you.
But I think he's probably been manipulating you.
Just like he's done to other people.
The one who's been putting ideas
into your head.
Isn't me.
But it's probably someone who hates me.
I...
want to make a blood pact with you.
I want to ask you
to leave Jane alone.
You do know, don't you,
what someone like me
is capable of doing to you?
That's enough!
Wasn't this necklace  supposed to be a promise
that you'd always tell me the truth?
I'm sure
that one day, you'll be like them.
You..
will be the one crawling back
to ask me for something.
I think..
I did the right thing,
breaking up with him.
Why does it hurt so bad?
Just cry it out.
I'll be right here.
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Ooh
I think from now on
I will believe in myself
because you're the one
who told me to believe in myself
that's why I entered the competition.
I'm glad
that I could inspire you.
(Do you want to delete this photo)
(or remove this picture from this album?)
(Remove from album, delete)
(Do you want to delete this photo)
(or remove this picture from this album?)
(Remove from album, delete)
(This photo has been removed from "Photos on iCloud")
(on all your devices and will remain in Recently Deleted for 30 days.)
(Delete photo)
Babes, I have a surprise for you today.
Today, I'm going to have all of you
switch dance partners continuously.
By switching partners throughout the lesson,
you'll learn
to trust and feel more confident
with your dance partner,
no matter who that person is.
Alright then,
let's start by pairing up first.
Get into your starting position.
Let's start.
And while you're dancing,
listen to me very carefully
I'll give you a signal
when it's time to switch partners.
Okay, babes?
Alright,
everyone, listen carefully for my signal.
As soon as I give the signal,
switch partners immediately.
Ready? Count.
One.
Two.
Three.
Go.
One, two, three.
Have you found time to clear
things up with him?
Gap.
It's up to you.
Whatever you want.
Alright, switch partners.
Ready?
Count.
One, two, three.
If you're ready, then...
Switch partners.
Okay, everyone, switch partners.
Feel confident and smart.
P'Jane.
What are you doing?
Hold on to me tightly.
Otherwise, the dance won't look good.
One, two, three.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
Liar.
I'm just doing the move the instructor taught us.
Unless you're hoping I'll do something else.
Your eyes are giving you away.
They say you want me to do that.
But if you don't want me to do this,
then ask me.
(Thanapat Piboonosot)
Hello.
Why are you here?
I'm here to buy medicine.
What do you need?
The medication set you gave me before has run out.
But I still haven't recovered.
Lately, it's been happening
more often than before.
What game are you playing now?
I'm telling the truth.
But I guess you don't believe
anything I say anymore.
Because you've lied to me before.
You can think of me that way.
But what if I'm not lying this time?
What are you going to do then?
Are you really going to leave me like this
and do nothing?
I'll prepare the medicine my dad recommended.
Thank you.
For still believing me and caring about me.
In that case,
I'll become a regular customer here.
That's enough.
Stop bothering me.
Didn't you tell me before
that if anything happened to me,
I could come here anytime?
Why won't you look at me?
Or are you afraid that if you do,
you'll feel something?
Because he doesn't want to
see your face anymore.
Stop bothering Jane.
And what right do you have over Jane
to tell me I can't talk to him?
Take your hand off.
Hey!
Both of you, stop!
Stop fighting!
Hey.
I'm hungry.
Should we order some pizza?
I'll come back another time.
I'm not hungry.
I'm not in the mood to eat either.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
How did you get here, P'Dan?
I was worried about you.
So I asked Put for your address.
I didn't expect to run into him here.
Good thing I came today.
He's not really sick.
I don't know what to do
to stop him from bothering me.
What about you?
Have you come to peace
with not being with him?
There will be a day.
And until then,
if I ask to be the one who
protects you from him,
what would you say?
Hey!
Why is Little Jane with someone else?
Why isn't he here with P'Jane?
Don't tell me they broke up.
They seemed so in love.
Always going everywhere together.
That sucks.
Well...
If you need any help from me
just call.
I'm sorry
for not believing you.
You can punch me back.
Hey!
I'm just kidding.
Damn!
I was tensed up waiting for the punch.
Your face was pretty funny.
Huh?
I see you're getting along well with P'Dan.
I'm relieved.
Come on.
Let's go!
Would you like a brochure?
P'Dan told me that
he's going to put these photos
in an exhibition.
Did he invite you?
Not yet.
P'Dan knows photography too?
Yeah.
He may not look like it,
but he's got an artistic side to him.
Is it too heavy?
Hey. Actually,
you don't have to help me.
I can handle it.
I wanted to thank you
for helping me with so much.
The photos in the exhibition,
I'm going to let people buy them too.
The money will go to the club.
I had no idea
that you liked taking photos.
The reason I like photography
is because it lets me
capture how I saw the world at that moment.
I think I understand.
For me, it's drawing.
Really?
Have you ever thought about
submitting your work
for an exhibition or a competition?
I did think it about.
But not anymore.
Jane.
Try standing over there.
No way.
Come on.
It'll only take a sec. P'Dan.
Like a candid shot.
Come on.
Stand right here.
Natural?
Yeah, just pretend you don't notice.
Natural, okay?
One...
Alright, natural.
Is it ok?
Yeah.
Keep going.
Hey, try looking over there.
Hey.
Is that a real flower, P'Dan?
Maybe it has to be a bit fuller.
Here.
Thank you.
Uh, P'Dan.
The exhibition concept,
The colors
that remain.
Ah..
What does it mean?
Well..
It's black-and-white street photography.
But they're photos that still feel colorful
even though they're black and white.
Actually, here's a better example.
I take a picture of the sky.
And then..
Here.
We try to turn it into black and white.
Even so, you can still imagine
that it blue.
Oh.
I get it now.
Hey, do you like this one?
Do you like this photo?
Hey.
Yeah, I do.
I look better than in real life.
Can I keep these photos?
Let me edit it first and I'll send it to you.
Okay.
Here.
Let's take a photo.
Whoa.
Very Gen Z.
Okay.
Let me take you home.
Sure.
Are you interested in me?
Since when?
Well...
There was a time when
I stopped playing football, right?
And when I came back to practice,
you encouraged me.
That's all?
It's just...
I don't know if you remember it, but...
to me,
your encouragement meant a lot.
It helped me really get back to myself.
Yeah...
Let's go.
Hello.
Oh.
Hi.
Everyone,
this is P'Dan.
He's a senior from my university.
I invited him to have dinner at our house.
Wait... This isn't P'Big Jane.
Jean.
Uh..
Make yourself at home.
Jane called and told us to prepare extra food.
Yes, ma'am.
Shall we go eat, Mom?
Uh, sure.
Come on.
Let's get the food ready.
They're definitely not just friends.
Excuse me.
Are you closed yet?
Oh.
Not yet. You can still order.
Half a tael of sliced ginseng.
100 grams of Chinese yam, please.
Oh.
Jane.
Could you do it?
Sure, Dad.
Ah..
Come on.
Jean.
Help me set the table.
Okay.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Do you need any help?
Do you know how?
I've never done it before.
But I'd like to try.
Here, P'Dan.
Here.
Thank you.
Mom.
Oh.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wow.
You're good at this.
Next time, you can come help us at the shop.
Mom...
In that case,
I'll stop by and help more often.
You said it.
If everything's ready, let's go eat.
Is there anything else I can help with?
Just a little, help carry the drinks please.
Okay, I'll do that.
Come here, dear.
I'll carry the food.
Then I'll help carry it.
It's hot.
Oh, it's fine.
P'Jane.
What is it?
What?
P'Jane.
It's just that...
Can I borrow some money?
I need to pay for my school's sports day expenses.
I don't want to bother Mom and Dad.
I'll pay you back as soon as the event is over.
Why?
How much do you need?
Fifty thousand.
Huh?
Fifty thousand?
Keep your voice down.
Why are you being so loud.
What kind of sports day costs fifty thousand baht?
What are you even spending it on?
Jane.
Your mom is asking for you.
Is something going on?
They're all beautiful.
So...
Where are your photos?
They're inside.
This whole section is mine.
Wanna take a look?
Oh, look at this.
So cute, right?
You're right.
Yeah.
Oh, this photo is so cute.
Overall..
The compostion is great honey.
Uh...
He really put a lot of effort into these.
Yeah.
I wanted to surprise you.
That's why I didn't tell you beforehand.
What?
To me,
your black-and-white photos
can't hide the colors that exist inside you.
You brought color into my life.
You made it feel alive
in a way I've never felt before.
Isn't that the person in the photo?
Really? It is.
Oh my God.
This one is 3,500 baht.
That's too expensive.
Is the person in the photo
the photographer's boyfriend?
Jane?
You don't like it?
When I asked you before,
you said you liked every photo.
So I chose these.
I like the photos.
But I don't like
having my photos put on display
for everyone to look at without my consent.
And you even put a price on them.
Hey, but all the money goes to the club.
I'm not selling them commercially either.
Didn't it occur to you
that I'd feel like I was being priced?
I'm sorry.
I should've asked how you felt first.
I'll take responsibility for this.
I'll call the juniors and have the photos taken down.
What's up, P'Dan?
Hello, Hot.
I need a favor.
Take down all the photos in the portrait section.
I'm not exhibiting
and I'm not selling them anymore.
Too late, they're all sold out already.
What?
Who bought them?
I'll head over.
Hey, make sure every single photo gets taken down.
Don't display that set anymore.
Hot.
Oh, P'Dan.
Why do you want to take the photos down?
Will there be a problem
with the ones that were already sold?
Who bought them?
I'll tell them myself
that I'm not selling them anymore.
Uh...
It's me.
Yeah...
That makes me want to sell it even less.
I've already transferred the money.
The ownership belongs to me now.
Besides,
the sales agreement never said
I needed your permission.
You're unbelievable.
That mafia mentality of yours never changes.
I was just helping Jane.
You're unhappy about this, right?
Having your photos priced and sold
without being told first.
You put a price on my photos too.
If you don't want me to own the photos,
then let's make a contract.
I'll give them back.
You're not right for Jane at all.
Can you calm down for a second?
And are you really okay
with him taking your photos like that?
It's fine.
Whatever he wants to do with them
is his business.
Hey, Jane, but...
I said it's fine.
If you hadn't put my photos up for sale,
none of this would've happened.
I want to be alone for a while.
(Big Jane: Meet me at the fire escape.)
P'Jane.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I saw that you were feeling troubled,
so I helped you.
I didn't ask you to.
P'Dan was already going to take the photos down.
You should be thanking me.
If someone else had bought them instead of me,
what would you have done?
Anyone would've been better than you.
Why?
What do you think
I was going to do with your photos?
If you don't want me to keep them,
put your fingerprint here.
And I'll do what you want.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you always forcing people?
P'Jane.
Let go.
I'm not forcing you.
You didn't have to come see me.
But you chose to come here.
Oh.
Are you sure you don't feel anything?
Ow.
P'Jane, stop.
If you don't stop, I'm going to shout.
Has Dan ever made you feel this way?
Probably not.
Stop.
If you don't stop, I'm really going to shout.
Then shout.
Let everyone, including Dan, come and see
what you and I are doing here.
You're hurting me.
Let go.
It hurts.
Is this fun for you?
Do you think this is fun for me?
Jane.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Was that him?
Did he do something to you?
Let's get out of here.
Jane, Jane.
Are you okay now?
Yeah.
I think I'd better go home.
I'm sorry.
About the photos.
Forget it.
Let's not talk about it anymore.
Let me take you home.
No.
Jane.
I know this isn't the right moment,
but I want you to know something.
I've liked you for a long time.
Do you remember?
My family went through a rough period.
I had to stop playing football for a while.
But I didn't want anyone to worry about me.
When I started playing again,
I would secretly practice by myself.
But I couldn't get back into form.
Back then, I kept wondering
if I should stop it all.
Football.
School.
Everything.
You're P'Dan, right?
Yes.
I heard you're coming back to football.
Keep it up.
I brought you some water.
We weren't very close.
You probably didn't think much of it.
Keep it up.
You were just encouraging me.
But I've never forgotten
your encouragement that day.
After that,
I kept watching you from afar.
Why are you telling me this now?
Because I don't want to lose you.
Will you be my boyfriend?
I'm not ready to think about that right now.
But I'll think about it.
Then come and give you answer?
You bastard!
Good job.
The finals are next round.
Give it everything you've got.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go, everyone.
Fight!
One, two, three!
Business Faculty, let's go!!
Woooo!
Let's go!
Let's go practice over there.
Yeah, practice.
Let's go over there.
Come on.
Yeah.
Hey.
The football!
Such a tiny football.
Oh.
Come on!
P'Jane.
Leave.
Can't you see everyone's practicing?
Do you really want me to leave?
If you're just here to cause trouble, then leave.
How can you tell me to leave?
Does this field belong to you?
It doesn't belong to you either.
But I can buy it.
Then I can be the one kicking you out.
P'Jane.
Let go.
If I want something,
I always get it.
Including you.
Let go of Jane!!
P'Dan.
How are you?
Ow.
P'Jane!
What right do you have to tell me to let Jane go?
P'Dan has every right.
P'Dan is my boyfriend.
Are you okay, P'Dan?
Thank you, Jane.
Let's go.
Last night...
Yeah.
Wow.
Our friend's really popular.
(Aren't you coming to the exam?)
(Dan: What are you doing?)
(Jane: Nothing, just lying around.)
Jane.
Is something wrong?
No.
I was just spacing out.
Give me your hand.
Thank you for the past month.
Has it already been a month?
Time flies so fast.
This is an amethyst.
The birthstone for people born on Saturday.
Did I ever tell you
I was born on a Saturday?
I checked your Instagram.
Then I looked back through the calendar.
I was born on a Saturday too.
I never knew
that you believed in things like this.
I don't really.
But if we're born on the same day,
it's kind of like wearing matching bracelets, right?
Thank you, P'Dan.
But I didn't prepare a gift for you.
That's okay.
But if I asked you for a gift,
would that be alright?
Hello?
Really?
Okay, I'll head over right away.
P'Dan.
I have to go.
Wait...
Sorry, I really have to go.
Jane, wait.
Jet! Jet!
P'Jane.
Jet, what happened?
What happened?
Please don't be mad at me.
I got into debt from football gambling.
And they came to collect.
When I told them I didn't have the money,
they beat me up.
Debt?
Since when?
Is this why you wanted to
borrowed money from me?
Forget about that.
Right now,
if I can't pay them,
this won't end with just me getting beaten up.
Please help me.
How much do you need?
Fifty thousand, right? I'll transfer it to you.
No..
P'Jane....
1.2 million.
1.2 million?!
Do you even realize what you've done?
At first it wasn't this much.
But I kept betting more.
I thought if I won,
I could use it to pay off the old debt.
But I lost.
I never thought
the debt would grow this much.
When do you have to pay it back?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Where am I supposed to find
that kind of money by tomorrow?
No one's going to lend me that much money.
P'Jane...
What about him?
Your ex!
The one with all the supercars.
Can you ask him to help me?
Please, I'm begging you.
Please help me.
Calm down.
Please, I'm begging you.
Jet, calm down.
(081-148-8776)
P'Jane!
They are calling again!
I'm too scared to answer!
Okay.
This is Jet, right?
You know what'll happen
if tomorrow comes
and you don't get my money.
You know what'll happen, right?
I'm Jane.
Jet's older brother.
Oh? Is that so?
Then come meet me behind the hospital.
No!!
When are you going to pay me back?
You're Jet's brother, right?
You know exactly how much
your brother owes me, don't you?
It's almost the deadline.
He has to give me back my money tomorrow.
I really can't get that amount of money in time.
Could you please...
give me an extension?
I'll pay in installments if I have to.
Installments?
Boss Jeng is a very kind man.
I'll be charging extra interest.
And I'll be taking one of Jet's
fingers each day.
One finger a day.
Until all ten are gone.
And when all ten fingers are gone,
I'll start breaking his arms.
Then his legs.
I'll break every last part of him.
How about that?
If you touch Jet,
I'll go to the police.
If you're planning to report me,
send my regards to the officers at the station.
Because at the station
they all know who Boss Jeng is.
Because Boss Jeng
takes very good care of all of them.
By the way,
I heard your family's pretty cute.
A small Chinese medicine shop.
In a little alley, right?
Maybe when I'm not busy
I'll drop by sometime.
Don't drag my family into this!
Ow!
I told you,
don't raise your voice at me.
I get startled very easily.
You!!
Ow!
Like I said,
I get startled easily.
Let me give you
one final warning!
If you don't want your home destroyed,
you'd better get my money by tomorrow!
Understand?!
But...
Can I please ask for more time?
I swear I'll find the money and pay you back.
Please give me a bit more time.
Fine.
But I think
it's about time
your family's shop closed down.
Because tomorrow...
Ow!
it's going to be
completely destroyed!!
Ow!
Finish him off.
Ugh!
Aah!
Ow!
Hey!
Do you have a fucking death wish?!
Why were you walking in the rain?
What happened to your face?
Let me get you a towel.
P'Jane.
I need to ask something from you.
You're asking
for a favour?
Jet owes money from football gambling.
1.2 million
The debt collectors are going to
destroy my family.
Can you clear the debt for me?
Are you in your right mind right now?
You're sure you want to do this contract with me?
The deal where I can ask for anything in return?
Yes.
I'll do it.
Then our agreement...
is complete.
Let's talk about out contract.
The first rule
is don't be too emotional.
The second rule is
You said you'll belong only to me.
But words aren't enough.
You have to show me too.
Let's break up.
You didn't really want to break up with me, right?
I won't let them force you.
In the end,
you still chose this.
Do you even see me as a friend?
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Ooh
You can paint me with all your darkest sides
And I’d still wear them like they’re paradise
If this love is a perfect crime
Then I’m guilty for life
You tell me,
don’t be too emotional that’s rule no. 1
I’d give up everything to be your only one
Ooh
You’re the only one
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line