I'll leave you, Grandma,
and never come back.
The two of us
have both been running from love.
If I can start over, then so can you.
Can I ask you something honestly?
Why did you help me?
Would you mind if I wanted to date you?
Who is this woman to you?
I don't think we should be together.
Piang.
It's me.
Are you asleep?
Hello?
Where are you?
Hello, I'm from the rescue team.
Do you know the owner of this phone?
What?
She was hit by a car.
Huh?
What?
Where is she?
In front of Saint Che Hotel.
We're rushing her to the hospital now.
CHAI
Why are you calling so late?
Madam, Ms. Piang…
Grandma.
Grandma. Grandma.
Piang.
What happened to Piang?
Grandma.
Grandma, Grandma.
Piang.
Song, what happened?
How did Piang get hit by a car?
-I'm not sure either.
-But you were with her.
Then you must know.
Please calm down, Grandma.
Song, go sit down and rest.
Trust me.
Yes, Boss.
Doctor.
How's Piang?
She hasn't regained consciousness yet.
But she's out of danger.
She suffered a head injury.
But her CT scan shows no brain bleeding.
She only has a few minor scrapes.
She also has a fractured wrist.
Once she regains consciousness,
she'll be able to go home.
But for the next week or two,
please keep a close eye on her.
If she develops a headache
or starts vomiting,
bring her back right away.
Sometimes brain bleeding
doesn't show up until some time
after the accident.
It can be delayed.
But it doesn't happen very often.
Try not to worry too much, Song.
Doctor, you know me?
Of course I do.
Piang has told me about you.
I see.
Then you two must be really close.
Not really.
It's more like I was forced to.
Do you want to know
what Piang said about you?
No, thanks.
But I think you should know.
Is the patient okay?
Yes, they're safe.
I'll take you home.
Namking.
There's something I need to tell you.
What is it, Piang?
I already like someone else.
Even if we keep dating,
I'll never fall for you.
Okay.
Same here.
What?
Namking, you like someone too?
No, it's just…
I don't plan on liking anyone.
As you can see,
my work keeps me very busy.
If I had a partner,
I don't think I'd take good care of them.
But I'm curious.
If you already like someone,
why did you go on a date with me?
Or… were you just doing
what Grandma asked?
That's part of it.
But the person I like,
doesn't feel the same.
So I thought I'd try opening
my heart to someone else.
Did it work?
No, it didn't.
That's why I wanted to be honest with you.
Do you remember the woman we passed
after leaving the party?
That was her. Her name is Song.
And I'm deeply in love with her.
She's my first love.
Then…
I think you should give it one more try.
Piang said you don't like her,
but what I see says otherwise.
You're worried about her,
and you're uncomfortable
seeing me with her.
If that's not love, then what is?
Don't run from your own heart.
And if you're worried about Grandma,
I'll find a way to help you.
There's no need.
I heard every word.
I'd like a word
with this young lady alone.
Do you understand now
why I've been trying to keep you away
from my granddaughter?
You're not only unworthy of her,
you diminish her worth.
You can't even protect her.
I just don't understand
how Piang could ever fall
for someone like you.
Then please give me just two weeks.
Just two weeks to stay by Piang's side
and take care of her
until she's fully recovered.
After that,
I'll never let her see me again.
You've said that before.
But you never kept your word.
This time, I promise.
That woman promised me
she'd stop seeing Piang.
But she asked for two weeks
to care for Piang until she's recovered.
Okay.
Don't you have anything to say?
No.
I'll leave it to your judgment.
If that's all, I'll get going.
Mudmee.
Yes?
-I slapped you…
-I know, Grandma.
And now that woman has broken up with me.
You won't have to worry anymore.
I won't disappoint you again.
Piang.
How are you feeling?
Song.
Don't lift it.
Your wrist is fractured.
If you need anything, tell me.
My head hurts.
Is it bad?
Do you feel like throwing up?
The doctor said it'd be
like this for a while.
As long as it doesn't get worse,
there's nothing to worry about.
Hang in there.
Why did you go out by yourself?
Didn't I tell you to come get me
if you needed anything?
It was already late.
I didn't want to bother you.
You always make me worry.
So you finally admit you worry about me?
Yeah.
I do worry about you.
I'm so happy.
I never thought I'd hear you say that.
Could you say it more often?
No.
No one says that all the time.
It means there's always
something to worry about.
Then use a different word instead.
What word should it be?
How about using your own name?
I like it when you call yourself "Song"
instead of "I."
It just feels warmer.
When did you hear that?
You really want me to say it?
Well…
When we slept together.
You don't have to say it.
I know.
Hello.
I'd like to speak with my granddaughter.
Of course.
I'll be back, Grandma.
Mm.
Grandma, why are you here?
Or are you here to make me
feel even worse?
I don't feel anything.
I'm here to make you a deal
about that woman.
The more I tried to stop you,
the worse things got.
I'll let you date her.
What?
But there's one condition.
You have two weeks
to make her fall for you.
If you can't,
then accept the truth and let her go.
Why two weeks?
Because when you're chasing someone,
you should set a time limit,
not chase them forever.
If she's really going to love you back,
then two weeks should be
more than enough time to decide.
Do we have a deal?
Deal.
Good.
Careful.
If you throw up a lot tonight
or get a bad headache,
call me right away.
Okay.
So… you're really not staying
with me tonight?
I'm afraid I'll bump your wrist
and hurt you.
Just two weeks.
Let me stay with Piang
and take care of her
until she's fully recovered.
After that,
I'll never let her see me again.
You have two weeks
to make her fall for you.
If you can't,
then accept the truth and let her go.
-Oh.
Where are you going?
What about you?
I was on my way to see you.
Song.
I want to get out of town.
I don't want to stay
cooped up in this room.
Please.
Fresh air and beautiful scenery
might help me recover faster.
What a coincidence.
I was about to ask you too.
-You mean…
-Let's go together.
Why did you choose this place?
Do you remember when I told you
my parents brought me
to see the sea of mist?
This is the place.
Where's the mist? I don't see any.
All I see is smoke from forest fires.
And the PM pollution.
Song.
What? I was just asking.
That was during winter.
It's summer now.
How could there be any mist?
Even without it, it's still beautiful.
Because it's full of memories.
You forgot again.
I'm sorry.
I ruined the mood.
I'm the one who should be sorry.
I wanted to comfort you,
but I didn't know how.
I've lost someone in my family too.
Even now, whenever I think of them,
I still can't fully move on.
Then I guess we feel the same.
If you want to comfort me,
you don't have to do much.
Just wipe away my tears,
and I'll feel better.
Then cry again, so I can wipe your tears.
Song.
You're awake?
I am.
When did I fall asleep?
Right after you took your medicine.
These meds…
I'm throwing them all away.
I'm not taking them anymore.
Why are you being so stubborn?
I'm not being stubborn.
I just don't want to miss
a single moment with you.
If we sleep, we sleep together.
And if we shower,
we shower together.
After saying that,
why are you still just standing there?
So we don't have to
sleep back-to-back anymore?
Piang.
Don't be naughty.
You're still injured.
Does that mean
once my hand is healed,
you won't stop me anymore?
Hold on. I need to take this call.
Where are you?
I'm out of town with Piang.
What? Seriously?
You just got out of the hospital
and went on a romantic trip?
It's not like that.
Piang just wanted a change of scenery,
so she asked me to bring her here.
And you said yes.
Song, did you tell her about it
and work things out?
No.
What's wrong with you?
What are you waiting for?
I'm not waiting.
I just don't have much time left with her.
I don't want any more drama.
I'd rather spend
the time I have left well.
What?
I've got to go.
Here's your hot spaghetti.
-Here.
-Is this Chef Ploy?
-Does it look good?
-It looks amazing.
Homemade bacon, mushrooms,
sauce, everything's homemade.
You're the ultimate food researcher.
So what did Song say?
She said something strange.
Something about not having much time left.
Like she's counting down
the time she has with Piang.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Why don't you eat first?
You can't worry so much
about your friend that you forget to eat.
That's not good.
Okay.
Then feed me.
Just now, I used up all my energy
worrying about my friend.
-Really?
-Mm.
Get up.
I'll feed you. Come on.
I'll give you a huge bite.
-Go on, feed me.
-It smells so good.
Does it?
Looks like I'll eat it tomorrow.
Here.
So that's how you want to play?
-How is it?
-Delicious.
-Really?
-Mm.
Of course it is. I made it.
My turn.
PLE PIJIKAA
SOMSAK2511
Is something wrong?
No.
Okay, let's keep eating.
Here, some fresh salad.
-How is it? Is it good?
-It's delicious.
-I picked it myself.
-I like this one better.
You spilled it everywhere.
-It's all over you.
-Come here.
Piang.
Can I sleep with you?
We came all this way together.
We can't sleep separately.
-But your wrist…
-Don't worry about hurting me.
Even if we sleep apart,
it still hurts when I toss and turn.
I've endured worse when you did it.
I even liked it.
Piang.
Please, Song.
Let me sleep with you.
Please.
Okay.
Then get back into bed.
Let's go.
Sleep carefully.
I don't want to hurt your wrist.
What does "sleep carefully" mean?
Sweet dreams, Song.
Wake up.
I've been awake for a while.
Then why haven't you gotten up?
I want to stay like this a little longer.
But my arm's gone numb.
Then I'll get up.
But promise me first
you'll sleep with me again tonight.
And every night after that.
How many nights are you planning to stay?
Until you finally…
finally…
say yes to me one more time.
You may not be worried about your wrist,
but with that cast,
you can't really use that hand.
But this hand still works.
And…
Are you running away because you're shy?
No.
I'm going to take a shower.
If you want to shower together, hurry up.
So we can head out.
Okay.
It's so beautiful.
It is.
It's so beautiful, it feels like a dream.
Thank you for bringing me here.
I'm so happy.
I hope we can come here together again.
Song.
Would you like to dance with me?
I can't dance.
I only know how to dance in clubs.
Then I'll lead.
I'm actually really good at it.
-Really?
-Mm. Really.
My grandma loves dancing.
So she had Mudmee and me
take dance lessons since we were kids.
Our teacher even became
close friends with Grandma.
Now she often invites
our teacher over for dinner.
Then they dance together afterward.
Come on.
Can we dance with just one hand?
We can.
There are many kinds of dancing.
Let's go.
Song.
I don't know…
how you'll feel if I say this now.
But please let me say it.
I love you.
Let me do it.
I told you,
not to use this hand.
Song, what are you doing?
You'll see.
Keep your wrist like this.
Don't lower it.
Or I'll stop.
And…
be patient.
Until I'm satisfied.
The Mega Excellent Awards are next week.
The ceremony will be on the rooftop.
Song, don't be afraid.
I'll be there with you.
-Today I'm wearing a polka-dot look.
-You went all out?
-And yours are black and white.
-Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's head up, Song.
There are many VIP guests here.
Behave like the company's heir.
Go with Grandma first.
I'll catch up.
Go on. Don't worry about me.
-Yes.
-But you made it happen.
-Madam President.
-Yes.
Hello.
-Hello, Piang. Hello, Boss.
-Hello.
Ploy, call Song.
Why isn't she here yet?
The award ceremony is about to start.
She has to go accept the award.
Hurry.
-Hurry.
-Hello.
Welcome, everyone,
to the 2026 Mega Excellent Awards.
This event is hosted by
126 Food to honor outstanding employees
and boost everyone's morale.
Did she answer?
-She's not picking up.
-Then text her.
Where is she?
Song is never late. She's so responsible.
She's not replying either.
Without further delay,
please welcome our president,
Duangphamorn Chatpimuk,
to present this year's
Outstanding Researcher Award.
Please give our president
a warm round of applause.
-She's not replying.
-Put your phone away.
This year's Outstanding Researcher Award
-goes to…
-Ploy.
She's not answering her phone.
What do we do?
Miss Sadanun.
From Research Team B.
Is Miss Sadanun here?
Song.
-I'm sorry.
-Neung.
I really can't stay. I'm sorry.
Don't forget your promise.
Please come up and accept
your award, Song Sadanun.
Hey, someone fainted!
Hey!
Song!
Song, what's wrong?
You're okay. I'm here now.
Song.
Song!
-Song!
What's wrong?
Why did you suddenly collapse?
Piang, get Song out of here first.
I'll take care of the award.
Okay. I'm counting on you.
-Song.
-Song, are you okay?
It's okay now, Song.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
I told you,
I'd protect you,
just like you protected me.
By now, your grandma must…
It's okay.
I'm more worried about you.
Do you remember
when I told you I lost a family member?
I do.
She was my twin sister.
Her name was Neung.
She chose to end her life on a rooftop…
eight years ago.
And I was there too.
She left this world in so much pain.
Not only could I do nothing to help her,
I was part of that pain too.
Did Neung tell you that?
No.
But it's true.
I keep having the same dream
almost every night.
And whenever I go somewhere like that,
it all comes back.
It's as if she's always reminding me
that she left this world in pain.
So I don't deserve to be happy either.
Song.
I don't know what really happened,
but if I were Neung,
I would never think that way.
I would…
forgive my little sister
and wish her happiness every single day.
Because I know
I would never get that chance again.
Do you really think so?
I do.
Even though I never knew Neung,
I believe she felt the same way.
The reason you still see Neung
is because your subconscious
still blames you.
But it's okay now.
Please stop blaming yourself.
Song, go ahead and cry.
Let my shoulder catch your tears.
Yes.
Who is that?
Dad.
Wait.
You're not even going to welcome me?
It took me forever to find you.
Looks like you're doing just fine.
Song is feeling better now.
Dad, just go.
-I don't have money for you.
-I don't buy that.
It's only twenty or thirty thousand.
How could you not have it?
I'm your father.
You're not my father.
Ever since you and Mom abandoned me.
Ple!
Don't you dare lay a hand on me.
I'm not Mom. I won't let you.
What the hell are you gonna do?
I'll fight back.
-You'll fight me?
-Yes.
Let's see how tough you really are.
You ungrateful bitch.
Why?
Ple. Don't!
-Who the hell are you?
-And who are you?
-What do you want?
-I'm her father.
I want money. Do you have any?
Ploy. Don't.
This is all I have. Take it.
If you need anything else,
come to me instead.
And leave her alone.
Is she your girlfriend?
You're damn lucky.
Ple.
Are you okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm here.
Why are you crying?
It's just a scratch. I'm okay.
Ploy.
Let's break up.
What?
I can't take it.
I can't watch you get hurt
because of me again.
I know my father.
He'll do it again.
It's just a scratch. I'm okay.
It's nothing.
But it's not to me.
Ple.
We both helped Song and Piang
find their way to each other.
So why, when it comes to us,
are you the one letting go?
Let's get through this together.
Please.
Okay.
If you really want to break up,
then okay.
But let me say one thing.
The pain you're facing now…
you've overcome it before.
Don't let it hurt you again.
Take care.
Song, get some sleep.
I'll stay right here with you.
I was supposed to be
the one taking care of you.
Now you're the one taking care of me.
That's okay. I want to.
I like doing it too.
If my hand weren't injured,
you'd be eating my
chocolate muffins already.
Haven't you learned?
I threw away the whole box last time.
Then I need to keep baking.
Until you finally eat one.
So when will your hand heal?
I don't know.
Then wait for me.
Don't go anywhere yet.
Get some sleep.
Oh.
I have to go to the office today.
I have something to take care of.
Then can I come with you?
I want to stay by your side all day today.
Why today?
It's nothing.
I just… want to be with you every day.
Wait here for me.
I'll just grab my bag.
Let's go.
Boss.
I'd like to resign.
It's been two weeks already?
So you knew about it?
Mm.
But…
I'd like you to think it over again.
Follow your heart.
Forget about that promise.
Let me…
be the only one who suffers.
I want to see my little sister happy.
I've made up my mind, Boss.
All right.
If you've made up your mind,
I'll respect your decision.
Thank you, Boss.
I'll get going now.
Why are you standing here?
I told you,
I'd stay as close to you as I could.
Song.
Can I ask you something honestly?
All this time…
we've spent together…
Have you ever felt anything for me?
Felt…
what?
Do you love me?
Why are you asking me that?
I just want to know.
Please don't stay silent.
This…
is my answer.
Okay.
I understand.
I give up.
Song didn't choose me, Grandma.
Go to sleep, Piang.
Just think of it as a bad dream.
I think you should ask yourself, Grandma,
whether what you want
or what Piang feels matters more.
When we're around other people,
I think we should pretend
we're still together.
I've shared your pain, Neung.
You don't have to bear it alone anymore.