[Sin and Love]
[Episode 1]
In just 2 years,
the buildings have gotten taller,
and there are more people.
But Seoul is still the same.
[Sung Ho, Inspector]
Keep the speed at 100.
Requesting permission
to land at Seoul Airport.
to land at Seoul Airport. Over.
The places where light cannot reach
are often the darkest.
In the past, I wanted to be a good cop
recognized by the public.
But what I really should do
is not stand in the sunlight,
but actively step into
the darkness where no one
is willing to set foot.
And then in there, become
a ray of light for someone.
[Kim Minho, Lieutenant]
Sung Ho
just arrived.
The special training
ended earlier than expected.
The special training was supposed
to take 10 years,
but he finished it in just 5.
His return this time...
doesn't seem like just a simple return.
[One hour ago]
[Yoo Sehyun, Boss of Gangnam Palace]
[Kwon Hyukjae, Senior Superintendent]
I can't do this anymore.
It's been 5 years.
How long do I have to do this?
I want to return to the police force.
All right.
I'm kneeling to you too.
We are both kneeling to each other,
so it means nothing anymore.
Got it?
Are you joking with me?
Does it look like I'm joking?
I
am asking you
when can I return to the police.
Do this for another 2 years.
Got it?
Officer Kwon.
To you,
am I just a tool
for your promotion?
Damn it. So darn dirty.
Come here.
You suit places like this.
You built this place with your own hands,
right?
Sehyun.
There are important guests
coming in a few days.
Prepare well for me.
Both men and women.
Yes.
Sung Ho
just arrived.
The special training
ended earlier than expected.
The special training was supposed
to take 10 years,
but he finished it in just 5.
His return this time
doesn't seem like just a simple return.
Okay, got it.
I'll be right there.
Hey, look up.
Officer Kwon.
What do you have against—
Sehyun.
You know Sung Ho, right?
I heard he is the ace of the headquarters
who just came back
from the special training in the US.
I heard he's your first love.
[30 hours later]
I really hope we get something.
All right.
Follow me.
Search according to protocol.
Don't mess around.
Yes, understood.
Police!
Please cooperate with the search.
Officer Sung Ho.
Long time no see.
Sehyun.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
I'm reading.
Who would suddenly...
Fine.
I'll show it to you.
One, two, three.
Did you see it?
I'll show it...
Got it.
Fine, I'll let you listen to music.
Nah!
Wanna listen?
Fine.
Sehyun.
Ta-da!
This isn't just milk.
I...
Fine.
Take a sip.
I said take a sip.
The straw recognizes its owner.
This thing actually...
Okay, okay.
I'll stop messing around.
It's good.
Say "ah."
Stop filming.
You've filmed long enough.
It's been over a minute.
Stop.
Save me.
Help me.
Please.
Save me.
Are you crazy?
I'm on my shift.
You...
don't remember what happened back then?
Sung Ho.
If you don't help me now,
it's over.
What are you doing now?
Sung Ho?
What are you...
What are... you...
Minho.
You go out first.
I'll handle this here.
Close the door.
I told you to close the door!
Y-Yes!
Understood!
What's going on?
Those two...
The special training wasn't all that.
Officer Kwon.
I'm back from patrolling
the Gangnam district.
Any findings?
Nothing special.
Including Gangnam Palace,
there were no issues.
Where's Sung Ho?
He's still at the scene.
I came back first.
It's your first time out
with Sung Ho, right?
How was it?
Sung Ho...
He's a neat worker
and he deduces quickly too.
I don't thing there was anything special.
Got it.
Go back.
Yes,
understood.
Nothing special, huh?
Impossible.
Sung Ho and Yoo Sehyun.
This is just the beginning.
Aren't you going to explain?
Sehyun.
It's been 5 years.
It's been 5 years,
and this is your gift to me?
My ex-boyfriend
finally came back as a cop.
How is it?
I built this place myself.
Let's talk about work.
Did what I do to you
made you uncomfortable?
Or
did you not want me to stop at all?
Let's talk about work.
Work.
You always use that as an excuse.
Does wearing this uniform
wipe away years of feelings?
Do you become cold
when you wear this uniform?
Enough.
You go your way,
and I'll go mine.
Get out.
Wait a minute.
It's been 5 years.
Do you know how I've held on until now?
It's been 5 years!
Did you ever look for me?
I've been looking for you all along.
Don't do this.
I'm not prepared yet.
Why did you leave me?
It's because of you.
Five years ago,
why did you leave me?
Because I didn't want to break your heart.
What do you want right now then?
You.
Can I take your uniform off?
Police!
Is anyone inside?
[Sin and Love]