Previously on  Dating Alys Perez.
Oh, Baby Ethos!
How're the wedding preparations going?
A bit stressful.
Good thing Drake's really
hands-on with all this stuff.
One in a million, that he is.
Good thing I found him.
Alys,
he waited for you.
He's doing fine.
He's happy together with Cristine.
I'm asking you to not
make trouble for them.
Alys is not nice.
You make Drake cry.
Alys is bad.
Enter your 4-digit code
after 00, then press #.
What was their anniversary again?
I remember it’s same as ours.
Verification failed.
Drake's birthday!
0, 1, 2, 2, 9
Verification failed.
No!
- Drake wouldn't make that his passcode.
- 0, 1, 1, 3, 1
He has a fiancée.
Unlocked.
0, 0, 1, 1, 3, 1
Weird.
It's an office but
nobody’s here.
What is this? A storage room?
Drake?
Nobody's here.
I'd better leave.
I might see something strange.
Hey, Silly!
Look who's talking!
Look behind you.
You're messing with me.
Sorry.
I couldn't help it.
So, when are you coming back?
Soon.
Come on, I asked when,
and all you said was "soon."
When will you be here, Silly?
I'll just have to surprise you.
When is the surprise?
Silly, you're here!
Drake, what the hell?
Hello? Zy?
Hello?
-What the hell?!
-Zyril?
Hey! Are you still there?
Silly, I'll call you later.
I'm busy. Bye!
But —
What’s wrong with you, Drake?!
Never do that again!
I can't promise that.
We missed your 20th birthday.
Remember when I told you,
that I'll let you have my
body on that special day.
- Why did you slap —
- Asshole!
It was well deserved, Drake.
You're a pervert.
How dare you mention
my 20th birthday
when you left me when I was 18?
You freakin', freakin’ jerk!
What the hell is
your problem, Drake?!
Why show up now?!
What the hell do you want?!
I was minding my own business.
Now, you're starting this mess!
What are you trying to prove?
Does this make you happy?
Is this what you want?
- Is this how you want things?
- Sshh!
You still love me,
don't you, Alys?
I don't love you anymore!
Then we’ll figure it out, Noob.
No, Alys.
Don't let him trigger your anger.
It's just a simple pet name, okay?
There's no reason to overreact.
Are we doing this all over again, Drake?
I don't want you anymore!
Alys, how many times
do I have to tell you?
I won't give up until
we're together again.
You're nuts, Drake.
There's something seriously
wrong with your head!
My mind's a beautiful place, Alys.
Because you're the only one in it.
I won't destroy what Tripp
and I have just for you.
You're just
not worth it.
You're not worth our
beautiful memories.
Congrats, Alys!
Congrats Zyril Fatty!
Watch your mouth!
Congrats, Silly.
Of course!
You two should
have believed in me.
Seriously, congrats, Silly!
We're so proud of you.
Especially that
you took culinary classes.
I'm sure you'll do great at it.
And not just any culinary school,
it’s in Paris!
Wow.
It already went to her head!
It's the truth.
I have a right to flex
because this time,
I did it without the
help of my parents.
I really want to make
a name for myself.
And this time I want to achieve
everything because of my own skills.
Not because of my family's influence.
Fine.
You’re the best!
I’m the best!
So?
Where to next?
Las Vegas, baby!
Woohoo!
What?
Las Vegas.
Fatty...
and deaf.
Hey!
That's enough, Tofer.
He called me a fatty.
No, no, you're not fat.
- Vegas!
You know, that's getting annoying.
You're all cuddly but
when people ask,
"Oh, we're just friends!"
Oh no!
Is Baby Tofer upset?
Tofer, Tofer...
And that too!
I'm not your baby!
What are we? A happy family?
You're the Dad and she's the Mom?
Really...
You think you're just friends?
You're not really a baby.
More of a manchild.
Chill, Tofer. Relax.
Man, you're making this hard on me.
Tripp...
What's the deal
with you and Alys?
We're... uh...
Friends!
- Mhm!
- We're friends!
Friends, friends...
Fudge, fudge!
Dude!
I'm going to ask you straight.
You love Alys, don’t you?
So much.
You finally admitted it!
Whoo!
Oh no.
No matter how many years have passed,
no matter many times I reject him,
no matter how much I cry to him,
no matter how much I tell him
I'm being hurt because of his cousin,
he still loves me?
What about you, woman?
I'll ask you straight.
Do you love Tripp?
Stop thinking about me, Drake!
Because I...
I stopped two years ago.
I can't imagine it.
The thought of forgetting
you drives me insane.
You stole my heart.
And I don't plan on taking it back.
It's your choice.
Make me or break me.
I'm done letting you fool me, Drake.
The Drake Palma way of making me fall?
Bullshit.
You're just gonna make me
fall just to hurt me again.
I choose to break you, Drake.
That's my choice.
Break me.
But I'll never get tired of loving you.
At first,
when you appeared
out of nowhere
and told me I was your boyfriend.
I didn't mean to believe it.
I didn't mean to fall.
But I've already fallen.
And it's hurting me.
It hurts so much.
God, Drake, you exhaust
me way too much.
Alys...
Hey, Alys.
Why?
Why?!
Hi, Silly!
Tripp!
How are you, Zy?
What are you doing here?!
This is for you.
Thank you! It's so cute!
But what are you doing here?!
It's like you don't want me here.
Come on.
That’s unfair!
You didn't even tell me?
You just had to surprise me?
Chill, Perez.
Can't I get a kiss first?
Eww...
You guys are so disgusting!
See?
Now, you scared Dane away.
It's your fault.
You love me too much.
It’s so pressuring.
So you think I'm funny now?
Because you’re so dramatic!
You're the one who said
you love me so much.
More than anything, right?
Of course, Zy.
More than anything.
So, are you hungry?
You look like you just arrived.
You smell like the airport.
Cook for me, Silly.
I really miss it.
Okay!
- I’m hungry.
- Let's take Mini Tripp with us.
See? He looks like you.
So you're mean now?
Let's go.
You're such a bully.
Silly!
What do you want to eat?
Filipino food, Silly.
I've had enough of the food there.
Are you even eating?
Well...
Why did you let Tofer
come with me to Paris?
Look what happened.
You had no one to help
you cook your meals.
Hey.
I still eat.
Really?
Let me see.
Liar.
You've lost your chubby cheeks.
Eat a lot, okay?
What is it now?
I'm sleepy.
Let me sleep.
Oh no. Let me cook for you, first.
Come on.
I've been travelling all day.
Let me sleep, Silly.
Later. I’ll cook first.
I’ll never finish this.
Fine.
But I’ll get a kiss first.
Okay, go now.
Alright.
I'm really sleepy.
I'll be on the sofa.
Wait. Do you want to sleep
in my room?
No, I'll be fine here.
Okay.
Sleep well.
Marco...
Wake up.
Let's eat, my love.
Wake up, Marco.
Come on, wake up.
Come on, the food's really good!
Wake up, please.
Let's go.
Come on.
- Let's go!
- Okay, Zy...
Let's go!
Come on.
Alright, I'm up, Zy.
I'm up, Silly.
Come on, let’s eat.
I'm up.
Time to eat, Marco.
Here’s your Filipino food.
Adobo, rice,
foam cake, soup
and of course,
freshly squeezed-- oopps!
Freshly-made cucumber juice.
Looks good, Zy.
Thank you.
Eat up!
Marco, by the way,
why are you here already?
You were supposed to arrive
the day after tomorrow.
I missed you, Silly.
Is that not reasonable enough?
May I have some juice?
Sure.
Can we meet tomorrow?
Sorry, I can't.
Mmm! It's good.
Anything interesting?
You're playing with me again, Drake!
Enough!
I love you, Alys.
Can't you feel it?
I feel it so much that it's killing me.
Fuck you, Drake!
Fuck you!
Fine!
You love me.
Am I supposed to love you back?
Is that how it goes?
You loving me means
I have to love you back?
Well, if that's the case, it's still a no.
I will never love you,
Drake Palma.
Not now.
Not someday.
Not ever.
I loved you, Drake.
I loved you!
More than I loved myself!
More than anyone else!
But what did you do?
You broke me into tiny little pieces!
You devastated me
beyond repair, Drake.
You crushed every hope
I had left in my body!
Please...
Please Drake, just let me have this.
Loving you was a mistake.
You started all this.
You played Seducing Drake
when we were in highschool.
So face the consequences, Alys.
Because I'm here to stay.
Hey.
Silly!
I said,
anything interesting?
Nothing.
After you eat,
you should go home and rest.
Okay?
What?
Ouch!
You're sending me home?
Stupid.
You'll see lots of me.
But for now,
go home and rest.
You look freaking tired.
Okay.
You will need all the
energy you can get, Marco.
Drake won't leave us alone.
I'll just finish all of this.
- Okay.
- I'm kidding.
What? Finish all of it.
Be strong, Tripp.
For me.
For us.
Bestie,
isn't it too early
for all that work?
Bestie...
You might overwork yourself.
I saw Kent yesterday.
So?
Oh, come on, Aya!
Don't you feel bad for him?
He said he's been pursuing you
but you keep turning him down.
So what?
You're on you witchy stage again?
Come on, Alys!
Don't you know better?
Didn't you and Drake break up over —
Well, I don't actually know why.
But I never pestered
you about it.
Extend the same courtesy to me!
Jeez, Aya. Okay, fine!
I won't...
I won't intrude anymore.
It's just that I feel bad for him.
Give him a chance.
At least talk to him.
He likes you big time.
And plus, you know he's good for you.
You know that.
He changed you for the better.
Bestie, you have to calm down.
You'll get overworked.
I'd rather be overworked than have
time to think of that Drake Palma.
I saw Tripp yesterday.
My god, Alys.
I knew he looked good, but...
Damn, he's gotten
even more handsome.
So, you’re crushing on him now?
Really, Alys.
Oh, come on, Aya. It's fine.
I'm used to people
being attracted to that Silly.
I remember when we were in New York,
I can't believe so many people
are into that silly guy.
Tofer and I call his
fans club the United Nations.
- United Nations?
- Yes! Imagine...
Europeans flirt with him,
then there are Americans
and the Asians.
But mostly Asians.
He's something else.
That silly guy just has a certain appeal.
He's really handsome.
So who am I to blame you?
I get you.
Okay, fine, fine, fine!
- See?
- He is my crush.
Can I really resist?
That boy looks freakishly good!
I know.
- Right?
- I know, right?
I'm so lucky.
What is his secret, bestie?
Don’t tell anyone, okay?
Well, the thing is...
What is it, bestie?
What?! Tell me!
Well, the thing is...
Hi, Ma'am.
Here's your coffee, Ma’am.
Thank you.
On my way. Sorry.
Just running a little late.
Hey!
- Silly!
- Hey, Silly!
I was just about to call you.
Where are you?
At a restaurant.
I'm waiting for a client.
- Silly?
- Hmm?
We have a...
reunion coming up.
But if you don't want to go,
that'd be okay.
Oh, jeez.
The last time the Palma clan saw me,
I was Drake's girlfriend.
Now, after four years,
I'm going as Tripp's girlfriend?
Really, Alys?
Playgirl much?
Of course I'm going. Why not?
Don't you want me to go?
Why? Are you ashamed of me?
Crazy.
Not at all.
I love you, don't I?
More than anything.
Anyways,
I'll be working out, Silly.
I'll pick you up later.
Okay, Marco.
Bye.
I love you. Take care.
Alright, Alys.
If she's not here in
15 minutes, go home.
Alys! Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry!
Well, I had to attend an
unannounced last minute meeting!
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry, Alys!
It's okay.
Well, anyway...
Are these the goodies?
Yes, these are the baked goods.
Uhm...
By the way,
is your mom coming too?
Oh, about that...
Can I like
uh... just
drive you there?
My mom can't make it.
Sure, no problem.
I can't let her miss out
on tasting my baked goods.
Okay, sure, sure!
The car will be here in a moment.
I can hold these.
Thank you!
Uh, by the way, Alys...
Say, if you were to be married,
how would you want
your gown to look like?
Huh?
I mean...
What do you mean?
I mean how would you
envision your gown?
Well, of course, I want
it to be beautiful.
With a long trail.
I don't know but I fell in love with
Bella Swan's wedding gown.
That type of gown.
So beautiful.
It's gorgeous. It's so pretty.
You get it, right?
Yeah!
So that kind of gown.
Why does she seem interested
in the gown I'd want?
Weird.
And where do you want to get married?
Honestly,
anywhere would be good as
long as I'm with the person I love.
But I hope it's a beach wedding.
I know right?!
You know, I keep on telling
Drake about beach weddings.
He says the sand is rough on the feet.
All the other sorts of excuses.
That guy is so picky!
You know,
a wedding is a bride's affair, darling.
If you want to have a beach
wedding, have a beach wedding.
So...
Beach wedding.
Mhm.
Sorry.
Hello?
Yeah, she's with me.
What?
You're coming over?
What? No!
Drake, what's with you?
Oh, noes!
He really can't leave me alone, huh?
You'll take Ethos with you?
Fine!
Yeah, you'll have to thank
Ethos for this, weirdo.
Alright, bye.
Uh, so...
Alys, there's a situation.
Drake's gonna be there as well but...
I think it's fine, right?
I mean he told me
you were highschool
classmates or something.
Yeah, highschool classmates.
And many other things...
Shall we?
After you.
Can you hold on to this, okay?
Alys, let's go!
Thank you.
Mom?
Here, Honey!
Mommy!
Hi!
I’ll do it.
- Hi, Honey!
- Thank you.
Hi!
Thank you so much.
We have a guest.
Is she Alys?
I’m Alys Zyril Perez.
Nice to meet you, Madam.
Nice to meet you, too, dear.
Please sit down.
Let's go, let's go.
What are your credentials?
Oh!
I initially studied Advertising in NYCU but
I had to stop to pursue my real passion.
So, I studied in Paris
to take Culinary Arts
Major in Pastry and Baking.
Wait,
is this a job interview?
I thought
this was a taste test,
and then we'll sign the deal?
Impressive.
My daughter finished her
undergrad at St. Collete's.
And had her MBAs at Harvard.
Hi, Auntie!
Drake! You're here!
- How are you?
- Baby Ethos, come here!
I’m okay.
How are you?
I'm doing fine.
A little tired from Ethos.
Oh, okay.
Looking good.
Thank you, Auntie.
I missed you.
- Nice to see you.
- Nice to see you again.
I think my mom has a crush on Drake.
She's mad at me for marrying him.
Baby Ethos, I missed you!
Did you miss me?
Okay, kiss!
Okay, kiss Godmother Alys too!
No!
No?
Ethos, you want? Cakes?
No!
Okay, Alys. He’s just a kid, okay?
Don’t take it personal.
He is Tripp’s cousin.
Okay!
Okay, you sit here, okay?
Just play with your helicopter, okay?
Just stay safe.
Okay?
Drake, I told you!
Beach wedding!
Alys said she likes beach wedding, too!
Okay.
Yay!
Okay!
And about the wedding dress,
Palma,
I'll change it, okay?
Okay.
Oh wait, Alys,
I forgot to tell you.
We have a problem.
So, our wedding planner
scammed us.
He cancelled and since
you're hands on with the preps and...
you're friends with Drake,
can you please step up for us?
Please!
Uh...
Uhm...
Great! Okay!
Silence means yes!
Thank you so much, Alys!
You're really my savior!
Thank you, thank you so much, Alys!
Oh, Ethos!
My baby!
I have so many lollipops in my room.
Wait, why is this
happening all of a sudden?
I'm done.
I'm leaving.
What?
Are you going to the reunion?
Tripp invited me.
Don't go, Alys.
Please.
Don't go.
Why, Drake?
Give me one good reason.
Because...
Because the next time
you see the Palmas,
I'll introduce you as my wife.
You'll only confuse my
family as Tripp's girlfriend
but my future wife after.
Please, Alys. Don't go.
As far as I'm concerned,
I'm not a wedding planner.
But why the hell am I
planning Drake's wedding?
My god. How did they get me
to agree to this?
Did I feel bad for them because their
wedding planner cancelled last minute?
Oh my god, Alys.
What did you get yourself into?
- You're here!
- Silly!
What's with the long face?
Hi, Silly!
Have you been here long?
I'm sorry, Silly.
It's all Cristine's fault!
You could cancel.
Cancelling is not an option.
This is important to me.
And plus she's super nice.
As for her mom,
she gave me a huge job.
I'll be serving pastries
in her art galleries,
and it's one of the finest.
So this will be my biggest break.
That's great.
But...
If it's taking a toll on you,
you can always say no.
Not really.
I think I'm just overwhelmed.
Okay!
I think I'm done for today.
Mushy much?
You're just so busy now, Perez.
You don't have time for me anymore.
Well, that's why we have dinner later.
Unfortunately,
Tofer's coming.
Why are we taking Tofer?
Your cousin really misses you!
Take some responsibility, Marco!
Come on.
You're his favorite cousin, right?
Play nice.
Okay.
Fine, Silly.
I love you, Silly.
I love you, too.
What?! No!
Don't send them a freakin' notice!
I'll arrange for that!
You got that?!
Copy?
Good.
Oh, geez!
You should really control
your caffeine intake!
It's too much.
How long were you standing there?
Just long enough for me to hear
your supposed assault.
Who is that, anyway?
Stalker.
Disgusting.
Not my type at all.
Really?
You sure?
Tripp!
Geez!
You’re hugging me too much!
Oh, man.
Are your sure that hug is for me?
You don't have to be mean.
You guys are really a couple.
Hey, I'm not as mean as you!
So? Let's go!
I'm starving.
Come on.
Let's go!
Who’s the couple now?
You left me behind!
So annoying!
Hey!
Ma’am, here are your slippers.
Thank you, Manang.
Hello?
Alys?
Sorry to bother you with this.
But I'll be going to
Paris for a convention.
And I won't be back until
the day of my marriage.
Please coordinate with Drake instead.
Wait.
Hold on.
Am I hearing this right?
You're leaving then coming back
on the day of your wedding?
I'm sorry for this. Really!
But this is really important.
Is she mental?!
She's leaving then coming back
for the wedding itself?
Wait, can't we just...
you know, push the wedding back?
This is a big deal, Cristine.
You have to be here!
Oh, no, no...
The date will be the same.
I'll just be gone for a bit, Alys.
You could still call me.
It's just my physical presence
won't be there anymore.
Please coordinate with Drake instead.
Thanks a lot, Alys.
And I really have to go now.
Bye!
She just hung up on me!
Cristine's gone.
It's you and me again, Alys.
Hello, pseudo bride.
Make your groom happy.
You ready?
What the f —
SOS!!!
Oh!
I thought this was an S.O.S?
Which market are you going to, Perez?
What are you wearing?
Why?
What's wrong with this?
I'm wearing crop top and shorts!
Is that what being on the market is?
Well, you don’t know
anything about fashion.
You’re so annoying.
Get over it.
So much for fashion—it looks cheap.
Cheap my ass!
What is it now?
Gosh, your car smells good.
It smells like strawberries.
Of course.
It’s strawberry-flavored scent!
That’s why!
It smells amazing.
Hey! Stop that! Stop that!
What are you doing?!
Eww!
Stop!
You're disgusting! Eww!
You’re mean to me!
What's so gross about smelling
things with my eyes closed?
You're like...
I don't know.
It's a disturbing image!
Ugh!
Stop that!
Your face should be censored!
- Okay! Fine, fine!
- It’s gross, Alys!
I won't close my eyes!
It’ll just be wide-eyed forever!
You'll look insane.
I'm about to go
insane on your ass.
Yeah, whatever.
Just shut up and drive.
You know too much.
Come on, let's go.
So?
What's up?
Keep it coming!
Whoa!
Looks like you’re geared up.
Oh, take it easy!
I really needed that.
Okay.
So, here's the thing.
Drake and Cristine are
getting married, right?
What?!
Don't tell me you didn't know.
That's news to me!
You had no idea?
No!
Married?
- Really?
- Yeah!
They're like tying the
knot in less than a month.
Wait, wait. To who again?
Cristine Ann Stinson.
Ring a bell?
Here's what I know.
So, supposedly,
Cristine was Drake's bestfriend
in their college days
when Shaira went off to migrate.
Go on.
I don't know.
But...
Everybody seems to really like Cristine.
They like her for Drake.
Hold that thought.
Have a shot first.
Cheers!
The real question is...
Do you like her for Drake?
Sure!
Of course!
Drake and I?
We're over.
Come on.
We were probably never meant to be.
Maybe he was meant for Cristine.
Oh my gosh.
Really?!
Alys...
It's true!
Really?
Tofer, I'm 22.
Okay?
Sure,
maybe I was happy with
flirting and thrills back then.
But...
It's different now.
It's so different now.
I want assurance.
I want constant love.
I want consistency.
Do you get me?
Do you understand?
Sure, fine.
You can say that
Drake did make me feel like my heart
was gonna jump out of my chest.
But that was when I was 18 years old.
Come on!
He left me when I was 18.
And now, he wants me back at 22.
That's just not gonna happen.
That's not how it works.
I'm 22 now!
And wiser.
I'm 22 and so freakin' in love
with Tripp Marco Palma.
His cousin.
Well, when you say it like that,
it sounds really weird.
Because it is weird!
No, it's not!
But I gotta give it to you.
Your answer though,
straight out of a beauty pageant, like...
“And I... thank you!”
- You rehearsed that. Didn't you?
- I did not!
For your information,
I can be profound if I want to be.
Profound?
Doesn't suit you.
Shut it!
In all seriousness,
Alys...
Tripp
loves you
very much.
I know that!
Tripp loves me and I can feel it.
Then, good!
So you should know the
consequences of your actions.
And how your decisions
have impact.
Listen.
You'll break him, if you leave him.
But you'll destroy him,
if you leave him for Drake!
Do you get that?
I know.
Okay.
So?
Are you leaving Tripp for Drake?
What the heck?!
It’s so early to ruin my day.
What time is it?
Oh no, I'm late for the meeting!
Ouch!
My god.
My head hurts!
Damn that Tofer!
He got me completely drunk!
Should I call in sick today?
I mean I do feel sick.
No, Alys!
Let’s be professional.
We can't lose like this!
I'm on the way.
You have five minutes, Alys.
One... two... three!
I said I'm on my way!
Please coordinate with Drake instead.
Thanks a lot, Alys.
And I really have to go now.
Bye!
You're really leaving?
Yes.
It was scheduled a long time ago.
I mean,
even before the wedding preps.
This convention is already set.
Can't you still cancel it?
No way.
And I already told Alys to coordinate
with you on the wedding.
So behave, Drake.
Please.
Are you really sure?
That sad boy routine
won't work on me.
I'm already stressing making
the perfect wedding happen!
Would you let me,
at least, enjoy Paris first?
Look, I really have to go now.
Okay?
Bye now.
Cristine's gone.
It's you and me again, Alys.
Hello, pseudo bride.
Make your groom happy.
You ready?
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
No, thanks.
Good morning to you, too, Alys.
Come on.
Cristine and I aren't even the same size.
So you're telling me that
you're fat?
Excuse me?!
Ms. Alys, the gown might get ruined.
Shut up!
On the count of three,
you're gonna zip it up.
I don't care if it splits.
You're going to do it!
Why would you agree
to be wedding planner
for your own ex?
Right?
Same old Alys.
So?
Where’s our next destination?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to pick up Ms. Stinson's gown.
I'm taking it to Batangas.
You'll forever be a martyr.
Can you feel it, Alys?
Can you feel it?
That's the heart of a man
who's obsessed with you.