Burger Mcjo?
Burger McQueen?
And he has a background
in forensic accounting.
He is assigned to track down the money.
So we can use his expertise
to map out their financial network.
You did nothing.
You let Isabella decide for our daughter?
Whatever she wants, let's give it to her.
Agent Alex, these are all the files
you asked for from me.
You're already working?
You're such a workaholic.
So I hope both of you will behave
while I'm working.
I can't do this anymore. I hate this.
Now Agent Alex is our babysitter, too.
Sorry, sweetheart. This is my fault.
If only I hadn't come up with
our ice cream date.
Then we wouldn't have
another person watching us.
I know you only did that to make me happy
and you did make me happy,
so thank you very, very much.
I'm just annoyed because
I can't control the situation.
There you go, sweetheart.
Just keep walking.
As they say, walking helps lower
your cortisol levels.
Which are your stress hormones.
So that's good.
I have an idea!
What?
If Agent Alex wants to stay here with us,
then she should be willing to put up with
whatever she ends up hearing.
Blah-blah-blah.
Just kidding!
Sweetheart!
Yes?
You're so funny!
Of course, I know! I really am!
You're really something, sweetheart!
You know me!
Sweetheart!
Oh, boy!
The spicy part has started.
It's like an island tropic,
and the best part
is there's a third wheel,
who isn't really a third wheel.
Because she can't say
that she's loving him too much.
Heart-stopping.
Break it down.
What, are you rapping over there?
You know you're here to work.
Not to gossip about everyone.
I'm just telling the truth, and besides,
you're the real gossipers here.
You installed CCTV cameras in their room.
It's for safety reasons.
All I'm saying is,
if you really want to know
what they're doing,
then go to the security room.
Two lovers trapped inside the room.
That third wheel is intense.
Jealous but can't admit it.
She's so mad at me, it's crazy!
I have no idea what she's going to do.
She's thinking hard, she doesn't know
what she's going to do.
She's coming down, here she comes!
Things are about to get chaotic!
We really are perfect for each other.
Hey!
-Bro, how are you?
-Hi!
I missed you so much.
-I missed you so much!
-Gosh…
Come here.
Wait, why are you guys here?
Isn't it obvious? We're on vacation!
But how did you know where we were?
It's not hard to find.
Actually, everything was posted
on Sofie's Fishbook.
Seriously, with complete details!
Complete details?
So you saw our exact location
just from that?
Because of Sofie's post?
Oh, Angelito.
That's the power of social media.
Yes.
And you, Sofie,
your profile is really easy to stalk.
If I were you, I wouldn't post
too many details
or your real-time location.
Everything I post is safe, and besides,
it's all on CF.
What's CF?
Close Friends.
Just kidding!
It just means only friends can see it.
That's what Close Friends means.
I'm not really on Fishbook.
-I'm more of a TokTok guy.
-Obviously.
You know what,
I'll invite you to my house. Let's go.
I'll introduce you to my parents.
-Hey, let's go!
-I'm so excited!
Okay!
How do I click this?
-Just hold it.
-Hold it?
-I hold the clicker?
-Yes.
Like this?
Alex, you're not doing this to gossip.
You're doing this because
you just want to know
what they're doing
without alarming anyone.
Who am I kidding?
Why is there no feed?
Here, it's not working.
Do you know why there's no feed in Room 1?
Did the camera break?
They probably covered it again.
I just checked that earlier.
Those two are really something, huh?
Look away for just a second,
and you'll get played.
-Look at that Isabela.
-Please show it to my followers.
Like an Italian,
food vlogger.
Doing mukbang.
Jeez.
Oh, my gosh.
Who would think
that's a big-time mafia boss.
If she lived a normal life,
maybe she'd be in the food industry.
Fair enough.
If she's going to stay here,
Viktor,
maybe we can charge her rent?
Exactly.
-Things are expensive these days.
-True!
And she eats a lot.
We can use her rent fee
to pay for her food.
Maybe around,
-70K for monthly rent.
-Right.
-Period.
-Okay.
Would you like to try our banana fritters?
-Oh, please, thank you.
-She's always hungry.
Sorry.
It's okay, I'll handle it.
You're pretending again,
but you're also interested
in what the two of them are doing.
Welcome to Big Sister's house!
Again, I'm just doing my job.
Try lying to someone else.
You know,
it's natural for the two of them
to be doing that.
That they're "doing stuff."
Doing stuff?
Playing Jenga.
If they're both bored,
I also have a way to make
things interesting in this house.
Okay?
Mikoy, seriously!
Not there!
-I'm here!
-Stop! Sweetheart, not there!
-Sweetheart!
-Yes?
You're so funny!
Of course, I know! I really am!
You're really something, sweetheart!
Mikoy, I told you to stop!
We're just playing.
-Ouch! That hurts!
-Oh, does it hurt?
Sweetheart!
Sweetheart, really!
Wow, I'm exhausted!
Me too.
You know, pillow fights
are actually fun, huh?
Don't you have slumber parties
for pillow fights?
No.
There's no such thing for the poor.
Slumber means overnight, right?
We don't have that.
We don't do overnight, only overtime.
Overtime work,
so there's food for the next day.
And the pillow fight?
Oh, please. Try getting hit
by our hard pillows.
Let's see if you can still get up.
So dramatic!
It's true!
The pillows you see in that house?
The soft ones?
Oh, please.
Those are from everything
I worked for in Prague.
So you know, I'm really lucky I met you.
Because
you really changed my life, somehow.
I should be the one saying that.
Who would've thought that one day,
I'd be fighting for my freedom.
I could only dream about it before,
but now it feels like,
it's within reach.
You know what?
Why are you so sweet?
Did you do something?
No!
Come on, I just said "I love you"
and suddenly I'm guilty?
Because usually I'm the one
who says "I love you" first.
I go first.
I don't know about you.
All right, I'm going
to take a shower, I feel sticky.
Wait, are you sure?
Don't you want round 2?
All right then, fine, never mind.
Go take a shower, I'll drink some water.
Okay?
What happened?
I was just changing the light bulb.
I'll help you.
No, no, it's fine.
Can you turn it on?
Okay.
There!
Hey, hey!
What is happening?
This is because Alex was changing
a light bulb and lost her balance.
Good thing I was here to catch her.
You know?
I feel like I've seen that before.
What are you doing here, sweetheart?
Well I think I also need a drink.
You want juice?
Sure.
Okay.
Alex, are you okay?
Of course.
Tess!
-Tess.
-Yes!
Yes, Captain Pepe?
Looks like someone wants to apply
as a baker again.
Again? Who is it this time?
What happened to the motorcycle?
The battery keeps dying.
I just fixed that yesterday.
Oh, no, it's Angelito again.
You know, it's Angelito's friends,
they're considered friends
of the Pinagpala.
So it's fine, we're good here.
Okay, thank you.
-Let's go inside.
-Okay.
So, what? Introduce them, come on.
Mom. Dad.
By the way, this is Laurence
and this is Luisa Mae.
-Hello.
Laurence is my roommate in the dorm.
And this is Luisa Mae--
Wait, let me guess.
Luisa Mae is Laurence's girlfriend?
You're a couple!
No, we actually have more
of a connection with Angelito.
Do you want to go see our oven?
Let me show you how we make
the special torta.
Let's go.
Mom, dad, we'll just go inside. Let's go.
I'll give you a tour here. Come on.
-Excuse us.
-We're going.
-We'll stay there.
-Okay, then.
Come on, let's go!
Here.
Honey, you know,
that might actually
be the trend right now,
dating someone else's partner as your own,
and then, well, it's legal.
I think that's called
an open relationship.
Kids these days, really.
Right?
I guess back in our day, that existed too.
We just didn't have a term for it,
for the label, right?
I think
I may have underestimated Angelito.
Angelito? Why?
He's still into it.
Look at you being a father.
Is the oven getting hot?
It's rising.
Oh, what a hot oven!
Do you see those?
Those are the tortas Sofie baked.
Cool, right?
It's just that the shape isn't perfect
but it's delicious.
Wow, teach me how to bake too.
I want to bake something for you.
Okay sure, when do you want to?
Tomorrow?
Wow, with Luisa you say yes right away,
but with me it's a lecture first.
Isn't he sweet?
He's always like that when it comes to me.
Like he can't say no.
Don't worry.
I'll be the one saying yes to you.
Whatever you order.
As long as it's not math.
That's Angelito's specialty.
Really?
You'll say yes to anything?
Of course.
You already made me say yes, didn't you?
But it would be better if,
I could also make you say yes.
Wait, wait.
You're kinda vague.
Chow!
Tongits!
I win again!
If this were a reality show
and this was the task…
I'd always be the winner.
Again?
Wait, wait, are you cheating?
You've been at it!
You always win!
I knew it!
It's boring if he's
always the one winning.
Exactly!
Right?
There's a lot of waiting here.
And even more hiding.
La Morte Bianca already has the bomb.
Meanwhile, we're just here fixing
a busted lightbulb, right?
We need to wait for all
law enforcement agencies to align
before we make a move.
Because if we act now,
there's a chance of a misencounter
with other police units,
or even the military.
And since the threat is national in scope,
we need to update everyone at the top.
And that's why the government
will always be a step behind
when it comes to criminals.
Okay. Op! Op! Op!
Let's pause the discussion for now, okay?
I'm going to get some drinks!
I'll come with you.
Okay, let's go!
Open up where?
Come on!
It's only now that
I'm really getting to know you.
You know, for an agent,
you're not that good at hiding, huh?
The first time I met you, you were
just pretending to be Mikoy's friend.
Mikoy!
So.
Did you mean it?
When you said,
that Mikoy loves me very much.
That I don't need to worry.
That I should feel secure
in his love for me.
You have nothing to worry about.
Mikoy loves you very much.
Or…
was that just one of your lies?
Because, between two women, Alex,
What do you want to wish?
I wish
that we can be free.
No agency. No Concordat.
Just the two of us.
In our own world.
Did you find them both?
Not yet.
But we sent some people to check the place
where we think they're hiding.
Report to me once you find them.
It doesn't matter who or how many
have admired him.
The important thing is, he chose me.
And he loves me.
Then in that case,
you have nothing to worry about.