[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 31]
Tian Xing,
take these over.
Here, Suyin.
This is a kind of pastry
unique to Jing City,
called "Reunion Cake."
It's specially made for
the Autumn Moon Festival every year.
I didn't expect
Jing City to have such delicate customs.
Yeah.
Just like I used to think
people in Jing City were all
martial and aggressive.
I never expected there to be
such gentle and kind-hearted people
here, either.
Gao Ran.
About us going to Jing City,
you haven't told my father yet, right?
Lord Fan Qi has been off duty
and resting at home these past few days.
He probably doesn't know yet.
Then...
Then let's do this.
Don't tell
Dad just yet.
Let's just enjoy the Autumn Moon Festival.
I'll find a chance later
to talk to him properly.
I agree.
Are we expecting guests?
Probably someone Lord Fan Qi invited.
What brings you here?
Governor, what are you
holding in your hands?
Let me formally introduce it to you.
This is a special Autumn Moon Festival
offering from Gao City.
I haven't had the chance to study it yet.
It's said that
if you place it in a room,
it can freshen the air.
Your Excellency.
This fruit is called pomelo.
It's a close relative
of the mandarin orange,
but its flavor
is even sweeter and more refreshing
than that of a mandarin.
Eating it moistens the lungs
and relieves dryness,
and even just smelling it
gives off a pleasant, fresh fragrance.
You truly are knowledgeable, Lord Fan Qi.
I could tell this item was extraordinary,
so I specifically brought it over
for Lady Fan Yun—
someone who appreciates the finer things
both in life and romance—
to have a taste.
Thank you, Your Excellency,
for giving us
such a wonderful gift.
I'll go chill it in well water right away,
and we'll all enjoy it together later
when we admire the moon.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you for the trouble then.
Be careful.
Governor.
Today is the Reunion Festival.
Is there no banquet in your mansion?
Don't tell me
you sneaked over here again.
Like you said, it's the Reunion Festival.
So of course you should spend it
with your family
for it to count as a reunion.
I
have already sent
all the attendants and maids
in the mansion home for the holiday.
And now that everyone's gone home,
I was the only one left in the mansion,
all alone.
That's why...
Fan Yun.
It's a festival, after all.
Let His Excellency stay.
It's okay.
It's your family reunion.
I...
I won't bother you further.
Your Excellency...
Enjoy yourselves.
You didn't even try to stop me.
I didn't ask you to leave
in the first place.
I knew it.
We are family, after all,
right?
We used to be.
Once married...
Shut your mouth.
Don't talk nonsense.
This tofu is really delicious.
Look,
that little sapling
has grown so much.
Yeah.
As long as it's placed
in the right environment,
it will grow quickly.
These saplings are just like you.
It's been a while
since I last had Yun's cooking.
It's really delicious.
Just thinking about it makes me hungry.
Absolutely.
Fan Yun's cooking is indeed excellent.
It's just
a bit of a shame to think
I won't be able to
enjoy her cooking for a while.
Your Excellency.
Isn't Yun's cooking something
you can have whenever you want?
How come
you won't be able to enjoy it for a while?
-You have no idea...
-Here's the thing,
Dad.
From today onwards,
I'll be quite busy with official duties.
So
I won't have much time
to cook delicious meals.
-Yeah, yeah.
-That's why.
Right. Right.
I haven't had the chance to ask you yet.
Were you ultimately assigned to
the Commerce Bureau
or the Affairs Bureau?
A... Aff...
The Affairs Bureau.
Well, the Affairs Bureau...
No, I said it wrong.
It's...
It's the Commerce Bureau.
The Commerce Bureau...
No, not that either.
It is...
So what is it exactly?
Lord Fan Qi.
We don't often get holidays like this.
Let's not talk about official business.
Yes, Dad.
Have some fruit.
Here. Have some.
Why do I feel like
you guys are hiding something from me?
-Well...
-We aren't.
How could we?
What could we possibly
dare to hide from you, Dad?
Don't tell me you two haven't...
We haven't got to taste the pomelo yet.
Your Excellency.
What exactly is this about?
I just wanted to say...
-Governor!
-Your Excellency, have a taste first.
Is it sweet?
Why haven't you been
talking to me tonight?
Besides,
this matter can't be kept
under wraps forever.
-Your Excellency?
-Governor.
Look, it's getting late.
You've been out of the mansion
for quite a while now.
It's time for you to go back and rest.
Your Excellency.
What is it that can't be kept under wraps?
I...
Dad!
Come on and take a look.
-Gao Ran's hand is having an allergic reaction.
-Bring him the medicine!
Your Excellency, what is it?
I...
have already promised...
-Fan Yun...
-Dad.
I'll tell you.
Actually,
next,
I'm neither going to the Affairs Bureau
nor the Commerce Bureau,
but to Jing City.
Zheng Xian, come here.
I have something to tell you.
Grandfather,
what are your instructions?
Zheng Shi is returning to Jing City.
You must keep a close eye on him.
You want me to go back?
Then what about you?
The governor is now suspicious of me,
and I've made another misstep
regarding the position of gate commander.
Qi Zheng will definitely
try to stop me from
returning to Jing City.
Now is not the time
to fall out with him yet.
If he insists on keeping me here,
I'll stay.
Then I'll stay with you.
Silly boy.
If Zheng Shi goes back
and you don't,
wouldn't that be like handing the position
of clan leader to him on a silver platter?
So you mean
you want me to go back
and take up the position of clan leader?
After you go back,
be sure to do everything you can
to support Zheng Jin
in becoming the clan leader.
Okay.
Zheng Shi is unpredictable
and deeply scheming.
I'm worried that this time,
while he's ostensibly returning
to bring back your Granduncle's ashes,
he's actually setting his sights on
the clan leader's position.
With the whereabouts of
the clan leader ring unknown,
I feel uneasy.
Zheng Jin is straightforward,
and you, Zheng Xian, are simple-minded.
Neither of you is a match for him.
Only if you two brothers work together
can you have a chance of success.
But Zheng Shi never said
he wanted to be the clan leader himself.
Silly boy.
Just because he doesn't say it,
does that mean he has no such intentions?
Then what do you make of
him favoring the Fan family girl
as gate commander?
You must follow my instructions
on this matter.
Absolutely do not act on your own.
Remember this—
you must not drift apart from Zheng Jin.
Okay. I'll do as you say.
Since you saw me,
why didn't you come over?
I saw you enjoying the lake view,
Miss Wei,
so I didn't want to disturb you.
I was thinking,
could there be at least once when,
at the moment of parting,
you're the one who comes to find me?
Maybe this time,
could you take me with you?
No.
This time is different.
Actually, I already guessed.
I just wanted to try and see
if there would be a different answer.
As expected.
Honestly,
since you're always hustling around
out there,
there's really not much I can do
to help you.
I just want
to do whatever little I can
to support you.
Then what if I'm not hustling around?
Just the thought of
not seeing you for a long time again
makes me…
It would be nice to have an amulet with me
when I'm away from home.
An amulet?
You've started believing in that too?
It's better to believe it than not.
Don't underestimate yourself.
Besides, the help you gave me before
really meant a lot to me.
Then, does this count as
your validation of me?
It's my validation of your intuition.
Come back soon.
Don't keep me waiting too long.
Your Excellency.
Lord Fan Qi.
I heard from Fan Yun
that you usually visit your wife's grave
on her birthday
rather than on
the anniversary of her death.
So I came here early this morning
to wait for you.
I never want to remember
the days of parting.
I understand.
I won't let Fan Yun disobey your order.
But I'm sure you feel reluctant
to part with her deep down.
We are both Your Excellency's subjects.
But Fan Yun
is my only daughter.
In my heart,
Fan Yun is different from other subjects.
Regardless of our current status,
in my heart,
Fan Yun's always been my wife.
I won't let her go off
on a dangerous journey alone.
There's something
that shouldn't be revealed,
but I feel that
only if you put your mind at ease
will Fan Yun be able to go to Jing City
without any lingering worries.
What is this?
This is a headband I obtained
from the Sacred Rites Bureau.
It has the power
to change one's appearance.
I've discussed this with Gao Ran—
I'll disguise myself as him
and stay by Fan Yun's side.
This way,
you can rest assured.
That only makes me even more worried.
Your Excellency,
your martial skills
can't even hold a candle
to Gao Ran's.
My devotion is second to none.
But in times of emergency,
you may have the will
but not the strength to act.
Please rest assured, Lord Fan Qi.
In times of emergency,
I'll definitely protect her with my life.
Your Excellency.
I can see how much you care for Fan Yun.
I have no qualms about
entrusting Fan Yun to you.
I also know
what Your Excellency intends to do.
May everything
go smoothly and safely
for you both.
Thank you, Lord Fan Qi.
Back then,
you wanted to practice medicine
to save lives.
And now,
she wants to serve the people
as a government official.
Both are for the good of the people.
This is good.
If this is
the kind of person
you wanted our daughter to become,
then please watch over her for me
and guard her
from the heavens.
Your daughter is here.
Alright, show yourself.
Dad.
Make sure to make the most of
the opportunity you've earned yourself.
Don't bring shame on
me and your mother.
Dad,
thank you.
There's nothing wrong with
Gao Ran dressing like this,
but his posture feels
a bit too stiff and restrained.
Gao Ran, why don't you try relaxing a bit?
According to
the Services Bureau's etiquette,
when the governor is standing,
the feet should be together,
straight and orderly like a plant,
the neck extended, head held up,
and hands naturally at rest.
If I relax any more than that,
it would be improper and against decorum.
Um...
Then try walking a few steps.
Stop. Stop.
This is way too stiff.
Is that how I usually walk?
As recorded in the "Nine Cities Canon,"
when a governor walks,
he should be dignified on the inside
and upright on the outside,
without swaying from side to side,
and his movements measured and proper.
Your usual way of walking, Governor,
is really a bit undisciplined.
But...
I told you,
Gao Ran looks more like a governor
than His Excellency himself.
More accurately, it's that His Excellency
just doesn't look like a governor.
I think
we can wrap up the course now.
I haven't even left yet,
and you're already
-Ouch! It hurts!
-starting a rebellion, huh?
Oh well, oh well.
What can I do? Our Gao Ran
is naturally cut out to be a governor.
See? See?
Just this "oh well"
is not something Gao Ran would say at all.
Gao Ran is dignified and graceful
in his interactions with others.
Compared to His Excellency,
he's definitely not as wild...
Charming and dashing!
Move aside.
During morning assemblies,
I do come across as dignified and serious.
Gao Ran can imitate that part
just fine.
It's just in private settings—
if anyone who knows me is present—
that I'll need the two of you
to play along.
Gao Ran only needs to respond briefly.
Respond to what?
It's simple. I'll teach you.
You may rise.
Granted.
You may leave!
Not bad, not bad.
With just those few lines,
you can't tell the difference.
Your standards are way too low.
You just need to practice more.
It seems like you'll get there in no time.
Don't blame me for saying this,
but I really can't bring myself
to cheer like that normally,
especially in front of Fan Yun.
You must not forget that.
Then, Gao Ran, why don't you tell me
how you usually communicate with Fan Yun?
There's no fixed way of talking.
Fan Yun has been lively and restless
since childhood,
not very concerned with etiquette.
I've basically just been
fulfilling my duty as a caregiver.
Just act like an older brother
and ask her things like
whether she's eating well
or dressed warmly enough.
What else...
Right.
I rarely turn down her requests.
Whatever she says, you just do it?
Yeah. I don't often stop her
from doing what she wants.
Well, as her "older brother,"
you really do spoil her.
Alright.
As long as we keep these in mind,
we shouldn't get caught.
I think it's about time.
Let's get started.
Today,
to send off Lord Fan and Lord Tian
as they take up their posts in Jing City,
an official farewell ceremony
has been arranged.
Begin.
In the fifth month
of the year of Bingshen,
we pay homage to our ancestors
and successive generations of governors.
Please perform the following rites:
offer the Qi jade to Heaven,
and the 9 clans are brought forth
in succession.
Bow.
Offer the yellow jade to Earth,
and pillars stand firm
through generations.
Bow.
Ancestors of the Nine Cities,
please bless our territory.
Bow.
Gao Ran.
Gao Ran?
Why are you ignoring me?
I didn't hear you. I'm here.
You're wearing a headband today?
You mean this?
It's a kind of amulet, I guess.
An amulet?
Didn't you
ask me for an amulet before?
Now that you're wearing this,
what about mine?
What should I do with this then?
Well, this was
specially bestowed by His Excellency.
I couldn't really refuse it. But yours—
I'll wear it as well.
Together.
Specially bestowed by His Excellency, huh?
That's more like it.
But
even if you have 2 amulets now,
you still can't let your guard down.
You need to stay safe, okay?
Just relax and put your mind at ease.
Why do you
seem a bit strange today?
Strange?
I don't think so.
Come on.
You know what?
Our plan for Jing City
is very well thought out.
So don't worry at all.
While I'm away,
just keep a close eye on His Excellency.
Then does that count as
me doing you a favor?
Of course it does.
Because your Gao Ran will be fine.
My Gao Ran?
Then rest assured.
I'll definitely take good care of
His Excellency.
I'm leaving.
Perfect.
Ceremony finished.
-God bless Nine Cities.
Your Excellency.
Thank you for the farewell ceremony.
Right now, I
feel completely filled with energy.
From now on, I'll treat every
newly appointed official
with equal care and respect.
Your Excellency truly loves your officials
and cares for the people,
with the welfare of the realm at heart.
You...
Please mind your manners.
Okay.
By the way, Your Excellency,
I noticed you and Gao Ran are both
wearing this on your foreheads.
What is this?
This is
an amulet presented by the Ping family
during the Autumn Moon Festival.
I thought it looked good on Gao Ran too,
so I gave him a pair.
That's all.
An amulet?
Well, since Gao Ran is coming with us
to Jing City,
it makes sense for him to wear an amulet.
But do you have to be so cautious
in Ling'an too?
I think it looks nice.
It really suits my style.
I see.
I'll wait for you to come back.
Take care of yourself, too.
Fan Yun?
Yes?
Why is he traveling with us?
You mean Second Young Master Zheng?
He suggested a few days ago
that the two groups travel together.
And I figured
since he's relatively familiar
with the route to Jing City,
it'd be nice to have someone
to look out for each other along the way.
Look out for each other?
I think
it's more like an annoyance.
Annoyance?
What annoyance?
I mean,
we appreciate your kind intentions,
Second Young Master Zheng.
It's just the more people we travel with,
the more we stand out as a target.
Isn't that a bit too ostentatious?
It's true that we shouldn't draw attention
to ourselves on a long journey.
But given this is a trip to Jing City,
our Zheng family banner
is the best protection.
Lord Gao, you're worrying too much.
Thank you.
Hold on.
Why is there no meat at all?
The harvest wasn't good this year.
All the chickens, ducks and fish
have been sent to Ling'an.
Apologies for the poor hospitality.
It's all right.
Gao Ran.
What do you want to say to me?
I just wanted to say
that Dad's cooking
was way worse than this,
yet you could bear with it.
You must be too used to the good life now.
Just go ahead and eat.
Second Young Master Zheng,
can you get used to the taste?
It's just everyday food.
What's there not to be used to?
Still, I hope that
in the future, people can eat meat
freely in big bites,
and won't have to rely on
pickled vegetables to get by anymore.
These are pickled vegetables?
Yes.
What's wrong with you, Gao Ran?
You don't even recognize these?
It's delicious.
Delicious.
Since it's so delicious,
you should eat more.
Eat more.
Thank you, Fan Yun.
What's going on?
We're moving.
-Mayor Zheng.
Why did you two come
without giving me a notice in advance?
Well...
His Excellency just issued an oral decree,
ordering the two of us to come here.
There's another decree?
That's right.
In recognition of the heroic sacrifices
of your entire Zheng family,
and in light of
the upcoming election for clan leader,
His Excellency has hereby proclaimed
that the new Zheng clan leader
may directly inherit your military merits
and be granted
the rank of Third-Rank General.
The new clan leader
will
be granted the rank of Third-Rank General?
I think this is actually great news.
Just think about it—
we've been working hard
for most of our lives,
and isn't it all
for the sake of a happy retirement?
Right?
If you ask me,
you shouldn't go to Jing City
and meddle in the clan leader's affairs.
Let's stay in Ling'an together
and enjoy our retirement, shall we?
Well, Mayor Zheng,
His Excellency's intention
is to help the Nine Cities
take on a new look.
Look,
if we old folks can just
live a free and unrestrained life—
how carefree is that?
Zheng the Second, stop dithering.
J-Just give us a clear answer.
The Zheng family is facing
a leadership vacuum.
If I don't go back now,
it'll be left to
my grandchildren's generation.
They lack experience and are still young.
I have to go back to Jing City
to take charge of the overall situation
for them.
Please return the detained Zheng's Army
to me.
What?
Detained?
Zhao.
You know about this?
I had absolutely no idea.
Wait, there's no such thing
as being detained.
Our Ling'an is a place of
outstanding people and beautiful scenery,
and the land and climate are nurturing.
Anyone who comes here
never wants to leave.
Your army has also
gotten along very well with
Gao Ran and Commander Wei
since they arrived here.
And none of them wants to leave.
Yes. That's right.
Mayor Zheng,
with so many people staying here,
if you're not here to watch over them,
we won't feel at ease.
Exactly.
You guys...
What does he mean?
Seems like he's not leaving.
So,
this is your first time
sleeping in the wild?
Yes.
If we go to
a post house or an inn
at a time like this,
we'll easily be targeted.
Let's just have a simple meal tonight.
Fan Yun, the soup is boiling.
Okay.
We can start cooking the vegetables.
Here.
The vegetables have been washed.
Suyin,
come on.
Give me the vegetables.
Let me do it.
It's okay, I...
Let me do it, Fan Yun.
We've been on the road all day.
You must be exhausted.
I-I'm not really tired.
Come on.
Zheng Xian, let's go pick
some wild vegetables.
It'll be ready soon.
Show yourselves.
How dare you follow me?
Do you have a death wish or something?
Right,
you can help me with something.
Careful, it's hot.
Okay.
Add a bit more firewood.
Fish?
For you.
Where did you get this?
Thank you for letting me travel with you.
We have fish to eat.
I never agreed to let you travel with us.
What happened to those
who were following us?
We've driven them all off.
Things should be fine for now.
What's bound to happen will happen.
It's actually understandable.
After all, Jing City is expecting
a new gate commander.
Those people won't have it easy either.
I'm afraid the road ahead
will only get tougher.
Master Chief Military Officer.
Fan Yun, rest assured.
To protect you,
I'm willing to pay any price.
Okay.
I see.
Then... you two talk.
I'll go over there and check on
Tian Xing and Suyin.
Be careful.
What's wrong, Your Excellency?
Why are today's dishes
so salty?
Your Excellency, every dish was
made according to your taste.
If you prefer a lighter taste today,
I'll go change it for you right away.
No need.
Since they were made
according to my taste,
let's not waste them.
Your Excellency.
Forget it, forget it.
I was wondering why it's so salty.
How could anyone eat it anyway?
Take it away.
These
are some pastries I made myself.
I thought
you might be tired of the food here,
so I brought you something different
for a change. Try it.
You've certainly become more sensible.
How is it?
A gift full of sincerity
really is different.
Even a picky eater like him
can't resist it.
What's this pastry made of?
This is
our Gao City's specialty—
Egg and Pomelo Cake.
Pom...
Pomelo?
What's wrong, Your Excellency?
Didn't you say
you liked our Gao City's pomelo?
I thought I'd make more for you.
Don't let the small size of
this plate fool you—
I squeezed a whole pomelo into it.
This...
What's wrong?
Is it not good?
Your Excellency, what's going on?
I'm fine.
Quick, call Lord Jiang over.
-Okay.
-I can't breathe.
I'm on my way.
I... I'll go.
No, I'll go.
I'm faster than you. I'll go.
There's less than
half a day's journey left
to Jing City.
Let's move a bit faster
and try to arrive before dark.
Here.
Thank you.
Take a rest first.
Shi.
Come here.
Now that the Gate Commander Residence
has been burned down,
Brother probably wouldn't
have the mood to repair it.
Where will Lady Fan Yun and her party stay
once they enter the city?
Jing City is such a large city.
Surely there won't be a shortage of places
for just a few of them to stay, right?
How about
the two of us enter the city first
and arrange accommodations for them?
Otherwise, we'll be scrambling
at the last minute,
and it might look like our Zheng family
is neglecting the gate commander.
You're actually right.
We should prepare in advance.
Jing City is now filled with
undercurrents.
It's no longer what it used to be.
There might very well be people
inside the city
plotting to harm the new gate commander
and preparing a breakaway faction.
Shi, that's not what I meant.
We should always prepare for the worst.
Fan Yun.
I'll wait for you in the city.
Okay.
Get ready to hit the road.
He said something about
preparing for the worst...
What are you looking at?
Are you that reluctant to part with him?
-Keep looking then.
-I…
He won't come back no matter
how long you look anyway.
He...
He's already come back.
No way...
Second Young Master Zheng,
why did you turn back?
Being the gate commander of Jing City
is not like being one anywhere else.
The road ahead is dangerous.
Please take good care of yourself.
Anything else you want to say?
You can leave now.
I'll wait for you in Jing City.
-W-Who asked you to wait?
-Okay.
Ridiculous.
This guy...
He's really such a pain. What a pain.
Gao Ran?
Come on.
Come sit.
Sit here.
Come on.
You don't have a fever or anything.
Why have you been acting so weird
these past few days,
targeting that Second Young Master Zheng
all the time?
You don't usually act like this.
I...
I know.
You know?
You must have
spent too much time with that Miss Wei,
so you've become as quirky as her.
Have you two already...
Yes...
No, it's not like that.
He said it himself
that the Zheng family is plotting
to harm the new gate commander.
He's a member of the Zheng family
after all.
It's better to be safe than sorry.