[Adapted from Che Ye Liu Xiang's
novel of the same name]
[Episode 4]
Hurry up and get ready to go, Mr. Bei.
Do I have to come up and get you myself?
Big Bro.
The soup will be ready in half an hour.
What a pity.
I'm afraid...
I won't be able to have soup tonight.
Big Bro, there's someone outside.
No way, Mr. Bei.
It doesn't look like
you're just fooling around with him.
Mind your own business.
All right.
Anyway, it's better this way.
It's safe.
Lv Qing.
You're really a master at picking places.
In a place like this,
even mosquitoes would need
a credit check to get in.
Finally got rid of that tag along?
Oh, my dear young master.
Let's talk business first.
Xiao Fan.
Bring the documents over.
Yes, they're on the table.
The driver is waiting for you downstairs.
[Document Folder]
Now this is something new.
So, I think...
Oh, Xiao Fan is here.
We've been waiting for you.
Have a seat.
Goodness.
I knew it.
Big Bro, your documents.
I... I also brought some soup.
Go and share it with everyone outside.
Okay.
Lv Qing, you just leave
documents like that at home?
Are you sure he won't peek?
That's the good thing about Xiao Fan.
He's timid and cautious.
He might not be the sharpest,
but he knows his place.
Oh, please.
He doesn't know a damn thing.
Even if you laid it out for him,
would he even understand it?
Big Bro.
Zi Yang.
Look, this guy doesn't even
have a brokerage account.
Why the hell is he reading
the securities newspaper all day?
I'm just browsing.
Look at what you're saying.
Ordinary people like to read Global Times, too.
So what? Are they all UN Secretary-Generals?
I think Lv Qing is right.
Xiao Fan isn't cut out
for speculation or stocks.
The best thing about Xiao Fan
is his simplicity.
Simplicity?
More like stupid and ordinary.
Zhuo Xin.
Are you out of your mind?
Why else would you be acting so cocky?
Look at you. You just had to
make Lv Qing speak up.
How was it? Quite a mouthful, wasn't it?
Come on. Let's have a drink.
I saw that report Lv Qing had.
The news about loosening
stock market regulations is true.
Think about it.
The Songnan and Yunjing gangs
are fighting so hard.
To boost the economy,
they have to let the Songnan gang take over.
The price of rice is going to rise.
It's going to skyrocket.
It's expected to hit one yuan within two years.
Rice is only fifty cents a pound now.
The government is subsidizing it now
to keep the price of rice stable.
But they can't hold it much longer.
The situation in the south is unstable.
And there's a red-headed document
ordering an increase in rice reserves.
So, the price of rice is bound to go up.
If rice goes up,
wheat will likely follow suit.
That's why, by the time
we pull out of the stock market,
we'll be just in time to catch
this wave of rising prices
in agricultural products.
Let's just get out of the stock market first.
Why are you calling so late?
Mom.
Did we plant any wheat this year?
You silly child.
Calling in the middle of the night
just to ask if we planted wheat?
Why would we plant wheat?
If we plant wheat now,
we'd lose dozens of yuan per mu.
Who would still plant wheat?
No one in the village plants it anymore.
Not even enough for us to eat?
We did when you were still at home.
But your dad's picky now.
He loves that wheat from Huanglong.
So, we just dug up all our own wheat.
- Mom!
- We're planting apple trees this year.
But why aren't you
planting food for yourselves?
If you can't buy wheat later,
won't that be a problem?
How could we not be able to buy it?
They sell it right here in the village.
We don't even have to go to the county seat.
We eat 400 to 500 catties of wheat a year.
If it goes up to one yuan a catty next year,
won't you have worked all year for nothing?
One yuan a catty?
Xiao Fan, are you serious?
Huh? Did you hear some inside news?
People will starve at that price!
Oh dear! Xiao Fan said
the price of wheat is going to skyrocket!
- What are we going to do?
- No, no, no.
I just said "if."
I'm hanging up now.
Big Bro, are you hungry?
I'll go make you a late-night snack.
Do you know what is most valuable?
Big Bro.
Information is the most valuable.
I'm sorry, Big Bro.
Did I cause trouble?
What trouble could you possibly cause?
I let you tag along because I wanted you to see
how business is done.
You sent that piece of news back home.
What impact could that have?
A few hundred bucks' worth of harvest?
Do you have any idea how much money
you could have made with that information?
Don't you have any ambition?
If you're still going to be a useless loser,
don't embarrass me tomorrow.
No way.
Can't you two be apart for even a second?
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's talk business.
I've done the math.
It'd be a huge loss to miss this market trend.
I managed to squeeze
200,000 out of the old man.
I got 200,000, too.
So, how much more do you need?
Actually, it's not that much.
Just...
Hold on a second.
Fan Fan, Xiao Fan, hurry up!
Something happened to your dad!
- Xiao Fan.
- Yeah?
It's your mom.
Why is she calling my phone?
- Xiao Fan!
- Mom.
- What's wrong?
- Something terrible happened!
Your dad panicked after hearing your news.
He borrowed the village chief's tricycle
to go buy up wheat in town.
He got hit by a car on the way!
Is Dad okay?
He's in the hospital now.
The police say it was our fault.
Quick, send some money back.
- Hurry!
- Okay, got it.
Mom, don't worry.
I'll head back right away.
Big Bro.
I have to go back to my hometown.
Let's talk outside.
Tell Manager Li to give me 5,000 in cash.
Deduct it from this room's bill.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Big Bro.
I'm still causing you trouble.
Go ahead.
Give my regards to your mother.
Thank you, Big Bro.
Thank you.
Big Bro, are you coming home tonight?
I'll make you some soup.
Don't bother.
I haven't felt like having soup lately.
How about I make you porridge instead?
As they say, one's background
determines one's vision,
and vision determines one's choices.
That's enough, Master Zhuo.
When Lv Qing comes back later
and sees you acting like this,
do you think he'll be happy?
Being gay isn't like a common cold.
You can't just take a pill and be cured.
Even if you drive Lu Xiao Fan away,
it won't change the facts.
Red gates are for stone lions,
and wooden gates are for bamboo horses.
Lu Xiao Fan is just a peasant.
Do you really want Lv Qing
to get bogged down in petty interests
and commoner trivialities with him?
Bei Lv Qing may like men,
but he deserves better.
Fine, whatever.
Hello, Fan Fan.
Are you doing okay over there?
Oh.
Let me tell you.
Lv Qing made a call
to the best hospital here.
Your dad got admitted right away.
He even arranged full checkups
for both of us.
Ah.
Everything's great, we're doing fine.
Anyway, take good care of yourself.
Oh, and,
be sure to thank Lv Qing for us.
I heard
Lv Xin's mom is coming back to the country.
All right.
Congratulations to Lv Qing on his graduation.
Lv Qing, do you really not plan
to continue your studies?
I've already thought it through.
I think it's better to start working early.
The domestic market has just opened up.
What's the use of more schooling?
In the end, it's just
to secure some minor official post.
Son, this is the start-up capital from me.
Go out and make a name for yourself.
Lv Qing has to report to
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs next week.
Money from dubious sources is no good.
Dubious sources?
This is money from a mother to her son.
How can you call it dubious?
Or are you implying something, Mr. Bei?
Xiao Fan, Lv Qing has graduated.
How about you stop living at the school dorms?
Come and live at home.
He hasn't been living
at school for a long time.
Oh?
Xiao Fan, you're not living on campus?
I'm staying at Lv Qing's place now.
I help him with the cleaning and the cooking.
Xiao Fan was being bullied at school.
He's staying at my place
to lie low for a while.
The judiciary and the press agency
held a joint press conference today.
The CPPCC inspection team
is inspecting the Yellow River Delta.
Hanshan Power Plant's
first 300,000-kilowatt unit
has begun generating power.
The Prime Minister of India has withdrawn...
Xiao Fan.
Big Bro.
Will you be back for dinner tonight?
No.
You haven't been back for days.
Do you need me to bring you anything?
I don't need anything.
In the next couple of days,
move your things back to the dorm.
I'll be needing this place in the future.
There are only a few months until graduation.
Why are you making such a fuss?
Everyone else is out on internships.
True.
You don't need to bother with all that.
All right. I've delivered all the invitations.
Right, today is Lv Qing's birthday.
You've already booked the private room?
Sorry, I'm in the wrong room.
Zi Yang.
Oh! Xiao Fan!
Why did you move back here?
It's my brother's birthday?
The presidential suite at Jinfan Hotel.
What?
Didn't your brother tell you?
He's been very busy lately.
I'm very busy, too.
Busy keeping up with national affairs?
Since I've graduated, I need to find a job.
Why are you looking for a job yourself?
Don't make the Bei family a laughingstock.
Talk to Mr. Bei.
Lv Qing and Wen Xi
have a lot to deal with every day now.
Wen Xi.
I'm off.
Where did you buy this pen?
This is a branded item.
I bought it just for my advisor.
How much was it?
120 yuan.
That's half a year's internship pay for me.
Are you happy that I'm here?
- I am.
- How could Lv Qing be upset?
- I'm very happy.
- Happy birthday.
Thank you.
You're still meeting up
every day behind our backs?
Cheers!
You two can't drink in secret.
Of course not.
How can you call this "in secret"?
Pour another glass. Fill it up!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Come on!
Li Wen Xi, where have you been?
Why did it take you so long to return?
It's been a long time since we've seen
Young Master Bei this happy.
Yeah. Look how joyful he is today.
- Take a penalty drink!
- Guys, let's have a drink. Bottoms up!
Bottoms up!
I'm drinking?
Young Master Bei, it's your birthday,
but all the drinks are coming my way.
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
Let's do a cross-arm toast.
It's been a long time since we all gathered.
Now that Li Wen Xi is back,
he shouldn't be leaving again, right?
Let him stay for a long time.
Come on, Master Bei.
Then how long can I stay?
Stay forever.
Are you serious?
Then someone is going to be overjoyed, right?
Not bad.
Sir, are you going in?
Hey.
Isn't that Lu Xiao Fan?
No.
Big Bro.
Happy birthday.
Mr. Bei and Lv Xin are still upstairs.
Are you scared?
I...
Then... keep your voice down.
Big Bro.
You've had too much to drink.
Fan Fan.
Big Bro.
Since when did you like drinking coffee?
[Coffee]
Your brother has always liked coffee.
- Hello.
- You're here.
Sit down.
Why are you just standing there?
Please, sit.
I'm sorry.
I booked this cafe.
It's relatively quiet,
making it easier for us to talk.
I just got back from Africa.
I brought some fresh coffee beans.
Everyone, please try some.
Don't tell me you're addicted to coffee.
There are only two things I'm addicted to.
First is you,
and second is coffee.
You brought these back from Burundi, right?
How did you guess?
Indeed. It's fragrant and mellow.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I don't like sugar in my coffee,
so I didn't add any for you all.
Let's get him a cappuccino instead.
Isn't that a girl's drink?
Just kidding.
I often hear Lv Qing mention you,
so I was quite curious about you.
He said you aren't very fond of coffee.
But I still insisted on inviting you over.
Let's get to know each other.
I'm Li Wen Xi. Nice to meet you.
Hello. I'm Lu Xiao Fan.
Hey, Lv Qing.
Do you still play the piano?
I haven't played since I came back.
Why? You've been playing for so long.
Actually, I never liked playing the piano.
That's because you lacked a soulmate.
Then I'm not leaving.
Lv Qing.
You still haven't thrown this away?
Didn't you tell me not to take it off?
I heard you've been on blind dates lately.
Yes.
But none of them were satisfactory.
I don't like meddlers
or people who are too demanding.
I'm afraid they'd be a nuisance to us.
I've booked dinner.
Xiao Fan, come with us.
Okay.
You're here.
Big Bro. Try this.
It's the signature dish here.
This is also delicious.
Big Bro. Have some water.
Here.
This is also delicious.
Xiao Fan.
That's enough.
Lv Qing has hands.
Big Bro.
Are you coming back tonight?
You have things to do tomorrow morning.
I'll get up early to make you soup.
Lv Qing.
Xiao Fan... is just being kind.
Xiao Fan.
Get in the car.
I'll wait for my brother.
Your brother asked me to pick you up.
Oh.
What were you doing just now?
I just wanted to try one more time.
Hey, Lu Xiao Fan.
What's going on in that head of yours?
Do you even know how to be a gay man?
You know how it works, right?
A gay man means being with one guy today,
and with another tomorrow.
But look at you.
One minute you're all mopey and whining,
and the next, you're like
a dog guarding its food,
clinging to Bei Lv Qing.
Think about your relationship with him.
And who is Li Wen Xi?
He's Lv Qing's childhood sweetheart.
He hasn't even given you the cold shoulder yet.
Xiao Fan.
We're friends.
As your dear buddy, let me ask you one thing.
Do you know what your most valuable trait is?
It's that you're sensible.
For a man like Lv Qing,
the people pursuing him,
both men and women,
could form a line around the block.
Someone like you being by his side
is enough to make people envious.
You're back. I specially made some soup today.
Xiao Fan, I'm going to stay here
with Lv Qing for a while.
So... I'm afraid you'll have to move out.