Grandma.
Termite mushrooms.
Azaleas.
Come in, come in.
Hurry, hurry!
Change your shoes.
Oh, this is wonderful.
- Grandma.
- Changyang is here!
Hello, Auntie.
Come on in, hurry.
Okay.
I have food cooking on the stove.
Come on in.
Junjun, count for Grandma.
How many times has Grandma invited you?
According to WeChat,
no less than ten times.
Twelve times.
Ah.
Well, whenever I see
those mushrooms,
Grandma,
I think of you.
Hey, Grandma.
I'm back too.
Grandma.
I was so worried my cooking
wouldn't taste as good as yours.
Qingtian gains ten pounds every
time he comes back from Molie.
He always comes home raving
about how well Changyang cooks.
Kids his age...
can't do anything on their own.
He feels so inadequate around you.
It's not that big of a deal.
I've just spent a lot of
time in the mountains.
If you keep doing the same thing,
anyone can do it well.
My eldest grandson, come here, quick!
Look, look.
Is it Christmas today?
These are all gifts from Junjun.
And this outfit too.
Look, does it look good?
Does it look good?
It looks great, Grandma.
"A Winter Sun Wakes the Wind in Spring Hills' Dream"
(Episode 8: Hunter)
Sing, sing!
I'm so hungry, so hungry, so hungry.
I'm really so hungry.
You should sing too!
If you don't know how, just learn.
You teach me.
Learn it yourself.
Let's eat first. After dinner,
you can teach him.
Sure. He's tone-deaf, though.
I actually sing very well.
Since it's my first time here today,
I'll show off a bit.
Next time I come, I won't cook.
I'll leave it all to Changyang.
Sure.
Did you hear that? You're cooking.
Okay.
Haha.
Why do I feel like the outsider here?
You're a regular guest here.
He made preparations in advance.
Eat up! Why isn't anyone eating? Come on.
Grandma,
when did you find out?
Two years ago.
Junjun told me when he added me on WeChat.
He said he was a fan of yours.
And he also said...
he liked you...
and wanted to date you.
Grandma, I never said that.
Alright, Grandma will stop talking.
Let's eat, let's eat.
Eat up.
Get some food for Grandma.
Sure thing.
My brother took Changyang home.
Mr. Xu, this contract has been approved.
There's also an overseas contract.
I'll work on it as soon as I get back.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Changyang is like a hunter,
and you're like a trap.
How so?
One chases after the prey,
while the other waits
for the prey to fall in.
That doesn't seem quite right.
I've been the one chasing your brother.
Changyang was the one hiding
in the mountains setting traps.
Thinking back now,
it doesn't seem that way.
Changyang has been chasing
in the woods for two years.
He has both my mom's
and my grandma's WeChat.
He sends tea and mushrooms
to my family every year.
He even bought colorful dresses
for my grandma in Tianyi.
You threw tens of
millions of dollars out there,
but it didn't make as much of an
impact as Changyang's few thousand.
I admit defeat completely.
Brother Wenshu, are you giving up?
No. I want to be the
eternal white moonlight.
Deep in Molie, there's a camellia Village.
I wanted to take you there,
but maybe next year. This year,
I could only bring it back to you.
Come in.
Are you trying to make me
remember you even after I die?
I want to be remembered
by you even after I'm gone.
I'm an actor.
I'm very emotional.
Doing this makes it very easy
for me to get into character.
I won't stop you.
The ultimate hunter.
You should seriously
consider Director Li's project.
I really like her style,
but I'm really not in the
mood to act right now.
A secret relationship.
There's no other way.
The contract is finalized.
I heard Kevin's side signed
a new drama with Qi Haoyu.
He's confirmed as the second
male lead in an idol drama,
and they're fighting for the male lead.
It's a romantic pairing,
and there are kiss scenes.
Kevin is actually quite honest.
I asked around.
Kevin's side didn't say anything.
Exactly the same.
Let's write his character
off in the spin-off.
If he's more clear-headed than Shi Yuhao,
he might still be saved.
There's one more thing.
Sister Lan had booked an MV shoot before.
Brother Guo only found out
when checking Lang Di's schedule.
The shooting contract is already finalized.
It was originally scheduled for July.
Didn't the brand push for it?
Maybe the brand has a good
relationship with Sister Lan,
or maybe they wanted to lie low
during the controversy back then.
Sure.
I'll choose the location.
The location needs to
be chosen by the brand.
The place you choose might
not fit the brand's image.
Let the director figure it out.
There can't be a male and female lead.
I'll do it myself.
We can have Director Li direct it.
It's a good opportunity before the movie
for us to collaborate
and build some hype.
It's impossible to shoot.
Sister,
(Qi Haoyu, we debuted together, [starting]
from nobodies to where we are now,
we have popularity and commercial
endorsements as a result of our work together.
Without this partnership, we might've still been bit actors with no commercial value.]
No matter what the commercial
motives were behind our activities,
the hearts of our fans deserve the greatest respect.
Their love for us is genuine, and
their efforts should be rewarded.
I despise how you use your volatile
emotions as a way to hide from reality.
The most shameful act is benefitting
from betraying someone's trust.]
these words sound a lot like
what I said to Shi Yuhao back then.
How did you handle it later?
Our relationship?
Yeah.
Do you love Qi Haoyu?
I do like him.
Even though he can be
a bit crazy sometimes.
Falling in love through
acting is easy. But is it love?
What exactly is love?
Put it this way.
I used to think I loved Shi Yuhao,
because he could always affect my emotions.
Whether he annoyed me
or ignored me,
I would cry my eyes out.
I told Sister Lan everything back then.
She taught me a skill.
She told me to step back when emotions hit,
observe my own feelings,
look inward, and talk to myself.
Ask myself why I'm crying,
and why I'm feeling sad or hurt.
Later, I found this method very useful.
It really helps heal my
uncontrollable emotions.
Sister Lan said many people make
spiritual practice sound mysterious,
but what everyone
actually needs to practice
is how to regulate their emotions.
Only when you can control your emotions
can you control your destiny.
I cried because of Shi Yuhao
because I was always
focused on how he treated me.
But when I looked closely at myself,
I realized I didn't like
him as much as I thought.
I only liked the character in the drama.
Looking at it another way,
it wasn't Shi Yuhao's fault either.
We just had an emotional accident
at an age when we didn't understand love.
Now I understand.
Love is keeping someone in your instincts,
always caring about whether they need you.
I didn't come to see you.
President Fang asked me to be the guide.
She said you're going to Molie
to shoot an MV. Are you crazy?
Crazy? Like a bear shot with an arrow,
running wild in the woods.
Where did it get shot?
Hey, Brother Peng.
I'm heading into the mountains
with Lang Di to shoot an MV.
Will you pass by Xi Gui?
I was worried you'd get carsick,
so we didn't take that route.
We'll stop by on our way back.
Okay.
Oh, the timing doesn't work out.
How about this? Give Jialin a call.
Hey? Hello?
Why aren't Brother Guo
and Yezi staying here?
To keep you from
disturbing the peace at night.
Come up.
Come down.
Disturbing the peace, huh?
Let's see how I disturb the peace tonight.
Show me how you're going to do that.
Bro, can you do another livestream for me?
Selling what?
These are all hand-embroidered
by the local weavers.
Charity again?
Of course, that's why I came to you.
Alright. Go ask Brother Guo to schedule it.
Thanks, Bro! You're the best.
Oh, cut it out.
So if we hadn't come,
you weren't planning on
returning to Shangjing?
We've traveled to so many places.
Tian drives all day long.
A month just flies by like that.
It's been almost two months, right?
Qingtian took me to six coffee estates.
And four tea estates.
It works out perfectly since I
applied for an off-campus internship.
Changyang, can you ask
your cousin to stamp my form?
Sure, I have the stamp with me.
How convenient.
Should I, as your guardian,
write a little note for you?
Appears to be an internship,
but actually a vacation.
False advertising.
Who's false advertising?
Appears to be a shoot,
but actually a honeymoon.
Feng Qingtian!
Feng Qinglang!
Your cousin's company?
Changyang is a shareholder.
It was your company that
asked me to shoot the MV.
At the end of last year,
I booked the schedule with Sister Lan.
So even if I didn't go
into the mountains in April,
I couldn't escape it in July.
You were destined to be caught.
Can you two stop being
so affectionate here?
Come down.
My brother can be quite stubborn.
You're much better.
You've prepared so much,
what if I wasn't interested in you?
Is that possible?
Aren't you two heading back with us?
Who knows how many more days you
two will be lovey-dovey after the shoot.
Brother Wenshu doesn't seem very happy.
Can you tone it down a bit in front of him?
At least don't get between the Xu brothers.
Was I that bad?
You were totally over the top.
I've said my piece. I'm off.
Back to Shangjing?
Brother Wenshu is driving
me back to the Tea College.
Let's go.
Yezi, give me your phone.
[The last message from God of
Wealth Xu: Interesting, see you later.]
[Take good care of my younger brother!]
Tian,
can you give me a ride to
town to buy some things?
Hop in.
How long does it take to get to town?
About half an hour.
Oh, okay.
That won't delay my hair and makeup.
I made it.
How are you getting back?
The lighting truck will be here soon.
I'll hitch a ride back then.
Alright, we'll head out first.
Thanks, Mr. Xu.
Fell asleep.
Okay, cut!
Let's watch the playback.
Your company's planning is pretty good.
I invited Director Li to shoot this.
It's within budget.
I pulled some favors.
Your face is indeed quite valuable.
Director Li wants me to
star in her new project.
Take it!
I'm not in the mood to act.
You don't even want to pretend anymore.
Changyang,
look at this angle.
Coming!
Oh, stop fooling around, you two.
We're about to shoot. Go back.
I'm off.
Let me take a picture of you, Guo.
This hat really suits you.
Really?
Yes, come on.
Oh my.
So beautiful.
You've still got it!
What do you mean, 'still got it'?
A friend of mine wants to shoot
a documentary about the tea mountains.
They need a male lead.
He's really not cut out for it.
Documentaries don't require acting skills.
He wouldn't want to do it.
You can cast my brother.
My brother is even more handsome than me.
Plus, he comes to Molie every year,
so he knows the place well.
Then introduce us.
Do I look beautiful?
Send it to me later.
Okay.
Director Li has her eye on you.
For what?
What else when a director
has her eye on you?
Lang Di,
coming!
This one is even prettier.
Not everyone on the crew is one of us.
199.
Got in this afternoon.
Dad.
Yeah.
Changyang's roasted tea
is good for the stomach.
Oh?
Mainly because I don't
know how to brew it properly.
Steeping it directly is simpler.
Have a seat.
Good tea.
How is your mother doing in the UK?
She's fine, though she's
still not used to the weather.
Thinking of coming back to work here?
No.
I only came back because of an opportunity.
What opportunity?
An old friend passed away.
The producer of the film you invested in?
Yes.
Don't get too close to people in showbiz.
A single photo can
easily be misinterpreted.
I understand.
Your aunt recently introduced a girl to me.
She's great in every aspect,
and she also studied abroad.
Since you're back,
go meet her.
President Fang,
Kevin's side refused to shoot for
the magazine we recommended.
Seeing Qi Haoyu taking their side,
they've started playing hardball.
Qi Haoyu,
Han Lu told me
you haven't been replying to his messages.
This is also the last time I'll call you.
You debuted as a duo with Han Lu
to get the traffic you have today.
Your appearance fee for a single
commercial event is now 100,000.
If you're willing to keep cooperating,
there's no limit.
Don't tell me you don't care about money.
Look at your classmates.
After graduation, they're still doing
short dramas for 800 yuan for four days.
And there's a crowd
fighting to perform for free.
If you want to go back to
acting in those trashy web dramas,
no one is stopping you.
Our company has never cast
artists from other agencies.
You were an exception
specially approved by Sister Lan.
If you're cutting ties just
because Sister Lan is gone,
then we all misjudged you.
Many follow-up tasks
are bound by the contract.
Now, because of your attitude,
your agency is refusing to cooperate.
We don't want to take this to court.
Jialan Shanying would
rather discard you as a pawn
than drag this fight in front of the fans.
Think about it carefully.
Kevin didn't agree to the
magazine we arranged.
If you shoot Kevin's choice,
I'll have Han Lu cooperate with you,
but we won't have a
future together anymore.
Where is everyone?
Want some water?
Over here.
Come on, makeup, wardrobe,
photographer, camera assistant.
Hello, everyone.
Lao Xie.
This is Mr. Qi.
This is Mr. Han.
Hello, Mr. Hu.
Hello, Mr. Chen.
You got it wrong. This
is Mr. Qi and Mr. Han.
Mr. Nie, Mr. Liu.
There are too many CP ships
lately. I'm getting them all mixed up.
It's fine. Come on.
Come touch up their makeup.
Hey, where did you two go?
I managed to get the company to agree
to a joint magazine shoot with you guys.
That's great.
Don't you want to know how I got it?
Not interested.
Are you not interested
in me anymore either?
Was I ever?
Hurry up and shoot.
Let me.
Oh my.
Editor-in-chief, this won't
sell. It's useless to shoot this.
The two of them are
really good at selling it.
I meant the magazine.
The overseas edition will sell.
Lao Xie, take more photos.
[Fans freaking out over the magazine
shoot [which is somehow already out?]]
[Some negative comments about how BL stars are
only in it for the money, or the shoot being bad]
[Xu Wenzhu: Hello, sorry, I
won't make our meeting.
First let me apologize, and
then say that I don't like women.]
Do you know who the girl you met is?
Is your sexual orientation something
you can just talk about so casually?
You've known about my
orientation for a long time,
yet you still set me up
on blind dates with girls.
Did you show any respect to either of us?
Don't talk to me about respect.
Only normal people deserve my respect.
So,
is finding two women considered normal?
Or,
is finding even more
women even more normal?
Hello?
Hello, Brother Wenshu.
Are you in Shangjing?
What's wrong? Don't panic, take your time.
The caregiver messaged me saying
Brother Chen Zhu is in critical condition.
I bought a ticket to fly back.
Can you pick me up from the airport?
What time do you arrive?
9:30.
Okay, I'll wait for you at the airport.
The flight is delayed.
I don't know when I can leave.
I've been in touch with the caregiver.
He's keeping me updated
on Chen Zhu's condition.
He's stable for now.
Just wait for your flight calmly.
Let me know when you board.
I'm afraid I won't get
to see him one last time.
You're Qingtian.
Auntie, how is Brother Chen Zhu doing now?
Don't you dare say my son's name!
Get out!
This is all your fault!
You caused my son's car accident! Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Uncle, Auntie,
I'm Chen Zhu's high school classmate,
class monitor Wenshu.
I'm here to visit him on
behalf of our Class 2 alumni.
We don't need this.
Do you think if you all come,
my son will wake up?
Will he wake up?
It's you. It's all your fault.
It's all your fault!
Why did you have to ruin him?
Why my son?
Why did it have to be my son?
There are so many boys in Class 2,
and even the class monitor is here.
Why did you have to be gay with him?
Why my son?
You're gay!
Why did you have to go after him?
My son, why did it
have to be you? My son...
Fasten your seatbelt.
[Messages sent from the caregiver to both of them
saying Chen Zhu is out of danger and not to rush]
I'm not going anymore.
As long as I'm still your father,
I will never let you be with a man.
Damn it, do you even know how to drive?
You...
Is our son sick?
He got into the car
accident while calling me.
It's so hot.
It smells bad. My hand is burnt.
Keep yesterday's tea cake for me.
Keep it until when?
Keep it until we can stand
proudly in front of everyone.
Okay, I'll have my cousin put it in
the temperature-controlled tea cellar.
Xu Jinbai wants to see you.
Your dad?
I came out to my mom.
She'll definitely tell Old Xu.
But I didn't expect it to be this soon.
What do you want me to do?
Just be yourself.
Why didn't you bring
the director here to shoot?
It's a secret base.
It can't be shared with anyone else.
I don't like winding mountain roads.
They're like tracks.
Too narrow and too crowded.
Only at the end of the
tracks is the open wilderness.
We're having dinner at
Changyang's place tomorrow.
He said we don't need to bring anything.
Bring a dozen signed photos.
Photo cards work too.
Get lost.
He brought so many gifts
when he came over last time.
It wouldn't be right if I
didn't bring anything, would it?
He's someone who's used to giving gifts.
As they say, he has high
emotional intelligence.
Do you?
Are you calling me socially inept?
Low EQ just means being
straightforward and direct.
It's also a virtue.
Are you afraid his family won't like you?
Not really.
I just can't explain it.
Brother, are you serious?
About what?
About Changyang.
Doesn't it look like it?
Your acting has improved a lot.
I just feel that if I lose him,
there will never be anyone better.
Selfish.
All you think about is
your own gains and losses.
Then what was your
relationship with Chen Zhu?
I guess it was love.
If he dies,
I won't go on living either.
Tian.
You wouldn't actually do
something so foolish, would you?
I'm just kidding.