Hey!
Are you a ghost?
You walk without a sound.
No wonder, you're pounding herbs so loud.
Ren Feifan, act like a decent human.
All these years you were gone,
I was the one caring for her and her mom.
Fine.
Miss Jiang, please accept my humble bow.
Oh, cut it out.
With that silver tongue of yours,
you could coax sparrows from the trees.
Did you come just to mock me?
Spit it out. What is it?
Ren Feifan,
don't you think
Ruo Jin is a bit different than before?
She is a bit different.
She's become
much more resilient than before.
That's a good thing.
What?
Do you think something's wrong with...
Where'd he go?
Vanished again.
Feifan, time to wake up!
You slept so soundly.
You're awake.
I... I was just...
How did you sleep last night?
Pretty well.
What about you?
Is your cold any better?
I still don't feel that great.
Then let me go prepare your medicine.
No need.
I've got some here. I already bought it.
Let me prepare it for you.
Hold on.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong with this medicine?
The smell of Aconite.
It's the same as that prescription.
Where did you buy this?
From the pharmacy nearby.
What are you doing here?
Weren't you watching Premier Medical Hall?
What am I doing here?
You never call me when there's a fight.
I came all the way back from abroad,
not to babysit your place.
Then what do you want?
Do you know for four years abroad,
I trained in European-style Taekwondo?
So?
So...
Watch this!
Nobody move!
Behave yourselves!
Don't move!
Alright, we've got the evidence.
Time to go see Wang Chengren.
Time to take down the big boss.
Right.
I, Young Master Gu, can handle it alone.
How could you handle it alone?
Hello?
A huge crowd just showed up.
Alright.
I'll head back right now.
Young Master Gu,
we'll do it your way then.
Go see Wang Chengren yourself.
Remember,
just hand him over to the police.
Don't complicate things.
You're not joking with me, are you?
No, I'm not.
This is our final showdown.
You're not gonna finish it with me?
A crowd swarmed Premier Medical Hall.
They can't handle it.
I have to rush back right away.
Besides, compared to fighting,
I prefer saving lives.
What's wrong?
Young Master Gu, are you scared?
Scared?
I, Young Master Gu, fear no one.
I love things like punishing the wicked.
You old bastard!
Trying to run?
What are you gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
Eliminate a public menace, of course.
I've come to finish you off!
Wang Chengren, you're one sick freak.
Dragging the whole city down with you.
You're an animal.
Don't...
Stay away from me!
Animal?
I'm the animal?
They're the animals.
What do those people have?
Nothing at all.
Can't even afford three meals a day.
People living like ants,
what's the difference if they live or die?
My life is worth a thousand times theirs.
They trade their lives for money.
They're all test subjects for my drugs.
Your drugs?
So you don't make drugs to save people,
but to save your own life.
I...
Is saving myself a crime?
One dies, the family gets rich. Good deal?
Still trying to fight me, you old fossil?
The pills!
My pills!
I was wrong to insult you.
I insulted the animals.
Animals are way better than you.
I can't die!
I still have so much money!
What are you doing here?
If you can't say anything nice, shut up.
Ruo Jin said you wanted our ER records.
Yeah.
I brought them for you.
You brought them?
Yeah.
Did you organize all these yourself?
Obviously. We psychiatrists
also had to finish every
basic course in med school, okay?
Alright, alright, fine.
What, are they no help?
I need to study them first to know that.
Which herb are you still missing?
How about I take a look for you?
Western medicine might offer a new angle.
What are you doing?
My beauty-enhancing pomegranate juice.
Men can't drink it!
I didn't drink it.
You'd better not.
Did you add Herbal extract to it?
Yeah.
That's no big deal in Western medicine.
Why didn't I think of that?
Isn't Chinese patent medicine made so?
It's a piece of cake.
Glad I could help.