Only then did I realize the drug was highly unstable
and could cause severe adverse effects.
But the Wang Group discovered this drug.
They're morally bankrupt
and driven purely by profit.
They tried to force my parents to hand it over.
My parents refused.
So they murdered my parents
and had me framed and imprisoned.
What nonsense are you spouting?
This is slander!
I'll sue you!
If what I said was false,
why are you so worked up, Young Mr. Wang?
Triggered?
If you don't want your daughter to die,
get the hell out of here now.
Then I might spare this little thing.
While Ruojin was attending the wedding as promised,
what do you think I was doing?
Da Long wasn't by his side.
That was our way in.
You eat first, I need the wrapper.
Thanks.
Stop right there!
No!
Don't do this, Daddy!
Yixin, are you okay?
Daddy!
Yixin is fine.
Big Brother Da Long took great care of me.
Come on, let's go with Daddy.
Wang Wenhao!
You incited murder, kidnapping, extortion,
and ruined a Family of TCM practitioners.
You ran illegal experiments.
The evidence is ironclad.
This time,
you won't escape.
Dad!
Say something, Dad!
None of this was my doing!
I truly never imagined
you'd commit such evil behind my back.
You unfilial son!
Dad!
I'm your own son!
Why are you doing this to me?
A child's misdeeds are the father's fault.
That you've turned out like this,
much of the blame lies with me.
Just go and serve your time.
Wang Wenhao,
you're suspected of murder and other crimes.
Dad!
Come with us.
Dad, save me!
Dad!
Satisfied now?
Wang Chengren.
You murdered my parents.
This is only the beginning.
But I've got to hand it to you.
You'd even throw your own son under the bus.
You may have escaped today,
but you won't escape tomorrow.
The next one
will be you.
I harmed your parents?
Ren Feifan,
your parents died because of you.
You're the real reason.
Don't you feel even the slightest guilt?
Ruojin
It's been hard on you.
Hey, hey, he's proposing!
Xu Ruojin
Will you marry me?
Say yes! Marry him!
Marry him! Marry him!
Yes, I will.
The grand hall shines in splendid silks
Fair day, fine scene, music resounds
Today we raise our cups to kin and friends
True love unites a perfect pair
Wonderful!
Bravo!
Hold on
Are we really using Wang Wenhao's wedding?
Only a fool turns down a freebie
The money we save will all go to you and our daughter
But we haven't collected the gift money yet
That's right
Congratulations.
You finally got Wang Wenhao locked up.
Congratulations to you too.
Your wife and daughter are safe.
I...
You...
You go first.
I came to thank you.
And also...
to say goodbye.
Are you leaving Beishi?
My editor loved the Wang family story.
So I got transferred to Gangshi.
Congratulations.
That's a promotion, isn't it?
Feifan.
Are you really married?
Yes.
We crashed Wang Wenhao's wedding yesterday.
And got married.
But later on,
I'll still hold a proper ceremony.
I want to give Ruojin a perfect ending.
Make sure you come when I invite you.
Do you really love her?
Or is it because she had your child?
Our paths diverge,
we won't meet again.
We won't meet again.
Are you a ghost?
Sneaking around without a sound.
Hero Ren,
you sure have a lot of female admirers.
Ruojin even had a daughter with you,
and raised her all on her own.
I'm warning you,
you'd better rein in that wandering heart.
Or else I...
What did I ever do to deserve this?
Here's the prescription.
Go to the back to get it filled.
Okay, thank you.
Next.
Recently,
many citizens have mysteriously developed
strange symptoms of bleeding
from the mouth and nose.
It has caused significant panic.
Experts are currently studying the patients.
The child's symptoms are a bit severe
but he should recover, don't worry
When will it be my turn?
Let me take a look
Please examine me
Hold it down
Press here
Wait for me outside
Keep holding it
Doctor
Sir, sir
Help, doctor!
There are still many people waiting outside
What illness do they actually have?
Their pulses show no major abnormalities
but their symptoms
are very similar to the patients
we saw in Wang Wenhao's lab
but theirs are more complex and severe
Could it be this isn't over yet?
Wang Wenhao isn't the only one behind it.
Let's take care of them first
Why isn't it my turn yet?
Hello, have you eaten anything unusual lately?
Have you eaten anything unusual recently?
Hello?
You have to answer our questions
so we can treat you
Is your stomach hurting?
Where does it hurt, sir?
Head
Does this hurt, sir?
Sir
Sir!
Give me your hand
How is it?
The condition is under control for now
but we have to treat the root cause
To truly cure it,
we have to find the source of the illness
Mr. Wang, the drug's formula has been changed
Excellent. Release it to the market
But the aconitine in it is highly toxic
I'm afraid
Afraid of what? Just do it
Why aren't you asleep this late?
I can't sleep
I wanted to keep you company
You're so sweet
How's your investigation going?
I checked all the patients' connections,
and found nothing unusual
I suspect Wang Chengren must be involved
but I have no proof
It's fine, we can take our time investigating.
What's that? It smells so nice
Perilla, mint, clove
and also
the moxa you made back then
You still have it?
Mm-hm
It's getting late
Go back and rest first
I'll head back after finishing this
Okay, but hurry up too
Don't stay up too late
I'm really leaving now
Hurry up, don't work too late
Okay