We did it.
North City is saved.
Hey, Ruo Jin.
We succeeded.
North City is saved.
Hurry back.
Really? I'll rush back after grocery shopping.
Have Ning Le stay for dinner.
Lao Jiang, Ruo Jin said
you should stay for dinner tonight.
No way am I having dinner with you two.
I'm not being your third wheel.
Alright.
I'm off.
I won't see you out.
Don't mention it.
Bye.
Thanks, Ning Le.
Pomegranate Seed tastes sour.
Warm the middle and strengthen the stomach.
Though this is a common item,
it can strengthen the foundation.
Got it?
Mm-hmm.
Mm, so sour!
Feifan.
Help me trim the celery, would you?
I'm still not done with this medicine.
Hurry up.
Where are you going?
I've still got food cooking inside.
Fine.
Congratulations, junior brother.
Senior sister.
Why are you back?
With something this big happening in North City,
of course I had to come back and check.
I even brought an admirer of yours.
Mr. Ren, I've heard so much about you.
I'm a director at the Meniersen Group.
Come.
This is Mr. Sen, an old friend of my father's.
He wants to take you somewhere.
Where?
Don't you trust me?
Just come with me.
Ruo Jin, I'm stepping out for a bit.
Okay.
Feifan, Feifan.
Take the herbal tea with you.
Feifan.
Ren Feifan.
Is he going to leave me again?
He won't forgive me.
Ruo Jin.
Look at me.
It's me, Ning Le.
Ning Le.
Wang Wenhao has been arrested.
Wang Chengren will never let this go.
What do we do? They're going after Feifan again.
What do we do? What do we do?
What do we do, Ning Le? What do we do?
It's okay.
It won't happen, it won't.
What do we do?
Ruo Jin, Ruo Jin.
Don't you worry.
That old scoundrel Wang Chengren
has already been put away by yours truly.
He'll never mess with your family again.
Right, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's all my fault.
It's all me. I got Feifan's mother killed.
You didn't.
It's all my fault, all my fault.
Ruo Jin.
Think about Yixin.
You still have Yixin, right?
She's your child with Feifan.
She won't leave you.
Think about Yixin.
Right.
Ruo Jin.
Feifan will be back any minute.
We'll wait here with you.
Okay?
Right, Yixin.
Right.
We still have Yixin.
I had another episode just now, didn't I?
Yeah.
Jiang Ning Le.
How could you hide something this big so well?
Tell me, do you have feelings for Feifan too?
Me?
Gu the Poor Sap.
Your mind takes so many twists and turns,
even GPS would get lost.
Xu Ruo Jin is my best friend.
How could I steal her man?
You'd better not.
Then why are you hiding it from Feifan?
Dude, I'm a psychiatrist.
Without a patient's permission,
I can't disclose their condition to anyone.
That's called professional ethics.
Besides,
I already hinted at it to Ren Feifan.
But he thinks Ruo Jin acts perfectly normal around him.
That's because he hasn't seen her having an episode.
If it's hard for you to tell him, I will.
I have to get back to the hospital for my shift.
I wonder,
could someone bring me a cup of coffee?
Coffee.
Oh.
Something this big,
this young master has to handle it personally.
This patient has congenital leukemia.
It's one of our cases here.
Using our current technology,
we can reach a clear diagnosis quickly.
Is this kind of tech common now?
This is our company's AI diagnostic device.
Mr. Ren, take a look.
Hua Tuo is also examining him?
Yes.
Look again.
This conclusion comes from big data.
You could say our AI
has created a virtual Hua Tuo,
using the real Hua Tuo's data to treat patients.
Then show me other doctors.
Do other doctors share this diagnosis?
Yes.
We've input a vast amount of medical
theoretical knowledge and clinical experience.
It's extremely helpful for diagnosis.
So you brought me here
to input my information and experience?
Yes.
Rather than just inputting information,
what we really want is to buy your formula.
Can this AI medical system
truly bring my formula to more people?
Feifan.
What are you thinking about?
Dad.
Today my senior sister and I
went to Meniersen Group to see that AI medical system.
You know what?
It diagnoses ten times faster than me.
Before I've even finished checking the pulse,
it's already written the prescription.
Watching that AI, I thought,
you know,
North City has so many people who struggle to see a doctor.
Maybe they wouldn't even need to leave home
to get their illness treated.
And through it, we could heal even more people.
Maybe
this AI medical system really is a good thing.
Dad,
should I sign with Meniersen Group?
A doctor's duty is to save lives and heal.
Whether it's AI or you and me,
anything that benefits patients
should be promoted.
If you've made up your mind,
whatever you want to do,
Dad will support you.
Come, sit down.
Okay.
Can AI truly bring my formula
to more patients?
But behind that seemingly efficient precision,
is there really nothing hidden,
no unknown secrets?
Feifan, Feifan.
There's something I have to get off my chest.
Spit it out, make it quick.
I've got things to do.
Xu Ruo Jin has a split personality.
I didn't say it, that sourpuss Ning Le did.
Do you have proof?
Yes.
Right here.
Split personality has histrionic, paranoid, and depressive types?
Yeah.
How is this any different
from the mumbo jumbo of those street fortune tellers?
Mr. Gu, you don't even believe in ghosts, but you buy this?
This is science.
Split personality refers to
a patient possessing different selves,
able to simultaneously display
different identities and personality traits.
Speak plainly.
As the man who shares her bed,
you really haven't noticed anything off about Xu Ruo Jin?
She's obsessed with revenge.
Don't seek revenge. It's too dangerous!
I don't want you to repeat what happened four years ago.
Don't repeat
the dead end
from four years ago.
You're not Xu Ruo Jin.
Get away.
Feifan, love me one more time, please?
Ruo Jin really has changed a lot,
but four years is a long time.
It's perfectly normal for her to change.
Do you really not get it, or are you just refusing to face it?
If this personality keeps resurfacing,
one bigger shock and she'll crash completely.
Dr. Ren, Dr. Ren!
I'm Nini's father.
I'm begging you, save my daughter.
I remember.
Doctor, let me tell you,
their patented drugs are just way too expensive.
My family has no money.
I can't afford it.
I saw you this morning.
I know you're an excellent doctor.
I know you can save her, doctor.
Please, save my Nini!
Please, get up.
I'm begging you.
Feifan.
I asked doctors who used to work at Meniersen Group.
Once a formula is signed over to them,
apart from Meniersen Group,
no one else, not even the original owners,
can ever use that formula again.
So their so-called "benefiting patients worldwide"
is just a scheme to swindle formulas from others,
then sell the drugs at outrageous prices,
profiting off sick patients.