Where did you buy this coffee? It doesn’t smell the same.
Check the CCTV for me. I need to know.
There’s only one camera angle, right? Then find another one. Find out who it was.
You smelled something strange?
What kind of smell?
The scent isn’t clear. Not like a normal Alpha’s.
What do you mean?
Maybe you should get your secondary gender checked first.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Shit
Damn it
Do not move that hard
you just get up
You might feel headache
aww
see?
I told you
aww
I got a bad headache
What are you doing?
Do not be afraid
I'll take responsibility for you
responsibility?
Why did you have to take responsibility?
Do not tell me that you
You got bitten by me
bitten?
Why did you bite me?
Are you a dog?
This is so hurt
You got bitten by me
We've already formed a bond
bond?
What bond?
Wait, Are you alpha?
This is not fair
Then why did you bite me?
I..
Can not control my self
wait
If you are alpha
and you just bite me
then what am I?
You are Omega
Omega!?
impossible
so you have no idea about Alpha Omega?
Well, I've heard
You got bitten by me
I'll take responsibility for you
You can't fall for anyone else now
You're mad
It's just a small bite
why can't I fall for anyone
even though
I am not thinking about get into relationship
you have to stay with me
Don't you understand?
We don't even know each other
and this mark of small bitten
You do not have to take responsibility for anything
You're stubborn
I am not stubborn!
You're mad
Why did you bite stranger?
I don't even know you
Why?
You want to be a dog?
your smell good
I used perfume before I left my home
Do you want it?
I got lots
If you want I will bring it for you
So you do not have to bite other stranger
That's not the point
Your Smell
It's only you
It's unique
Alpha and Omega
each individual has a unique smell.
like your smell from you
It's smell like cold rain
mixed with dry mud
What about your smell?
Do not be shy
When I first smell you
I want to kiss you
I didn't allow you to kiss me
It's all about pheromones
Your smell type is my favourite
If you release pheromones
I want to kiss you instantly
If you do not believe me
try to release pheromones your self
Who can do it like you anyway?
What's that smell?
how to release it?
Did you just fart?
Well, why your fart smell so good?
You can do it
just focus
and release it
Hey
Calm down, Brother
Get out!
Do not threaten me
If you’re this possessive, it means…
my future sister-in-law?
None sense
I bite him
Shit!
Did you really bite him?
What are you going to do?
Do you have to get married?
I'll tell dad
I said I haven’t thought about it yet.
well
Let's not disturb you
just incase you want to
Where are you going?
go back home
you can't
you have to stay here
why I can not go back home?
Did you chain my legs?
Alpha and Omega that just bonded
shouldn't separate
I do not understand
I'll go back home
You're stubborn
I am not
If you're not stubborn then stay here!
No decent omega would leave their bonded mate
If a decent one that you were talking about
Are the one who bite the stranger
I do not wish to be a decent one then
You have no idea
yeah right
I know nothing
I got bitten and you brought me here
and you force me to stay
I do not want to stay here
Fine!
you can leave now!
So you will see
what will happen
fine
I'll go now
Don’t chase me away
Phat
Please wait
You look pale
I told you many time
do not hang out that often
let me have a look
your under-eyes are really dark.
Even though my under-eyes are dark
I am still handsome
one more thing
I didn't hangout last night
then where were you?
Well, just some issue
I already took the test
Really
let's have a look
that you
are alpha or not
Phat
You are Omega
Is it strange?
If we talk about percentage
in 10 persons
Could be 7 beta
and could be 2 alpha
and the last
could be omega
well it is ten percentage
If you are talking about "normal omega" then yes
check your test report once again
the information shows that you are "pure omega"
this is so rare
These days
there is hardly find this kind
you are
one in a million
That's overacting
It's not that rare
This is not a joke. Pat
Pure omega
and omega
are so difference
normal omega
Beautiful, sweet-smelling, and seductive
Can become pregnant and give birth
Despite being male
but the weakness
immune system is rather weak
but pure omega
General characteristics
almost like alpha in every way
and there a chance
to give birth
in Enigma type
wait a minute
I do not understand even alpha and omega
what the hell is "enigma"
well
but right now
You'd better be careful
not to get bitten by anyone
brother
so
do not tell me that you.....
Phat!
Who's bitten you?
I do not know
you must return to person who bitten you immediately
Alpha and Omega that just bonded from bitten
if they are apart
It will trigger Bond Fever
this symptom
It’s unbearable
some person
It may even lead to death from shock
it's not that bad
you must return to him immediately
I just told you
never!
Last night
Naphit got invited to the police station
on charges of assault
but Nakhun and Nakin
have already spoken with our police officer
everything is under control
next time
you better be careful
and calm your self
However
It's normal at your age to involve with violent
yes dad
but last night
NaKhun brought stranger to the house
to stay overnight
Is that true?
bring stranger to our house
I will not going to condemn you
but you should do it carefully
don’t just bring random strangers home easily.
If you want to make love that much, just take them to a hotel.
Nakhun doesn’t bring just any random stranger to our house
who is that then
Is he so important
I told all of you
Not to bring stranger to our house
he is not stranger
But he is the person whom Nakhun bit
what did you say?
I never thought
You’d become so desperate that you’d lose control and start choosing anyone just to find a partner
end up bitten a stranger
You should be smarter than this
please calm down. Let your son speak first
What else is there to listen to?
An alpha who brings no value to the family like this
I’m really disappointed
Dad
Nakhun
I'm sorry
It's okay
at last he will know
Why did you bite him
I do not know
I can't control my self
The smell is so attractive to me
It's like the smell surround me
and when I realize
I already bite him
Usually, A true alpha like you has very strong self-control
Did you feel rut?
then why can't you control your self
or because
finally
met your soul mate
how is that even possible
in this world
there are some Alpha
and Omega
Fated to be together
We call them destiny-bound mate
or soul mate
It's so rare
some people may not find for the rest of his life
but some said
If you found your soul mate
you can’t resist or control your feelings toward each other
that's mean?
Nathan really found his soulmate
I do not know yet
But Nakhun already bite him
you already bonded
erm
where is he
Phat
Are you okay?
I think you should return to him
I'll never ever return to that mad dog
What temperature is the air conditioner set to?
It's so cold
It's a normal temperature
Wait for me
here
use this to cover
Ongsa
How many days have you not done laundry?
the smell is so bad
I just do the laundry yesterday
here
I can still smell the scent of fabric softener
brother
I think I can not stand anymore
I'll go back home first
Or you should return to...
I said
never
I will never ever go back to him
Why can’t I finish?
Phat
what's happening to you?
Wake up Phat
Phat what's happening?
Phat answer me!
Phat get up
I'll bring you to hospital
Phat
Let's him go
brother do not hurt him
It's okay
Phat
you!
Let me go
Who took my brother!
Don't you know that my brother is about to die!
he is going to die!
Calm down!
I said let me go
let me go!
Phatsa!
Are you under heat?
I do not know
Phatsa!
Don't you like it
I love it
If you are insist that you will do it
Don’t mind what happens next
I'll take care of you
Are you awake?
from tomorrow
You have to move and stay with me
I'll take care of you
Move and stay with you?
no I do not want to
I have my own house
and you
don't have to take care of me
we just make love
It's not a big deal
So you think that making love with me
Not a big deal?!
well it is not a big deal
I'm sorry
Please stop crying
why did you do that?
Are you mad?
You frightened me
What are you
I will not do it again
Please stop crying
If you want anything
Just tell me
I'll give you everything
Just don't do that again
Promise me
Yes I promise
why do we have to stay together
you and me
already bonded
technically
We are already couple
Alpha and Omega
when bonded
each side
will addict to smell
and sensation
of couple
So, the fact that we are together…
will be good for both me and you
but
I do not want to stay here
but I want you to
at least stay with me
Stay with me
I will give you everything
you
said like
you are asking me to get marry
in practice
me and you
are husband and wife
none sense
okay
I'll stay here
but I have condition
You must not act inappropriately with me
Do not touch me
without my permission
Is that okay?
why
Are you going to do like that again?
Is that okay?
fine
Stay there
It's okay
I'll handle it
Thank you
Let's go
Please after you
Phatsa
This is my mum
Sawasdee kub
sawasdee ja
Nakin told me that your name is Phatsa
What a lovely name
Yes
It's mean "Rain"
Your smell really like "Rain"
Your parents seem to know what names you after
Let's have breakfast together
make your self comfortable here
Think of it as if you were son
Nathan told me that
you just know that you are Omega
We are the same, I am Omega too
Thank you
yes brother
how are you
well the house is quite big
too big actually
That's Devathitirat house
one of the most powerful family
you will be more comfortable than you thought
I do not wish to be this comfortable
I just graduated and other thing
I just apply for job
But right now
you got bitten by him
It's big deal now
I didn't ask for this
and other thing
I do not want anyone to take responsibility because of this stupid bite mark
I didn't mean that way
I am just worries about you
At least
you are safe there
Ongsa
you knew it that I do not want to be Omega
I do not want to be Omega that got take care all the time
I want to work
I want to earn income
I want to live like a normal person
so that
without relying on the Devathitirat family
How about Nathan
What did he said ?
he didn't say anything
I think
he do not want to bite me as well
Poor you
Alright
Let's meet up at cafe
I"ll let you do dirty americano, oops! americano
you might feel fresher
Is that a joke?
What's that dirty americano
Okay
Can I get two cups
Thanks
for bring here and pay for the cake
This must be a reward for students with good academic performance, right?
Yes
That's lovely. Primprao really love Nongluk
Those people look suspicious
Can you just pretend
taking a walk or go shopping
I won't tell your boss
Phatsa please make your self comfortable
my only duty is just to protect you
Don't you understand
It's not protection it is more like control prisoner
how the hell can I make it comfortable
Nakhun might worries about you
Being concerned or being harassed
I’m so damn embarrassed.
Keep following me
Right now
you are the number one prospective daughter-in-law of the Devathitirat family
He might afraid he lost his wife
that's why he send all these bodyguards
Stop saying that
I am not his wife
aww goosebump
He is handsome
and he is true alpha
if he got child with you
no way
who said I am going to have child ?
I am a real man
Well the male Omega
can pregnant
not to mention that
Special Omega like you
Brother
when you are talking about how rare I am
please do not tell anyone
okay
I won't say a word
I am still your Phatsa
your brother
Do you understand
You can count on me
Can't you just go outside
It's quite hot outside
I do not want to ruin my skin
Let's have banana cake first
It's still fresh
Pat I am leaving
What are you doing here
Boss instructed me to take care of my sister-in-law’s safety at every step
Could you please stop calling me that
Your brother and I are not in any relationship at all
If you do not want me to call you sister in law
Should I call you brother in low then
none sense
If you want to go back just go back
stop talking to much
damn
I feel like I am a criminal now
then, After you
Let's go
After you
Damn you
Phatsa just return home
Bring him to me
Yes sir
Did you move your belonging to my room?
Your house is big
Can't I stay in other room
No you can't
I am not familiar
I never sleep with anyone
You have to sleep with me
This is Ai
he is my best assistance
From now on
Ai will take care of you
I can take care of my self
Ai will take care of you including your schedule
If you need anything you can let Ai know
Don't you understand
I said I can take care of my self
Hello Mr.Phatsa
If you need any assistance
you can call me anytime
What's wrong with these people
If you need anything
you can ask Ai
I'll follow your order
but
Can I go to work
your work is not necessary
I'll take care of you
So you want me to stay still?
and die of boredom?
I graduated high degree
I want to use my skill and talent
to do the actual work
you are strange
normal people
They do not want to work
your company
Is  big
Do you want new employee
that just graduated
good skill and good looking like me
will you accept me
I am good at it
fine
I'll let you assist my work
I'll tell Ai and Sila
prepare all information
At your service boss
off you go
I want to work
You misunderstanding. Phat is Omega
What?
Phatsa is Omega
I want to know
The person who can make a true alpha react this strongly
I challenge you
or are you a coward
When you’re not here, I don’t know how I should behave in this house
You’ve never been a burden to this house
From now on, don’t make the life of a beta like me any more complicated
If things keep going like this, one day I'll die of heartbreak