(Come in at the office today
to talk about the fan meeting, Kaye.)
And remember…
It has to be fun, exciting,
but heartwarming.
You copy?
That’s your homework for the day.
Oh, there he is!
Our main character.
Listen. I’ve got good news.
The pre-order for your new comic
just hit the target!
Well done!
And… my commission?
Come on. I won’t forget that.
Don’t forget either
that you wouldn’t be here today
if I didn’t give you a chance.
Fame is more important than money.
You hear me?
Look.
You gotta smile more.
Sign your autograph.
I guarantee you’ll be rich.
Alright?
Why’d you let it slide?
You’re gonna miss it.
(Following the mysterious disappearance
of Mr. Krekpol Thanupaisarn,)
(the CEO of KT Group,)
(police are currently investigating)
(and questioning
his close friends and family.)
Krekpol never disappeared like this.
He always lets me know where he’s going.
But it’s been four days.
Who knows what’s going on with him?
Who was the last person who saw him?
The maid.
She said she saw him in his office
late at night on Friday.
But he was gone by the morning.
His car is still here,
as well as his phone.
No sign of forced entry.
The security guard said
there were no visitors.
Please, officer.
No sign of struggle.
The victim is a middle aged man
with a stout figure.
If he resisted, it should have
made a mess of this room.
Maybe the victim knows his kidnapper?
Maybe…
The kidnapper had the upper hand,
such as pointing a gun at the vic,
or poisoning him.
BEST CO-FOUNDER AWARD
THAI INVESTMENT BANK, 2003
Antihypertensive.
Heart disease medication.
From the evidence,
we can conclude
that the victim was forced to disappear.
In most ransom cases,
the kidnapper makes contact
within the first two days.
But it’s been dead silent.
…Which means?
Which means the kidnapper
doesn’t want money,
they just want to take him
or…
His life.
Inspector.
We found Krekpol.
Is this some kind of Satanism?
Listen up.
Secure every bit of evidence.
The murderer didn’t just want to kill him,
they wanted to send a message.
I don’t believe there’s only one body.
Sieve through missing person cases.
Report back to me
when you find anything suspicious.
Yes, sir.
Kaye.
What happened to your arm?
It’s black and blue.
Oh.
It’s nothing.
I slipped and fell in the bathroom
this morning.
I guess it left a little bruise.
I don’t think it’s little
by the look of it.
You gotta take better care of yourself,
you know?
You’re as thin as a rake.
You need to be persistent
about your commission, you know?
Dude’s gonna pretend he forgets.
Of course.
Oh, look at that smile.
You’re too adorable when you smile, dude.
He ain’t gonna be scared
when you make a demand.
Be more firm!
Ask for your money firmly, you hear me?
Let’s get back to our beloved job,
shall we?
All good?
What?
You brought a hammer to work?
Did you plan to smash our editor’s head?
Oh, no.
I was fixing my chair at home yesterday.
It must have slipped into my bag.
It’s a hammer, not an inhaler.
It doesn’t just slip into your bag, man.
But that’s alright.
I’m borrowing it.
There’s a nail sticking out under my desk.
It tore two of my favorite pants, actually.
These are new.
Sure.
Thanks, bro.
Nice weight!
I’m just gonna take a minute.
(Yesterday at 5 p.m.,)
(police found the body of a man
in an abandoned warehouse in Bangna.)
(Initial report identifies him
as Mr. Krekpol Thanupaisarn, 52 years old,)
(the CEO of KT Group.)
(The police are working
to gather the evidence right now,)
(as well as checking all security cameras
around the area)
(and questioning everyone involved.)
Oh, they found the body.
So he’s dead?
Isn’t this the man
who swindled his company
and laid off 40,000 people?
Yeah.
Karma works fast.
And he definitely paid for it.
His time of death
was between 24-30 hours ago.
Which means the victim was held captive
three days before he was murdered.
Why three days?
Was it out of guilt?
Or were they waiting for something?
HAMMER
None of the injuries were fatal.
The murderer only meant to hurt,
likely so the victim begged for his life
until his last breath.
Hey, you’re back!
Hello?
Look at you.
You look like a zombie.
You need to sleep more.
I got you some snacks.
I’m working.
I told you not to barge in.
You probably didn’t hear it but I knocked.
Speaking of which, I need your help.
What?
You need money again?
Nope.
I have to apply for an internship
at school tomorrow.
But there’s an important appointment
I can’t miss.
Appointment? With who?
Can you get his autograph for me?
Romance manga?
Yep.
Nope. I’m not doing it.
Please.
I don’t know if I’ll ever get
another chance like this.
If I’m in the interview,
worrying about not getting
Kaye’s autograph, what will I do?
You want me to miss my internship?
Fine.
Okay.
I’ll get it for you.
You sure?
Yeah.
-Are you sure?
-I just said yes.
-You mean it?
-I do.
Give me a hug.
My bro.
But right now,
you have to go.
I’m working and I need complete focus.
Okay.
Let me see.
Hey.
Go back to your room!
-Go!
-I just need a peek.
You’re a kid. You’re not allowed.
Go.
Look.
You gotta smile more.
Sign your autograph.
(I guarantee you’ll be rich.)
Hello!
Welcome to today’s event.
This is your chance to meet
the famous comic author,
whose anthology is coming out soon.
I bet you can’t wait to meet him.
2500?
For a whole set and an autograph.
At this point, I think everyone knows him…
5500 for a VIP package?
Does a twelfth grader
really need all this?
Please welcome Mr. K.Cupid.
Hello.
Please have a seat.
How are you feeling?
Hello.
Can I have your name
and your ticket, please?
Uh… I’m here in my sister’s place.
Then please show us your ID card.
Okay.
Alright.
Miss Praew, VIP ticket.
V–VIP?
Yes, sir.
VIP ticket holders will receive a T-shirt,
the book, and autographed
exclusive posters for all three series,
and a photo session with the author.
You will receive all of these on stage.
Do I… have to take a photo with him?
Yes.
Will you pay for the ticket
with cash or by QR code?
It’s not paid?
Only the deposit, sir.
QR code?
Yes.
-All done?
-Here.
Yes.
Thank you.
-How should I do it?
-Kitty kiss.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
Hello.
What a hellish day.
I should have made Win do this.
Thank you. Don’t forget to get
some souvenirs before you leave.
Thank you.
What do you think you’re doing?
No.
I’m not doing anything.
I’m just taking some photos of Kaye.
-Let go.
-Kaye, my foot.
You held your phone too low.
I didn’t do anything!
Show me your phone.
-Let go!
-Hey.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Please let go.
Take it easy.
What happened?
Did you have to be so forceful with him?
Nothing.
I didn’t do anything.
I didn’t do anything wrong.
If you didn’t, show me your phone.
Let go!
Let go.
Let go of me.
I didn’t do anything wrong. Let go.
Let go of me!
Let go.
I didn’t do anything wrong! Let go!
Let go!
Let go of me!
We’ll let you know
when everything’s sorted out.
Thank you.
Of course.
I’m really sorry about earlier.
I thought you were attacking him.
I didn’t know he was a…
Never mind that.
Perverts at crowded events like this
are more common than you think.
Right.
Excuse me.
Would it be okay if I have a snapshot
of the famous author and our hero today?
Sure.
Of course.
Over here, please.
Allow me.
One, two…
Alright.
Can you get a little closer?
That’s nice.
Alright.
I think that’s enough.
The flash is hurting my eyes.
Oh, right.
Thank you.
Sure.
Uh, wait, wait.
I want to thank you for earlier.
If you weren’t there,
I might be in trouble.
Can I do anything to thank you for that?
That won’t be necessary.
I’ll send you the photos from the event
when I have them.
Oh, uh…
Oh, I know.
It’s… it’s alright.
Here.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
My autograph.
Please don’t tell anyone I did that.
My editor will have my head
if he finds out.
Autographs are lucrative these days,
I heard.
You can let me know
which ship is your favorite.
I’ll write it down, too.
Oh, crap.
You got it wrong.
I’m only here because my sister couldn’t.
Ugh!
-My jacket.
-Shit…
I’m so sorry.
I’m sorry.
Forget it.
It’s worth something, right?
I’ll sell it to my sister.
She tricked me into paying
for your fan meeting.
Kaye.
Please be on standby.
The fans are waiting.
This way, please.
Hello, sir.
Inspector.
Is that a celebrity’s autograph?
Right on your back.
That must be so damn exclusive.
Any updates on the case?
From the missing person files,
this one stands out.
Mr. Teerakorn Dechorattana,
the former permanent secretary
of the Ministry of Agriculture.
He’s been reported missing
for 48 hours now.
Witness pinpoints his last sighting
at his own home in Pathum Thani.
His car was gone, too.
48 hours?
Kidnap and ransom?
His position at work would make him
a lot of enemies.
What’s with the pesticide policy
all those years ago.
No…
48 hours.
Missing.
No contact.
Radio silent.
Just like the Krekpol case.
4 DAYS MISSING
1 DAY BEFORE MURDER
3 DAYS LOCKED UP
Krekpol’s autopsy shows
he was tortured for three days
before he was murdered.
Teerakorn has been missing
for two days now.
If this pattern sticks…
Are you suggesting…
This is the work of a serial killer?
I’m sure it is.
Listen up.
Based on Krekpol’s case,
he was missing for three days
before he was murdered.
Right now, Teerakorn has been missing
for two days.
That means we have 24 hours…
Or even less.
Remember this.
We’re not looking for a body.
We’re looking for a man who’s still alive.
Show me that one.
Yes?
Send me the coordinates.
I’m on my way.
FORENSIC
They want us to find the body.
This is set up for us.
I should finally really
take away that spare keycard.
I mean, it was you
who bought the room next to mine.
How come you came home in the morning?
Where’s my Kaye’s autograph?
I didn’t get it.
What?
Here.
Oh!
On your jacket?
How did you get the VIP treatment?
That’s a big autograph, too!
How’d you do that?
What the heck?
Hold on.
13500.
Pay up.
That’s too much! You must be joking.
That’s overpriced.
You want it or not?
I’m your sister!
I’m throwing it
in the washing machine, then.
Hold on, hold on.
I’m kinda broke right now.
Can I pay in installment?
Sure.
Deal. Got it.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Where’s my boxset?
5000.
I’m kidding.
Here.
Thank you.
This is insane!
That’s sick.
Hey.
You’re too young to be seeing these.
I just want a peek.
Those corpses look exactly like
a manga I read.
Manga?
I’m gonna give you a mega hit in the head.
Get out.
I’m going to bed.
Are you, though?
Yes, I am.
I’m going to sleep.
Get out.
Liar.
Do you want me to take that jacket back?
Don’t you dare!
Alright.
Beautiful.
Smells awful, though.
I should frame this.
Frames near me.
Let me see.
Hey!
Nekros!
The next candidate, please.
Oh, clumsy me.
Are you nervous?
Yeah.
Don’t rush.
Take a deep breath.
Thank you.
I’m Prim.
I’m Praew.
Be confident.
Just say what’s on your mind
in the interview.
Do your best.
Smile more.
Good job.
Thanks.
Praewphat Traikanawut.
That’s a famous surname.
But this is Thun Insight.
I don’t care about that.
We only care about your brain,
not your surname.
I remember you, you know?
From last year at my lecture.
An eleventh grader who gave me an answer…
on media ethics
and public moral satisfaction.
You know,
you have good ideas.
That’s why you’re the candidate
for this internship.
You remember?
Yeah.
Of course.
But it’s too bad.
You looked more confident that day.
I’ll give you one minute.
You can say whatever you want.
If you don’t have anything to say,
the door’s that way.
The…
The serial killer case on TV right now,
I think it’s just like…
this one underground webtoon
I’ve read before.
What’s it called?
Nekros.
How was it?
Thun liked it!
He did?
Thun said my ideas are cool!
Congratulations.
I told you you got this.
Two thumbs up!
Inspector.
Yeah?
Here’s the list
of all psychiatric patients
with a history of violence.
Most of them are currently imprisoned,
otherwise, they have alibis.
As for the people with personal grudges,
no one is especially suspicious.
There has to be a connection.
The two victims have nothing in common.
They work in different businesses.
They run in different circles.
What’s the criteria here?
(Breaking news regarding
the serial killer case)
(in which the police
are still searching for the murderer.)
(Our research found that this murderer)
(imitates the murders
in an underground manga called Nekros.)
(Whether or not that is accurate,
I implore you to decide for yourself.)
MURDER CASES IMITATE MANGA
Crap.
It’s the same.
(It begs the questions:
who writes this manga,)
(and how did they know
these murders would happen.)
(That is what we need to find answers for.)
Nop.
Yes?
Get in touch with Cyber
and find whatever there is to find
about this comic.
Yes, sir.
(If the murders are based off
the underground manga Nekros,)
(that means the police’s investigation
might be leading the wrong way.)
(The murderer chose their victims)
(and was inspired by the manga,
panel-by-panel.)
(It wouldn’t be an overstatement to say
Nekros is the murderer’s Bible.)
I guess you saw the news.
I did.
You wouldn't listen to me.
I tried to tell you,
but I bet you think I was being silly.
See?
I got my internship because of this.
You know why?
Because Thun actually listens to me,
unlike you.
Alright, alright.
It was my fault.
I’m sorry.
But I really need to know more
about this manga right now.
Can you send it to me?
I don’t have it.
Or I do?
Hey.
I mean, if you give me
that jacket for free,
I might have something for you.
Alright, alright.
Fine.
Here it is.
The author’s been
on hiatus for years, though.
I didn’t download every chapter,
by the way.
Who’s the artist?
His pen name is Mr. Kill.
He’s pretty much a niche artist,
well known among underground audiences.
Dark fantasy, you know.
You know who he really is?
No. No one does.
He’s never revealed himself.
But if you want to know,
you should try asking around
publishing houses.
His art style is unique.
I bet some editors have seen this before.
This is the last one.
If there’s still no lead,
we gotta find another way.
Yes, sir.
Let’s go.
Oh, Mr. Kaye.
Uh…
What a small world.
You…
The hero from that day.
It’s Phat. Please call me Phat.
Okay.
Do you work here?
Yes.
I’m a manga artist under this company.
What are you doing here today, Mr. Phat?
I’m here to meet someone.
I see.
But it’s good to see you.
You know, that jacket
you signed the other day.
My sister was practically screaming for it.
Not to mention the profit I got out of it.
It’s all thanks to you.
Thank you.
I’m glad my autograph
is at least profitable.
I thought you’d get mad at me
for ruining your jacket.
Of course not.
Seeing you smile makes it all worth it.
Please.
Thank you.
Inspector, the editor’s in today.
We might find something here, after all.
Excuse me.
Yes?
We’re here to see Editor Vichai.
Is something the matter?
We’re looking for the artist
behind this manga.
Can I see?
This way, please.
Yes.
-Editor.
-Oh, hey, Kaye.
These people are here
to see an artist of ours.
Oh?
Where are you rushing off to, Mr. Kaye?
Well, then, Mr. Kaye…
This way, please.
Yes, Nop?
Who’s missing?
How long?
I’m on my way.
He even drew a heart, huh?
Hey.
Do you recognize this artist?
Excuse me.
Other people wouldn’t panic like that
even when he’s being cornered.
Only someone with a secret does.
Mr. Kaye.
The man whose autograph is on your jacket.
You need to stay
where I can see you. 24/7.
You go where I go. Eat where I eat.
Sleep where I sleep.
Are you for real?