♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 17=
(Qingning Hall)
Eunuch Xu,
tell us already!
How is
His Majesty?
Is he badly hurt?
- How is His Majesty?
- Eunuch Xu, His Majesty's safety is paramount.
Please let us in
so we know he's alright.
Please, Eunuch Xu.
Your Majesty!
Please stay where you are.
Why is she allowed in?
Your Majesty.
You promised to take me to the market.
You can't leave me.
I wrote poems and painted for you.
Your Majesty.
You're awake.
I'll get the imperial physician.
No need.
I'm fine.
You wrote poems and painted for me?
Where?
Where are you hurt?
I'm not hurt.
Look.
I was faking it.
You faked it?
What's your plan?
Nan,
you're so clever.
As expected.
Who sent you?
Yan Qiu,
we may have been rivals,
but I've always admired your talent.
Why get involved with Fushou Cream?
People don't always have a choice.
I'm not saying a word.
Just kill me.
What did your boss
offer you
to earn such loyalty?
Do you realize
how many lives it destroys?
So what if I do?
I've got nothing left
to lose anyway.
Is your family being held hostage?
If you've got nothing to lose,
then take a chance.
Trust us.
We'll rescue your family.
You've seen
families destroyed by this drug.
If it were your family,
would you still stay silent?
Where
is the Fushou Cream?
It's hidden somewhere in the capital.
But I have no idea
where exactly it is.
Who's behind it?
Grand Chancellor
Hu Wenyuan.
It was him?
I never imagined
he'd hidden it so well.
Your Majesty,
if you're unharmed,
is my brother
safe too?
Your Majesty,
it's time to choose tonight's consort.
Nan,
I'm still alive.
Don't worry.
Bei.
Are you alright?
I wasn't hurt,
but I almost was.
Allow me
to explain everything.
Are you alright,
Gu Bei?
Gu Bei!
Water...
What?
Water?
I'll get it.
Water.
Gu Bei.
I haven't...
Take off your clothes and let me check.
I'm good with sewing.
I'll do it.
I...
I'm not hurt.
It's just dust,
not blood.
Easy.
We've completed phase one.
Is it time for phase two?
So,
you two
have another plan?
How can I help?
You can't.
Of course you can.
Your Majesty! Wake up!
Your Majesty!
Is His Majesty badly hurt?
- What do we do?
- You've left me with nothing to live for.
Exactly.
- (Xiao Ce,)
- Your Majesty!
(your time has finally come.)
Your Majesty!
How was my acting?
Perfect.
You're good at everything you do.
I'm standing right here, you know.
That's enough.
We're faking our injuries
so they'll think
they've won.
That way,
we can lure them out.
But what if
they don't take the bait
and stay put?
Then we'll just
force their hand.
First,
we'll lower their guard,
make them relax
and get overconfident.
Even after I recover,
I can't act like my usual self.
I have to look
sick,
weak, and feeble.
Only then will they think
they have an opening
to strike.
Playing sick?
I'm an expert.
Whenever I skipped class,
remember how I did it?
This kind of thing,
you should learn from me.
First,
keep your eyes on the ground.
Droopy eyes.
That's how you look convincingly weak.
Second.
Walk like you're on clouds.
Stagger every step.
Always lead with your right foot.
What are you staring at? Learn!
Are you sure this works?
Of course it does.
Why do you think
I always got away with skipping class?
Learn the essence of it.
Three,
two,
one.
Go.
Your Majesty.
Careful, Your Majesty.
His Majesty's injuries are so severe.
Uh...
What are we going to do?
General Gu Bei risked his life to save me.
He's hurt even worse than I am.
How is he now?
Your Majesty,
Official Gu
is still unconscious.
His condition is critical.
How could this be?
Send for the imperial physicians.
They must save Gu Bei.
Your Majesty!
Blood!
This...
Please take care of yourself,
Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty!
- Take care of yourself!
With
my grave condition
and Gu Bei still unconscious,
the court
can't be left unattended.
Your Majesty!
All state affairs
shall be entrusted
to Chancellor Hu for now.
Your Majesty,
I'm old
and lacking in talent.
I'm unworthy of such a duty.
(That old fox
is an even better actor than me.)
(He even squeezed out tears.)
(I've got nothing on him.
Oscar goes to you.)
Chancellor.
I
can only rely on you.
Your Majesty!
Court is dismissed!
- Your Majesty!
- Ministers, please head back.
Please head back.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪