♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 16=
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
Why are you looking for Fushou Cream
at Xiaoyao Pavilion?
I don't know anything.
Under the Jing law,
selling Fushou Cream is punishable
by exile to the northern frontier.
Besides,
you're using drugs.
Didn't you think about your family?
My family?
Enough.
Quit giving a lecture
to someone like him.
If you know what's good for you,
you'd better confess now.
I told you, I know nothing.
What right do you have to arrest me?
Let me out!
Someone!
Help!
Tough nut, aren't you?
Proceed to the final step.
What are you doing?
Easy there, tough guy.
We're just checking your condition.
Go.
Let me out!
What are you doing?
You're so weak,
and you're still doing drugs?
I don't know anything.
More.
I'll talk!
I'll tell you everything.
Well.
People in the capital
are selling the Fushou Cream.
How?
They pack the Fushou Cream
inside Xiaoyao Cream boxes.
It looks just like face cream.
Where's your supplier?
How would I know?
Put me down!
We shut down Zuixian House,
yet Fushou Cream is everywhere
in the capital.
They switched from wholesale
to street sales.
That makes them harder to catch.
Taking them on one by one won't be easy.
But we can
catch them all at once.
How?
We'll make good use of Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Let's set a trap.
A sting operation.
Could you be a little more specific?
Well...
Before...
No.
Didn't they use
Xiaoyao Cream
as a front to sell drugs?
Now that
you've stopped wholesale,
they're bound to panic.
So
you want me to resume wholesale?
Exactly.
Not only that,
we're going all out.
We'll hold a huge sale.
The more you buy, the more you save.
That way,
we can secretly watch the bulk buyers.
We'll follow the trail
and find
who's behind the drug trade.
Business at Xiaoyao Pavilion
has been great lately.
But
most of our customers are women.
If we're throwing a huge sale,
I'm afraid
it won't draw enough attention.
Xiao Ling
managed to bring this place
back from the brink.
As her brother
and the Emperor,
this time,
I'll be
your spokesperson.
(The Best Pavilion in the World)
Bold, powerful strokes.
A remarkable piece of calligraphy.
Eunuch Xu,
have this plaque beautifully mounted.
Yes, Your Majesty.
My ministers,
tomorrow marks Xiaoyao Pavilion's
first anniversary.
Why don't you join me
in presenting this plaque
to General Gu?
What do you think?
Your Majesty,
though Official Gu is your trusted aide,
Xiaoyao Pavilion is still private property.
I'm afraid it may invite criticism.
Chancellor Hu, I disagree.
Though privately owned,
much of its profits go to the treasury.
It has contributed greatly to Jing.
You're right, Your Majesty.
Not only should we go,
but we should also invite more people.
Summon the ministers from the Ministries
of Works, Justice, and Personnel.
They'll all come with us.
I obey, Your Majesty.
(The Best Pavilion in the World)
- Bravo!
Thank you, Your Majesty, for this honor.
To celebrate our anniversary,
everything is buy one, get one free.
And all services are half price.
Enjoy yourselves,
and happy shopping!
- Bravo!
- Everything's half price today!
- Your Majesty.
Follow me.
Free samples here!
Come on.
Today,
everything is half price.
The Snow Cream  smells wonderful
with just one dab. You'll look years younger.
Come get yours.
Come!
Take a look at our Snow Cream.
- Look at the texture.
- We have gift sets too!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
We're outside the palace.
Let's leave rank behind.
We're all guests here.
No need for formalities.
Just enjoy yourselves.
Please spare my brother.
That's easy.
Just do as you're told,
and he'll be safe.
Kill Gu Bei.
Then you and your brother
will both be free.
What?
Can't do it?
You've fallen for him?
I
will carry out the mission.
Official Gu,
congratulations.
May Xiaoyao Pavilion prosper
throughout Jing.
Thank you, Chancellor Hu.
Your private room is ready.
This way, please.
Congratulations!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you. Please.
Well?
Did you notice anything?
I thought I saw Yan Qiu.
Are you sure?
I only saw her back.
I can't be certain.
Eunuch Xu.
Take the Imperial Guards
and search every corner of Xiaoyao Pavilion.
Yan Qiu may be here.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Official Gu.
Hearing about today's celebration,
I had a golden lock crafted
as a small gift.
You're too kind, Official Li.
Your private room is ready.
As soon as everyone is seated,
we'll serve the dishes.
This way.
Your Majesty.
Congratulations!
Official Qian.
- Official Xi. Please.
- Congratulations!
(Xiaoyao Pavilion)
Well?
Any leads?
Today's promotion is pretty generous.
Sales are several times higher
than usual.
But
if someone's buying in batches
and splitting up their orders,
it'll be hard
to track them down.
Your Majesty!
- Someone! Fetch the Imperial Physician!
- Your Majesty!
- Fetch the Imperial Physician!
Gu Bei!
Your Majesty!
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪