♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 14=
Your Majesty,
what's bothering you?
About my empress.
- Your Majesty!
(Honoring Learning and Confucianism)
Out of the way.
Wait for me.
- Your Majesty.
What is going on here?
Your Majesty.
- You can't always show Gu Nan such favor.
- Your Majesty.
Today, you have to
spend some time with us.
Your Majesty,
I've just had a new silk dress made.
You must see it.
Your Majesty.
Gu Nan...
Your Majesty,
I've learned a new pastry recipe.
You must come try it at my place.
- Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty. Come to my palace.
Have a taste.
What did you put
in the soup?
I added
sea cucumber,
abalone,
and shark fin.
I...
I'm allergic to seafood.
Your Majesty.
The moon passes the red pavilion, through
carved windows, upon the sleepless.
Your Majesty.
You laughed, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I don't know what got into
Concubine Chun,
Noble Lady Li, and Consort Yu.
They wouldn't leave me alone.
They must've seen me
promoted to Noble Consort
and now want Your Majesty's favor too.
How about
I issue an edict
to disband the imperial harem?
They can
go home and find husbands of their own.
No.
They've done nothing wrong.
If they're suddenly sent away,
wouldn't they
become the laughingstock?
True.
But this can't
go on forever.
They've been confined
to the palace for so long.
It's only natural
they would feel lonely.
They've money, property, and no debts.
Which is to say
they've got too much free time.
Bei,
what brings you here?
I was going to invite you two
to Xiaoyao Pavilion to try some new dishes.
But I overheard someone
competing with my sister
for Your Majesty's favor,
so I came to see for myself.
Stop teasing me.
Help me think of something.
People only have so much energy.
If they've got that much spare time,
all you have to do
is help them burn some of it off.
Oh, right.
Bring Xiao Ling along too.
She looks like
she's got too much energy as well.
Now
here's what you're going to do.
You Central Plains ladies
are too delicate.
Don't worry.
Train with me,
and you'll be tougher
than the men on the grasslands.
Let's go.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't.
I give up.
What are you looking at?
Get up and keep training.
Monster!
- You...
Ow!
It hurts!
I can't take this anymore.
All right.
How do you feel?
Feeling any better
after that stretch?
I do feel a lot looser.
That's amazing.
I told them to work out.
How did you end up joining them?
It has been days
since I've had Qinghuan cakes.
Your Majesty,
you're the Emperor.
Having a palace full of consorts
is only natural.
I've never expected
to have you all to myself.
But
why are you so good to me?
Though the Weak Water
stretches three thousand li,
I take but one ladle.
To me,
love is meant for
one person
for life.
Right!
I've prepared
some gifts for you.
See if you like any of these.
You don't like them?
I...
I'm actually
not very good at making girls happy.
It was all Gu Bei.
He said girls love getting gifts.
I can't believe I listened to him.
If you don't like them,
we could
go on a date.
We could also go fishing
in the imperial garden.
The peonies are in bloom.
We...
Your Majesty, I have a memorial.
Your Majesty has long
ascended the throne,
yet the position of Empress
remains vacant.
I humbly ask Your Majesty
to appoint an Empress soon
to reassure the people.
I think
you make a good point.
Consort Nan
holds a special place in my heart.
I intend to make her Empress.
What do you all think?
Your Majesty,
I don't think
it's a good idea.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪