♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 13=
You're awake.
Your Majesty.
Were you here the whole night?
You were hurt because of me.
Of course,
I would stay by your side.
Promise me.
You must never risk your life
for me again.
I...
I'm sorry.
I wasn't reproaching you.
It's just that
I hate seeing you hurt.
It breaks my heart.
I've been so occupied
with court affairs
that I never understood
how you truly felt.
I've neglected you.
Your Majesty.
The man we caught last night
confessed everything.
(Wang Cheng's Confession)
This is outrageous.
Someone's actually dealing drugs in Jing.
They sell Fushou Cream.
No wonder the Zuixian House
is packed every day.
Once you're hooked,
it'll bankrupt families
and tear them apart.
Given Jing's climate and soil,
we can't grow such a crop here.
The Fushou Cream
must've come from the Western Yi.
I can't believe someone
sold out the country for personal gain,
working with foreign barbarians
to bring this drug into Jing.
We suspected all along
that Zuixian House had powerful backers.
Now we've found Fushou Cream here.
The mastermind
must be someone inside the court.
Without protection
from high-ranking officials,
there's no way it could've
reached the capital so easily
and been sold so openly.
Corruption can be punished.
Fractional strife can be dealt with.
But drug trafficking
can bring down an entire nation.
Bei,
we both know
how devastating drugs can be.
The current situation
is no longer about
the two of us surviving.
It's about
the nation
and its people.
We have to expose
the mastermind
and wipe out this scourge
once and for all.
Bei,
I know you want a carefree and easy life.
Yet I keep dragging you
into all these intrigues.
Even if I enjoy an easy life,
I know there can be no peace
when the country is in turmoil.
Taking it easy isn't giving up.
I simply refuse
to be consumed by the world.
I don't work hard
to win any competition either.
I do it
to protect the people I care about.
(Zuixian House, The Best Massage Parlor)
That's all?
Where is the rest?
No more.
That's everything.
Impossible.
Zuixian House was doing huge business.
This wouldn't even last two hours.
I've searched everywhere.
This is all I found.
I thought it was strange too.
Where is Yan Qiu?
She escaped.
By Your Majesty's order,
we raided Zuixian House,
arrested several drug traffickers,
and seized over one jin of Fushou Cream.
Unfortunately,
the owner of Zuixian House,
Yan Qiu, has vanished.
Issue a wanted notice.
Search the entire capital.
Bring her in at all costs.
Your Majesty, Zuixian House
has sold Fushou Cream for a long time,
and business has been booming.
How could they have only one jin left?
In my humble opinion,
they've hidden
most of the Fushou Cream somewhere else.
Chancellor Hu makes a good point.
Gu Bei, receive my decree.
Fushou Cream has spread
throughout the capital,
bringing ruin to the people.
I hereby appoint you Imperial Inspector
to oversee the investigation
into its trafficking.
I obey Your Majesty.
Fushou Cream
destroys families
and brings the nation to ruin.
In the name
of the Son of Heaven,
I hereby proclaim this.
Anyone involved with drugs,
official or commoner,
will be punished severely,
without exception.
Jing
shall be free of this scourge.
- Long live Your Majesty!
No!
Because of your mistake,
Fushou Cream at Zuixian House
was exposed,
and we suffered massive losses.
I know I failed you.
I swear,
from now on,
I'll never...
What makes you think
you'll get another chance?
Please.
Please spare my brother.
He's still young.
He's just a child.
That's easy.
Just do as you're told,
and he'll be safe.
Yes.
I'll do whatever you command, Master.
(Fu Qing, Consort Yu;
Shen Furong, Noble Lady Li)
(Xie Chun, Concubine Chun)
There she goes again.
Taking pastries to His Majesty.
Her brother was just promoted
to a First-rank General.
She has won His Majesty's favor.
She's only borrowing
her brother's prestige.
Jeez.
If you ask me,
Gu Nan's nothing but a temptress.
She's wrapped His Majesty
around her finger.
She's not even as pretty as I am.
I thought His Majesty
wasn't summoning anyone anymore.
Looks like I'll have to take matters
into my own hands.
Ladies,
I have something to do. Excuse me.
(Is she going to see His Majesty?)
(I'd better beat her there.)
Noble Lady Li, I have something urgent
to do too. I'll be off then.
Where's everyone going? Why the rush?
Oh no!
Are you all going to see His Majesty?
Wait for me!
(Honor Learning and Confucianism)
I've been busy
investigating the Fushou Cream case
and rooting out the drug trade.
I've neglected you these past few days.
It's time I gave some thought
to my own matters as well.
Your Majesty,
what's bothering you?
About my Empress.
- Your Majesty!
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪