♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 15=
I intend to make her my Empress.
What do you all think?
Your Majesty,
I don't think
it's a good idea.
Why not?
Though Consort Nan is virtuous,
she comes from a humble family.
Besides, her brother, Gu Bei,
commands the Imperial Guards.
Since ancient times,
have there not been enough cases
of imperial in-laws meddling in politics?
An Empress should be judged
by he character and ability,
not her family background.
As for relatives meddling in politics,
that only happens
under weak and incompetent emperors.
Official Li,
are you calling me incompetent?
Your Majesty,
I would never dare.
Your Majesty
is a wise and capable ruler.
I've always been loyal to the court.
You claim to speak for the court,
yet you make veiled attacks
on His Majesty
and malign your fellow officials.
Isn't that outright treason?
Gu Bei, that's a baseless accusation!
Your Majesty, that's not what I meant.
Enough.
Choosing an Empress is a family matter.
We'll discuss it no further.
Your Majesty,
even ordinary families
consult their elders before a marriage.
Surely the imperial family
should do the same.
Your aunt, the Princess Royal,
has been in seclusion for years.
Why not invite her back
and discuss it with her?
- Please reconsider, Your Majesty.
Very well.
I'll do as you suggest.
Summon the Princess Royal back
to the capital.
Court is adjourned.
- Long live Your Majesty.
Here you go.
(Xiaoyao Beauty Cream)
There's plenty for everyone.
Please come again.
Yes, we still have more.
This way.
There's a seat.
This way, please.
You'll have skin
just like Her Highness.
This one is our bestseller.
Here you are.
Please come again.
Here you go.
Gu Bei!
I'll be back in a moment.
What's wrong?
My arms are worn out.
I'm a princess, you know.
You've got me working like a servant.
Of course not.
Your Highness,
business is booming,
which just proves
how popular you are, right?
I've heard
my brother plans to make Gu Nan Empress.
When are you going to give me
an answer about us?
Yes. I will.
I will.
He said he wants to make her Empress,
but he hasn't done it yet.
Besides, there's still opposition in court.
Chancellor Hu said they should wait
until the Princess Royal returns.
By the way,
what's the Princess Royal like?
Will she support His Majesty?
My father
only had one sister.
The Princess Royal.
I hardly saw her growing up.
I just remember
she was devoted to Buddhism
and often left the palace
for spiritual retreats.
A Buddhist?
Then she should be pretty reasonable.
Aunt,
greetings.
(Xiao Zhaoning, Princess Royal of Jing)
You're here, Your Majesty.
Have a seat.
It's been years.
You seem much thinner
than before.
Have you been well?
Don't worry, Aunt.
I'm doing well.
Your room seems
a little too plain.
I'll have someone bring
a few decorations.
Most people ask for nothing more
than three meals a day.
Wealth and glory are but superficial.
This is more than enough.
I'll remember
your teachings, Aunt.
While I was on my way back here,
I heard
you plan to appoint an Empress.
That's right.
I wish to make Gu Nan Empress.
However, many at court oppose it.
So
I'd like to hear your thoughts.
If so many oppose it,
why are you so determined
to choose Gu Nan?
Because I love Gu Nan.
And Gu Nan
truly loves me.
In the imperial family,
schemes and suspicion are all too common.
A bond like yours
is rare indeed.
Your marriage
should be your own decision.
In that case,
I have every reason
to support you.
Thank you,
Aunt.
On my way back,
I heard all of the reforms
you've introduced.
The people say
Jing has finally found a wise ruler.
You're too kind, Aunt.
As Emperor,
my duty is to serve the people.
I want everyone in Jing
to have land to farm
and live in peace and prosperity.
You've changed
a lot.
I've carried these prayer beads
for many years.
Now
I'd like you to have them.
Consider them a gift
from the people of Jing.
May Your Majesty
enjoy a long life
and continue protecting
the people of Jing.
I've made my decision
about the Empress.
This matter is no longer open
for discussion.
Your Majesty,
the Western Yi envoys
are already on their way to the capital.
They've sent a diplomatic letter ahead.
They request that Your Majesty marry
the Ninth Princess of the Western Yi
and make her Empress to seal an alliance
between our two nations.
(To His Majesty the Emperor of Jing,
Respectfully sealed by Princess Royal)
Reject them.
Your Majesty,
the Western Yi borders Jing,
and clashes along the frontier
are frequent.
A marriage alliance
may keep the border at peace.
If they dare invade,
our cavalry will show them
the might of Jing.
Aunt.
What brings you here?
I visited
the Ancestral Shrine today and thought
I'd stop by to see Your Majesty.
I hope
I'm not interrupting.
Please have a seat.
If we agree to marry
their princess today,
what if they demand
one of our cities?
Will you hand that over too?
Your Highness,
our spies report
that the Western Yi has massed troops
along the border.
I'm concerned that refusing them outright
would give them an excuse to invade.
No one decides who my Empress will be.
Agreeing for now
could buy us valuable time.
Please reconsider, Your Majesty.
- We ask Your Majesty to reconsider.
(To His Majesty the Emperor of Jing,
Respectfully sealed by Princess Royal)
You!
Remember this well.
Jing
will never send a princess in marriage,
never pay tribute,
and never bow to another nation.
(Xiaoyao Pavilion Specials)
(Long Island Iced Tea, Mojito,
Romance of Jing, Screwdriver)
Xiaoyao Cream, please.
We're closed today.
Give me some Xiaoyao Cream.
You're a man. Why do you need it?
What's your problem?
- Fushou Cream?
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪