"Unfold"
(Episode 7)
Wear my clothes for now.
Get changed and come have breakfast.
Here.
I've washed your clothes for you.
I put the documents on the table.
By the way,
why do you carry a tape measure with you?
This is a ledger.
It contains records of organ trafficking.
Since I was sixteen,
he made me work as a cleaner.
A third of the records in this ledger
are related to organ trafficking.
They made the bodies
look like accidental deaths
or suicides.
Once they fooled the police,
they had me do the final house cleaning.
And I wasn't adopted either.
He kidnapped me.
This is all the information
from back then.
Everything will get better.
I will make them pay.
Bai Che went to the police with the ledger.
Now the port is locked down.
The police won't find anything on us.
Who cares about the police?
With the port locked down,
how am I supposed to ship the goods?
If I can't deliver on time,
how am I going to pay the penalty?
Hello?
No official announcement has been made yet,
and they already dare to
squeeze us by thirty percent.
How much
time do we have left?
Three days.
If we can't clear this up,
we'll have to pay the penalty.
If we do,
the deal goes through
at the original price.
Then,
what about Bai Che?
What do you want to do?
First, buy back the shares
from those old geezers.
Leave Bai Che alone for now.
Alright.
Then it's settled.
A'Che,
you're back.
The police were just here.
They were asking about the boss.
They said
the boss was murdered.
We know.
These past few days,
we've been dealing with this too.
I wanted to tell you,
the bookstore will be closed for now.
Don't worry, Sister Xiao Yun.
If you're really scared,
you should go away for a while.
A paid vacation.
Sister Xiao Yun,
the police will get to the bottom of this.
Once it's on the news,
you can come back.
Then...
I'll head home first.
It's good for Sister Xiao
Yun to leave for a while.
After all, those people are ruthless.
Are you afraid
they'll silence her?
Is human life
really that cheap to them?
When Lao Bai kidnapped me back then,
my parents' company
was very influential.
It caused a huge uproar in the city.
But overnight,
the tables turned.
Public opinion condemned my parents
for child neglect,
leaving me with the elderly.
The public backlash drove them to the edge,
and they jumped to their deaths.
Shortly after,
my grandmother was driven mad too.
Are you saying
someone manipulated
public opinion back then
to protect Lao Bai?
My parents' deaths
were swept under the rug.
People's attention was quickly
diverted by other hot topics.
It was as if
this whole thing never happened.
With Lao Bai's cautious nature,
dealing with someone so dangerous,
he would definitely have a backup plan.
There's a small storeroom in there.
Start searching from the inside.
I'll search from the outside in.
You haven't eaten all day.
Let me cook something for you.
I'm not hungry.
Except for Bai Che,
all the transfer contracts
have been signed.
And now Bai Che has gone missing.
The rumors online keep escalating,
and dirt on the Zhao family is everywhere.
To save his own skin, that man...
whether it's Bai Che
or us,
we all have to die.
That man?
Yu Guangming.
My old man and Lao Bai...
That old bastard's good buddy,
Yu Guangming.
The mayor.
The reason the Zhao family grew so fast,
and why Lao Bai's dirty deeds
never caused any trouble...
Without Yu Guangming,
they would have died dozens of times over.
Now that Lao Bai is dead
and Bai Che found the ledger,
aren't they afraid?
They're scared to death.
So what do you plan to do?
Cheng Fan,
if I asked you to do
something very dangerous,
would you do it?
Yes.
Without asking why?
Without asking.
Zhao Lingye,
I need you to promise me one thing too.
Name it.
Don't die.
[A letter from Yu
Guangming from 1965]
Yu Guangming.
Bai Che.
(Unknown number: Come to
the abandoned building alone)