Gao Zhun!
I was raped.
By a man.
Lin Lin is over there.
Go to her. Don't worry about me.
I'm not going.
Come with me.
Okay?
Trust me.
Okay.
[Episode 6]
I texted Lin Lin.
I told her to go home.
You spoke about it.
That's good.
I like your courage.
But it's not enough.
What else do you want me to do?
I already told you.
I've bared myself to you.
I know.
You did well.
But I need you to tell me everything.
Every detail.
Every feeling.
That's the only way...
I can help you.
I know you can do it.
I don't know who he is.
I don't know why.
Got it.
I'll arrange for someone to handle it.
It won't affect the progress.
It was late.
I was asleep at home.
But there was a problem at the exhibit.
I had to go to the site.
So, I went to the basement to get my car.
It's okay.
Just follow the plan.
That's all.
Who are you?
Darn it.
No!
Let me go!
I'll give you money.
So, you're hooking up with me?
No.
Get lost.
In the end, he took a lot of pictures.
Pictures of my face.
I even hated myself.
Why didn't I have the strength to fight him?
Did you call for help?
Answer me!
I couldn't do it.
I was more afraid of
being seen with him on top of me
than what he did to me.
So, you endured it.
Back then...
was it face-to-face?
Are you trying to help me
or are you curious about
how I was raped by a man?
I just want to know the details of the trauma.
The details are that he was on top of me.
He put one of my legs on his shoulder.
He kissed me and fucked me at the same time.
It took him over half a month to disappear.
Are you satisfied?
No, I'm not.
I also want to know if you felt good
when you were raped.
Did you moan?
Did you have an orgasm?
How...
How did you know?
I didn't want to do that.
That wasn't me.
I'm sorry.
I was too impatient.
Let's go wash your face.
Please don't look down on me.
I didn't want to.
I'm clearly the victim.
He violated my body.
I was in pain. I bled a lot.
But I don't know why.
I... I felt...
I felt good.
I couldn't help it.
I didn't want to.
How long did he do this to you?
I don't know.
I feel like...
I've become an animal.
Did he use a condom?
He came inside me.
And you?
Me?
On myself.
It was him.
He used his hands.
I'm a bitch, aren't I?
It's not your fault.
There are many records
of men getting off on sexual assault,
with erections or orgasms.
First, it's physiology.
Second, it's intentional by the assailant
in order to achieve sexual conquest.
Then they use the victim's enjoyment of sex
to get away with it.
Really?
So, I might not be gay.
You doubted your sexual orientation.
What happened next?
I had a fever the next day.
I didn't dare to go to the hospital.
I didn't dare to tell anyone.
If my family found out,
they would only scold me for not being a man.
Lin Lin.
What woman would want to
live with a man who was raped?
I was scared.
I didn't dare to watch TV.
I couldn't watch any news about sex.
I always had a fruit knife.
And stabbed him in my dreams.
How long has this been going on?
Before I met you,
I've always been like this.
Cut.
Why are you running?
In a rush to break character?
The mood is different in the next scene.
I need to sort my emotions out.
Mr. Zhang, you need different makeup
for the next scene.
Got it.
Tell them to wait for three minutes.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it that way.
I'll go now.
Okay.
Mr. Zhen, take a break.
- Have some water.
- It's okay.
I'm fine.
Let's change your makeup.
Here.
[Powder Room]
Why are you...
I need to change, too.
We're two men.
What's wrong with this?
You can change next to me.
Why are you squeezing in?
Let me change with you.
Don't be like this.
People will talk if they see us.
I'm not doing anything.
Even so, people talk.
Don't look back.
Do you remember?
When we first met...
we were in the same situation.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
Forgive me for being rude.
It's because there's no time.
Don't look back.
I'm afraid you'll look at me.
There are many things
I don't have the courage to say.
I know you like to steal.
Because there's nothing in your world.
I gave you a chance.
Money, jewelry, property, and my heart!
I put them all in front of you.
If you're willing to steal,
I'm willing to give them to you.
But...
But why?
Why did you return them one by one?
Because of Xia Cheng Feng?
I'm sorry
I love him.
I know.
You're going to put on a wedding dress
and attend the wedding downstairs.
You'll be his bride.
Don't worry.
I'm not here to steal you away.
I just want to tell you this.
You can't repay me.
At least not my heart.
You can't ever pay that back.
Xiao Mei.
You're a vixen.
And a bastard.
I remember.
It was the last day
of filming for North Summit.
In the last scene, the heroine hurt her back.
So, I, the stunt double, became a back double.
In North Summit,
Xiao Mei dumped me, the simp,
because of her fiancé.
What about you?
What are you talking about?
North Summit is one thing.
Deep In is a different film.
But that's all me and you.
Zhun.
Zhun, I brought you some water.
Open the door, Zhun.
Are you going to abandon me again?
Zhun.
Zhun!
Why is he here?
He came to get changed.
- He...
- You don't have to make a fuss.
Gao Zhun can't leave Fang Chi now.
He wants to see Fang Chi all the time.
From this scene onward,
Fang Chi has to show love
without self-awareness.
Love without self-awareness.
Is your interpretation of the script different?
My interpretation is that
there's a strong attraction.
It's like a magnet.
Once you've been exposed to it once,
there's an unstoppable
attraction and collision.
Are you saying it's an instinct?
But attraction and desire aren't love.
Love is an inevitable result.
Attraction and desire
are the inescapable manifestations
of this fateful collision
I don't object to your interpretation.
We're going in the same direction anyway.
Fang Chi is fierce.
But his actions are restrained.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Good, let's get ready.
Let's shoot.
Have you noticed?
In the film, you want to see me all the time.
Outside of the film, you avoid me all the time.
Acting is acting.
Life is life.
But we're actors.
You and I can't live without acting.
I'll wait for you to come to me.
Dr. Fang, it's time to get off work.
But we have a last-minute patient.
His last name is Gao.
Do you want me to turn him down?
No.
He's my friend.
Let him in.
Please come in.
Mr. Gao.
What's the matter?
I'm fine.
I just wanted to see you.
If you're not busy,
can we have two sessions a week?
If you aren't available, it's fine.
Are you free at this time every day?
From 5:30 P.M. to 6:30 P.M.
I'm free.
From now on, it's once a day from now on.
Okay, Dr. Fang.
You should know.
Lin Lin isn't around.
I'm all alone.
I'm scared.
How did you feel yesterday?
I feel like I'm not alone anymore.
I'm glad I could tell you about it.
I used to think that if people found out,
I'd end my life.
But now that you know, I feel like I'm alive.
You said you had nightmares.
Let's talk about your dreams.
Dreams?
It's always the same thing.
Is it always him?
Or someone else besides him?
I'm talking about...
my name.
Fang Chi.
Excluding me.
N-No.
You seem a little nervous.
I...
I'm...
Don't lie to me.
You want me to bring the pointer?
I was wrong.
Only once.
Only once...
It was Justin.
Why him?
There was an auction.
He had too much to drink at the dinner party.
On his way back to his room,
he tried to hold me back, but I avoided him.
That night, I had a nightmare.
In my dream, I fought back.
But he didn't let me go.
Did you feel pleasure in your dreams?
Not with them.
In my dream,
I only feel pleasure...
only with you.
Because I want to.
What? What's this nonsense?
I'm sorry.
I've tainted you.
I'm shameless. I'm sick.
But when I saw it was your face, I just...
Go on.
I want to hear it.
At first, I couldn't believe it.
Until I touched your face.
Even if it was a dream,
I just wanted to hold you.
And cry on your shoulder.
Why did you cry?
Because...
you finally came to my rescue.
I'm glad you're brave enough to ride in a car.
That's because you're the one in the car.
Do you want me to walk you up?
No.
If it's on your way,
you can come and have coffee with me anytime.
Won't that trouble you?
Not at all.
I can't wait for you to come.
What?
Nothing.
Dr Fang.
See you next time.
Hello, do you have an appointment?
I'm a friend of Mr Gao Zhun.
He left something in my car.
Please wait a moment.
Mr. Gao isn't picking up
I understand. I'll just wait here.
Why don't you come in?
This way.
Mr. Gao and Mr. Jia are having
a meeting in the conference room.
Once the meeting is over,
I'll inform you immediately.
This way, please.
[Justin, Jia Shao Ting, Research Manager]
I want to...
find an opportunity to corner him.
Excuse me, is this Mr. Jia
who's having a meeting with Mr. Gao?
Yes, Mr. Jia is from our company.
Where are they meeting?
The conference room on the eighth floor.
Sir, what are you doing?
Where is the conference room?
Over there.
Who is he?
Dr. Fang.
What are you...
Come with me.
What's going on?
Let's continue the meeting.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I was in a meeting.
I put my phone on silent mode.
Are you free today?
Yes.
I always have time for you.
Then come with me.
I just remembered.
You have one more checkup to do.
Okay.
Dr. Fang.
I'm glad you came to see me.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here with you.
If I really am down with it...
Just leave me be.
Let me die.
It's going to be okay.
Wow, two guys holding hands.
Don't worry about what they think.
I only care about how you feel.
It won't take long.
It doesn't hurt that much.
Press it.
I can do it myself.
I'll bleed.
What if...
Your hand.
Give it to me.
Don't worry.
I'll be by your side no matter what.
I'm going to get the report.
Your boyfriend is so good to you.
He's not your boyfriend?
No.
He's my doctor.
Doctor?
The kind who gives injections at night, right?
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
Are you a doctor?
Yes.
A psychiatrist.
I see.
I can come to you
for psychological problems, too.
I have insomnia and nightmares.
I don't know what to do.
You can come for a consultation.
It's free for the first time.
Then can I have your number?
Call me if you need a consultation.
Okay.
However, if you ever need help,
you can call me, too.
Even if it's three in the morning.
What's wrong?
Mr. Gao.
Gao Zhun.
Look at me.
A tiff?
Did they say something?
Are you afraid they'll think
we're in a relationship?
They're all alone.
So-called friends and friends with benefits.
They didn't come with any of these people.
But you have me.
That's why they're jealous.
Don't overthink it.
Do you understand?
So, we're...
You're safe.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Doctor...
Dr. Fang.
Are you afraid they'll think
we're in a relationship?
If you ever need help,
you can call me, too.
Call?
I can call.
Someone else can do that, too.
It doesn't matter who it is.
Anyone can do that.
I'm not afraid they'll guess our relationship.
I'm just afraid...
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid that once I'm better,
we'll go our separate ways.
Mr. Gao.
Writing letters to patients
is a form of narrative therapy.
For others,
I usually repeat the treatment at the clinic.
But this time, it's for you.
I think it's a bit different.
Mr. Gao.
Do you want to know
what you look like in my mind?
Remember that exhibition?
You were waiting for me in the dark.
It's me.
Remember the contact exercises?
You were so scared.
But you didn't run away.
Don't be scared.
It's okay.
Remember the fireworks
and the fountain at the Qixi Festival?
You were brave enough to tell me your story.
What I remember most about you
was your courage to risk your life.
And your beauty.
Maybe beauty is not
the right word to describe a man.
But you are beautiful.
You're like a beautiful flower.
Beauty has caused you
to suffer some bad experiences.
But you should know this.
Beauty is not something to be blamed for.
The last thing I want to see
is you torturing yourself
for someone else's sins.
I'm most afraid of hearing
the word "death" from you.
Lastly,
thank you for your trust
and cooperation all this time.
No matter how unreasonable my request was,
you'd always give in to me.
More than once,
I thought that meeting you
was one of the biggest gains of my life.
Thank you, Gao Zhun.
[Gao Zhun]
Mr. Gao.
It's late.
What's the matter?
The letter.
I received it.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have sulked.
Why did you sulk?
I just...
I couldn't stand that you gave
that boy your business card.
I can't stand it when you're as good
to others as you are to me.
I just want you to be good to me.
I just want you to look at me.
I...
I get jealous.
Mr. Jia.
Please calm down.
As you can see, I didn't go there to see you.
Right.
It's a coincidence.
Don't worry.
I'm a doctor.
I have to protect my client's privacy.
Yes.
He doesn't know that you're my client.