[Episode 6]
Young man.
You shouldn't have taken
money you weren't supposed to.
Leave it here.
Try running again!
You can't take this. Give it to me.
Let go!
- Beat him up!
- Take that! Take that!
Stubborn, aren't you?
Try running again!
I dare you!
- Go.
- Go! Hurry!
Let's eat.
- Did you make all this?
- Yes.
What happened to your face?
How did you get hurt?
Go and pay your tuition.
Where did you get the money?
How did you get hurt so badly?
I got hurt playing pool.
Don't worry. It's clean money.
Playing pool wouldn't leave you hurt like this.
I'll get the medicine.
Does it hurt?
No.
Done.
Done?
That's plenty.
You should have more. You're still growing.
It's really enough. I can't eat any more.
Have some fish.
The kitchen light flickered again today,
but I fixed it.
Leave anything electrical to me
from now on. I'll handle it.
It's good.
You're a good cook.
Are you asleep?
I'll drink the sweet soup myself then.
I'll drink it.
Done pretending to be asleep?
I was asleep, but you woke me up.
Fine. Go back to bed then.
I'll finish this before I sleep.
Where's the sweet soup you promised?
What about not staying up late?
Is high school really this stressful now?
My ranking wasn't high enough.
If I want to get into the science top class,
I need to make the grade's top 20
in the placement exam next month.
I don't have any good advice for you.
But some architectural design students
on the construction site told me,
that science graduates are indeed
in high demand.
But it's fine if you prefer liberal arts.
You have me to support you.
Got it.
After my exams tomorrow,
I'll go to the factory with you.
It's fine. Once I get rid of the copper wire,
I won't need to go there anymore.
I found a new job in District Seven.
What are you going to District Seven for?
It's just...
I'll go there at night, cool off,
and watch the security feeds.
Pays well, not much work.
Things are pretty chaotic over there.
Besides, there are so many people
stirring up trouble these days.
The way we're living now is perfectly fine.
Don't go.
Just eat your food.
What's wrong, Miao Jing?
- Nothing.
- Are you okay?
I'll be fine in a moment. My stomach hurts.
Your stomach hurts?
Then...
I'll go buy you some painkillers
or sanitary pads?
No need. That's not it.
Maybe we should go to the hospital.
Doctor. So, what's the cause
of her stomachache?
Nothing too serious so far.
There's just some inflammation.
Our initial suspicion is food poisoning.
Has she eaten anything unclean lately?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
She ate the same things I did.
Everyone's constitution is different.
Especially for young girls,
you need to be more careful with them.
Remember, don't let her catch a cold.
Don't eat overnight leftovers.
Don't eat food bought from outside.
And make sure she eats properly these days.
She'll need an intravenous drip all night.
You need to stay with her.
Is it just you?
I'm the only adult in the family.
It's fine. I can take care of her.
Have some water.
This is almost finished.
Does your hand hurt?
Why don't you sit down?
All that pacing is making me dizzy.
Does your stomach still hurt?
The intravenous drip helped a lot.
Don't look at me like that.
It's like I have a terminal illness.
Don't talk nonsense.
From now on, just throw out all the leftovers.
I'll do the cooking.
You're being too dramatic.
It's such a waste of food.
Nurse! This one is almost finished.
Okay.
- Miao Jing, right?
- Yes.
Okay.
Tell me when this one is almost done.
What's gotten into you today?
Take a nap.
I need to study.
I'll read it to you.
Close your eyes.
A DNA molecule's structure allows it to
store vast amounts of genetic information.
Besides, it also uses a DNA molecule...
Close your eyes.
If we were still in elementary school,
I'd be lucky if my books survived you.
Go ahead and laugh.
I'll pretend I didn't see it.
Genetic information is passed on
through the replication of DNA molecules.
DNA replication uses the parent DNA molecule
as a template...
as a template to
synthesize daughter DNA molecules.
This process occurs
during the interphase of mitosis and...
and the interphase
of the first meiotic division.
Still feeling unwell?
How about skipping the exam today?
I'll ask your teacher for leave.
I'm fine. I'll be right out.
Are you really okay?
I'm really fine. Let's go.
Tell me if you feel unwell again.
I'll head inside, then.
Wait a second.
Do your best on the exam.
After the college entrance exam,
I'll buy you a thicker one.
At least this thick.
I'm off.
Tell the teacher if you feel sick.
Don't just tough it out.
Are you here to drop off Miao Jing?
I'm her class teacher.
Hello, Miss.
By the way, Miss.
Miao Jing's gastroenteritis isn't better yet.
Please look out for her.
No problem.
Miao Jing really puts too much pressure
on herself.
You should also show her more care.
Her family's not with her,
and she's going through puberty.
She probably overthinks more than other kids.
She doesn't think about much else.
She just wants to get into the top class.
That won't be a problem for her.
But she wants to be in the top 10,
to apply for a scholarship.
Alright. I'll head in now.
I'll take good care of her. Don't worry.
Thank you, Miss.
[District Seven Night Club]
Cheers.
Welcome to District Seven.
- Cheers.
We have to come here every now and then.
No two drinks you make ever taste the same.
- Well...
- What's wrong with...
You've had a bit too much. Please calm down.
What's the matter, sir?
You mix it.
I'm speaking plain Chinese.
What don't you understand?
Why don't you come and do it for me?
Fine. I'll mix it for you,
until you're satisfied.
But if you disturb the other guests,
I'll have to apologize to you in advance.
What do you mean by that? What...
What I mean is I'm new here.
I might not know my own strength.
Okay. I get it.
Interesting.
He's even more interesting now.
Isn't that Chen Yi?
I've seen him at the pool hall
a couple of times.
He's got some skills.
Aren't the exams over?
Miao Jing, what's wrong?
Don't come in yet.
Does your stomach still hurt?
Is this what you need?
Let's go. We're going to the hospital.
Judging by her condition,
it's likely a corpus luteum rupture.
A corpus luteum rupture? What does that mean?
Has she done any strenuous exercise lately?
From what I can see,
she must've had abdominal pain before.
She saw a doctor before.
He said it was acute gastroenteritis.
I thought it was just an upset stomach.
You were far too careless.
She definitely needs surgery.
A corpus luteum rupture can be very serious.
If she loses too much blood,
the patient could go into shock.
Surgery? Yes, let's do it.
Are you an immediate family member?
I'm her brother.
Her biological brother?
This surgery requires general anesthesia.
An immediate family member must sign for it.
I'm her brother.
I'll take responsibility for anything.
But...
Doctor, please. I can take responsibility.
But the hospital's policy...
Chen Yi.
Doctor. I'm from the Nan City Branch.
Nice to meet you.
Let us handle the paperwork.
The patient's family can't come in person
due to special circumstances.
As for the specific documentation,
I can provide it to you later.
All right. Zhang, process it for him.
Okay, got it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's nothing.
[Operation Room]
Don't worry.
Here. Have some water.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I've asked Wen
to handle the admission procedures.
If Miao Jing needs anything,
feel free to contact her anytime.
No, it's okay.
I've troubled you too much already.
I can manage on my own.
Don't overthink it.
Because of her mother's situation,
I was listed as the emergency contact.
I didn't have any cases today,
so when I came over when they called.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
You're still just a kid, after all.
By the way, have you ever thought about
applying to the police academy again?
You've got potential.
I have high hopes for you.
I really do.
If you're interested,
I can look into the application process.
No, thank you.
Right now, I don't have the energy for that.
[Operation Room]
I bought some congee for Jing from downstairs.
The food you bought's a bit greasy for her.
Okay. Thank you.
You don't need to be so formal with me.
Just like Jing, you can call me Wen.
Wen. You should go back and rest.
I'll stay here to look after Miao Jing.
The nurse told me she just finished surgery.
Wiping her down will make her feel better.
Okay.
Actually, let me do it.
Go get some hot water for me.
Okay. Thank you.
Go on in. She's awake.
I want some water.
Okay.
Do you want more?
It really hurts.
Where does it hurt? I'll go get the doctor.
Did you bring this? I want to eat some.
Don't eat that.
It's hard to digest.
Have some porridge instead.
I was going to say, you really do know
exactly what I like to eat.
When the semester is over
and the class results are out,
let's go have hot pot.
It hurts so much, I want to eat meat.
Okay.
My son did quite well on the exam.
How about yours?
Mine is hopeless.
Come over to our place tonight.
What's wrong?
You're awake.
Rest well this weekend.
After you eat, remember to take your medicine.
You haven't been to the site lately.
I told you last time. I found a job.
In District Seven?
Didn't you promise me you wouldn't go?
The work at the construction site's tiring.
I wanted to find an easier job.
Don't worry about it.
Who is it?
I don't know.
They've called several times lately.
I'm going out for a bit.
There's food ready in the fridge.
Just heat it up yourself.
Come back early.
I'm worried it's those people
from the Green Life incident.
Don't worry. I'll be back tonight.
After I leave, lock the door from the inside.
Remember to take your medicine.
Call me if you feel unwell.
I'm off.
Yi, where should I put this? You take that.
- Bring it here.
- Okay.
And this. Put them all in there together.
Sure. No problem.
Yi, don't you ever sleep?
You're pulling all-nighters every day.
You're so busy.
No wonder you can't even get a girlfriend.
Yong's cousin asked
for your number a few days ago.
Should I give it to her?
I don't have time for that right now.
Honestly, it'd be good
for you to get a girlfriend.
You're a grown man, right?
Find Miao Jing a sister-in-law.
Right now, otherwise,
many things are inconvenient.
That's true.
Stop acting like you're in a tragic drama.
You've got a girl dragging you down,
but you still need to enjoy yourself, right?
Dragging me down? I'm living quite comfortably.
Won't you really consider my cousin?
She's a really nice person.
Don't ever say that to me again.
And you.
You're giving it all to her? Give me some too.
- You're so annoying.
- I really like it. Eat your eggs.
I'll leave then. I'll head down now.
- You handle it, okay?
- Both of you, get out. Go downstairs.
- Keep it down.
- Yi.
Close the door. Keep it down.
That should be about it.
[Expenditure: 2685 yuan, Income: Scholarship]
[Teng City Experimental No.1 High School]
Look! I'm in Class Four.
- Which class are you in?
- Class Four. Top five! Top five!
I made it into the top five!
- Which class are you in?
- Science Class One.
That's impressive! Really?
The classes were just assigned.
See you next week.
- You're amazing.
- Bye! Bye!
That's so impressive.
I heard the scholarship is worth thousands.
Yeah, that's amazing.
Jing, eat something.
Is everything okay at school?
Are the holidays coming up?
Why did you want to see me?
Why are you being so distant?
I know you hate me.
But you know how it was back then.
If I hadn't laid low for a few days,
I'd be in real trouble now.
Since you knew that, why did you leave me here?
I know you resent me. You blame me.
I know I was wrong.
But I never wanted to leave you here all alone.
With things like that back then,
I couldn't drag you all over the place with me.
As soon as I settled down, I came to get you.
Well...
Don't just sit there in silence.
Go ahead and eat.
I ordered so much. It's all for you.
Don't you love studying?
I met this guy.
He helps people apply to schools overseas.
In the future, we can go abroad together.
There are many good schools out there.
You're my only daughter.
Mothers and daughters
don't carry grudges overnight, do they?
It's too late for all this.
You owed everyone so much money.
You cheated Chen Yi out of so much money.
And now you want to take me away?
I've already paid back everything I owed.
If you're willing to come with me,
I'll pay Chen Yi back. Every cent.
I carried you in my own belly.
A mother and daughter are connected.
I know...
I know I've caused you a lot of suffering.
You have to give me a chance to make amends.
Jing, think carefully about what I've told you.
This time, I came back specifically to get you.
I'm going up now.
I hope you'll come with me.
Take this.
I'll be waiting for you.
We're having hot pot today.
You're home early from school today.
The exam results came out today.
How was it?
I got into Class One.
Is that the top class?
Yes.
What do you want as a gift?
Something delicious? Or something else?
My mom came back for me.
She said she'll pay back the money.
Really?
That's good.
Will she pay interest?
She left you here for so long.
Will she pay back your living expenses?
I have a scholarship.
Your mom must be happy then.
To have such an outstanding daughter.
Well.
Is she moving back to Teng City?
She's just here to visit me.
As long as she's not here to scam money.
You're all set now. Once you go abroad,
your life will get better.
But remember,
once you find opportunities abroad,
don't forget who stood by you through all this.
Let me make a little foreign money too.
No problem.
Okay, it's a deal then.
- Bye.
All right.
I got all the information you wanted.
Not long after the Green Life incident,
Wei Ming Zhen was arrested.
She just got out a while ago.
She's hooked up with a wealthy man.
I looked into him too.
He has a decent reputation.
He really does handle study-abroad
and immigration services.
He even paid back all the money
Wei Ming Zhen owed from before.
Yi.
I almost didn't recognize you.
What are you doing here?
Well, you left in a hurry back then.
I still remember what I owe you.
I've collected all the money.
Jing told you, right?
- I asked her to get your account number.
- No need.
Keep the money.
Live a good life with Miao Jing.
Just don't lie to her.
This one is pretty.
We've been looking for a while.
Is there anything you like?
It's okay.
I specifically took you out shopping today.
Why don't you want anything?
You don't have to save money for me.
Look at these jeans.
Do you want to try them on?
There are dresses over there.
Come on. Let's take a look.
Yi! What a coincidence.
I was just telling Jing
that we'd go see you later.
There's no time like the present.
Let me take you both out for a meal. Let's go.
No, thanks. I have to work.
[Ling, let me know if you've thought it over.]
[I really do want us to live together.]
[Meet me at the auto shop tomorrow at nine.]
What's wrong?
Let's just leave it at this.
My mom said she wants to take me with her.
If I go with her, she'll send me abroad.
She'll also pay back the money.
That way, you won't have to work so hard.
And you won't have to work that dangerous job
in District Seven anymore.
I saw your clothes drying on the balcony.
I know that going with my mom
is a better choice.
This way, I won't be a burden to you anymore.
But...
the life we have now makes me feel
at peace and grounded.
My scholarship will be coming in next week.
Chen Yi.
Are you listening?
That's all I wanted to say.
I want to have egg pancakes tomorrow.