[Episode 7]
Jing.
You handled the ledger I told you about, right?
What ledger? I never saw it.
Didn't I tell you? The one under your bed.
Forget it.
It doesn't matter anymore. It's fine.
Take this. Keep it safe.
Right now,
my daughter and I are at the bus station.
Yes. Just come over later and pick us up.
When did this happen? This is way too sudden.
No, I...
My daughter and I already talked it over.
Fine. I know.
Jing.
There's something I want to discuss with you.
I want to hear what you think.
My friend called me.
He said his son suddenly came back
from overseas.
It was very sudden.
So I was thinking,
maybe I should go over first and say hello.
You can go in a couple of days.
Don't overthink it.
He really likes you, and he's a good man.
He told me before that once you get there,
he'll introduce you to his friends' kids.
Later on, you can all go abroad together
and keep each other company.
Mom.
I'm only in Grade 11.
Yeah, you'll graduate next year.
Then we'll need to go abroad.
Why do I have to go abroad?
My grades have always been good.
I've always done well in school.
I can make it on my own.
Do you not trust me?
This time really is a special situation.
Did you not understand what I said?
I said I can make it on my own.
I came today just to see you off.
I wish you happiness.
Stop joking.
If I leave, you'll be alone in Teng City.
What will you do?
Mom. I was really upset today.
I was afraid you would be sad,
but you're just like before.
So now, I truly wish you happiness.
And what do you mean, "you'll be alone"?
Back then, when you left me here,
did you ever think about me?
Besides, I'm not alone now.
No, Miao Jing.
Attention, passengers.
Passengers traveling to Peng City,
please pay attention.
Your bus is about to arrive.
Please begin ticket check and boarding.
I'll take you to Teng City.
To our own home.
Let's just hold on a little longer.
I promise you, this is the last time.
Who was the one who begged me
to bring my daughter here?
You said your wife was dead. You were scared.
You asked me to bring my daughter over.
You wanted a son and a daughter,
a perfect little family.
You're not scared anymore, are you?
Mom. Mom, wait for me.
Mom, wait for me.
Mom.
Line up for ticket check. The bus has arrived.
Passengers traveling to Peng City,
please line up for ticket check.
The bus has arrived.
Passengers traveling to Peng City,
please pay attention.
The bus has arrived.
Please line up for ticket check immediately.
Passengers traveling to Peng City,
please pay attention.
Please come over here immediately
and line up for ticket check.
The bus has arrived and will depart soon.
Don't leave.
I don't have money to get home.
Why did you come back?
Overseas is too far away.
I wouldn't get used to it.
What's there not to get used to?
Haven't you always wanted a home?
This is good, isn't it?
I already found my family long ago.
Today, we face the national flag,
before our family, friends, and teachers.
As you come of age at eighteen,
please all rise.
Raise your right hand,
and solemnly swear with me.
I swear.
I am a citizen
of the People's Republic of China.
I have grown into an adult.
I swear.
From this day forward,
I will treat others with sincerity.
I will serve society with passion.
I will serve my country with loyalty.
I swear.
From this day forward,
At this new beginning, I will work even harder.
Let heaven and earth bear witness.
Let the national flag stand as proof.
I come of age and make my vow.
Long live youth.
Sworn by Miao Jing.
Sworn by Huang Yi Lan.
I now announce
the coming-of-age bracelet ceremony now begins.
Parents, please rise. Face your children.
In the name of youth,
let us carry our passion into senior year.
Parents,
please place the bracelets on your children.
Happy coming-of-age.
Thank you.
Miao Jing.
Your parent isn't here.
I'll help you complete the ceremony.
Here.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm Miao Jing's guardian.
You are late.
My bad.
I was making money to buy you
a lucky charm bead this thick.
Miao Jing has excellent grades.
She has a real shot at Jiao Tong University,
even Tsinghua or Peking University.
And finance is very popular right now.
Her grades are good enough for it.
Yes. She's steady and detail-oriented.
Finance really does suit her.
But finance means dealing
with all kinds of people.
It's too exhausting.
That's a rather fresh perspective.
Not many parents would think of it that way.
But that's all for
after the college entrance examination.
When it's time to choose a major,
we'll ask you for advice again.
Sure.
- Could you take a photo of us?
- Here, Teacher.
Take one with us.
- Alright.
- I'll take one for you two.
- Okay, thank you.
- It looks great.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
- Let's take a photo with the teacher.
- Teacher!
Do you want another one?
Okay.
Three, two, one.
It looks really good.
It does.
No one can see it here.
It still has to be neat.
Obsessive much?
Who was that just now?
Our class monitor. Why?
Nothing. Focus on your studies.
Miao Jing. Let's go to class together.
I'll go first, then.
She is a classmate.
She's very good at studying.
Is that so?
I've been through them.
Right. You should focus on studying.
You two talk. I'll go take a look.
Hello. You're Miao Jing's brother, right?
What did you want to see me about?
You're Miao Jing's classmate.
Yes. I'm the class monitor.
My name is Li Yu.
Class monitor.
At your age,
you should still put your studies first.
Everything else can wait. You're still young.
I understand.
At this stage, I won't confess to her.
What I mean is
she and I are just study partners right now.
I won't affect her studies.
In a while, Miao Jing is going to Bei City
for a math competition.
I'll be going with her too.
I know.
When you like a girl,
you have to give her a better future.
How many days is the math competition
in Bei City?
Three days. Why?
You'll be staying in Bei City overnight?
Of course.
At night, we'll review together.
Hello. Let me drink to you.
Mr. Zhai. You've had too much.
Slow down. Easy.
Zhai. What's going on?
Come on. Move aside.
Move aside.
Careful.
Who let him drink that much?
He wanted to drink.
Bin.
Get back to Kuangxia right now.
I can't handle this by myself anymore.
I can't handle it.
Even if I went back to Kuangxia,
I still couldn't do it as well as you.
These people are awful.
Once they start drinking,
it's Rémy Martin after Rémy Martin.
Look at me. They turned me into a pig.
Handsome!
Where did you find him?
Let me introduce him.
Chen Yi.
Yi.
Gets things done.
Looks respectable. Knows how to handle things.
Yi. Come work for me.
Come work for me.
All I have are useless punks.
Boss.
You are like brothers, after all.
It makes no difference to me who I work for.
You heard what Yi said.
Stop coming over here to steal my people.
- It's all the same.
- I'm leaving.
Then it's the same with me too.
Come to my side.
Mr. Zhai, you're drunk.
- Yi.
- I'm not useless.
Careful.
All right. Don't catch a cold.
Teng City Restaurant...
- What are you looking at?
- is the oldest and best restaurant here.
- Hey, Miao Jing.
- Don't be fooled by the plain decor.
They keep the flavor authentic.
I had to book several days in advance.
This way.
Chen Yi.
Please. Right this way.
Come on. All the dishes are here.
Come on, fill the glasses.
A warm welcome to Ms. Linda here in Teng City.
Welcome.
Come on.
The first toast is to you.
- Good.
- All right.
Thank you.
Everyone, eat up.
Sorry.
It's too strong. Come on. Eat.
- Eat, come on.
- Could I have some water? Thank you.
Eat up.
- Are you okay?
- Here, Ms. Linda.
This hind shank is the best piece. Try it.
A local specialty.
Everyone who comes here has to try it.
Trotters.
I don't think anyone'd eat pig's feet today.
I'll eat it later.
Okay.
- What did she just say?
- I can't eat this at all.
Thank you.
If you don't like it, let's get some fish.
Switch it out. This one.
I'm still burning.
Come on. Ms. Linda, have some fish.
- This one is softer.
- Okay. I'll help myself.
People all over the world eat this.
I think we should finish right now.
Mr. Zhai.
Here's the thing.
I grew up overseas.
My Chinese really isn't very good.
If we work together later,
communication might be...
It's okay.
I can also do simple translation.
Chen Yi, right?
Yes. Chen Yi.
Our youngest vice president.
Come on. Since our glasses are already raised,
Come on. The second toast is also to Ms. Linda.
Cheers!
To a pleasant partnership.
I'll drink water instead.
Sure. That's fine.
To a pleasant partnership.
Come on. Eat up.
Come on. Try it.
It's a local specialty.
The power is out.
Finally, we can rest for a bit.
When I was doing English Weekly just now,
I saw a reading passage.
It's about first love in adolescence.
That English Weekly is amazing.
It actually talks about
how to tell if you're attracted to someone.
English Weekly really is ahead of its time.
How do you tell?
If you look into each other's eyes
for three seconds, it triggers dopamine.
Two people who like each other will have...
the urge to kiss!
Really?
Teng City is a good place.
Teng City is a smart place
to look for business opportunities.
I think so too.
This place is very interesting.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No. But I have a kid at home to take care of.
You have a child?
- How old?
- 18.
18?
Have you watched it?
This is pretty interesting.
If I were you, I'd practice speaking more.
Good spoken English will come in handy
when you do business later.
Thanks.
[Teng City Experimental No.1 High School]
I'm so hungry. Let's go get something to eat.
Sure. Then I...
There's a snack street over there.
Takoyaki. Let's go together.
Come on.
Thanks.
Chen Yi.
I had a great time today. Thank you.
I hope I can see you tomorrow too. Bye.
You got out pretty fast today.
Let's go.
I'll take you out for late-night food.
I'm not hungry.
Not hungry?
You're hungry, aren't you?
What do you want to eat?
What's wrong?
Want some congee?
One bowl of congee.
Sure.
You didn't eat dinner just now?
I was busy the whole time. I didn't eat enough.
What have you been busy with lately?
I haven't heard you talk
about work in a long time.
Nothing. Just some social dinners.
Why do you keep rubbing those chopsticks?
You're going to sand them bald.
Do you need chopsticks to eat congee?
Hurry up and eat.
After that, go home and sleep.
Right.
How's Bei City been treating you
these past three days?
Not great. Just normal.
Where did this disc come from?
What's it about?
A friend gave it to me to help
with speaking and listening.
Don't you want to learn English?
Come on.
Come here.
Well said, Jack.
To making it count.
Excellent.
The last thing I need is another picture
of me looking like a porcelain doll.
Rose.
I'm the paying customer.
I get to do what I want.
Tell me how to pose.
Your arm, like before.
Raise the other hand to your face.
Now lower your head a little.
- Look at me.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Try to stay still.
I've really never watched this kind of movie.
What's wrong with this kind of movie?
What?
You've watched something like this before?
Yes.
I watch them once in a while too.
- Miao Jing, go pour me a glass of water.
- Okay.
Chen Yi.
Take a look.
Can this be any cheaper?
Hello. I'll take some of this.
Son.
- What do you think of this one?
- It doesn't look good.
Two years ago, I asked you
to come pick flowers with me, but you said no.
What's different this year?
You don't happen to like the girl
who went to the competition with you, do you?
I'm telling you. Her family won't do.
You understand? You're too young.
- Mother!
- Flowers!
I know. Stop talking.
This doesn't look good.
Let's go. Hurry. Let's go.
Whenever I say something, you...
- Sweetheart, pick whichever one you like.
- Excuse me.
- Here's the money.
- This one, and this one.
- Give me that one too.
- Are you buying?
What do you think of this one?
- What?
- Are you buying it?
- This one's almost wilted.
- Do you like this one?
The one next to it is better.
A peach tree.
Not lying, my peach blossoms
are growing very well this year.
Peach trees bring romance.
Put one at home, and romance will keep coming.
Love will be perfect.
She's still in high school.
What flower is this?
You're so old-fashioned.
There's a dragon procession today. Come on.
Let's touch the dragon head.
Look. Dragon dance. Come on.
This way. Touch it for good luck.
Hurry. Make a fortune. Prosper in the new year.
Touch it.
Hurry.
The first one to touch the dragon head
can go pray for blessings later.
Okay. All right. Here it comes.
Good.
I didn't touch it.
You're lucky.
When they pray for blessings later, come over.
Yi should come too.
Good luck all year long.
Miss. Could you give this chance to my son?
Not for free. I can pay you.
He's been looking forward to this all year.
Sorry, she's taking
college entrance examination next year.
The college entrance examination?
Then all right.
Okay. Her examination is very important.
Understand?
We'll come again next year, all right?
A whole year of good luck.
Did you really want to touch the dragon head?
She's taking the college entrance examination.
That only happens once.
Jing.
May you both be safe and well.
Do you want to try?
I don't believe in this stuff. You do it.
Don't say you do not believe
in front of the statue.
What is it?
Nothing.
Was the result bad?
Not exactly.
One face up and one face down means yes.
Two backs means no.
But this laughing cup means
the question has no answer.
No answer?
It can answer like that too?
Let me try.
Forget it. It isn't accurate.
I'm not asking anymore.
What question did you ask?
Nothing. It just isn't accurate.
Tell me. What question?
It just isn't accurate.
Do not say things like that in front of it.
Looks like it's about time. The time has come.
Our ceremony is about to begin.
Everyone, please get ready.
Good.
May everyone have good luck.
May every family be safe.
- Good.
- Thank you.
The ceremony is about to begin.
Everyone, please hold your family's hand.
I think that question hit you pretty hard.
Close your eyes.
Make a wish.
My wish is simple.
I hope she has a smooth and peaceful life.
From this moment on,
may we always walk this road together.
What are you doing? You scared me.
Nothing.
Don't move.
Whether you believe it or not,
it's just for peace and safety.
Don't throw it away.
I didn't say I was going to throw it away.
Then put it back.
Miao Jing.
We don't need to pray to any god.
From now on, we will be safe and well.
Because I said so.
Okay.
Sorry to interrupt.
I hope we have a pleasant partnership.
Of course.
Looks like business has been good lately.
Thank you.
Yes. It's been all right.
Let's have a drink. Cheers.
Sure.
You two talk.
Linda.
Did you watch the audio-video disc I gave you?
What do you think?
I've been a little busy lately.
I haven't had time to watch it.
Then should I talk to your boss,
and get you a day off?
I've been in Teng City for so long,
but I haven't gone out to have fun.
And you've been working the whole time.
Come on.
Linda.
Once we sign the contract,
I'll take you around Teng City properly.
How did your boss find such a good manager?
I almost want to steal you away to Lingang.
You'll have to ask both bosses about that.
Your sister who plays piano
is also the best in Teng City.
Sir, the police are here.
Come on, officer.
Who's in charge here?
Officer.
How can we assist you?
We're from the precinct station.
Someone reported that you're suspected
of selling counterfeit liquor here.
Is that true?
Counterfeit liquor?
You really trust Chen Yi that much?
- I'll take the officers to inspect the place.
- Don't you need to go check?
No need at all.
- My brother chose him.
- This way, please.
- Don't worry.
- You guys...
- Take the officers over there.
Collect evidence from all the liquor here.
- Over there.
- Yes, sir.
This is where we usually sell our liquor.
All right.
So who exactly runs this place?
Mr. Zhai or Mr. Zhang?
Mr. Zhai is Mr. Zhang's friend.
He doesn't manage the nightclub.
He only comes by sometimes
when he's here to talk business.
What work are you responsible for here?
I'm just an employee.
Wherever the two bosses need help,
that's where I go.
What's kept in that room?
Some liquor, and some employees' belongings.
May we go in and take a look?
Of course.