- Ouji?
- Let's break up.
Sorry.
I'm just... sorry.
Haru, I think you're cute, and I cherish you.
But my body refuses to respond.
I haven't been able to get it up,
with anyone.
Get it... up?
Well... I know there are remedies.
I've heard about them before.
I can help look into it.
Mind if I take a smoke?
It's freezing out here.
Thanks.
It was boiling during our ceremony.
Has it been half a year already?
It's been about three months.
Oh.
Guess I'm finally paying the price, huh?
What?
I've never actually enjoyed sex before.
Ouch, my ear.
Sorry, it's just...
I became insanely popular
when I debuted with the band.
Sure, at first I let myself bask in it.
But over time...
Girls would imagine their own versions of me,
and come at me aggressively
in the name of "love".
Eventually, I got fed up with it all.
I couldn't stand these girls
having their way with me,
so I decided to go on the offensive
before they could.
To eat, before I was eaten, if you will.
Repeat that cycle,
and I ultimately ran myself dry.
Both my body and heart, emptied out.
And then the kidney stone? Poor me.
You really do reap what you sow.
That's not...
You came to care for me after that debacle.
It was a huge help, sure.
But I thought you'd ultimately ask
for the same thing,
only to be disappointed
I had nothing to offer.
Except, you were different.
You made no moves.
You completely ignored my room.
That's because your room was...
It seriously put me at ease.
You saved me.
Sorry.
Let's break up after all.
If you stay, you won't ever get to have sex.
No.
I don't want to break up.
I saved you?
Well, you saved me.
Of course I want to stay with you.
But don't you want to have sex?
Sorry.
I don't mean that in a bad way, really.
In the end, it's all my fault.
I won't touch you again, I promise.
I'm sorry our marriage turned out like this.
[Episode 6]
Sorry. Let's break up after all.
If you stay, you won't ever get to have sex.
[Open Relationships]
[Couples who consensually have sex
with other partners]
Unbelievable.
Something the matter?
No.
I'm sorry our marriage turned out like this.
What the hell, man?
Got into an argument with Haru?
If only it were an argument.
What? He left?
When?
About a week ago.
Is this leading up to a divorce?
Sorry, I shouldn't be so blunt.
When he asked to break up,
did he mean a divorce?
That's usually what it means, yes.
Thought so.
You know, I was over the moon
to hear Ouji say he actually liked me.
I know. I witnessed your elation firsthand.
Can you blame me?
I suddenly became the heroine
after living as an extra my whole life.
- Fair enough.
- I was speeding towards my happy end,
as the Ouji I dreamed of turned my way.
He chose to love me, to hug boring ol' me.
Sounds straight out of a drama, right?
Sure does.
But reality looks towards what happens next.
You won't protest the break up?
I already told him I wanted to stay.
Why not be more clingy about it?
I couldn't be.
Girls would come at me aggressively
in the name of "love".
Eventually, I got fed up with it all.
Because I wasn't any better.
I was just like those people
who cornered him in the first place.
I pushed my expectations onto him.
You couldn't help it. You were a fan of his.
I know that.
But I realize now how it was suffocating him.
You couldn't know. He never told you.
Right?
Anyone would think Ouji
was a romance powerhouse.
I suppose.
You are too, Akina.
I guess.
But I'm a weakling when it comes to romance.
- That, you are.
- No need to affirm it.
Anyway, I thought a weakling like me
would never get through to a guy like him.
So since he finally looked my way,
I thought he'd notice my efforts,
and make the first move.
How bold.
But I guess I was pressuring him after all.
I never once gave Ouji's feelings a thought.
He looked like he was really struggling...
Haru.
To tell you the truth...
No, never mind.
Say...
What does it mean to be a weakling
or powerhouse...
when it comes to romance?
Huh?
Is the one who fell first the weakling?
Is there no equality when it comes to love?
I guess so.
Then that makes me a fellow weakling.
Huh?
What?
You've fallen for someone?
What? Akina, in love?
Akina, who prefers sex over romance, in love?
You could say one thing led to the other...
A brothel?
A brothel, like, a brothel?
Don't make me repeat myself.
I'm just as surprised.
You look so cute right now, Akina.
So you fell for this "therapist"?
I know. I know you want to call me stupid.
No, well... Do you love him for his body?
You don't?
I don't know.
Of course, he's always making me feel good.
But I go and check his reviews,
and feel weird knowing he does this
with other women.
I get sad, and miss him when he leaves, too.
So do I love him physically?
I think it's more than that.
Right? I thought so.
Powerhouses can become weaklings too, okay?
Relationships that aren't equal,
are pointless.
So I'm seeing him again later tonight.
What happened to it being pointless?
They're two separate matters.
If I have the money to see him, I'll pay.
Akina, you're you, powerhouse or not.
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean, you're super cool.
Dear.
What's wrong? You're spacing out.
Sorry.
The sink. You're leaving it running.
Aren't you always talking about conservation?
Sorry.
Are you out the entire day tomorrow?
Yeah.
I'll be doing makeup
for a stage play poster shoot.
You're still doing makeup work?
I thought you were going to look
for better gigs.
Hello?
Sorry, I know we promised not to call...
It's okay. So?
It wasn't about us.
The article.
Do you know Ryuhei Sato?
He's often cast as a main lead.
No, I don't think so.
I don't know who his partner was, but...
Fuyumi?
I hear you.
Thank goodness.
Fuyumi.
Can we meet sometime soon?
I want to speak to you, in person.
I can't think about that now.
Sorry, I'll text you back.
My stomach was hurting.
I see.
Were you speaking to someone?
I thought I heard some voices.
I was watching a video.
Watch it only after you finish cleaning up.
Sorry.
[Naoki]
Let me go.
Why do you keep ignoring my texts?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who called me easy,
and told me to buy a man.
- I was only...
- Well, thanks for the great advice.
- Huh?
- Bye.
Wait.
Don't tell me you actually bought a man.
Like I said, you told me to.
Then it can be me, right?
Hey, let go!
Hey!
If you're doing it with a dude
who sells himself, do it with me instead.
Screw off! Let me go!
Why're you acting like a virgin?
- You're used to this, right?
- Stop!
Stop it!
Akina, are you alright?
Naoki...
The hell? Piss off, man!
Well, I mean... This was a play.
She wanted to do it outside.
Like hell I did.
Says the one buying men for herself.
What's so wrong about that?
I won't have sex with men I don't want to.
I'll pay money to have sex
with the ones I do.
What's so wrong about that?
What's so wrong with living true to myself?
Akina. Let's report him to the police.
H-Haru?
Haru!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What about you?
Are you okay?
- I'm totally fine.
- No, you're not.
What a scumbag...
Here, your phone.
Thank you.
Sorry to get you involved in that.
Well...
Thank you for earlier.
Haru answered your phone
when I called to ask why you were late.
She told me you may still be in the area.
I see.
I was right to come and get you.
Then I'll get going.
Please take care of Akina for me.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Do you do that huffing around Haru, too?
What huffing?
It's that narcissistic pity smirk
you do sometimes.
You're only satisfying yourself doing that.
Why?
I thought I'd made a pathetic excuse.
What happened?
I tripped.
What are you doing?
Where'd I put the first aid kit...
You, why do you trip so much?
Whoops, slipped back into it again.
What's so wrong with living true to myself?
Ouji.
I can't help it, habits are hard to break.
I want to stay with you.
I want us to stay together.
But that's...
I've loved you all this time,
and you finally looked my way,
so why do we have to break up now?
You can't expect anything from me, you know?
You may be fine with it now,
but think in the long term.
Can you really put up with that?
Well...
Sorry.
I put it crudely, but I'm not blaming you.
I may not be able to put up with it.
Because every time you touch me,
I crave for more.
Every time I try to ignore it, I just...
[Open Relationships]
I'm going to make an absurd suggestion,
but hear me out, okay?
Can I have sex with other individuals?
[Preview]