[ Watch on kissasia.li ]
[theme music playing]
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED SAFELY
WITH SUPERVISION
[Soo-jin] Si-woo.
[soft pop music playing]
-[Ji-yoon] Why are they…
-[chuckles]
[chuckles]
Did they choose
to stay friends after breaking up?
Shall we?
Sure.
[Ji-yoon] But why am I feeling this way?
[sighs]
[chuckles]
This feels so awkward,
just having tea together.
Congratulations.
Hmm.
You were shocked that I asked to see you.
What's this about?
Remember the first thing I said
when I ran into you again at SAEUM?
I do. You said, "Nice to meet you."
I wanted to bury our personal history
and keep things strictly professional.
That makes two of us.
I want to stop pretending we're strangers.
You know there are many rumors
circulating about you, right?
I'm used to it.
And I don't care.
That's good, but it went a bit too far.
I'm glad Young-hun
posted on the company forum.
Thank you.
Hmm?
Did you contact him
after what Mr. Ko said?
It wasn't me.
Did you see your photo at the game?
There was a photo?
[scoffs]
I feel things must've been really tough
for Ms. Cha.
First, everyone made a huge fuss
about her dating her boss,
then they turned her
into some victim being exploited.
I had no idea about this.
Ji-yoon…
I care a lot about her, okay?
Besides,
she's your one and only team member.
I just wouldn't like
to see either of you get hurt.
[Ji-yoon] If you got married
and then divorced,
what would you call your ex-husband?
Why would I even talk to him?
What is this, Hollywood? [scoffs]
If I saw so much as the back
of Goo-won's head, my blood would boil.
[chuckles] You could end up
working at the same company.
Ugh, I don't wanna think about that.
Couples who aren't married change jobs
quickly after a breakup.
-Imagine after a divorce.
-[chuckles] That's true.
Also, sweetly calling each other
by their first names.
There's a couple like that at our company?
Uh, no. It was on Blah Blah.
I guess it's one of two things.
Either they have no feelings
for each other,
or there's still something going on
between them.
Then…
Then what does it mean if seeing them
like that makes your heart pound?
They said that on Blah Blah?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Maybe…
-they have a crush?
-It's not that!
Um, I mean… I'm sure.
Let me see. I'll read it myself.
Oh. It was deleted right away.
-Mm-hmm.
-[phone buzzing]
Hi, Na-ri.
A what?
Just a moment.
Wanna go to a group blind date?
-Ms. Cha.
-Hmm?
-Mm-hmm.
-Mmm.
She says yes.
Hmm?
EPISODE 5
HAVE A "MEETING," STILL CLOCKING IN!
I already said no!
I'm not planning on dating anytime soon.
It's not a date.
It's just doing something different
to have some fun.
[sighs] Listen. I just don't have
the mental bandwidth
for that right now, okay?
What, is there something going on
with Mr. Kang?
[gasps] Hey! No way.
There's nothing going on.
I mean, aren't you guys
starting a new project?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
There's nothing yet.
-[chuckles]
-[phone buzzes]
[Si-woo] We'll start our afternoon
schedule in the product showroom.
Looks like it's starting,
our next project.
[chuckles] I'll see you.
Well, give it some more thought!
What if someone saw them
being so informal to each other?
Well, no wonder I was freaking out.
[scoffs]
[gasps] Mr. Kang?
Is he sleeping?
[tender music playing]
[No-ah] Maybe…
they have a crush?
[Ji-yoon] Do I? Mr. Kang?
That can't be it.
To me, he's just someone I work with.
His face is definitely my type though.
Is that a citrus scent?
[gasps]
I missed it.
What did you miss?
The mosquito.
Where did it go?
[mosquito buzzing sound plays]
[gasps]
[comical music playing]
[sighs]
[clears throat]
So, going forward, what kind of products
would you like to make?
The ideas I had in my notebook
have either been made
or are currently being developed.
I would really love if my appliances could
read my mind
and work on their own
when I get home from work.
Let's make that our next project. Home-AI.
Home AI?
Yes. Our next project
will be focused on delivering
an advanced user experience using AI,
as a team reporting to the President.
Directly to the President…
in the States?
It's a project I've been planning
alongside the President
since I was in the States.
So the reason the task force
was formed in the first place…
Was to bring this project to completion.
Wow. I guess nothing happens by accident
in this company, huh?
The Development Team and I
will handle the technical side of things.
Ms. Cha, you'll create the scenarios.
I need you to imagine the user's lifestyle
to anticipate what they'll need
in different situations,
and build a narrative around that.
That sounds like fun.
[gentle music playing]
I guess you aren't scared
of failing anymore.
Sorry?
When I first asked you to join
the task force, you said,
"I'm scared of failing right now.
I'd like to work on something
with a higher chance of success."
But now, I've gotten a taste of success.
And I want to succeed again
together with you, sir.
However, I'm a little nervous,
as it's something I've never done.
Doing what you know is comfortable,
but it's also easy to fall into a rut.
Taking on new challenges
sparks a fresh dose of inspiration.
Being in a relationship you know
is comfortable,
but it's easy to fall into a rut.
Taking on a man of mystery
will spark a fresh dose of inspiration.
I don't think it should
just be the two of us anymore.
Well, I guess that you're right.
Because it's a major project…
Then we'll run
a second round of recruitment.
Right.
[thunder rumbles]
-That's not right.
-I told you I don't wanna talk to you!
[Ji-yoon] Oh.
I'm sorry, sir.
I know the rumors about
me putting you in a tough spot.
Oh! No, sir. Not at all.
If anything like that happens again,
tell me. I'll be more careful.
The storm cloud is gone.
Storm cloud?
There was a storm cloud
hovering over your head.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
Oh. That's rain.
[chuckles]
[clears throat]
Wait here a moment.
I'll go get an umbrella.
Why? I'm having so much fun.
I don't remember the last time
I ran through the rain.
Wanna make a bet on who gets there first?
Ready…
Go! [chuckling]
[soft pop music playing]
Did you see it? The post?
Oh, yeah.
FUTURE HOUSEHOLD APPLIANCES TASK FORCE
SECOND ROUND
[sighs]
-Ms. Yoon No-ah.
-Yes?
Is this garbage the best you could do
for your executive report?
Have you actually learned anything
from Ms. Cha? Honestly.
Geez.
Every one of you,
please go get your act together!
[Young-sam sighs]
[sniffles]
He was fine for a while.
What's gotten into him now?
What do you think?
It's because of the task force again.
Hey, it's me.
Uh, how about
the team leads grab a drink tonight?
Want revenge?
What?
They say you should enjoy life
after you get revenge.
FUTURE HOUSEHOLD APPLIANCES TASK FORCE
SECOND ROUND
[sighs]
How is it all going?
The team leads agreed to use this chance
to get rid of the thorn in our sides.
Hey. You still don't get that guy, huh?
Why do you think
he caught the President's eye?
Throwing a few bad apples into the mix
isn't going to cut it.
[tense music playing]
If we wanna bring the task force down,
we go after the head.
By "head," you mean…
[lighter clicks]
[blows]
Dig into Kang Si-woo.
I'm sure you'll find something.
Sure.
There are a lot of applicants.
All the rumors about Mr. Kang
have been debunked
and Cha Ji-yoon totally nailed it there.
And it's AI.
Are you going to apply?
You know quite a bit about AI.
That's a luxury I can't afford with twins
and a wife working three shifts.
And you?
Aren't you interested?
[sighs]
Every time Mr. Ko
starts his ridiculous nitpicking,
I wanna quit on the spot.
But I don't feel confident
applying without strong achievements.
And I still find Mr. Kang intimidating.
Well, he is.
Even more so,
now that we know he's completely clean.
[No-ah sighs]
Thank you, sir.
[sighs] This is harder than I thought.
Some were pushed into applying,
rather than doing so willingly.
[knocks on door]
Ms. Na-ri!
Hello! I am Shin Na-ri
of the Marketing Team.
Please take a seat.
May I ask why you decided to apply?
Well, can I be completely honest
with the two of you?
-Sure.
-I'm being kicked out.
Why?
I'm the "Three-Why-Girl," you see.
By "three why,"
do you mean, "Why me? Why this? But why?"
Yes. It's just a habit of mine.
Oh, but my team lead said
they'd had enough and told me to
go to the task force
and do whatever I wanted.
[chuckles] And what happened this time?
Thing is… they told me
to take on a boring project
I was against in the first place.
There was nothing fresh about it,
and we still went ahead with it anyway.
So I said,
"Why me? Why this? But why?"
And that's that.
[Na-ri chuckles]
I can't stand doing anything predictable.
Were you wearing that when you said it?
-Lost your touch…
-[gasps]
…"Lost your touch, damn it"?
How did you know that?
You're actually the first superior
to understand how I feel.
Some people have no eye for talent.
You're right.
We won't be needing any more meetings.
Please cancel the rest.
Sorry?
What about expanding the team?
I'll handle the team-building myself.
Oh. Okay.
And I'm taking a half day off today.
Why?
For personal reasons.
Do I have to share them with you?
No.
Of course not. No.
You should clock out early too, Ms. Cha.
Okay.
And don't drink too much coffee.
[chuckles] This is chamomile tea.
That's good.
[scoffs]
Who's he meeting that he even got flowers?
Does it really have a calming effect?
[sighs] No way.
-Oh, my gosh!
-[gasps]
[chuckles] Why are you so startled?
Oh, Ms. Choi.
Ah. Could you wait here for just a minute?
-Have you had lunch? [chuckles]
-Huh? Yes.
[sighs]
What on earth was I expecting?
Pfft. She just got married!
A little wedding favor.
Thanks for taking the time to come.
Oh, but you really didn't have to,
Ms. Choi.
-What? You don't consider me close enough?
-No, that's not what I'm saying.
-[chuckles]
-Thank you so much.
Anyway, how's the task force?
To be honest, it can be quite tough,
but it is also lots of fun.
"Lots of fun"?
[scoffs] Wait, has your team lead
brainwashed you?
[chuckles]
-Maybe. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
Ah, that Kang Si-woo… [clicks tongue]
It won't be easy,
but you'll learn a lot from him.
Yeah.
I'm learning a lot from him.
Sometimes,
he tends to brood alone and ends up making
the person next to him feel lonely.
[calm piano music playing]
Whenever that happens,
you just have to give him time.
You seem to know a lot about him.
Isn't he actually pretty easy to read?
[chuckles]
At least he doesn't say things
he doesn't mean.
[chuckles]
Far better than Mr. Ko,
who's always scheming, right?
Yes. [chuckles]
So, go and have lots of fun!
If things get tough, just come see me.
Sure.
I'm off. Good luck.
Yeah. Thank you.
[sighs]
BIRTH, JULY 11, 1962 SEO YUN-HEE
DEATH, AUGUST 22, 2014
It's been three years.
Yes.
How did you find living in the States?
Didn't feel any different from here.
Have you been well, Father?
Seeing as I'm not with your mom yet,
I guess I have.
I'll see you outside.
You should head home.
I'm thinking of selling the house
and moving to the countryside.
Why so suddenly?
I'm fed up with everything.
Today feels like yesterday,
and yesterday like today.
Old memories just keep getting more vivid.
[chuckles]
I've been in that house for too long.
I'm not sure where I'll move yet,
but it'll be hard for me to come.
See if you can match my schedule.
If not, we may have to visit separately.
I might not be here next year.
I may move back to the States.
[sighs]
[grunting]
Here. Take this.
[gentle music playing]
This is…
Yeah. It's the one you took apart, broke,
and then secretly fixed.
You knew that?
Wait until you have children.
We just pretend that we don't know.
But you loved this thing.
I don't need it now.
I haven't used it once
since your mom passed.
Throw it away, fix it. It's up to you.
I have nothing to report.
There's nothing urgent.
[scoffs] I don't have a single question.
[sighs] I don't have a single excuse
to call him. Ugh.
-[sighs]
-[phone buzzes]
[upbeat music playing]
APPLY FOR RATE BENEFITS AND RECEIVE
PREFERENTIAL RATES ON LOAN!
Wow, looks like
they'll offer loans to just anyone.
[door bells chiming]
[scoffs] It wouldn't hurt you
to tell me where you're going. Hmm.
But you had to leave me
wondering all day. [scoffs]
Oh?
I still have some left.
[sniffs] Ugh.
[sighs]
It'd be nice if a fridge
told you expiration dates.
Hmm.
[device chimes]
APPLICATION
NAME: SHIN NA-RI
Next.
It's acting up again.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE THIS?
No.
Just…
just hide it out of sight.
TIME SAVING, ENERGY EFFICIENCY,
PERSONALIZED CARE
KANG SI-WOO
[lighthearted music playing]
[sighs]
He's not on here.
Figures.
Why would he?
Mr. Kang is older than me, so…
[bebop music playing]
KANG SI-WOO
[gasps]
Why so many?
KANG SI-WOO HANKUK UNIVERSITY,
MECHANICAL ENGINEERING
KANG SI-WOO
NO POSTS
SAEUM HALL OF FAME
2020 BEST HOME APPLIANCE GRAND PRIZE
KANG SI-WOO, THE DRIVING FORCE
BEHIND THE TASK FORCE'S SUCCESS
He's even more impressive
than I thought.
DEGREE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING
FROM HANKUK UNIVERSITY
HANKUK UNIVERSITY
MECHANICAL ENGINEERING 06
ENTREPRENEURIAL PASSION!
STARTUP "NIKKE"!
[gasps] Found him.
[laughing]
Oh, what is this? So dated.
[gasps]
8:12 P.M.
Oh, I'm insane.
[groans]
[gentle music playing]
What am I even doing?
Fine. I'll do it.
The group blind date.
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
[No-ah] Okay, I'll let Na-ri know!
[sighs]
This place is worth the price.
-Let's clink glasses.
-Sure. [chuckles]
[classical piano music playing]
Mmm. Delicious.
Let's bring Goo-won here next time.
Our Dr. Kim is so busy lately,
he won't even answer his mother's calls.
What? He's not doing well?
Is he eating properly?
I honestly don't know, ma'am.
Why? Did you two fight?
Uh, no.
Of course.
We broke up, actually.
Gosh.
Couples fight all the time. That's normal.
You just have to let him win this time.
[clicks tongue]
You know he's going through a lot.
That's why I even begged on my knees.
But he said no, saying he met someone.
What?
Wait…
-What kind of girl?
-[scoffs]
Is that what you want to know?
Why? To see
if she looks better on paper than me?
Hey!
How could you say such a thing?
I'm just worried that Goo-won might have
fallen for a dubious girl. [sighs]
Don't worry.
She's a student from his med school.
So ma'am…
could you please talk some sense into him?
[sighs] Should've just stuck to the plan.
You know what he's like.
Once Goo-won makes up his mind,
there's no way you can get him to listen.
So you want me to just back off
so Kim Goo-won and that girl
can live happily ever after?
Why would you say that?
I'm just trying to tell you
to go find a better man
since I think of you as a daughter.
Do you really think anything I say
will change his mind?
No, ma'am.
You can't come
and treat me like this either.
Not after everything
I've done for Goo-won.
Because I trusted
we were going to get married anyway,
I bought everything,
from the appliances to the furniture.
And that bag you brought today?
That was my entire month's salary, ma'am.
[scoffs] Wait.
You did all that because you wanted to.
Is that why you called me every time
something happened to Goo-won?
And all the talks about marriage
and asking me to look after him?
[huffs] Geez.
You're incredibly rude, aren't you?
Excuse me.
I'm very sorry to interrupt
your lovely evening, ma'am.
But I've fallen for your daughter
at first sight.
[breathes shakily] She's not my daughter.
I promise I'm not some creep.
[chuckles]
If you're a lawyer,
you must know all about
what constitutes marriage fraud.
Of course.
Then could you give me some legal advice?
No-ah!
I'd be happy to.
[sighs]
Wait. [sighs]
You can pick up the bill for once.
After all, I'm the idiot
who wasted seven years with your son.
[scoffs]
[breathing heavily]
[No-ah sighs]
So this revenge plan was a bust.
Why?
I did it. She paid an expensive meal.
Revenge needs to be cold.
If you get emotional, then you lose.
But it's just so infuriating.
Now that she found a replacement,
she's telling me to get lost.
[scoffs]
-And whose business card was that?
-It was my uncle's.
We'll have to take a head-on approach.
This method won't cut it.
[groans] Forget it, I'm tired.
What am I doing,
taking advice from a kid? [sighs]
[phone buzzing]
KIM GOO-WON
What?
[Goo-won] What did you say to my mom?
What on earth did you say
to make her cry, huh?
What?
Hey, you piece of shit!
If you're gonna call me for this,
then go to hell!
Ugh! [exclaims]
-[whistles]
-[panting]
What's the head-on approach?
A three-way clash.
Huh?
That girl also deserves to know
what kind of jerk he is.
Then what was that about
the "enjoy your life
after getting your revenge" thing?
Ugh, never mind.
[clicks tongue] I keep asking a kid
for advice. [sighs]
It's about riding the rolling waves
and having fun.
Doing what you want without being scared.
Isn't that enjoying life?
On that note, wanna go surfing?
MY BOYFRIEND'S TEACHING ME SURFING
THIS WEEKEND! WHAT SHOULD I WEAR?
#DATINGASOFTODAY #HEARTHEART
#DAILY #LOVESTAGRAM #LOVEYOU
[sighs]
Well…
the thing is, I…
You scared?
-I'm going on a group blind date!
-Group date?
Yes… [chuckles] …I might be busy
this weekend because of it.
That's why…
I can't go.
[TA scoffing]
NEW HOME-AI SCENARIO PROPOSAL
[sighs]
PROPOSAL BACKGROUND
CONSUMER NEEDS ANALYSIS
So you already put this together?
I wanted a draft before
considering the technical limitations.
Uh, purely from
a consumer's point of view.
By pulling an all-nighter?
Nothing is better
than work to clear your head.
Right. It's great work.
The thing about AI
is that it's not something
you can see, like a refrigerator.
So there may be limitations
in expanding the consumer experience.
It'd be great to have a dedicated lab.
We have a dedicated lab already.
We do?
Where at?
Is it in the R&D building?
-Would you like to see it?
-Yes.
[comical music playing]
Basically…
you're saying the dedicated lab
is your home.
We still need to keep things under wraps.
I hope you understand.
Sure.
But I'm not so sure
it's okay for me to go.
It's just for work.
That's right.
I'm just going there for work.
[sighs]
If you feel uncomfortable,
we can always do this next--
No.
It's for work anyway.
As long as you're okay with it,
then I'm fine too.
Okay.
[tango music playing]
Whoa.
Tango? You like it?
Yes.
I recall you listening to rock.
I'm surprised
you're into such passionate music.
You find that shocking?
I thought that you were the type that
just liked classical music. [chuckles]
Hmm?
What is that?
What are you referring to?
I mean, how come there's a desk
in your living room?
The living room's the most spacious.
Exactly.
Why is there a desk
at the center of your home?
Work's the center of my life.
-Is that really so strange?
-Uh, no.
[machine whirring]
Oh.
I see that you set the vacuum to run
when you get home.
[Si-woo] It's in scanning mode.
Sorry?
It's the first time
it detected another person here.
It's a prototype in development,
so it still needs a lot of tweaks.
And it crashes frequently
for unknown reasons.
ROBOT VACUUM CLEANER
SCANNING
May I take a look at it?
The beta app is on here,
so go ahead and take a look.
I'll get tea ready in the meantime.
Okay.
[sighs]
[sucks teeth] Is this it?
-[robot vacuum whirs]
-Oh.
[sighs] It'd be nice if it could talk too.
[lighthearted music playing]
Well, I think it crashes 'cause
it handles too many functions on its own.
It has a home cam, sensors,
voice recognition,
and a projector function.
Shouldn't we off-load some of them?
Right, I'll give it some thought.
And on that note,
I'd like to explore case five
I presented to you.
"The lifestyle of a man
in his mid-thirties
who's single and living alone."
Oh, he's also a workaholic
like that robot vacuum,
and a self-care perfectionist who
follows a strict diet and workout plan.
[upbeat music playing]
WELCOME BACK HOME
What is this?
It's nice to have someone greet you
when you get home.
"Welcome home."
And when movement is detected,
the lights adjust accordingly…
LIKES VARIOUS GENRES OF MUSIC
AMBIENT LIGHTING
Excuse me.
How come a bed
is the only thing in your room?
Because I just sleep in here.
But you could watch videos in bed
or roll around reading comics
while eating some snacks too.
Eating snacks in bed?
That's simply unacceptable.
[pop music playing]
[sighs]
Eating snacks in bed?
That's simply unacceptable.
So, are you planning to replace dinner
with these snacks?
No, how about fried chicken?
That's the trifecta of high-fructose
corn syrup, gluten, and trans fats.
All of which I detest.
[Ji-yoon sighs] It's that citrus scent.
-Should I get changed too?
-No.
There's no need.
We'll skip getting changed.
Let's keep moving.
CLEAN BEDROOM
CITRUS FRAGRANCE
After I change into comfortable clothes,
I go to the kitchen to have a simple meal.
Don't tell me your fridge is full of
sparkling water and not much else.
Wow. Now that's an epic plot twist.
[Si-woo] I don't like eating out.
I prefer eating at home,
whenever possible.
Are you a good cook?
I can't say I am, but I enjoy it.
Once I finish eating,
I put the dishes to wash,
and brew some Pu-erh tea.
-Want a cup?
-Sure.
Thank you.
A MAN WHO COOKS
PREFERS TEA OVER COFFEE
After I drink my tea,
I sit there and work
until it's time for bed.
Is work all he does at home?
Oh, that's grim.
Oh, this is…
That's none of your business.
[Ji-yoon] But this is incredibly valuable.
You can't just leave it
lying around like this.
Wow.
Does this belong to you?
My parents bought it from an antique store
when they were traveling in Germany.
You're saying they carried
this heavy thing all the way from there?
Yeah.
My mother often told me
about how much of a hassle it was.
No wonder.
This brand was discontinued long ago,
so it's hard to find in Korea.
It's about 50 years old, I would say.
-But does it still work?
-I haven't tried connecting it yet.
But it seems you know a lot about stereos.
Well…
Someone close to me
is completely obsessed with stereos.
[chuckles] And no,
it's not my ex-boyfriend.
-Right.
-[chuckles]
There's no whiteboard.
So, what do you use these for?
CHA JI-YOON
[gentle music playing]
[robot vacuum whirring]
[beeping, static]
CHA JI-YOON
SHE MAKES ME LAUGH
What does…
that mean?
It's just a random combination of words.
SCANNING
You can just ignore it.
So…
do I really make you laugh?
[devices chiming]
HEART RATE IS HIGH
CLOCK OUT!
That's my clock-out alarm.
Let's wrap things up,
and call it a day.
All right, then.
I should get going.
[sighs]
So, I…
make Mr. Kang laugh?
[gasps] What does that even mean?
[sighs]
CHA JI-YOON
Hello, sir.
-Please take a seat.
-Thank you.
Let me get straight to the point.
Did you apply to the task force
because of its members?
Uh…
I don't think
I can deny that's the reason.
I'd like to hear more details.
Ms. Cha told me the task force
has a great driver,
so you just need to step on the gas
without having to worry about
whether you're headed
in the right direction.
So I'd like to meet a great driver too.
Better yet, I'd like my values
to be more recognized.
It seems Ms. Cha has got it all wrong.
Sir?
Ms. Cha is not the gas pedal.
She is yet another driver.
I see.
I appreciate your time though.
I'll be in touch.
Single-person homes make up
36% of all households,
so I think we should target
that demographic specifically.
What do you think?
Mr. Kang?
Let's do that.
We'll wrap up today's meeting here.
Did you have something to tell me?
Our bus will arrive in 17 minutes.
Ah…
The thing is,
I have plans tonight, Mr. Kang.
Please go ahead without me.
[whispering] I'll wait for you outside.
Go. It's okay.
[normal] We made plans to hang out after
work already. [chuckles]
-What do you guys have planned?
-Sorry?
Why does he want to know?
He didn't tell me anything when I asked.
What did you do
when you took that half-day off?
It was the anniversary
of my mother's death.
-I went to the columbarium.
-Oh.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Now it's your turn to tell me.
A meeting.
Is there a meeting I wasn't aware of?
Well, not that kind of meeting.
It's a group date
where men and women get together. Meeting.
I should've given you
more work to do then.
Sorry?
Enjoy your date or "meeting."
I was nervous as hell
sitting right across from Mr. Kang.
[groans] I don't remember
a thing that I said.
Wait. Did he mention anything to you?
I should've given you
more work to do then.
Ms. Cha?
Ms. Cha!
-Huh?
-Oh, wow.
-What are you so deep in thought about?
-Why? What?
No-ah!
-Hey, Na-ri.
-You're here.
[exclaims]
-Is this where the group blind date is?
-Yes. Why?
Because I don't think I can do this,
you know.
[No-ah exclaims]
-Hey, grab her.
-Huh?
What? Hey, guys. Wait, you guys.
[soft jazz playing]
Hello, everyone!
I'm Shin Na-ri, your host for tonight.
Let's hear it.
Okay, first of all,
please introduce yourselves
to the people at your table.
After that, feel free to move around,
enjoy some wine,
and have all the conversations you want.
All right, then. Hope you all have fun.
[chuckles] Hello.
So, we meet again.
Sorry?
Business card.
Hello.
I liked you at first sight.
Can I please get your phone number?
Oh. [chuckles]
I'm very sorry, but I'm already engaged.
Still, you never know
with people and relationships.
KIM GI-SEUNG
INTERNAL MEDICINE SPECIALIST
Oh! You're the one from back then.
[chuckles] Oh. Hello again.
Didn't you say you had a boyfriend?
Or did you lie
because you weren't interested in me?
No.
I did have one, but I don't anymore.
I told you, didn't I?
You never know with relationships.
You're right.
Life really is unpredictable.
Do you like wine?
Yes.
-[patron] Thank you.
-Sure.
Oh.
Hello.
-[chuckles] Uh, please don't mind me. Yes.
-[Ji-yoon] Thank you.
So, do you know him?
Well, yes, I've been here a few times
with a colleague.
Ah.
I should've given you
more work to do then.
[sighs]
Why did he say something like that?
Let's see.
-"Do you enjoy spending time alone?"
-[sighs]
What on earth is that idiot doing?
[Kee-tae] Goodbye! [laughing]
-Okay, goodbye. Okay, goodbye. Thank you.
-[teacher] Goodbye.
Oh.
-All right. Han-yul, Han-gyeol, say hi.
-[both] Hello!
-I'm sorry for asking you to come here.
-Not at all.
I was the one who wanted to meet.
-Daddy, I forgot my water bottle.
-And my jacket.
Ah…
Go right ahead.
[sighs] All right, you stay here with
this gentleman and don't go anywhere.
-Okay.
Okay. All right. Thank you so much.
Mister, who are you?
I know.
Dad called Mom earlier and said
he was meeting "Three-No-Man."
-Right? You're Three-No-Man, right?
-Yes.
Wow, then are you a superhero?
Well, that's top secret.
[shushing, laughing]
[Kee-tae] All right, kids. Play safely.
Yours was a proposal,
it wasn't an application.
Oh, well, it's just an area
I've always been interested in.
I apologize for overstepping.
So you'd like to join,
but your circumstances don't allow it?
Well, as you can see, I'm not
in a position to join the task force.
Listen, I owe you a favor, don't I?
Oh, when I called Ji-yoon for you?
Yes.
Thanks to you,
I got an excellent colleague.
Yeah.
She's great, isn't she?
And I believe Ms. Cha will also need
a good colleague like you by her side.
You can work flexible hours.
You're free to come in early
and leave early as well.
Or work weekends, if you prefer.
Really?
You even have a master's degree in AI.
It'd be a shame to waste that.
Thank you so much.
But there's one thing
that you should know first.
If the project succeeds,
I'll be going back to the States.
So I can't promise anything
about your position after that.
However, I'll make sure it succeeds
so that my team members will have
the power to choose for themselves,
either by switching jobs or taking leave.
Oh, so that's why there were rumors
about your team members disappearing
without a trace.
I'll do it. No, I-I mean I'll try.
Glad to hear that.
Yeah.
[sighs] Oh, by the way,
I heard that Mr. Lee Young-hun
is doing much better
since taking his leave of absence.
-Were you the one who contacted him?
-No, I just passed along his number.
And to whom?
To Ms. Cha.
She said she wanted to clear up
some of the misunderstandings about you.
[phone buzzes]
MESSAGE FROM LEE SEONG-MIN
[Seong-min] Geez, you loser. Ji-yoon's
here on a group blind date right now.
[Na-ri] So you're saying
you want to sit with that person, right?
"Do you see yourself
getting married someday?"
I'm not against marriage.
-Then you should hurry.
-Why is that?
You'll be turning 30 next year.
When it comes to getting married,
men prefer women who are young
because they want
fewer risks with childbirth.
[sighs] "Can you stay friends with an ex?"
[inhales deeply, sighs]
I don't think I could.
What about you?
Well, wouldn't that depend on
what your relationship was like before
and how it ended?
If you broke up on good terms…
[Soo-jin] Si-woo.
Thanks so much, for letting me see you
shine on stage one last time, Ga-eul.
In that case,
I do think you could stay friends.
Though, I don't feel ready to do that yet.
[chuckles]
WHAT MAKES YOUR HEART FLUTTER
THE MOST THESE DAYS?
[lighthearted music playing]
[Si-woo] You were just hiding,
and then I thought to myself,
"I don't want to let this person go."
I'm here from the future.
This has already been released.
[Ji-yoon] Sr. Associate Cha Ji-yoon
checking in.
I'd like to apply for the task force.
[Si-woo] Making one mistake is enough.
Repeated mistakes are not mistakes.
It shows their lack of competence.
[Ji-yoon] Tell you what.
You can be the wind,
and I'll be the sun.
[Si-woo] The launch
will be presented by Ms. Cha.
If my manager is saying so,
I suppose it does.
Your gestures need to be
bolder and bigger.
Well, that's a bit upsetting.
Don't be sick.
When you get nervous, remember…
[breathes deeply]
…and you'll know the answer.
-[Ji-yoon] Is that your sign, Coach?
-[Si-woo] Yes.
[applause]
WE'RE ON THE SAME TEAM, LOL
CHA JI-YOON
[Ji-yoon] So my feelings have
already grown this deep.
WHAT MAKES YOUR HEART FLUTTER
THE MOST THESE DAYS?
It's my new project
at work.
[door opens]
-[door closes]
-[whirring]
WELCOME BACK HOME
CHA JI-YOON
[No-ah] Ms. Cha told me the task force
has a great driver,
so you just need to step on the gas
without having to worry about whether
you're headed in the right direction.
[Kee-tae] She said she wanted to clear up
some of the misunderstandings about you.
YOU HAVE 1 NEW VIDEO
WOULD YOU LIKE TO VIEW?
Hmm. Play it.
Is this it?
Or not?
Wow. You do a lot of things, don't you?
[sighs] It must be really hard
to have such a neat-freak owner.
[Ji-yoon chuckles]
[soft jazz playing]
Why didn't you go to the second round?
He told me I should marry soon
if I wanted children.
What?
Marriage felt
like the easiest destination.
Now, it just seems like
an imaginary island.
Of course it is.
Because it's not somewhere
you can go by yourself.
[laughing] You're right.
-[sighs]
-[phone buzzes, chimes]
[Kee-tae] Did you know?
If the project succeeds,
Mr. Kang is heading back to the US office.
[Ji-yoon] What do you mean?
Who told you that?
[Kee-tae]
I heard it from Mr. Kang himself.
The task force is just a temporary team.
It's not a big deal,
but I thought you should know.
-Is there something wrong?
-No. [chuckles]
I just need to go to the restroom.
WOULD YOU BET ON A LOVE
WITH HIGH ODDS OF FAILURE?
[footsteps approaching]
Hey. She just left a moment ago.
[gentle music playing]
[Ji-yoon] Twenty-year-old me
never hesitated.
I wasn't afraid of a one-sided love
that offered me nothing in return
and when love found me unexpectedly,
I never kept score.
I just wanted it to last forever.
But the person I am now
knows the great pain that comes
from the sharp edges
of broken pieces of a failed love.
And yet, these feelings
have started again.
Can I really step onto the mound again
for a game with low odds
and a predictable ending?
[line ringing]
Yes, this is Kang Si-woo.
Should I come to you?
No, you shouldn't come.
Because I want to…
leave the task force.
[Ji-yoon] If there's one thing I've
learned from my past relationship,
it's that I shouldn't even start
a relationship that is doomed to fail.
What a way to draw the line.
I'm not his cousin.
I'm his ex he dated for seven years.
And this jerk cheated on me with you.
[Si-woo] You can tell me now.
What's the real reason
you want to leave the task force?
[Kee-tae] I wanted to feign ignorance.
I'm just not wired that way,
so I'll just go ahead and ask.
[grunts] There's someone in here!
[Si-woo] I was worried about you.
Why?
[Si-woo] Because to me, Ms. Cha…