[Gao Zhun]
Mr. Gao.
It's late.
What's the matter?
The letter.
I received it.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have sulked.
Why did you sulk?
I just...
I couldn't stand that you gave
that boy your business card.
I can't stand it when you're as good
to others as you are to me.
I just want you to be good to me.
I just want you to look at me.
I...
I get jealous.
Cut!
Good. That's a wrap.
Thank you, Director.
Gentlemen.
We're shooting the promotional posters
tomorrow morning.
Please get some rest tonight.
The makeup and departure times...
I'll sync them with your assistants later.
Thank you.
Good work.
Gao Zhun was difficult because of jealousy.
But what about you?
Do you need me to write you a letter?
There's no need.
The show is just fiction.
The car is here. Let's go.
Okay.
See you tomorrow, Mr. Zhen.
See you tomorrow.
The car is here for us, too.
[Episode 7]
Soften the top light a bit more.
Let's see it from the side.
Yesterday's scene...
I still haven't quite recovered from it.
The hardest part is over.
It'll be easier from here on.
Hey.
How are things going for you two?
Quite smoothly.
Wu.
Zhun.
Wu, your sugar-free latte.
Not bad. You still remember my preference.
Of course.
Zhun.
I saw today's shooting schedule.
Today, there's...
a kiss scene.
Wu Rong, you have some heavy dark circles.
Didn't get enough rest?
Don't even ask.
I had a fight with my wife over the phone.
She really pissed me off.
But it's fine now.
As long as you're okay.
- Wu Rong.
- Yeah?
Since you're filming this,
doesn't your wife mind?
She's my wife.
It's different from a girlfriend.
You can break up with a girlfriend at any time.
But would a wife divorce you over a role?
What do you mean a girlfriend
can break up at any time?
Zhun and his fiancée won't.
They have a great relationship.
Right.
Hey, Zhun.
Who was that just now?
Hey.
That psycho...
He didn't mess with you yesterday, did he?
Wu, Zhun.
Which psycho are you talking about?
Don't butt in on adult business, kid. Go.
All right, then. I'll get back to work.
Your state is very good.
Keep it up.
Okay.
Perfect.
Look here.
Good. Let's change the pose.
- Okay.
- Why are there so many flowers?
The poster uses the language of flowers
as a metaphor for the characters.
- Look here.
- So, we prepared several kinds.
Okay.
So professional.
As expected of you, Mr. Zhen.
The success rate of these shots is amazing.
Red roses are passionate...
and seductive.
They suit you.
Gao Zhun...
Red roses don't suit him.
Of course they don't.
Gao Zhun's love... is clean and pure.
In his world, there is no calculation.
Only white roses can express his pure heart.
The character arc between us
should naturally follow my perspective.
Mr. Zhen, aren't you overstepping a bit?
The scene centers on Gao Zhun.
He is the core.
Or are you habitually
trying to upstage him?
You're the photographer, you call the shots.
Me?
Then let's try everything.
Which pair is going first?
Me.
Lest I have to follow his lead.
Why are you laughing? I'm not wrong.
Guys, can you be more affectionate?
I'm already holding him, aren't I?
It's not sensual enough.
How about this? Mr. Wu, take off some clothes.
Do some push-ups before we start.
Fine.
Let's do this.
Come on.
Yes! That's the "forced love" vibe I want.
Nice.
Press down a bit more.
A little more.
Okay, Mr. Wu is done.
Next pair, get ready.
Come on.
What?
To destroy your rose?
I can't bring myself to do it.
Zhen Xin. We're shooting a poster.
I know.
But I just can't bear to.
Okay.
Let's do another set, but tone it down.
Or the promo materials won't get approved.
I wanted to tell you that day...
The acting is fake,
but I am serious.
Good.
Great, amazing!
Hold that.
Yes, that's it. Again.
Okay.
I have something to discuss with Mr. Zhen.
Could you watch the door for me?
Okay.
Mr. Wu.
What's your advice?
Did you not take a single word I said to heart?
- I did.
- Then why are you still pestering him?
Yes. You're a Best Actor winner.
You're young, reckless, and at your peak.
You can afford to make mistakes.
Starry Entertainment will always
protect you as their top star.
But what about Zhun?
He doesn't have as many chances as you.
He can't afford to lose,
and he can't afford to make a mistake.
This is between Zhang Zhun and me.
Even if you're his senior,
you shouldn't interfere in our relationship.
How dare you even mention a relationship!
What are your intentions for Zhun?
Do you think I'm blind?
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhang.
It's not convenient for you to go in now.
Yes.
I just want to get into Zhang Zhun's bed.
- Holy shit!
- Hush.
It's a misunderstanding, all of it.
I like him.
On and off screen, I like him.
- Why you little...
- Don't come in!
Zhun.
Wu Rong.
Let us handle our own matters.
Please take Xiao Deng back first.
Wu Rong.
Fuck.
Some jokes should never be made.
I'm not joking.
Zhen Xin...
You're not Fang Chi. Wake up.
I am awake. I...
You have no idea what you're doing.
Don't you like me?
What's there to like?
We're both straight.
It's impossible.
Why do you avoid me,
but not my kisses?
I...
I haven't thought it through.
Then I'll wait until you have.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
This four-panel comic is quite funny.
Mr. Zhang, look.
Look.
Isn't it funny?
Yes.
It's quite funny.
You know what to do.
Don't do this.
Someone will see us.
But I just want to hold your hand.
Not just that.
I want to kiss you passionately,
and pull you into my very being.
Let's go.
To my place.
Honey!
Honey, why didn't you answer my calls?
You must be Mr. Zhang Zhun.
Hello, Zhen Xin must have
caused you a lot of trouble.
No, not at all.
Well...
I'll head back to my room now.
Honey.
Let's go back to our room, too.
Didn't you miss me?
Honey.
Strawberry or glow-in-the-dark? Pick one.
You saw all that just now, right?
Saw what?
You tell me.
Oh!
I ship it! I totally ship it!
Happy now?
That was for work. I understand.
You know I'm not a petty woman.
I've had the crew get you a room.
You'll stay there for the next few days.
Get some rest.
I'm going out for a walk.
Honey, what do you mean by this?
Give me more time. I'll sort it out.
When did you two start dating?
We got together this time last year.
It's been almost a year.
Honey.
They're so annoying, asking questions.
Are you being so open about things
because you want to go public?
Is that not allowed?
He's so handsome.
I couldn't tell yesterday.
He looks better in person.
He looks very natural.
Today's makeup and styling...
is too pretentious.
Oh.
So, you don't like him in character.
You like him as himself.
Zhang Zhun.
Why are your eyes so swollen?
They're bloodshot, too.
Didn't you sleep well last night?
Last night...
There were mosquitoes in the room.
They kept me awake with their biting.
Mr. Zhang, try this.
It'll clear up the redness.
Don't let it affect the shoot.
Mr. Zhang.
Let me do it.
Don't worry.
I'm an expert at applying eye drops.
Then I'll trouble you.
Here. Come on.
It's heartbreaking to see you in tears.
You must be a natural at crying scenes.
All departments, get ready.
Three, two, one.
Action.
What will you think about after you go back?
About you.
Is this distance acceptable?
Yes.
How about this?
Like this?
It's a bit strange.
Now, let's try touching.
Can you stop?
You can try to endure it a bit longer.
Cut!
No, no, no. That's all wrong.
What's wrong, Director?
Zhen Xin, at this point in the story,
your feelings for Zhang Zhun...
haven't reached that level yet, got it?
- Zhang Zhun...
- Oh, my mistake.
Gao Zhun, Gao Zhun.
I just felt this would have more tension.
If we follow your logic,
we'd have to clear the set
for every dialogue scene.
No. This isn't the vibe I want at all.
Adjust it, quickly.
Honey, have some water and take a break.
We've only been filming for a bit.
Mr. Zhang, thank you
for working with Zhen Xin.
Tell you what,
I'll treat everyone to dinner tonight.
How about hot pot?
Don't go organizing things randomly.
The crew is on a tight schedule.
We don't have the time or energy to go.
I'll go.
Great, I'll arrange it.
Where are you from, Mr. Zhang?
I'm from Sichuan. I love spicy food.
That's a shame.
Mr. Zhen and I usually
don't really like spicy food.
He has a weak stomach.
How long have you two been together?
We've... been together for almost a year?
Not that long.
We both have our own work.
We don't even see each other once a month.
But even so, we're still together.
Isn't that true love, honey?
Mr. Zhang.
What about you?
Me?
I'm getting married soon.
After I finish this project.
Are you eating?
Yeah. I'm free.
Go ahead.
Yesterday, why were you holding his hand?
If I hadn't come,
what would you have done?
Look at this hot pot.
The two pots are different.
I don't care about your pot,
but don't touch mine.
Besides, that pot of yours is nothing much.
Why aren't you eating?
I was waiting for you to come back.
This is cooked. Try it.
Honey.
Eating so much spicy food
is bad for your stomach.
It's my stomach. I'll do as I please.
Enjoy your meal.
I have something to take care of.
[Today is a good day]
Why the hell are you calling?
Come out if you have the guts!
It's me.
I'm sorry.
Dan Yi.
- I...
- Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you... alone?
I was just with...
a friend.
I was with a friend.
And...
his girlfriend.
Are you coming back?
When this is all over, will you come back?
I...
Dan Yi.
I don't know.
I can wait.
I mean, if you want to come back,
I'll be waiting for you at home.
I'm sorry.
Please give me a little more time.
I need to find that answer.
I followed you out.
Zhang Zhun.
472 steps.
From the moment you left the restaurant,
you took exactly 472 steps.
You were on the phone,
and I was following behind you.
Like a stray dog.
Why are you...
crying?
I'll break up with her.
So will I.
Do you know what Chen Zheng Sen said about us?
He said...
we're finished.
[Xie Dan Yi]
Don't chase after them.
What's the point even if you catch up?
There's a bar nearby.
Let's have a drink.
I don't know you.
You do now.
Don't worry.
There are cameras here.
It's very safe.
I'm Feng Yun Ting, Zhen Xin's girlfriend.
I never drink.
Get us a non-alcoholic drink, please.
Then why did you stop me just now?
Did you really want to chase them
just to be further humiliated?
Be better to yourself.
In this world, there are many things
you can't live without.
But a man is not one of them.
If you keep compromising,
you'll be the only one who suffers.
- Enjoy your drink.
- Thank you.
This one is non-alcoholic.
Take your time.
Are you really willing to give up?
Silly girl.
It's just like this drink.
I've already paid for it.
I can choose to frown and finish it,
or I can throw it in someone's face.
As for what I'll do,
it all depends on what makes me happy.
Or... what makes my life better.
Silly girl.
Losing in love isn't shameful.
But if you lose yourself,
that's when it gets ugly.
Take your time with the drink.
I'm off.
I'll take care of everything.
Oh, for goodness sake.
Reporters are camping out at the door.
And you two are still being so flashy.
Everyone's watching you.
How can you still act like this?
You two, stay out of sight.
Everyone, this is the crew's hotel.
- Please don't...
- Mr. Zhen!
You've been dating
Ms. Feng Yun Ting for half a year.
Why choose to go public now?
If... you always dream about someone,
and the dreams are always intimate...
What does that mean?
Essentially, the subconscious is expressing
unfulfilled intimacy and sexual desire.
Also, this person symbolizes
a quality you desire.
Then...
does it mean I like them?
If the intimacy in the dream
makes you happy when you wake up,
and you want to be close to them,
and you follow their every move in real life,
then it's likely
your subconscious revealing itself.
It means you like them.
Why aren't you sitting in the second row?
Do you know why Laozi wrote the Tao Te Ching?
Because he felt like it.