[ Watch on kissasia.li ]
[Episode 5]
[Zhongshan Police Station]
Chen Yi.
It's a good thing they agreed to settle today.
It won't go on your record.
Or you'd never pass the background check
for the police academy.
I don't care.
I'm not taking the exam anyway.
Why?
Because of Wei Ming Zhen's case?
She wasn't legally married to your father.
It won't affect you.
It has nothing to do with her.
A young brat.
[Recipient: Chen Yi]
- This is a good one.
- Really?
Everyone, listen up.
The girls' dorm needs plumbing repairs.
Boarding students will have to commute
for the next two weeks.
After the self-study period ends,
everyone heads home on your own.
Boarding students,
take all your valuables with you.
Don't leave them in the dorm. Understood?
- Yes!
- What about the boys' dorm?
I can finally go home!
[Class 10-2]
Hey, student. Why haven't you left yet?
Hurry up and go home.
[Hotel]
[Contact]
[Hiring Temp Night Shift Workers.
(Meals and Lodging Included.)]
Another overnight session.
Can you handle it?
Guns are pretty weak right now.
- Go for it!
- Am I playing it right?
Don't hog the seat if you can't play. Alright?
Log me into computer fifteen.
I'm telling you, I've been waiting for you.
I need an ID card to log you in.
I'll go first. Okay.
You're the new girl, right?
Got a boyfriend?
Look, let me tell you.
When I surf the web here,
the boss usually turns a blind eye.
So be a pal, and cut me some slack.
I can't log you in without an ID.
Why are you being so stubborn?
I'm telling you this for your own good. You...
Why are you giving the girl a hard time?
Don't stop me from logging in.
- Fine.
- Computer four.
- The password is the last six digits.
- Okay.
What bad luck.
- Renew machine twelve for two more hours.
- Okay.
And make me some instant noodles.
Yong.
Your cousin goes to No.1 High School, right?
Ask around and see what's been going on
at their school lately.
Let's go, Yi. Time to eat.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I ran into Miao Jing at
the internet cafe a few days ago.
I heard their dorms are being renovated,
so the boarders have to commute.
She had nowhere to go,
so she works at an internet cafe at night.
I think it's good for her to be out there.
She can learn to be independent.
You've been too tired lately,
working several jobs at once.
It pains me just watching you.
And if you take on that burden,
it'll be nothing but trouble.
You're done?
Give her the house key.
I get what you mean.
Okay. She took it?
She did take it.
But she didn't seem very willing.
I had to force it on her.
As long as she has it.
I'm home. I'll hang up now.
Look. It's out.
- This is today's change.
- Okay.
Machines nine and ten.
Two cups of instant noodles and two sausages.
They haven't paid yet.
I'll note it down.
What time do you get off work?
Need a computer?
Didn't you get the key?
Don't you have school during the day?
Can your body take staying up like this?
You need an ID to start a session.
Did you have a fight with your family?
Are you the manager?
Can I ask for a day off for her?
He's not my family. I don't even know him.
Miao Jing.
Excuse me! What's wrong with the computer?
Come over here, quick!
I'll go. Coming!
I'm here. What's wrong? Is it lagging?
Look!
You're playing well.
Reboot it.
Okay, let's resume.
Let me know if you need anything else.
Sure thing. Let's roll!
Excuse me.
Can you add one more hour for me?
And get me a coke. Hurry up.
Sure.
Are you okay? Why are you following me?
You can go on living your life your way.
I want to stay here.
Just how long are you going to follow me?
You're the one who kicked me out.
Now you're following me. What do you want?
And didn't you say I'm not your family anymore?
You must think I look pathetic now.
I only kicked you out because I was angry.
I apologize.
And I don't have any other intentions.
You are my family.
That home is also your home.
Stop crying.
It's scorching out.
Let's go inside.
Well... Everything is packed.
Your toothbrush and stuff are where they were.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- I'm good.
Okay.
Don't worry. I won't let you suffer.
I'm a grown man. I can take care of my family.
You must be hungry.
I'll get you something to eat.
What was I thinking?
How could I say such things?
Let me give you a hand.
Don't worry about it. Go rest. I'll do it.
- I know how to do it too.
- Well.
Let's eat out.
I still have two tubs of these.
Stay where you are.
There should be a flashlight.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
The circuit breaker must have tripped.
I'll go check it out.
What's the matter?
I forgot to pay the electricity bill.
Let's go.
It's not ready yet.
Won't stirring it make it cook faster?
Let it sit a bit longer.
Just a bit longer.
The fork won't go through.
There are two sausages left.
It's about ready.
- Don't mind me.
- You give me yours. I'll give you mine.
Pay the electricity and water bills here.
For gas, you need the gas card.
Go to the window at the Civic Center.
They only take cash.
Got it.
I'll pay for it.
I'm the only one using the utilities
at home anyway.
Why would you pay?
I'll be using them from now on, too.
From the internet cafe and selling scrap,
I've saved some money.
Let me pay for part of it.
Otherwise, I'd feel bad staying here.
Is it enough? I only have fifty yuan.
For just the two of us. It's enough.
[Check Unpaid Bills, Amount Due]
How could I owe so much?
I have more.
Aside from selling scrap,
I also sell stationery to my classmates.
And, I don't want to only use your money.
Take it.
I'll pay you back later.
How's the shave?
Looking sharp.
- Five yuan for all of these. Thank you.
- Five yuan?
- How much is this?
- Five yuan.
Yi. Here, take these two bags.
- Two yuan.
- Thank you, Ms. Li.
You're welcome.
- Okay, bye.
Every Wednesday and Saturday,
they sell off a batch of scraps.
Many of them are still edible.
They only cost a little.
Let's go.
We can make money here.
Look for the most valuable stuff.
Copper wire, aluminum alloy, motors.
These are all things
that can be sold for a good price.
But don't come to places like this alone.
It isn't safe at night.
Watch your step. Don't step on any nails.
Don't get hit by anything.
Don't look down.
Look up.
If that falls, won't we die?
It's okay. If it falls, it'll hit me first.
No one watches the scrap from these factories.
Pick up whatever you want.
Here.
Chen Yi. Is this valuable?
Yes.
This kind.
Did you use to do this a lot?
Come to places like this?
Back in elementary and middle school,
I was always hungry.
I wanted something to eat.
Watch your hands.
We have enough for today, right?
Let's head back?
Sure.
- Can you carry it?
- I can.
You're getting better and better at this.
I've picked up quite a lot.
Back up slowly.
Run!
Chen Yi, run!
We were like two wild dogs,
wandering in the wilderness.
We were surrounded
by loneliness and desolation.
But we could still find scraps of happiness.
[Three months later]
Same as usual. 6.8 kilograms.
15 yuan per kilogram. That's 102 yuan.
As for the aluminum, that's 25 yuan.
The total is 127 yuan.
Can you add three more yuan?
Make it a round number.
- Don't do that.
- Fine. It's not easy for you two either.
Come back often, all right?
Thank you, mister.
- Thank you, mister.
- Bye-bye!
See? You need me.
We've gotten a lot lately.
How about I treat you to something nice?
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
So many things.
- Give it to me.
- Stay on the side.
Don't run!
We spent 12 yuan on the meal.
There's still 118 yuan left.
118 yuan?
You're giving it all to me?
Then what about you?
Don't worry. I still have some.
I shouldn't have bought the coke.
A bottle of coke costs two yuan.
Have a sip.
Alright. Let's go home.
[Miao Jing's estimated tuition: 2,000]
I think Miao Jing should spend more time
with her family.
She can talk things over with her mom.
It's much more convenient.
Right.
What do you mean, "right"?
Besides, how long do you plan to support her?
Until she finishes high school?
Or until she finishes college?
You can't even prepare her future dowry,
can you?
Wait, she's only in high school.
Why talk about marriage and dowries?
Exactly.
If she really left with her mother,
she might have fetched a bride price
by the time she was sixteen.
You're taking on everything yourself.
You sound like you can actually manage it.
Why wouldn't I be able to?
Since I've taken her in, I can manage it.
I can afford it.
No matter what,
I'm still better than her unreliable mother.
Miao Jing is moving out of the dorm.
I'm leaving first.
- Hurry up. They're at the playground.
- Coming!
- I'll wait for you downstairs.
- Okay.
Come here.
Check your things.
Did you leave anything behind?
- I'm not responsible for lost valuables.
- I have everything.
My teacher needs to talk to me.
Wait for me at the gate.
Miss, you wanted to see me?
Miao Jing, you did well this time.
Ranked 42nd in the entire grade.
Very encouraging.
Actually, I'm aware of your situation.
But this really couldn't be helped.
It's time we talked about it.
- Your mother...
- My mom?
Is there news about my mom?
Did she ever mention to you
that your tuition
for next semester hasn't been paid?
She didn't pay my tuition?
Tuition isn't usually paid once a year.
Before your mom left,
she did make one payment.
She said things were tight at home,
so she only paid for one semester.
The school understood.
After all,
our bottom line is not to let a child drop out.
But who knew later she would...
Take this.
[Tuition Fee Receipt]
Based on your current situation,
the school has waived part of the fee.
I'll make sure to pay this back.
But I only just got the notice.
I don't know how long the school can give me.
This is a lot of money.
You can't handle it right now.
Go home and talk it over with your family.
We're having fish tonight. Your favorite.
I'll go clean it up.
What's wrong? Why the long face?
My teacher told me about my mom.
Is there news about her?
No. But it is about her.
She is her, and you are you.
Don't put so much pressure on yourself.
Go put the meat in the fridge.
She's going abroad.
In such a short time,
she's already hooked up with a new man.
Wei Ming Zhen's quite something.
Don't think she's some harmless woman.
Sorry.
At the moment,
the subscriber you've dialed can't be reached.
Sorry.
At the moment,
the subscriber you've dialed can't be reached.
Please try again later.
Sorry.
- If it won't go through, stop calling.
- Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not trying to find her.
No. I am looking for her,
but it's for something important.
[Receipt]
The teacher came to see you today.
That's what it's about?
I didn't want to tell you.
I just wanted to talk to her.
At least, she should take responsibility.
What about you?
What were you going to say just now?
Nothing.
Don't worry about the payment notice.
I've got this.
Give me your dirty clothes.
Wait. This one too.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Okay.
This is a gift from Mr. Zhang.
- Another round?
- Consider yourself lucky.
I'm so sorry. Look at you getting cocky.
He doesn't know any better.
Please don't take it personally.
He loses track of himself when he plays.
Please bear with him.
This is just an exhibition match.
Why take it so seriously?
Second place is good enough.
Second place pays 8,000.
First place pays 20,000.
There are tips for every win too.
Why wouldn't I keep playing?
Is this about money?
Let me tell you, you have no backing.
Even if you win the championship,
they'll force you to cough up your prize money.
Do you believe me?
So you also think I can win the championship?
Don't worry. Once I sink my teeth
into something, I won't spit it out.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Nothing. The circuit breaker must have tripped.
I'll go check it out.