[ Watch on kissasia.li ]
[Episode 4]
Jing, it's raining. Let's go home now.
Let Yi stay with his dad alone.
Let's go.
[Chen Li Bin]
[Liang Xiao Qing]
[Du Billiards]
I heard you'd transfer this place.
Who told you that?
Du, living in Teng City for so many years,
I know the daily revenues better than you.
Since you'd transfer it, shall we talk?
[Du Billiards]
It's not that I don't trust you,
but that at your age,
you must think it through. It's no joke.
And your loans are no joke, either.
How's it, Yi?
Everything included,
plus six months' rents waived.
We can proceed these days.
Awesome, Yi.
Actually, you can go to a junior college.
You needn't stay in Teng City for me and Yong.
The pool hall itself is fine.
Du can't collect money for now.
So he's eager to transfer it.
True.
I heard many local small business owners
are transferring urgently.
What happened?
Did Du invest in Green Life?
It seems so.
[Green Life Health]
We can't live at home anymore.
Board at school from next week.
Wait, Mom. It's only mid-semester.
- Why should I board at school?
- Why do you ask?
Tell your teacher you'd board for months,
no, a year.
The money should be enough.
We won't live at home?
Are you leaving?
Open the door! Manager Wei, don't avoid me.
Open the door!
Don't hide! Open the door!
Open the door now!
I know you're here!
Open the door!
Auntie, the debt collectors are at the door.
Mom!
Mom, where are you going?
Mom, don't go! Mom!
Mom!
She's in her room, isn't she?
Why are you back?
Can't I be back?
It's your home. Of course you can.
What are you doing?
Don't board at school anymore.
Move back. I'll organize your items.
Are you sure you want me in your room?
The sheets and covers are washed and clean.
Look at your age.
Can't you have a sense of self-protection?
It's your home.
I can't occupy your room forever.
Now your dad passed away,
Mom and I shouldn't stay.
That's your room. Go back to sleep.
By the way,
if asked about Wei Ming Zhen lately,
don't say a word.
If anything happens, come to me.
You can't handle the debt collectors.
[Class 10-2]
Miao Jing.
Come out for a second.
It's your mom on the phone.
- Hello?
- Jing, pack up now.
Go to the school gate in 30 minutes.
- Uncle Li will pick you up.
- Why?
Don't ask. Listen.
I'm at the bus station. Come soon.
Wait, Mom. What are you doing?
Listen, I can't explain now.
The bus is about to leave. Pack up now.
Anyway, we can't stay in Teng City.
We must leave soon. Hurry!
Mom!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Your mom got you a half day off.
Go on in.
What? Mortgaged?
Look, your father Chen Li Bin signed.
All the procedures are legal.
[Chen Li Bin]
We really can't approve your loan.
It was signed when Chen Li Bin was in ICU.
Do you think it was his decision?
But the procedures are formal.
You mean not only can I not get a loan,
but also need to pay the mortgage
of my inherited house?
How about a third-party transaction?
No way.
- Yi.
- The pool hall is no hurry.
No. Wei Ming Zhen fled.
What?
Are we looking for Wei Ming Zhen?
To the school.
How did you know it?
A crowd at the bank entrance
claimed Green Life scammed them
and the dealers fled.
I asked around and
found the Green Life dealers in Teng City
were Wei Ming Zhen and her paramour.
How's that possible? Didn't she run a shop?
It's true.
They're wanted by the whole city.
Yi, some want to skin Wei Ming Zhen alive.
What should Miao Jing do?
Jing, hurry! Get in the car!
Wait, what happened to my mom?
Get in first. Hurry!
- We have no time!
- How can I leave with you like this?
Did she cause trouble? Are you fleeing?
You don't want her to have trouble, right?
If you don't go, don't blame us.
- Come, get in first.
- I won't go.
- Jing!
- Yi, it's Miao Jing.
- Hurry!
- Who's him?
- Explain first.
- I won't go! Don't pull me!
- Get in, Jing! Hurry!
- Who are you?
Security! Kidnap! Call the police!
What's wrong?
- Don't! It's a misunderstanding.
- Who are you?
- Jing, tell them we're acquaintances.
- Misunderstanding?
Her mom and I are picking her up.
- Are you leaving?
- That's nonsense!
- If you don't go, I'll call the police.
- Don't.
Jing, we'll wait for you at the bus station.
Go!
Miao Jing.
[Teng City Bus Station]
Move in.
Go.
3:10 PM to Lingang, please line up.
Don't push. Line up.
Give me your phone.
Let me explain. I really don't know.
Where will she take you? Lingang City?
If I knew, I wouldn't hide it from you.
Give me your phone!
Move forward. Line up.
Time for ticket check.
Passengers for Lingang, line up.
Yi!
- Did you find them?
- We searched everywhere but no.
Not even that man.
If we search one by one, we'll never find them.
Let's find another way.
[Lost Person Broadcast]
Please look for Wei Ming Zhen for us.
Wei Ming Zhen?
Yes.
Are you okay?
My brother's diploma is in my mom's bag.
I need it urgently.
Okay, don't worry. Calm down.
Attention, passengers.
Ms. Wei Ming Zhen.
Please come to the service station
in the waiting room immediately.
Your child is looking for you.
Ms. Wei Ming Zhen.
Please come to the service station
in the waiting room immediately.
Your child is looking for you.
This is the only bus leaving now.
Did she get out somewhere first,
then ask you to go find her?
No.
I saw that man trying to pull you onto
the bus. And now you're telling me "no"?
Do you take me for a fool?
Lingang! Anyone else for Lingang?
Come and line up!
- Lingang passengers, this way!
- Miao Jing, what are you doing?
- Line up!
- I thought you didn't believe me.
To Lingang. I'll take you to her.
You'd better find her.
- What are you doing?
- Looking for someone. Right away...
- I'll be right out.
- Get out!
- Who are you people?
Mom!
- Wei Ming Zhen!
- Hello? Where are you going?
- Did you buy a ticket?
Excuse me. Did you buy a ticket?
- Who are you looking for?
- I'm looking for someone. Right away!
I'm coming. I'm coming down right now.
Miao Jing, what are you doing?
Didn't you want me to find her?
Then look for her!
Get off if you don't have a ticket!
[Teng City to Lingang]
They're coming out.
Next time you don't have a ticket,
don't try to sneak in!
Sorry about that. I understand, I understand.
Are you satisfied now?
Go find your mom. I won't stop you.
Why are you taking it out on me?
I don't even know where she went.
Where can I go?
[Please make the payment promptly
to avoid overdue fees.]
Go wherever you want.
I can't control you anyway.
[Ticket]
For suspected false advertising
and illegal production and operations,
the authorities have opened an investigation.
The case involves a massive sum of money
and a wide range of victims,
drawing intense public attention.
The company used television,
radio, and other media outlets
to launch a large-scale ad campaign,
claiming that their products can
cure chronic diseases and slow down aging.
It has been verified
that said effects have no scientific basis.
The product contains only
ordinary food ingredients.
The company also forged health licenses.
[Due to unforeseen family circumstances,]
Product quality inspection reports.
[I was unable to continue my studies.]
And other documents.
As of now, the police
have taken compulsory measures
against 12 key suspects.
Seized funds involved
in the case exceed three million yuan.
The health department reminds consumers
that health supplements
cannot replace medicine for treatment.
When purchasing,
look for the Health Food Approval Number.
Don't believe exaggerated claims.
We will continue to follow
the progress of the case.
[Dormitory Affairs Office]
Hello. I'd like to pay for the dorm.
For a year.
Here. Enter your PIN.
You're paying for a full year. It's not enough.
It's not enough.
Then just for one semester.
Enter it again.
Ma'am.
Are there any work-study opportunities?
Finally, time to eat.
What's for lunch today?
Miao Jing, let's go eat.
I'm not hungry.
Yi.
I'm sorry, Du. This time, I...
It's okay.
Is everything at home settled now?
My condolences.
By the way.
This is my most prized possession.
I'm getting old now.
I don't have that passion anymore.
Here. Take it.
Take it.
Thank you, Du.
[District 7 Nightclub]
Yi. Are you really planning to start gambling
on pool here again?
The loan won't wait.
I have to earn whatever I can.
It's not like I haven't done it before.
The one in white, the girl playing the piano.
Do you know her?
Chen.
Mister.
Chen. The gambling matches are canceled.
You should head back for the week.
Why?
Yi is playing so well.
You can't just call it off like that.
Will they start up again later?
Ever since that tax fraud case broke,
there's a city-wide crackdown.
If the boss hosts gambling matches
at a time like this,
isn't he just asking for trouble?
So, just head back for now.
Understood.
Thank you.
Yi, why do you care what he says?
Worst-case scenario,
you can just mortgage your house.
[Contact: Fang, Du, Ports]
Wait, that's not right.
Your mom left you the house.
I won't sell it.
No. Then what should we do, Yi?
If we can't take over the pool hall,
then so be it.
But what about the bank?
There's still the loan to pay back.
Don't worry about it.
Don't be scared.
Do me a favor.
Can you make a call for me?
Hey, junk collector!
Have you seen an injured man?
I'm talking to you!
Thanks.
Young man.
If you ever need anything,
come find me in District 7.
You might not believe what I'm saying now.
But once I get back on my feet,
you'll know who I am.
Young man.
What's your name...
- Not bad.
- Splitting into classes after Grade 10?
- 90.
- My math is so bad. 9...
I can't do science.
90.
90!
9...
- You're good!
- It was okay.
I got lucky this time.
Mine, mine.
- You're fifth.
- Yeah.
- Congratulations.
- That's amazing.
[Class 10-2, Monthly Exam, December]
135 in math.
[Your grades have dropped sharply.]
I just got a bit lucky.
As you all know, next semester,
we'll split into arts and science tracks.
In recent years,
the science-track cutoff has been higher.
Choose carefully based on your own situation.
So only top students can choose science?
Not necessarily.
High-ranking students
with no major weak subjects are more stable.
Think it over carefully, everyone.
Class president, next week,
collect the letters of intent.
- Okay.
- Good.
Turn to "Autumn in the Old Capital."
Hello. How can I help you today?
I'm here to make a loan payment.
Okay.
Please check the remaining balance
on the loan for me.
After deducting this 800 yuan,
there's still 260,000 yuan in installments.
The account holder is Wei Ming Zhen.
This card shows it has been frozen.
- Did I hear that right?
- Did he just say...
Yes. I heard the name Wei Ming Zhen.
Then... I'll come back to handle this later.
- Wei Ming Zhen!
- You're Wei Ming Zhen's daughter, right?
Don't leave!
Don't go! Stop her!
- Where are you going?
- Don't leave!
You think you can run?
My mom will come back.
Don't cause a scene in a public place.
- Where is Wei Ming Zhen?
- Where is she?
- This kid...
- Isn't there money in this card?
- Exactly!
Others might not know her whereabouts.
- But there's no way you don't know!
- No.
- I've been trying to contact her too.
- Let's go. Come with us to the police station.
- Let's go. Come with us to the station.
- Take her to the police station.
- Let's talk at the station.
- If you keep manhandling me like this,
- Let's go. We'll talk at the station.
- I won't be the one the police arrest.
You can get in touch with Wei Ming Zhen?
W-Who are you?
Who are you?
I'm looking for the murderer's daughter.
What's it to you?
The murderer's daughter? Murderer?
Murderer? I didn't know about that.
Stop getting in the way.
Let's talk somewhere else.
- This is a matter of life and death.
- You can't leave!
It's much more important than your business!
[Teng City Commercial Bank]
Yi, let's talk this out.
Didn't you say you could contact your mom?
- Call her.
- She won't answer.
Do you think I'll believe that?
Call her. Call her until she picks up.
I've cleared my schedule today.
I'll wait until you get through.
- What if she doesn't answer?
- Yeah.
- Keep calling.
- What's going on?
If that doesn't work, use another phone.
- Right.
- Make her call.
I don't believe we can't find her.
Still not getting through.
- What...
- Who has a phone?
Don't you want to find Wei Ming Zhen?
- Let her keep calling.
- Give her the phone.
- Who's got a phone?
- We must find Wei Ming Zhen today.
- We have to get that money back.
- Give her a phone to call.
- What's going on here?
A bunch of grown men bullying a girl?
Go after the person who owes you.
- What are you saying?
- We want our money back!
- Shut up. Say that again.
Call the police.
Call the police!
- You can't leave!
- They're leaving!
- Don't leave!
- You can't leave!
- Don't let her leave!
Are you crazy? Watch where you're going!
I'll pay you back a little every month.
Miao Jing.
You think that makes you noble?
Wei Ming Zhen ran away from her debts.
They couldn't find her,
they had nowhere to vent their anger.
Then you walked right into it,
saying you could reach your mom.
Miao Jing.
Where's that smart girl you used to be?
Take your money back, I don't want it.
I'll take their anger.
I'll pay my mom's debts myself.
Miao Jing.
I told you, this jacket
doesn't look good underneath.
- But my mom insisted I wear it.
- I think it looks good.
Miao Jing.
Why are you here?
Aren't you cold?
I'm memorizing vocabulary.
The draft here keeps my mind sharp.
Then where's your vocabulary book?
I've memorized it all.
- Knock it off.
- I've never seen her in winter clothes.
She doesn't even have a book.
I pity her.
So pitiful.
Come with me.
- Sure.
- When should we go?
Let's go in a couple of days.
I know a place for painting and clay work.
- Really?
- It's a lot of fun.
- It's a deal then.
- Okay.
If you're no good, someone will teach you.
By the way, I just bought this sketchbook.
- I got it from that place.
- Really?
- Look at the cover.
- It's so delicate.
Isn't it nice?
I thought we had a burglar.
I'm just taking my own things.
Miao Jing.
Let me get you another outfit.
No need.
[Teng City Experimental No.1 High School]
What can I do for you?
I'm looking for someone.
Who? Are you delivering something?
Yes.
Sign in here.
Class?
Name?
Please pass on a message.
- Just say...
- Okay.
These are her mother's things.
Okay, sure.
Okay.
That's all for this lesson. Class dismissed.
All rise.
Goodbye, class.
Goodbye!
Miao Jing. Come out for a moment.
Your family sent you something.
Go to the reception room and check.
Is it my mom?
- Wait for me.
- If she's really back, keep it low.
Don't let this affect your studies.
Hello. I'm Miao Jing from Class 10-2.
I'm here to pick something up.
Class 10-2...
This bag.
Here.
Excuse me, did my mom come herself?
Or did she send someone?
A man brought it.
Oh, right. He left a note.
[Deal with your mother's belongings yourself.]
Thank you.
Okay. Take care.
Miao Jing, aren't you going to wash up?
In a minute.
[Deal with your mother's belongings yourself.]
[Auto Repair Co., Ltd.]
T-wrench.
Yi.
Why do you fix this car every day?
You wouldn't understand.
Maybe this car will be mine one day.
Didn't you find a job at a construction site?
Why are you still at this place?
The construction site pays too little.
Go back early.
Don't you have training at school?
Wherever you are, we'll be there.
At school, I'm learning auto repair anyway.
This is just like an internship.
Yi, Miao Jing is here.
[Auto Repair Co., Ltd.]
What's this?
I've already kept my mom's things.
You shouldn't have sent these.
Just take them.
I don't need your charity.
From now on, I'm done with her business.
Yi, don't say that.
I'm sure Miao Jing doesn't feel good either.
When Chen Li Bin locked you up,
she rushed over to save you.
Then she got into trouble,
and was kicked out of the house.
And now...
When did that happen?
She went back that day too?
You didn't know?
When we got there,
Chen Li Bin was just getting home.
If she hadn't stalled him at the door,
we might not have gotten out.
Fresh lamb skewers! Lamb skewers!
Century egg pork congee, one yuan a bowl!
- Two bowls, please.
- Okay, hold on.
- Come take a look.
- Here.
- Which one? This one?
- I want this one.
- I'll take this one.
- Okay, one moment.
One spicy cold noodle, please.
Grilled chicken, fresh off the grill!
- Okay.
- Here, thank you.
How about a non-spicy one?
Let's go with non-spicy.
Are you finished with this?
This is a duck leg.
Mister.
- We're finished with this.
- We don't want it anymore.
Freshly grilled, take a look.
Take a look at the fruit. Fresh fruit!
Come take a look.
Do you still want this?
No, we're done. You can take it.
Okay.
Come look at the fruit.
I have some for two or three yuan.
They're very fresh.
- Then I'll take these two.
- Okay.
- This apple too.
That one is quite fresh too. Take a look.
It's freshly picked.
You're in my way.
How much lunch money do you have left?
You can't even afford food,
but you're still this stubborn?
It's none of your business.
Go back and focus on school.
Miao Jing.
Miao Jing, I'm talking to you.
They're stalking you.
It hurts.
Did they bully you?
Miao Jing, I'm asking you a question.
- Miao Jing.
- Now, I have nothing to do with you.
Stop meddling in my business.
Argue with me when you can protect yourself.
So you helped me this time on a whim.
But what about next time?
I have my own way of handling things.
Running away is your way?
I can't fight like you.
Going head-to-head with them is stupid.
Running doesn't make me a coward.
Clever, are we?
Who is it?
It's late! Stop banging on the door!
I can't even sleep!
So you're saying...
you barged in and beat them up,
just because you didn't like them?
- Yes.
- He hit us! You...
She's Chen Yi's family member.
Yes.
- It's her.
- Are you Chen Yi's family member?
I'm not his family.
Liar!
He clearly stood up for you.
He was acting on your behalf.
- What are you doing?
- He stood up for you!
- Sit down!
Silence!
- No, you...
- He hit us! Look at him!
- Look at what he did to us!
- Sit down and talk.
Haven't had enough of a beating yet?
Look, he still wants to hit us! Look!
- Yeah, exactly!
- Look at the state he left me in!
- You sit down too.
- What did you just say?
You're so tough, aren't you?
Go on, say it.
- It hurts so much.
- Yeah.
What are you here for?
You're here to resolve a conflict.
- But Officer.
- Look at this.
She's the daughter of that con artist!
Instead of arresting them,
are you bringing us in?
- We're the victims!
- Exactly!
What? Do you have proof?
There's no justice anymore!
- We don't have any evidence?
- Exactly!
What kind of police officer are you?
Silence!
- Captain.
- This is no place to make a scene!
Captain, the statements are done.
He hit us!
Yeah!
Chen Yi.
I remember you applied to the police academy.
How did you end up here? What happened?
I didn't like the look of them.
Just looking for trouble.
- You...
- Calm down and talk properly.
The statement makes it very clear.
This afternoon, you also had an argument.
So, what's your relationship with him?
I have nothing to do with him.
- Keep lying.
- Nothing to do with him?
Then why did he call you here?
My mom and his dad used to live together.
Now my mom has run away, and his dad is dead.
- You're quite the storyteller.
- Yeah, exactly.
A con artist's daughter knows her stuff...
Did you know beforehand about his revenge plan?
I didn't know. I was in class at school.
In class?
You're the daughter of a con artist.
You're still going to class? Have you no shame?
That's enough. Be quiet.
- I'm just telling the truth.
- Shut up.
How late will you be working today?
It'll be a bit late today, you go home first.
By the way, Kai called in a relative.
This girl came over.
Drop her off on your way back.
Look after her a bit.
Okay.
I bought you some cakes and some soup.
Remember to eat.
Don't work so hard that you forget to eat.
Got it.
We'll be going now.
She'll take you back.
Let's go.
Where do you live?
I'll give you a ride home.
Thank you, I can go back by myself.
It's not safe to walk alone at night.
Besides, he asked me to do this.
How about this? Why don't you walk with me?
Did that police officer scare you just now?
No.
He's always that stern.
He may look fierce.
But he's actually very kind.
We're getting married soon.
Congratulations.
You're in high school now.
Is school exhausting?
It's okay.
You're still growing.
Don't just focus on your studies.
Make sure you're getting enough nutrients.
Take good care of yourself. Okay?
By the way, do you have a phone?
Let's exchange contact info.
You can call me if anything happens.
Let's go.