I was bold enough
to use the gold inlay method
to connect the broken parts,
for the good luck of gold inlaid with jade.
Please take a look, sir.
Forgive me, sir.
I tried to repair it,
but the making of this bracelet
is different from other amber.
The color is also extremely special.
Even if the broken parts are barely glued together,
these red cracks
cannot be replicated.
This gold inlay method,
though tacky,
is the only way to ensure
the original appearance of the bracelet.
Get out.
Know what to say
and what not to say.
Don't worry, sir.
I have never seen this amber bracelet.
Go find another.
He is already
the best bracelet craftsman in Kuizhou.
Who are you?
Let me try.
I can repair this bracelet.
Even the best craftsmen in Kuizhou can't do it.
Can you do it, my lady?
You can't blame them.
Their skills of inlaying gold and jade are excellent,
but this seeped-in color
is the specialty of our Yanzhi Pavilion.
You know seeped-in color?
Among
the rouge and lip balm
mixed by my cousin,
I've seen
dozens of shades of red,
if not a hundred.
I've seen this red color.
I can mix it.
Besides,
sir,
aren't you afraid that others will know
that you are repairing this bracelet?
You have something on me,
so I
will definitely keep my mouth shut.
Wouldn't that make me more useful
than those craftsmen outside?
If you can't restore
the original color of this bracelet,
you'll be whipped twenty times.
If you ruin this bracelet...
My life is yours.
But if I fix it...
Qionghua
is yours.
Okay.
It's a deal.
Without further ado,
let's go to the back mountain now.
These flowers have been in the sun long enough.
They have the least moisture right now.
It's the best time to extract the color.
Your injury...
I'm fine.
Wait a minute.
Keep this batch of juice for now.
Usually, it's discarded after squeezing twice.
But no one knows
that the color from the third squeeze is the deepest.
He eats nothing.
He only drinks a little sweet water every day.
Mrs. Fang is really devoted
to the master's matter.
Take good care of it.
Yes, sir.
This flower
has been out of the soil for two days,
and its roots are burned.
It really
can't be saved.
My mother planted Qionghua for many years
and is quite experienced in it.
Even her method doesn't work?
Unless it's
a miracle by the gods.
Never mind.
It's the will of heaven.
What about Lady Fang?
The time to go to the black market is tomorrow night.
Once I get the Qionghua seeds
and truly grow them,
she will definitely have a share.
I don't want to be a person
who breaks his promises.
Young Master, do you really believe
that Fang Qingcheng asked the lady to get the Qionghua?
What is the difference between believing and not believing?
Now this Qionghua
and Fang Zhuozhuo are the only two baits that can draw out
Fang Qingcheng.
Even if it's a trap,
I have to step in and see.
The Master ordered
that when he is not here,
no one is allowed near the study.
You really can't go in.
My lady.
Please don't make it difficult for me.
You really can't go in.
My head hurts so much.
Well...
It hurts terribly.
My lady.
Somebody, come!
Oh, you Chu Shengyi.
I spent three days fixing the bracelet for you,
but you actually went back on your word.
Not letting me near the study.
Could it be
that Qionghua is still hidden here?
Playing the lute at night in the Han Palace spring.
Under a cold moon and tent with snow as a neighbor.
The snowy night outside the Great Wall is windy and cold.
How could Zhaojun still have the mood
and strength to play the lute?
Lute at night,
Han Palace spring.
That's right.
The person in this painting looks so much like Qingcheng.
The word 'Xinxin'
seems to have been touched so much that it faded.
The person in the painting must have 'Xin' in her name.
So she is the owner of this bracelet.
I know.
Husband, do you recognize this painting?
You went into the secret room?
You went back on your word,
so I had to find something against you
to make you keep your promise.
But it's a good thing I went in.
It solved the doubt in my mind.
It turns out
Qingcheng is just a substitute for the person in this painting.
This girl named Xinxin
is the one you truly want to marry, right?
How did you crack the poetry code?
Your mechanism
is not even as delicate as a three-year-old child's nine-linked puzzle.
Give me the Qionghua.
Otherwise,
I won't even let you keep this little memory.
Xin'er.
His leg.
Oh no.
Zi'er.
Hurry.
Young Master.
The Qionghua you wanted
has withered.