Kuizhou honors plumpness.
A woman's full figure is highly valued.
The skinny girls
must obey the guilt order,
become the lowest class,
serve as slaves,
and barely survive.
Only a plump beauty
is what gentlemen desire.
Speaking of which,
the most gorgeous plump beauty in our state
is the owner of the cosmetic shop Yanzhi Pavilion,
Fang Qingcheng.
Master Fang
is born rich, elegant,
and noble.
And today
is her wedding day with the Third Lord of the Governor's Mansion,
Chu Shengyi.
She is here.
A lord from the Governor's Mansion
is really marrying a businesswoman.
Fang Qingcheng
has made it to the top.
I am so jealous.
It is almost time to light up.
Madam.
Have mercy.
The back door is locked due to the Lord's wedding.
I was forced
to enter through the front door.
Have mercy.
Madam.
The bride has arrived.
Miss.
The time...
Let me go take a look.
We can't afford to offend Madam Li.
Wait a moment.
Madam.
Mother.
This
new skinny slave doesn't know the rules.
She bumped into you.
I will
help you punish her later.
But the auspicious time is almost over.
Can the bride come in first?
I misspoke.
Mother.
You're getting married.
You should be more thoughtful
and careful from now on.
I will keep your teachings in mind.
This can't go on.
Hold on, Miss.
Hold on a little longer.
Let me go check again.
It is too late.
This...
Why did it expire so fast?
Why is there no movement?
Hold on a little longer, Miss.
I will rush them.
Why did it expire so fast?
The transformation rouge my grandmother left behind
has run out.
I thought I'd finish the ceremony before 9 p.m.,
but it got delayed.
What should we do?
There is no other way.
To get Qionghua,
this is our only chance.
Madam Li
hates skinny girls.
If you go in like this,
you'll be killed.
The auspicious time has come. Welcome the bride.
I have to get Qionghua
to make the transformation rouge.
Today, Qionghua is only available in Madam Li's mansion.
This time, Qionghua will be used as a bridal gift.
She will personally bestow it.
It is the best opportunity to get it.
No matter how dangerous it is today,
in order to turn back into Qingcheng,
I must complete this wedding.
Get Qionghua.
With your current figure,
Madam Li will see through you at a glance.
I can only hide it for as long as I can.
Qionghua.
The bride and groom are paying their respects.
First bow to heaven and earth.
Young Madam, retreat three inches with your right foot.
One inch less is considered disrespectful.
So many rules.
Oh no, why has this cushion sunk?
Second bow to the parents.
When bowing, keep the fan parallel to your face.
Husband and wife bow to each other.
Who are you?
Isn't the owner of Yanzhi Pavilion a chubby beauty?
Why is she a thin girl?
Mother, please allow me to speak.
This person is not Fang Qingcheng.
You!
Who are you?
Where is Fang Qingcheng?
How dare you disturb the Third Young Master's wedding!
Take her down!
Madam,
I have something to say.
I am Fang Qingcheng's younger sister, Fang Zhuozhuo.
Because it concerns my cousin and the Third Young Master's lifelong happiness,
I risked my life to marry in her place.
Please let me finish.
If Madam still wants to punish me after hearing me out,
I only ask for an intact corpse,
so that my cousin can recognize her flesh and blood when she returns.
Cousin?
I thank Madam for the opportunity to explain.
My cousin, Fang Qingcheng,
was preparing for the Makeup Selection Ceremony
supervised by Madam in two months.
She worked hard every day,
swearing to present Madam with a stunning makeup look.
Yesterday,
my cousin personally went to the back mountain to collect rare flowers.
Until now,
there has been no news of her.
My cousin loves the Third Young Master deeply,
and I couldn't bear to see this good match missed.
That's why I risked my life to marry in her place.
I know I deserve to die a thousand deaths,
but I hope Madam and the Third Young Master can understand
the true sisterly affection between us.
What a deep sisterly bond.
Then I will grant your wish
and reward you with an intact corpse.
Madam is perceptive.
I did have selfish motives for doing this.
I
have actually admired the Third Young Master for a long time.
I know my status as a flower slave is low,
and I am truly not worthy of the Governor's Mansion.
But if there was even a one-in-a-ten-thousand chance,
I wanted to try.
Flower slave.
Was the Third Young Master's deceased birth mother also...
A flower slave? Interesting.
Yi'er.
Your father is still ill.
Since you have established your own household,
whether to kill
or to marry,
it's up to you.
It is all my fault.
I have caused you trouble, Mother.
The Sin Appearance Teaching
is the physical standard Mother set for the women of Kuizhou.
If we let this skinny woman marry into the estate as a substitute,
it would truly waste Mother's painstaking efforts.
However,
this Fang Zhuozhuo
is Qingcheng's cousin.
If we just kill her,
I truly cannot bear to hurt Qingcheng.
How about this?
Qingcheng will be my primary wife.
As for you,
you can stay as a concubine.
Thank you, Madam.
Thank you, Third Lord.
Since she's not the Young Madam,
cancel the flower bestowal.
Take the Qionghua away.
What exactly is this woman intending to do?
I didn't get the Qionghua today,
so I can only stay here and look for another chance.
I must survive tonight safely first.
My lord.
Let me
help you undress.
Come.
Forgive me, my lord.
The wedding candle went out,
I'm afraid it's a bad omen.
For our wedding night, my lord,
why don't we postpone it?
You said
you've admired me for a long time,
and risked your life to marry as a substitute.
You aren't even afraid of death,
so are you afraid of a bad omen?
My lord.
I am truly sincere towards you.
Then I must ask,
what exactly do you admire about me?
I am quite curious.
I
once saw you from afar.
You have such elegant bearing,
and I could never forget it.
If that's the case,
and you have nothing else to say,
don't waste this beautiful night.
Mourning clothes?
Forgive me, my lord.
Someone in my family passed away last month,
and my mourning period isn't over.
I know this violates etiquette,
but given the emergency,
I hope you can show some pity,
and let me observe the mourning period with a pure body,
before I come to serve you.
If so,
I won't force you.
If you have any news about Qingcheng,
tell me immediately.
Of course.
Farewell, my lord.
My lady.
Nanny.
My lady,
are you alright?
My heart
was in my mouth.
Fortunately, you were alert.
Otherwise, today's mess would've been hard to resolve.
Thanks to the news from Wuming Workshop in the black market,
which let us know.
This Madam Li,
although she dotes on Chu Shengyi in public,
actually suppresses him at every turn.
Today is her son's wedding.
On such an auspicious day...
She actually killed someone.
I bet that she would use my status as a flower slave
to humiliate Chu Shengyi.
Now that
the Qionghua is gone,
how do we make the transformation rouge?
As things stand,
we can only steal it from the Chief Commander's Mansion.
Madam Li's birthday banquet is in three days.
This is a good opportunity.
It's too dangerous, Miss.
The mansion has strict rules.
You are a concubine,
so you can't attend the banquet.
If concubines enter without being summoned,
they will be beheaded!
The Qionghua is rare
and very hard to grow.
Over the years, I've read all the ancient books
and tried countless formulas,
only to find out that Qionghua
is the key to making this transformation rouge.
Now, looking at the entire Central Plains,
only Madam Li's private garden in Qiwu Courtyard has it.
If I don't have this transformation rouge,
with my looks,
I won't even be qualified for the preliminary selection of the Makeup Ceremony,
let alone leading Yanzhi Pavilion to win first place.
But...
Say no more, Granny.
My mind is made up.
The moon is full.
An old friend returns.
I've finally found someone who looks like you.
As long as I marry Fang Qingcheng,
kill her,
and let you take the position of his wife,
you won't have to suffer humiliation in Quantan anymore.
Wait for me a little longer.