Young Master.
I have checked.
That Fang Zhuozhuo is indeed Fang Qingcheng's cousin,
and also indeed a flower servant at Yanzhi Pavilion.
But I didn't find out
that any elder in her family passed away.
To be exact,
I can't find anything about her family background at all.
Since she has no feelings for me,
then
why did she marry into the mansion in Qingcheng's place?
Could it
really be because of their deep sisterly bond?
Fang Qingcheng's whereabouts are currently unknown.
The most important thing is to find her first.
We cannot affect the grand plan.
Later,
go find a few capable guards
and set off to the back mountain immediately to look for her.
Put on plain clothes.
Follow me to Yanzhi Pavilion early tomorrow morning,
and bring Fang Zhuozhuo.
You are the closest person to Qingcheng.
I
am just doing some trivial things for the Pavilion Master.
I heard you were the dowry maid of Qingcheng's grandmother.
Qingcheng's family passed away early,
and you have been taking care of her.
You seem like master and servant,
but you are more like family.
With such a close relationship,
how could you not know Qingcheng's whereabouts?
My Lord, please understand.
The Pavilion Master is dedicated to developing cosmetics.
To pick rare flowers and herbs,
she travels around.
It's common for her not to return for over ten days.
Before leaving to pick flowers this time, the Pavilion Master said
she would definitely be back before the wedding.
So,
I didn't take it to heart.
Yes.
My cousin went to the back mountain to pick Jinlumei.
That flower grows in the crevices of cliffs
and is extremely difficult to pick.
Perhaps there were none on the back mountain,
so she might have
gone somewhere else.
Yes.
The Pavilion Master did say she was going to pick Jinlumei.
Qingcheng left at the Si hour.
Why do you remember so clearly?
That day, I
had an appointment with a customer at the pavilion at the Si hour
to study the bridal makeup powder for her wedding banquet.
Before leaving, the Pavilion Master specially reminded me
that the customer likes rose dew,
and told me to add more.
Good thing I prepared in advance.
The Pavilion Master worked hard for the Makeup Selection Ceremony,
saying she must surpass the Linlang Pavilion in the East Market
and make Yanzhi Pavilion win first place.
It seems the Pavilion Master attaches great importance to the Makeup Selection Ceremony.
Madam Li is holding this Makeup Selection Ceremony,
so everyone is secretly saying
that the Pavilion Master agreed to marry just for this ceremony.
My Lord, please understand.
I saw with my own eyes that when my cousin left,
she kept your birth date paper close to her body.
She is deeply in love with you.
Before your Pavilion Master went missing,
was there anything strange?
There was nothing strange about the Pavilion Master,
but as for this flower servant...
Forgive me, Third Young Master.
It just slipped out.
However, this Lady Fang is quite strange.
Although she and the Pavilion Master are sisters,
none of us have ever seen them together.
They are obviously not close.
She risked her life to take the Pavilion Master's place.
She must have her own agenda.
Yes.
There is a world of difference between my cousin and me.
She is usually busy with her affairs,
so she can't often be with me.
But she brought me to Kuizhou
and gave me a place to stay.
I have nothing but love and admiration for her.
Marrying in her place was indeed for her sake.
But right after she went missing,
someone is trying to sow discord.
I think that person has an agenda.
Also,
that day,
I saw with my own eyes
that you and she had an argument in the backyard.
She clearly told you
that the hibiscus paste you made had an uneven color
and asked you to improve it.
You were very dissatisfied.
Could her disappearance be related to you?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I was discussing with the Pavilion Master
the techniques of making cosmetics.
What does a flower slave like you know?
My Lord, it's better to be safe
than sorry.
If someone around her harbors evil intentions,
you must interrogate them carefully.
Don't let the culprit go.
You...
Young Master, someone has seen Fang Qingcheng.
Let's go.
Send a few men to keep an eye on this place.
Yes, sir.
Chu Shengyi is investigating so closely.
I must get the Qionghua flower at this birthday banquet
and escape quickly.
If you want to plant these flowers
in the Master's manor,
you will violate the Third Master's taboo.
What taboo?
It's just a show for others.
Saying that flowers will ruin the manor's feng shui.
I think
he is just begging Madam Li for mercy like a dog.
Madam Li treats him like this,
yet he
even avoids mentioning his birth mother's background.
Such a shameless person
is truly despicable.
Such a person is the most terrifying.
As the saying goes, better to provoke a gentleman's anger
than a villain's resentment.
If you really piss him off...
I want to piss him off.
The more he bans flowers,
the more I will plant them.
Making him lose all face
will naturally please Madam Li.
That's my shortcut to attend the birthday banquet.
Besides Madam Li,
isn't there also the Grand Governor?
Everyone knows
that our Grand Governor is of royal descent
and values face the most.
Chu Shengyi's birth mother, Concubine Zhao,
was originally a flower slave.
This is a taboo in the Governor's manor.
If you make such a big scene
and really anger the Governor,
wouldn't it be
dangerous?
Don't worry.
Just tell me what you saw.
I won't make things difficult for you.
I was chopping wood in the back mountain that day,
and I saw a plump girl walking into the mountain.
Is it her?
The person in this portrait?
Then, about an hour later,
when I finished chopping wood and was about to go home,
I saw another skinny girl walking out of the mountain.
It's easy to get lost in the back mountain if you are not careful.
Few people usually go there.
Seeing two girls in one day,
I thought it was strange too.
Does the skinny girl you saw look like this?
Yes, that's her.
You may go back first.
We interrogated her for so long yesterday,
but Lady Fang never mentioned she had been to the back mountain.
Fang Zhuozhuo and Fang Qingcheng
appearing at the same place at the same time
is just too much of a coincidence.
So it is highly possible that these two
are plotting something.