Really?
They are all modeled after Qingcheng's personal belongings.
Even the patterns on my old belongings that were stolen in Dongxing
were on that paper.
After Chu Shengyi got the Qionghua seeds,
I followed him,
and saw him give a stack of drawings to an artisan.
On those drawings
were all of Qingcheng's personal belongings.
Third... Third Master.
What is he trying to do?
Logically speaking,
he is so obsessed with Xin'er.
If he wanted Qingcheng as a substitute,
he should make Qingcheng imitate Xin'er.
That's right.
Looking at it now,
it doesn't seem like he's looking for a substitute.
This is very suspicious.
There's one more thing.
This is...
Later at the black market,
I went to that stall again.
A fake made of rouge mixed with glue,
and you dare ask for a hundred guan?
You have a good eye, My Lady.
This is exclusively for the royal family.
You won't see the real thing outside.
If you hadn't seen it, boss,
you couldn't have imitated it so well.
Give it to me.
You are very clever, my lady.
But this rouge box is an extraordinary item.
It was originally
rewarded by the Grand Commander to Concubine Zhao.
The biological mother of the Third Young Master,
Concubine Zhao.
Yes.
After Concubine Zhao passed away,
this item eventually fell into my hands after many years.
But after all these years,
the rouge box was severely damaged over time.
If you really want to buy it, my lady,
I can bring out the authentic one
and sell it to you at a lower price.
It's a deal.
Copper rusts easily.
But no matter how long it has been or how easily it rusts,
it shouldn't look like this.
And these small holes are...
Poison.
But as for what poison it is,
I am not sure yet.
Could it be that
the Third Master's biological mother was poisoned?
This deep Marquis's mansion
truly eats people alive.
My lady,
after the matter of the Qionghua flower is over,
we'd better leave quickly.
Granny, please do me a favor.
Go and look into this poison for me.
Make sure no one finds out.
Okay.
I'm too involved with Chu Shengyi.
This copper rouge box
might become the key to saving my life in the future.
My lord is in such a hurry to run an errand.
I just want to remind you
not to rush out.
Young Master, Nanny Chang is here.
Madam asked me to bring a message.
The other day,
the Zhaoyebai presented by Lady Fang
pleased me very much.
Lady Fang's exquisite flower-planting skills
are unmatched by any craftsman in the Governor's Mansion.
Now I order the Third Master and Lady Fang
to plant Qionghua flowers in the mansion.
If they can make this flower bloom successfully,
I will reward them handsomely.
If the planting is fruitless,
then
everyone in the mansion will be punished for deception,
with no leniency.
I will do my best to tend to the Qionghua flowers,
and will never disappoint Mother's high hopes.
What does my lord say?
I will strictly follow Mother's instructions.
Then please, my lord,
give me the Qionghua seeds.
Then I will quietly wait
for the good news from you and Lady Fang.
Nice trick, my lady.
I had no choice.
After all, you fear nothing,
but you only listen to Mother.
I was just taking advantage of the situation.
Now that Mother has ordered us to plant flowers,
why don't we cooperate
and take what we need?
Why should I cooperate with you?
I said that when Qionghua blooms,
Qingcheng will appear.
In this matter,
our goals are the same.
When Concubine Zhao was alive,
the few Qionghua flowers in the private garden of Qiwu Courtyard
were tended by her.
As Concubine Zhao's son,
you must know the accurate planting method.
And I,
having never planted Qionghua flowers,
will inevitably make mistakes.
It doesn't matter if I die then,
but I fear that Mother, in her fury,
will implicate the whole mansion.
Qionghua grows faster than ordinary flowers.
Go buy some rootless water first.
Shopkeeper,
do you have rootless water for planting flowers?
Yes, yes, yes. Today's snow water is very clean.
I saved a lot
in the cellar.
How much do you need, my lady?
Just fill this bamboo tube.
Okay, just a moment.
This is so beautiful.
Would you like to buy one?
Sweep the board.
You.
Sir,
what kind of board game are you playing?
This is Shuanglu Chess.
Are you also interested?
I happened to see an endgame before,
and I have some doubts.
I take the liberty to ask,
please enlighten me.
I wouldn't dare.
It's rare to see a young lady
interested in Shuanglu Chess.
Just tell me your questions.
May I?
Please.
Brilliant.
Where have you seen this endgame?
What is so brilliant about it?
This is a deadly trap of substitution.
Logically,
he is obsessed with Xin'er.
If he wanted Qingcheng as a substitute,
he should've asked her to imitate Xin'er.
Looking at it now,
it doesn't seem like looking for a substitute.
A deadly trap.
The person in the portrait looks so much like Qingcheng.
Could it be?
Substitution.
Chu Shengyi wants Xin'er
to take his wife's place.
Kill his wife and replace her.
Young Master.
A body was found in the back mountain.
It seems to be Fang Qingcheng's.
Go fetch Weirui.
Yes.
Wait.
Bring Fang Zhuozhuo along as well.
Where did the body come from?
Don't worry, Miss.
She has been dead for days.
It's an unclaimed body.
There won't be any problems.
We can only wrong this lady for now.
After testing him,
we will give her a proper burial.
Yes.
Step forward and take a look.
I can't see the face clearly.
But the day the Pavilion Master disappeared,
she was wearing this dress,
and the figure is similar.
Did your Pavilion Master have
any distinct scars
or birthmarks?
I'm not sure.
But we couldn't find her for so long.
In all likelihood,
this is the Pavilion Master.
Pavilion Master.
You promised us
to bring back the best Jinlumei.
How could you leave us
and Yanzhi Pavilion behind?
Go back first.
Where is Fang Zhuozhuo?
Lady Fang is not in the manor.
We've sent someone to look for her.
Not here?
We've been looking for Fang Qingcheng to no avail.
Now she suddenly appears.
It seems Fang Zhuozhuo
has seen through my plan.
If this is really Fang Qingcheng.
I'm afraid Xin'er
will never come back.
Young Master.
Our guess was right.
What should we do now?
Play out the whole act.
After all, Qingcheng
still needs to be alive to attend the Makeup Selection Ceremony.