You, over here.
So many flowers bloomed overnight.
Over here.
Be careful.
Not a single flower is allowed in the Master's mansion.
Come with me to the backyard first.
Last year we missed that spot,
and the Master saw it by chance.
That manager was thrown directly into the private dungeon by the Master.
I heard she lost half her life.
I don't want to follow in her footsteps.
You,
take
the flowers.
Come and listen.
Are they turning the soil?
I heard the Lady of Huifeng Hall
used to be a flower slave.
Oh, my lady.
Flowers are forbidden in the Master's mansion.
If the Master finds out,
you and all of us will die a graveless death.
My lady.
You, get some people to break the door open.
What's hanging on the door is from your Master's study,
the most expensive jade ruyi.
Smash it if you're not afraid of being punished.
You stay here and watch.
I'll go find the Master.
Master.
The servants said
Lady Fang brought flowers to the backyard.
Yes, Master, please do something.
Lady Fang is planting flowers in the backyard.
Lady Fang.
She even blocked it with your jade ruyi.
We didn't dare to smash it.
Smash it.
Move aside.
Drag Lady Fang out
and lock her up.
Somebody come.
Bring a torch.
Master, please see clearly.
These flowers,
I planted them as a birthday gift for my mother.
It is out of my filial piety,
and also for your sake, Master.
Do you know that in my mansion,
planting flowers is a taboo?
I am new here,
how would I know about any taboos?
If I had known,
even if I were given a hundred times the courage,
I would never dare.
Master, please see clearly.
I did try to stop Lady Fang just now.
The head maid did say something.
But it was too late,
I had already planted the flowers.
Now I'm afraid the whole Kuizhou City knows
that I will present rare flowers to my mother.
If I cannot deliver them when the time comes,
and implicate the whole mansion,
I wouldn't be able to absolve myself even with ten thousand deaths.
Are you threatening me?
I don't believe a single word
you say.
Take her away.
Everything I said is true.
Even if you insist on executing me,
I will let
everyone in Kuizhou know
that I planted flowers for my mother
and died for my filial piety.
I heard the Commander was furious last night.
He was so angry he even overturned his medicine bowl.
Saying that the Third Young Master was acting recklessly out of favor,
not only did he take a low-status woman into the mansion on his own,
but he also caused chaos in his own household,
making the entire Kuizhou watch the Governor's Mansion as a joke.
The Third Young Master kneeled at the door of the study all night
and just went back.
My son,
he really is a romantic.
First it was that Lady Ye,
and now,
it's Fang Qingcheng.
The Third Young Master has had a leg ailment for a long time.
His official career has long been hopeless.
As a crippled person,
doesn't he only have some little desires left?
The Master didn't say anything else besides this.
Rest assured, Madam.
The Governor hasn't blamed you even half a word.
It was his own decision to let that flower slave into the mansion.
If he can't manage his own people
and the trouble reaches the Master,
it's not something I can control.
Everyone knows I dote on my son.
Don't I accommodate him in everything?
You are right, Madam. Not to mention this matter
has nothing to do with you,
even if it really had some connection,
over these years,
in which matter
has the Governor not followed your wishes?
The affection between the Master and me
is not something others can compare to.
Prepare some ointment to promote blood circulation and relieve stasis,
and send it to the Young Master's mansion.
Our Third Young Master's knees
can't take any more torment.
Yes.
As usual.
Rest assured, Madam.
Your affection for the Third Young Master
will be seen by everyone.
This thing about flowers,
you just have to trim it more for it to be to your liking.
Tell me,
for my birthday banquet,
he definitely won't bring that flower slave,
right?
It doesn't conform to etiquette,
not to mention the Third Young Master hates her to the bone now.
Pass on the word
to let her come.
Yes.
My lady,
do you know what is special about my water dungeon?
Ordinary water dungeons
take lives
using water.
But here,
I rely on fire.
Lady,
do you feel anything?
Please see clearly, my lord.
My devotion to you
is sincere.
I'm afraid there must be some misunderstanding in this.
I have a few questions,
and I hope you can
answer them truthfully.
Just ask, my lord.
I will certainly tell you everything I know.
At Wei hour the day before the wedding,
where were you?
I
was resting in my own room.
You're lying.
Maybe you forgot,
let me kindly remind you.
There was a woodcutter.
I saw you at the back mountain this afternoon.
My cousin went missing,
so I went to the back mountain to look for her.
If so,
why did you lie?
At a time like this,
if I admitted going to the back mountain,
wouldn't it arouse suspicion?
I didn't want any trouble,
so I never mentioned it.
Why did you go to the back mountain?
I...
realized
my cousin forgot her bamboo hook.
I went to look for her,
but couldn't find her,
so I came down.
Do you have any witnesses?
If you don't tell the truth,
it seems the water temperature needs to be raised.
Wait.
Every word I said is true.
My husband,
what will it take for you to believe me?
You two sisters,
one is an impostor,
and one mysteriously missing,
and now you both went to the back mountain.
One thing leads to another.
What is your intention?
I've said all I should.
If you insist on killing me,
I guarantee
that you will never
see Qingcheng again in your life.
Then I will kill her beloved sister.
I just want to see
if she will show up.
Do you still not want to tell the truth?
You
say I harbor ulterior motives.
But I think you
are not any nobler.
You, the Third Master of the Governor's Mansion,
are willing to marry a merchant's daughter.
Isn't it just for money?
How about
you let me go,
and the dividends of Yanzhi Pavilion,
I'll share with you?
What do you think?
A mere flower slave,
how dare you speak so arrogantly!
Tell me,
where did you hide Qingcheng?
Or
did you kill her
to take over Yanzhi Pavilion?
Young Master.
Madam suddenly sent word,
asking Lady Fang to enter the Governor's Mansion the day after tomorrow,
to attend the birthday banquet with you.
Men,
let Lady Fang down.
Young Master.
Do you really think Lady Fang works for Madam?
Madam Li's message
came a bit too coincidentally.
Since she came to my mansion,
she has been against me at every turn.
A mere flower slave
keeps saying
she wants to share the prosperity of Yanzhi Pavilion with me.
Such arrogance,
she must have someone backing her.
The one in Qiwu Courtyard
has been using this method to contact the hidden agents.
Go
and find a way
to put this in Fang Zhuozhuo's room.
What if Lady Fang really goes to Qiwu Courtyard
and meets with the Madam?
To save Xin'er,
then we definitely can't let her live.