Young Master, this bracelet...
It's my fault
for failing to protect Xin'er.
All these years,
what have I really been able to protect?
I couldn't protect my mother,
I couldn't protect Xin'er,
and I can't even protect myself.
You have done your best, Young Master.
That venomous woman has committed so many sins.
If you hadn't been maneuvering in secret all these years,
quietly burying those poor thin women who died unjustly
and compensating their families,
how could our mansion
have ended up like this,
reduced to an empty shell?
To keep you in check, that venomous woman
forced Miss Xin'er to marry
the little prince of Quantan as a concubine,
killed the guards we sent,
and planted spies around her.
It's truly despicable.
Xin'er is the only family I have left.
No matter the cost,
I want it restored to its original state.
Act covertly.
Yes, sir.
Where is the paper?
Lady Fang indeed hasn't read the words on it.
It seems Fang Zhuozhuo
is not Lady Li's person.
Now that all the viburnum flowers in Qiwu Garden are destroyed,
this is the only one left.
Miss, you're awake.
Granny.
Granny, where is the flower?
There was a fire in the private garden of Qiwu Garden last night.
I heard all the flowers were burned,
including the viburnum flowers.
But Granny,
I got the viburnum flower.
Who brought me back to the mansion?
Chu Shengyi?
Right.
You inhaled thick smoke
and fell into a coma.
It was the young master who saved you from the fire
and brought you back.
Chu Shengyi saved me.
Drink this medicine while it's hot.
The smoke hurt your lungs.
You need to rest well,
otherwise it will leave a lasting illness.
I brewed it myself, don't worry.
Since Chu Shengyi found me,
he could have handed me over to Lady Li.
Why did he risk saving me?
The viburnum flower.
The viburnum flower is in Chu Shengyi's hands.
All the viburnum flowers in Qiwu Garden are destroyed.
The one I picked is now the only one in the world.
Chu Shengyi
must have guessed my intention of marrying into the mansion as a substitute.
He wants to keep the flower
to force me to hand over Qingcheng.
Then,
it seems we can't leave.
Since he wants to make a deal with you,
does that mean he won't hurt you?
It's hard to say he won't want to kill me again.
Last time, I was accidentally saved
by Lady Li's birthday banquet.
Next time,
I might not be so lucky.
It seems Miss Fang really isn't Lady Li's person.
But it's just a flower.
To risk her life
for it?
Are you feeling better, my lady?
Thanks to you, I'm much better.
My lady, come and taste this Jiangling Shaochun wine.
A little osmanthus was added when it was sealed in the jar,
so it has a faint floral fragrance when you drink it.
Your wine
is naturally a fine vintage.
But I wonder if today's main course
is to be tasted or admired.
This Qiong flower is rare,
so naturally it cannot be eaten.
Of course it's for admiring.
The flower is indeed extremely beautiful.
But the way it was obtained was ungraceful,
ultimately tainted with dust,
and losing some of its charm.
A treasure covered in dust
also blinds the eyes of those with intentions.
Knowing it's a doomed fate,
yet still gambling on luck.
If one has intentions,
how could they rely only on luck?
It's just that
they ignored the villain watching the chess game from the sidelines,
letting him unexpectedly make a move.
If that person could succeed,
it only shows that the one playing the game
had some oversights.
Are you feeling unwell, my lady?
You poisoned the wine.
The wine is not poisoned,
but I can't guarantee
that your body isn't poisoned.
At the birthday banquet that day,
your face was flushed,
and your breathing was rapid.
I was quite worried,
but I didn't expect
it was because of this Qilin cactus spine.
And this wine
only triggers the remaining toxins in your body.
Do you know, my lady,
my mother's garden is full of blooming flowers,
but there are no cacti.
To steal the Qiong flower,
you not only feigned illness,
but even set a fire.
But do you know
because of this fire,
the entire Huben Guard was beaten with military sticks
and they are lying in the military camp right now.
Imagine,
if my mother knew you broke into the garden to steal the flower
and burned down her entire garden,
what would she think?
This is all your framing!
Since you used it,
you naturally have a wound on your body.
If you still refuse to confess,
I might have to find a way
to examine your body.
I
had no way out,
so I resorted to this.
I originally only wanted to burn a haystack as a diversion.
Who would have expected the wind to suddenly pick up?
So you admit it.
You risked your life to get this Qiong flower.
It shows that the Qiong flower
is very important to you, right?
The secret of transforming into rouge
must not be discovered by him.
It was my cousin's order.
I dared not disobey.
Qingcheng?
Since things have come to this,
I won't hide it from you anymore.
Actually, marrying in her place and taking the flower
were all tasks given to me by my cousin.
Why did Qingcheng want to take this Qiong flower?
Maybe for the Makeup Selection Ceremony.
As to what exactly,
how would a lowly flower slave like me know?
Where is Qingcheng right now?
I don't know.
Really, if I knew,
why would I have suffered so much
in your private dungeon that day?
Besides, your guards
should have already searched all of Kuizhou
and the back mountain.
Did you find Qingcheng?
Why don't you
give me the Qionghua first?
Maybe
my cousin will show up.
Young Master.
Zanghua Pavilion.
It should be here.
This wandering merchant really has a lot of rules.
I heard solving this riddle is only the first trial.
Huanbo offers a cup to the guest.
Sir,
you seek an item,
while the merchant seeks fate.
Sir, only by draining this cup
can you see the truth.
Now,
can you tell me?
Xin'er.
Madam Li specifically instructed us
to take good care of the little madam.
Let me go.
Don't let her starve and lose weight.
Don't neglect the noble lady from Kuizhou.
Pry her mouth open.
Feed her.
Eat.
This blade has no hilt.
It hurts both others and yourself.
You must think it through.
Xin'er.
Please don't take offense, sir.
The wandering merchant from the Western Regions set this rule.
He won't sell his treasures to those without true devotion.
Thus, he set up this pipe dream
so that you
could see your true heart.
Xin'er's pain
is probably deeper than this dream.
So,
I passed.
Naturally.
Sir,
when you go to the black market,
hang this item at your waist.
Upon hearing
the sound of the willow flute,
you will be able to see the person you want to see.
Thank you.
I feel that
I have an affinity with you.
I'd like to remind you,
this is the first trap set by the merchant.
As for what comes next,
I do not know.
So when you arrive at the black market,
you must
be extra careful.
Farewell.