Miss,
this flower
was destroyed by the Third Young Master.
If the Qionghua flower were alive,
Chu Shengyi would be able to control me.
He's not that stupid.
I was careless.
This flower,
when it was brought out from Qiwu Courtyard,
its roots must have been burned.
Never mind.
He broke his promise first,
and I destroyed the painting.
We are even.
Speaking of this.
Right, Miss.
Didn't you ask me to keep an eye on
the information trade in Wuming Workshop?
I found out something.
Take a look at this, Miss.
The traveling merchant from the Western Regions
is said to appear in the black market tonight.
Rumor has it that the merchant has
the Qionghua seeds.
Really?
Qionghua seeds are rare.
I have been looking for them for years to no avail.
But to buy things from the traveling merchant
is not an easy task.
That merchant has weird rules.
One must first solve the puzzle
to get the token.
To get the token now,
it must be too late.
I can't care so much now.
The Qionghua flower is destroyed.
The Qionghua seeds,
I must get my hands on them.
Granny,
stay here.
In case something happens,
we would all be trapped in the black market
and unable to escape.
But without the token,
how can you make the merchant give you the seeds?
We can only play it by ear.
This traveling merchant's temperament is really weird.
I heard there is another test.
Do you know what it is?
Nobody knows.
Even Wuming Workshop
can't buy any information.
Could this be the token?
Knife wound.
Are you blind?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, this is the dendrobium I just picked.
I was going to sell it in the black market for rice.
The grain in our Kuizhou
can make a dog wag its tail
and make a pig grow some meat.
Feeding you, a lowly skinny thing,
is simply a waste.
A waste.
Stop it.
The black market is not regulated by Kuizhou laws.
Only business matters here,
not your origin.
You
shouldn't treat her like this.
Another piece of bad luck.
It's not your turn to teach me a lesson.
Are you asking for death?
You...
Who do you think you are?
Mind your own business.
You're blocking my way.
Do you own the road?
Do you know who my father is?
Apologize to this lady.
Why?
Because
if you hurt someone,
you should apologize.
I only hurt a thin slave.
What does fat or thin,
rich or poor,
have to do with it?
You are facing a person right now.
Apologize.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Get out.
Sword wound.
Could it be related to the wandering merchant too?
There's actually someone in Kuizhou who doesn't despise thin women.
Why are you following me?
I just offended that fat man.
Seeing that you have great skills,
it must be safer to follow you.
My family is strict.
I sneaked out today
just to see the novelties in the black market.
I promise
I won't disturb your business.
No.
This copper rouge box is a rarity.
In the whole Kuizhou City,
you can't find another one now.
Take a close look.
I want this. Name your price.
What a joke. This brass rouge box is rare.
I'm missing this one in my collection.
Name your price.
Don't move.
Hand it over,
or her life is forfeit.
Whatever.
Sir,
it's useless to hold me hostage.
We really don't know each other.
Stop pretending, you two.
If you didn't know each other,
would you have protected her so much
at the entrance of the black market just now?
Wait.
This copper rouge box with the official seal of Linlang Pavilion,
only ten of them were made back then.
It is a specially made antique replica by the officials.
Later, a batch of affordable improved versions were copied
and are still in use today.
Why not take it under the light
and take a look?
This copper rouge box
is not brass at all,
but made of gold-plated bronze.
Since you said
you've collected rouge boxes for years
and seen countless of them,
how come you can't even tell it's bronze
instead of brass?
Since it's a fake,
then I don't want it.
Let's go.
I heard Qionghua doesn't exist in the Western Regions anymore.
Really?
It's absolutely true.
I just came from there.
Even if there were,
they couldn't survive the long journey now.
You don't still plan to do this business, do you?
Who made our Madam Li
like it?
But then again,
this flower is really weird.
It has no stamens,
no seeds, and no fruits.
Where the seeds come from
remains unknown to this day.
It's something you can only hope for, not seek.
I also heard
the Qionghua in Madam Li's private garden
were all burned down a few days ago.
Yes, what a pity.
In that case,
this might be the last seed in the world.
It must be very expensive.
Sorry, everyone.
I know why you are here tonight,
but tonight,
my goods
will only be sold to these two.
- Why?
Because my goods are unique in the world.
If you still want to do business with me in the future,
you have to follow my rules.
Please. This is outrageous.
Stop!
It's you.
So at the entrance just now,
was that also your way of picking customers?
In Kuizhou, fat is considered precious,
so I insist on defining business by thinness.
Qionghua is unique in the world.
I won't sell it to those
prejudiced
fools.
Come on.
Where's the token?
I want to see your sincerity.
What about yours?
Can I borrow your knife, Sir?
Knife?
I saw that all the merchants just now had knife wounds on their hands.
I guess showing sincerity requires some blood.
I wonder if this counts as passing the first test.
Brilliant.
You are so interesting.
Since you are so sincere,
I'll break
the rule tonight.
It's a pity.
There is only one
Qionghua seed.
Why don't
we play a game of uncovering the veil?
Uncovering the veil?
There is a children's game in the Western Regions called uncovering the veil.
Within the time it takes for a stick of incense to burn,
the one who reveals the other's true face wins.
The winner gets the Qionghua seed.
Wait a minute.
This gentleman is highly skilled,
while I am just a weak woman.
It's not fair to compete like this.
Makes sense.
In that case,
since it's a children's game,
let's play it the children's way.
We won't use martial arts.
Also,
within half an incense stick of time,
if you fail to take off the lady's mask,
the lady wins.
How about it?
Deal.
Alright.
Let's begin.
It's him.
His legs are indeed fine.
The rule of the black market
is to exchange secrets for something of equal value.
Since you could leave your crutch
at home so easily,
why don't you offer me something
to keep my mouth shut?
The black market is full of all sorts of people.
If I call out your name loudly
and let everyone know
that you came to the black market with your legs intact
to get the Qionghua seeds,
guess what Mother will do
tomorrow?
I can spare your life, my lady.
But my lady,
you must protect this secret with your life.
Otherwise...
Thank you, my lady.
The Qionghua seed is mine.