I can't believe a water dungeon exists
in the Young Master's manor.
Such torturous methods,
only Chu Shengyi could come up with them.
These injuries are too severe.
How long will it take to heal?
I used to think he married Qingcheng for money.
But in that private prison,
to save my life,
I tested him with Yanzhi Pavilion.
Yet he wanted to kill me.
Chu Shengyi's purpose for getting Qingcheng
is definitely not simple.
My lady,
maybe we should just leave.
This Young Master's manor
is a dragon's den.
The Third Young Master is treacherous and unpredictable.
I'm just afraid that if you deal with him for too long,
you might lose your life.
The Governor's Mansion is heavily guarded.
Without a summons,
we can't enter Qiwu Courtyard at all.
This is our only chance.
Where is the thing I asked for?
You were right, my lady.
It really was in the black market.
After the former Governor left,
the mansion was burglarized once.
The thieves in our Kuizhou are not stupid.
This map of the Governor's Mansion
is worth much more than ordinary gold and silver.
It's enough.
Qiwu Courtyard is in the southwest corner of the mansion.
And Madam Li
usually holds banquets in the East Flower Hall.
We need to grow the flowers quickly.
So this is the new lowly girl taken in by the Third Young Master.
I heard she's also a flower slave.
The Grand Governor's Mansion has really made a joke of itself this time.
How does a mere flower slave deserve to sit with us?
Watch me make this flower slave embarrass herself at the banquet.
The Third Young Master is here. Keep your voice down.
What's wrong?
The cushion has been soaked in rice water.
Someone, go get a new one.
Why are you helping me?
You haven't told me the truth yet.
Naturally, I won't let anything happen to you.
Madam Li has arrived!
Mother.
Be careful, Mother.
Why is Lady Fang still standing?
Mother, my cushion is wet,
and a new one hasn't been brought yet.
We can't let the new bride stand like this all the time.
I'm fine, I can just sit like this.
This is not a street gathering.
Lady Fang comes from a humble background.
It's understandable she doesn't know the etiquette here.
But since she has entered your manor,
she represents your face in the future.
You need to keep an eye on her at all times.
You are right, Mother.
Look at the Third Young Master.
Let the banquet begin.
Lady Fang has specially presented the hand-planted
Peony Zhaoyebai
to celebrate Madam Li's birthday.
Please extinguish the candles, ladies.
So beautiful! What a gorgeous flower!
I didn't expect this lowly girl to know how to grow flowers.
Mother,
this flower is called Zhaoyebai.
It glows brightly when the moonlight shines on it.
Today, I present this flower to celebrate your birthday,
wishing your blessings shine eternally like the moonlight,
bathing the entire Governor's Mansion in your clear light,
bringing brilliance to the courtyard,
and natural splendor.
They grew so well. So beautiful.
I've never seen anything like it.
So beautiful.
Absolutely gorgeous.
Guards,
light the lamps.
What's wrong, Lady Fang?
Mother, my cold hadn't completely healed before I came.
Now that I've had a few cups of wine,
I feel dizzy
and my vision is blurring.
I'm afraid I might make a fool of myself here.
I'd like to rest in the side hall for a moment.
Momo, go check if Lady Fang is alright.
Yes.
Madam, Lady Fang does have a slight fever.
Then you may be excused.
Thank you, Mother.
Nanny,
prepare a maid's outfit and wait for me in the side hall.
The venom of a certain cactus thorn
can cause a temporary fever.
I'll slip away from the birthday banquet then
and look for you in the side hall.
Based on Qiwu Courtyard's location on the map,
it should be in this direction.
Young Master.
Lady Fang indeed entered Qiwu Courtyard,
but she didn't go to the West Hall.
She went to the private garden.
Report!
Reporting to Madam.
An intruder broke into Qiwu Courtyard's private garden.
The Commander has surrounded them.
I'm here to ask for your permission.
May we enter the garden to catch them?
How dare they break into the Governor's Mansion on my birthday.
I'd like to see who has such audacity.
The intruder's background is unknown.
Please allow me to stay by your side
to protect you, Mother.
Fire!
The private garden is on fire! Put it out!
Hurry, put out the fire!
What happened?
How could such a big fire start out of nowhere?
Reporting to Madam.
I had my men surround the garden.
The thief must be desperate.
They set this fire to escape.
I've ordered all exits to be blocked.
The Qiong flower!
You must not let anything happen to the Qiong flower.
Otherwise,
I'll have the entire Huben Guard buried with it.
Yes, Madam.
I will definitely protect the Qiong flower.
Mother! Mother!
The Qiong flower.
My Qiong flower!
Don't worry, Mother.
I'll go save the flower too.
Young Master.
They're not here.
Head towards Shangmu Courtyard.
Fainted from the heavy smoke.
The thief must still be in the garden.
Search carefully.
Young Master, what should we do? Should we save her?
Since she's not the Young Madam,
cancel the flower bestowal.
Take the Qiong flower away.
Marrying into the mansion as a substitute...
Could it be for this Qiong flower?
I'll go distract them.
Who's there? Stop!
Chase him!
Hold on!
Don't die in this trap.
Please go back, Third Young Master.
Madam has taken her medicine
and is resting now.
Regarding the private garden,
Madam is still deeply troubled,
especially about the Viburnum macrocephalum flowers in the garden.
They were all given by the Commander-in-Chief,
and Madam loved them very much.
It's all my fault.
Please ask Mother to take good care of herself.
This is the bracelet Madam gave you.
Father, I know I was wrong.
That floral amber bracelet
is the only keepsake my mother left me.
I beg you, Father, don't destroy it.
Madam suddenly fell ill,
and the cause is unknown.
The diviner said
only by destroying what the Young Master cherishes most
can the illness be cured.
Young Master, this is filial piety.
The Commander-in-Chief ordered you to copy the Classic of Filial Piety.
Don't you understand?
Mother...
Shengyi.
My mother's bracelet!
My mother's bracelet.
Look what this is.
Why do you have it?
I searched all over the West Market these past two days
and found a similar one.
I secretly swapped them.
Those servants don't know any better.
They only destroyed a fake.
Smart, isn't it?
If she finds out,
she definitely won't let it go easily.
You're hurt.
Don't worry.
My father is the Commander of the Naval Forces,
and I am the daughter of a great general.
This little scratch is nothing.
Xin'er.
I don't have a mother anymore,
and now I don't even have a father.
Your father is out fighting wars.
Even though you're a hostage in the Commander-in-Chief's mansion,
you always protect me.
From now on,
you are my, Chu Shengyi's, only family.
If Madam Li ever makes things difficult for you in the future,
I will protect you even if it costs me my life.
Okay.
We are family for life.
A traveling merchant from the Western Regions
is bringing Viburnum macrocephalum seeds to the black market.
This merchant has just arrived in Kuizhou.
It's an extremely rare opportunity.
Madam ordered that
since the black market is not bound by Kuizhou's laws
and officials cannot easily intervene,
the Third Young Master must go and get them personally this time.
If the Third Young Master fails to bring back those seeds,
it won't just be this bracelet that shatters.
I
will obey.