When we were kids,
we met each other once.
Hurry up!
Hi, do you want to play with us?
Let's go on that one!
Okay.
That was so much fun!
Go away!
Zhang Junjia!
Time to come home for dinner!
Coming!
Aren't you going home?
Where are your mom and dad?
It wasn't an accident.
Instead, it felt more like fate.
Like the ninth fret of a guitar,
where a name hidden deep
in your heart lies—
once it sounds,
it can never be denied.
I found you.
[Smile After Tears]
[Fret 9: The Luck of Being Needed by You]
Give me the bag.
It's all wet.
Wait a moment.
Dry yourself off first,
or you'll catch a cold.
I can do it myself.
Just wait one more second.
I've put a clean towel
and some fresh clothes
in the bathroom for you.
Go take a shower first,
or you'll catch a cold.
Come on.
Come, have a seat.
I can do it myself.
I made you a cup of ginger tea.
Drink it before bed. It'll keep you warm.
Thank you.
Do you
live here by yourself?
My parents both work out of town,
so just make yourself at home.
I'm going to tidy up the room.
Wait a moment.
Well...
I've tidied up the room.
I'm going to take a shower.
Good night.
Dinner's ready!
So both your parents
work away from home?
Do you live with your grandma, then?
That's great.
Since you live nearby,
Junjia will have someone
to play with from now on.
Hey, little guy,
what's your name?
Everyone calls me Panda.
Panda?
That's adorable.
Hang on a second.
Here, have some vegetables.
Come on, eat a little more.
I have a panda too.
This is for you.
Really?
From now on, we're friends.
Morning.
Did you
make all of these?
After my grandma passed away,
I've been living by myself.
I make my own meals every day.
Eat while it's hot.
Go on, eat.
It's so good!
This is really good too.
I'm actually a pretty good cook.
From now on,
if there's anything you want to eat,
I'll make it for you.
Really?
Then I want
a lobster feast!
Well...
That might be a little difficult.
Here. I'm returning this to you.
I found it for you.
But
it seems to be broken.
I'm sorry.
It can't be put back the way it was.
Just like you said,
it can never be the way it was.
But
thank you anyway.
Junjia,
can you
promise me something?
What is it?
Don't say "thank you" to me anymore.
Because I don't do these things
for anything else—
as long as you're happy,
that's enough for me.
I know.
As for
what's bothering you,
you can tell me
whenever you feel like it.
So
stay
as long as you want.
Eat up.
[I'll be staying at a classmate's place
for a few days.]
Your parents passed away too.
They left you in my care.
Do you think I'm not tired?
Do you think I don't want to let go?
[I'll be staying at a classmate's place
for a few days.]
[Why bother someone else?]
Who's the one
checking in on you, then?
A friend.
Go away.
Are you sure?
I saw someone following you
when you came to work the other day.
I think you should go
get a blessing or something
—cleanse your aura.
Xingtian Temple.
Xingtian Temple is a good choice.
You're overthinking it.
Go wash the rags.
Did you secretly come to watch me at work?
[Tea eggs – 9 NT each.]
Who would be so bored
as to do something like that?
Towel.
Do you want me to grab a towel for you?
You were really clueless yesterday.
How could you forget I was home?
Don't even bring it up.
It's embarrassing.
[Jiasheng Memorial Building]
Smells so good.
Do you need help?
No need.
Just sit here and wait for me.
Here it comes.
The last dish—
stir-fried loofah with clams.
♪ I wanna hide away in the last century ♪
♪ And just let my mind drift for a while ♪
♪ Whatever's happening out there ♪
♪ I don't even want to guess ♪
♪ When I'm tired,
I'll pretend I've forgotten ♪
♪ And throw all my worries into the sea ♪
♪ I don't have superpowers ♪
♪ Even my strength runs out ♪
♪ When I'm tired,
I'll pretend I've forgotten ♪
♪ And throw all my worries ♪
[Learning Knows No Bounds.
Education Is for All.]
I've got an interschool
tournament next week.
Will you come and watch?
Of course.
Junjia!
What are you doing?
No, no.
Don't tear that down!
Get back to class!
Sir,
could you ask the school
No!
not to take it down just yet?
Those are the principal's orders.
Go back to class!
Hey!
Don't tear it down!
Junjia!
You may still have some bruising here.
It'd be best to get it checked out
at the hospital,
okay?
Okay.
Done.
Thank you, miss.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have gotten hurt.
It's nothing.
I get strains and sprained ankles
all the time
when I play basketball.
Besides,
the important thing
is that you didn't get hurt.
[School Infirmary]
That's mine.
You're injured, aren't you?
I'll carry it.
Okay.
Are you sure you don't want me
to go to the hospital with you?
No need.
Don't you have work?
But...
Are you sure you'll be okay
going by yourself?
Really, I'll be fine.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
If you're still worried,
I can send you a picture.
Then when you get off work,
we can go home together.
But...
Alright.
You're going to be late.
Go to work.
[Dalang: Korean Skewers,
Fried Chicken, Drinks]
This is my secret base.
Secret base?
[Dalang: Korean Skewers,
Fried Chicken, Drinks]
I'm leaving now.
Bye.
Why are you here?
I told you
I'd wait for you to get off work.
Is it
that serious?
The doctor said
I just need to keep it immobile for now.
A few days of rest and I'll be fine.
But
you're on the basketball team.
You still want to play
for the national team.
-How can you say...
-It's fine.
It's just a minor injury.
It's wrapped up like that,
and you're still calling it
a minor injury?
[Dalang: Korean Skewers,
Fried Chicken, Drinks]
I'll do it.
For the next few days,
you have to listen to me.
No pushing yourself.
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
I'm just injured,
not disabled.
If you're injured,
you need to take good care of yourself.
Where are you going?
I'm going to bring in the laundry.
I'll do it.
Go sit down.
You really don't have to do this.
Sit.
I won't take it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take a shower.
Are you okay?
What's up?
I'm fine.
[Basketball Tournament]
I'm sorry.
I caused you so much trouble.
You say
I'm always thanking you,
but you're no different.
You're always apologizing to me.
But I'm really sorry.
If I hadn't fallen just now,
I would...
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have gotten hurt.
I really don't want
anyone else
to get hurt because of me again.
I know.
You're afraid of troubling others,
and you're afraid of
becoming a burden to them.
So you carry everything by yourself.
But to me,
being someone you need
is something I'm lucky to be.
Is that
so?
Yeah.
You've already done very well.
Really?
I couldn't even protect
He's secret place.
How can I say I did a great job?
If you
really miss him,
then let yourself think about him.
Don't rush to forget him.
You're so good to me.
Panda.
What's your name?
Everyone calls me Panda.
I'll go tidy up the room.
Wait for me a moment.
You found out?
Do you remember this?
Of course.
Didn't I give this to you?
I didn't expect you to keep it until now.
This is for you.
Back then,
when I heard you were moving away,
I chased after the car
holding the panda doll
for such a long, long time.
And I cried for such a long, long time.
I'm sorry.
Something happened at home back then,
and my aunt suddenly decided
we were moving.
We didn't even have time
to say goodbye.
I never blamed you.
Actually,
I was already really happy
when I got to see you again
after school started.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Junjia.
So you recognized me back then?
Then why didn't you tell me?
We were still kids back then.
I was afraid I was the only one
who remembered
and that would've been embarrassing.
No way.
Besides, I remember you used to
cry all the time.
You were so chubby back then.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
I really want to finish He's song.
It's just that
the more I sing this song,
the more it feels wrong.
Excuse me,
have you seen Zheng Diaoqin?
He went to the hospital
for a follow-up today.
Junjia!