[ Watch on kissasia.li ]
[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 30]
Grandfather.
Is the Governor
going to shoot down
the Zheng family's Raven Legion?
No blood can be shed
on the ceremonial review's grounds.
This is the rule.
As long as Zheng Tao
dares to release his ravens,
we will shoot
every single one of them down.
Absolutely not.
Even if we can
shoot down all those ravens,
no blood can be shed
on the ceremonial review's grounds.
Moreover, if we killed the ravens
and the Zheng family
held it against us,
wouldn't we be penny wise
and pound foolish?
Fan Yun is right.
If we shot down
the ravens of Zheng's Army,
the consequences would be disastrous.
We saw those ravens
seemed to be trained
to only attack Qi's Army.
Why don't we have
Qi's Army change their uniforms?
That's even worse.
The uniforms of Qi's Army
represent the face of the Qi family.
If we win by changing uniforms,
it would be an unfair victory.
Actually,
I do have an idea
that we could try.
What idea do you have, Lady Fan Yun?
Your Excellency, do you still remember
that night in Yong City?
I keep my word.
How could I forget
what I promised Mayor Zheng?
Today, I witnessed
the Governor's great vision.
It's a worthwhile trip.
The Governor is wise and brilliant.
In this competition,
I, Zheng, accept my defeat.
Today also let me witness
the extraordinary strength
of Zheng's Army.
With such an army
stationed in Jing City,
how could I not feel reassured?
Thank you for your trust, Your Excellency.
Get out of the way!
Wei Ying!
How are Commander Wei's injuries?
Three arrows.
Each one was shot
from an extremely tricky angle,
all aimed at Commander Wei's vitals.
His life isn't in danger, right?
I certainly hope not.
I'm just afraid
someone else doesn't think the same way.
Your Excellency,
do you think I did this?
The three arrows all came from Jing City.
How do you explain that?
Could it be that you performed poorly
in the review,
and you're dissatisfied,
so you did this foolish act
in a fit of anger?
Zheng's Army
has strict discipline
and is well-trained.
Would we publicly retaliate
just because our formation was broken?
If this excuse spread,
wouldn't it be ridiculous?
Mayor Zheng,
even if your rhetoric
can convince me now,
I'm afraid it won't convince others.
Who else?
Me!
The wound is half an inch from the heart.
If my brother hadn't dodged in time,
that arrow
would have taken his life.
How exactly does your Zheng family
train your soldiers?
They are just a disorganized mess.
Not only do they have clumsy formations,
but they also have poor character.
A bunch of sore losers,
they aren't even as well-trained
as the Wei family's livestock.
Miss Wei,
don't get agitated.
Let's talk calmly.
That's my own brother.
How can I not be agitated?
This matter
has not been fully investigated yet.
Do not make false accusations.
Grandfather,
the military camp has done a count.
Three arrows are indeed missing.
Speak louder. I can't hear you.
Tell me,
what should we do?
There must be
something suspicious about this.
Miss Wei.
Give me some time.
Let me find out the truth.
Give you time?
So you can escape back to Jing City?
The members of the Zheng family
never deny our actions or shirk our debts.
Fine.
Then I will write a letter right now.
Dear Father,
my brother
was severely injured while sparring
with Zheng's Army.
His life is in imminent danger.
Mayor Zheng says
it was absolutely not their doing.
We'll give him some time
to find a scapegoat.
Miss Wei,
why are you so stubborn
and won't listen to reason?
If there's no explanation
for today's matter,
you'll be the ones
not listening to reason.
From now on,
don't even think about buying
another bag of salt from the Wei family.
I can't reason with a girl like you.
You don't call the shots
in the Wei family.
Wait until Commander Wei wakes up.
Then we'll talk.
Grandfather,
Miss Wei is deeply favored
by the Master of the Wei family.
She might actually call the shots.
Besides, the Wei family
controls the entire salt vein.
Falling out at this time
might be detrimental to Jing City,
so we'd better not push the Wei family
to become our enemy.
Miss Wei.
In your opinion,
how should this matter be resolved?
As for me,
I am very fair.
An eye for an eye,
three arrows for three arrows.
Even so,
the injuries sustained by Commander Wei
will not be lessened in the slightest.
How about we bring Zheng's Army
to Gao City to do hard labor?
You are taking advantage
of their precarious position.
And you show no respect for Zheng's Army.
Since you say no to everything,
then you make the decision for us.
How about this?
Zheng's Army is weak on the inside
and is easily defeated.
This shows that the commanding officers
are incompetent and fail to do their jobs.
Why not leave Zheng's Army
in Ling'an for a while,
so that Qi's Army can teach them a lesson?
What do you think, Mayor Zheng?
Sure.
It's settled then.
The Zheng family's things.
Look at you.
You almost ruined everything.
Well,
I was nervous.
Besides,
you were standing right there.
What if I missed?
You have the nerve to say that?
If I hadn't thrown myself at it,
you would have missed.
Move!
So you guys planned this all along?
Everyone knew about it,
except me?
It's not that we didn't want to tell you,
but we were afraid that if you knew,
you wouldn't have acted convincingly.
Look at you just now.
You were so imposing.
Weren't you afraid
I'd get mad and attack them?
We believe in you.
Although you look
very impulsive on the outside,
overall,
you're reasonable
and know what's important.
So the main credit today
still goes to
our Miss Wei.
Isn't that right, Gao Ran?
Yes.
Miss Wei played a crucial role
in making Zheng Tao suffer in silence.
Really?
Yeah, I told you.
Leaving such a small thing to me
is no problem at all.
Anyway,
my anxious heart
can finally settle down.
Next, about the gate commander,
we won't be led by the nose anymore.
I don't understand.
What does this have to do
with the gate commander?
Ignoring Zheng Tao at first
and making Zheng's Army suffer
not only broke their spirit,
but also gave us bargaining chips.
When they became unsettled,
we proposed a ceremonial review.
It seemed like we gave
the Zheng family a way out,
but actually, they fell into our trap.
I thought trapping them
and making them have a review
was to show the governor's power
and show them who's the boss
of the Nine Cities.
That was just
a show of strength at the beginning.
So,
letting them review was just a feint.
Making Zheng Tao suffer in silence
was the real move.
Actually, the governor wanted
to keep their people
and soldiers from the start.
This way,
Jing City not only lost its leader,
but also lost 20,000 elite soldiers.
If I were Zheng Tao, I'd want to die.
Your Excellency, you are ruthless.
Next, about the gate commander...
Our main goal
is to crush Zheng Tao's ambition
to secede.
As for the younger generation
of the Zheng family,
we will divide and conquer them,
defeating them one by one.
Then,
regarding the candidate
for Jing City's gate commander,
Your Excellency,
what are your plans?
Well...
Let me think about it.
Playing dumb and advancing step by step,
luring us into a trap,
they checkmated us,
leaving us with nothing to say.
This time, I have truly lost
both face and substance.
Is this the same person
as the rumored Governor?
Fighting without breaking bonds,
he really got some of
Eldest Brother's true teachings.
He didn't dare to completely fall out
for fear of forcing
the Zheng family to rebel,
causing turmoil in the world.
Eldest Brother
was convicted of treason,
losing all righteousness.
It is not suitable for us
to also turn against him.
If we offend again,
it is equal to making enemies
of the other eight cities.
This time
wasn't completely fruitless.
At least we figured out
Qi Zheng's background.
Ling'an's strength
is also not to be underestimated.
What a pity.
The offense and defense have switched.
We missed a good opportunity.
Well,
Grandfather,
about the gate commander...
First thing tomorrow morning,
I will go to the mansion again.
But
we don't have a large army
to rely on right now.
As long as the Zheng family is here,
even without an army,
Qi Zheng still has to call me Mayor Zheng.
Liu Mu died unexpectedly,
leaving the position of Jing City's
gate commander vacant.
I intend to appoint a new gate commander
to govern Jing City for me.
My beloved subjects,
who is willing to go?
-I'm willing.
Tian Xing?
Good.
In my opinion,
you are both excellent candidates
for Jing City's gate commander position.
Today, I plan
to break with convention.
and have the two of you
serve jointly as the gate commander
to govern Jing City for me.
-Yes.
Your Excellency,
two people jointly serving
as the gate commander
is unheard of
and unprecedented.
This is
against the rules.
The previous commoner selection exam
was also unprecedented.
But didn't the facts prove
that it is not only feasible,
but absolutely necessary?
Extraordinary times
call for extraordinary measures.
My mind is made up.
Fan Yun, Tian Xing,
step forward to receive your appointments.
This is the official seal
of the gate commander.
You two will supervise each other
and exercise power together.
In other words,
only together are you
the gate commander of Jing City.
Understand?
-Yes.
Summon Gao Ran for an audience.
Greetings, Your Excellency.
Gao Ran, I appoint you
as the exclusive military officer
for Fan and Tian.
Your mission is to accompany them
to Jing City
and protect their safety.
Can you do that?
Rest assured, Your Excellency.
These twin swords
are named Ganjiang and Moye.
They were given to Second Brother Qingyuan
by the late governor.
They were forged from the same ore.
Back then, Qingyuan gave Moye
to me.
The other sword, Ganjiang,
has been kept in the mansion
all these years.
Today, I plan
to bestow Ganjiang upon you.
Holding this sword
is like having me there in person.
I will strictly obey
the Governor's orders.
[Taiji Palace]
Great.
You've stolen the spotlight again.
But Jing City is not like Yong City.
If you want to be
the gate commander there,
you'd better improve
your self-defense skills.
Don't worry, Bo.
We will definitely stay safe.
Who cares about you?
Let's go.
Fan Yun,
stay here a moment.
I have a few words for you.
I'll take my leave then.
Your Excellency,
what are your orders?
Congratulations.
You finally got what you wanted.
Thank you, Your Excellency.
I didn't expect
you to come up with
the dual gate commander strategy.
This way,
it not only divides power,
but also puts pressure on those
who want to win over the gate commander
and undermine the Qi family.
Of course.
I've already agreed to
the things you asked me to do.
Then shouldn't you
do something for me too?
Tell me.
I sent you to be
the gate commander of Jing City
because
the situation there is unclear.
I have no one else to use,
so I had no choice
but to send you two
to change the situation.
However, this is not a long-term plan.
Jing City will be stable one day.
At that time, shouldn't you...
Shouldn't you reconsider...
Reconsider...
Reconsider what?
Reconsider the marriage.
What did you say?
Shouldn't you
reconsider the marriage?
This...
Why are you bringing
this up again?
Besides,
that didn't really count as
being married.
I know.
I don't mean to force you.
I just want to say
that you want the people to live in peace
before you start a family.
But in my heart,
I actually just want an answer.
What do you think
about me?
I...
I actually... actually...
You what?
Actually, I haven't...
I still...
Haven't thought it through, right?
Fan Yun,
you really care for the world
and the Nine Cities.
I just think
it's too early to talk about this.
Think about it.
The selection exam trial has just begun.
Besides,
I have to go be the gate commander.
Then after your term
as gate commander ends
and Jing City is stabilized,
could you reconsider
your marriage?
If
everything in Jing City is settled
and everything is on the right track,
then...
Then maybe
when I have free time,
I will...
You sure have a lot of demands.
What?
I can't?
You can.
You should.
Then I'll wait for you to come back.
Raise your hands.
Straighten your back.
Hold on a little longer.
Gao Ran,
learning martial arts isn't something
that happens overnight.
No need to rush.
Fan Yun,
if you're tired, get up and take a break.
No.
She just started.
How can she rest already?
Squat properly.
You don't have to start with the basics.
Just learn some self-defense skills
and that's it.
Come, get up. I'll teach you.
It's okay. I...
If you don't master the basics,
what's the use of learning a few tricks?
With me here,
who dares to bully her?
Fan Yun is going to Jing City.
Are you going?
I...
All right, all right,
Both of you, stop arguing.
I just wanted Gao Ran
to teach me a few moves for self-defense.
Your Excellency,
why did you suddenly come here?
Me?
I'm here for a reason, of course.
What reason?
I have something to discuss with Gao Ran.
You take a break first.
You're looking for Gao Ran?
Alright, you guys talk.
I'll go back and get some rest.
Take your time.
-Drink more water.
-Okay.
Your Excellency.
Gao Ran.
Don't you think that
if Fan Yun goes to Jing City alone,
it won't be smooth sailing?
Your Excellency, please speak your mind.
I want to go with Fan Yun.
You are going to Jing City?
How can that do?
The city cannot be
without its governor for a day.
I have made up my mind.
You will act as the governor.
Why are you saying this again?
I won't do
such a treasonous thing,
I am asking you to do it.
How can it be treasonous?
Besides, it's only temporary.
When I come back,
you will naturally return
the position to me.
Don't worry.
All the consequences
will be my responsibility.
No, this won't work.
Even if I agree,
the ministers won't.
As long as you agree,
I have my ways.
Trust me, okay?
Lord Jiang's masks
truly live up to their reputation.
I dare say the masks
in the Nine Cities
are all here.
Lord Jiang,
don't you feel stuffy
when wearing these masks?
When you wear a mask for a long time,
it becomes like clothing.
I'm more uncomfortable not wearing it.
Your Excellency,
you didn't come here
just to admire these masks, right?
Lord Jiang.
Give me some ideas.
Do you have any good methods?
I advise you
to give up these unrealistic thoughts.
I definitely have
a compelling reason to do this.
Why won't you help me?
Why are you like this?
Never mind.
Since you won't help me,
I can only find another way.
I'm leaving.
The past kings were indeed wise.
They must have anticipated that one day,
there would be a governor in power
that was full of wild thoughts.
That's why they created
the Sacred Rites Bureau.
I knew you cared about me.
Thanks for the reminder.
Teacher Ping, what did you say this was?
Some gold, silver, iron,
and bronze headband?
This item is called
the Silver-Threaded Gold-Edged
Eight-Treasure Headband.
[Manager of Sacred Rites Bureau,
Ping Ruying]
The name sounds impressive,
but its appearance is too ordinary.
How can you talk to
Teacher Ping like that?
You call this ordinary?
It's practically an eyesore.
Teacher Ping, are you joking?
Just relying on this thing
can let Gao Ran and me swap identities?
This item is imbued with a spell
that can confuse the mind
and deceive the eyes.
If you put it on,
in the eyes of others,
you will take on each other's appearance.
Moreover,
it won't interfere with each other.
In other words,
if one person takes it off,
it won't affect the other's appearance.
Yes.
What if someone else wears it?
This item is exclusively for you two.
If anyone else puts it on,
it will just turn into a hideous,
ordinary headband.
Is it really that magical?
You can try it on and see,
Your Excellency.
This is too scary.
Gao... Gao Ran, you...
You've turned into me.
Th-This is amazing.
Teacher Ping,
this is indeed a great treasure.
This is exactly what I wanted.
Shi.
Grandfather?
Sit.
Grandfather,
you're back?
I was worried,
so I came to see you.
I've been watching you
for a long time.
I'll leave after taking a look.
I know what you care about.
Don't worry,
I will definitely achieve it for you.
Then what about
the things you deeply desired?
♪ I could have ♪
♪ Played every trick in the book ♪
♪ But I chose painstaking devotion ♪
I don't want it anymore.
♪ Never caging my love ♪
♪ Even if I had to
trudge through a thousand miles ♪
I don't want them anymore.
♪ Henceforth, I shall wander the world,
plucking petals and holding the moon ♪
♪ Listen to the wind and admire the moon
for days on end ♪
Where are you going?
♪ Accept that I'm not your happiness ♪
♪ Let go of what's before me ♪
♪ Consider this the best ending ♪
Grandfather, don't go.
♪ I disdain everything
in the vast universe ♪
♪ So why do I care for
a single glance from you? ♪
Grandfather, don't go!
♪ Drinking a pot of the past ♪
Grandfather!
♪ I toast to my withering self
as the curtains fall ♪
♪ And you don't know the reason why ♪
My grandson, Shi,
just go
and live the free life
you want.
♪ Let go of what's before me ♪
♪ Consider this the best ending ♪
♪ I disdain everything
in the vast universe ♪
Let me
♪ So why do I care for
a single glance from you? ♪
bear those responsibilities
♪ Drinking a pot of the past ♪
♪ I toast to my withering self
as the curtains fall ♪
alone.
♪ And you don't know the reason why ♪
I prepared this meal today
to say goodbye to you.
Say goodbye?
Second Young Master Zheng,
where are you going?
I need to take my grandfather's ashes
back to Jing City for burial
as soon as possible.
From now on,
I have no relatives left in Ling'an,
so I have no reason to stay.
I don't know
when we will see each other again.
You're talking as if
we are parting forever.
Why don't you come with me to Jing City?
Sure.
Then see you in Jing City.
Then,
I...
I'll go prepare a nice carriage.
Second Young Master Zheng,
actually, the governor
appointed me as the gate commander
of Jing City.
This time,
I'll be going with the main force.
Being the gate commander of Jing City
is very dangerous.
But since you've decided,
I will do my best
to help you be a good gate commander.
Help me?
Zheng Tao
brought an army this time
to help Zheng Xian
get the position of gate commander,
but he returned disappointed.
As a member of the Zheng family,
are you sure you want to help me,
an outsider?
If someone else
were to be the gate commander,
I would naturally object.
But if it's you,
that's a different story.
Why?
You be the gate commander of Jing City,
and I'll be the Master
of the Zheng family.
Is there a better arrangement than this?
You want to be the Master?
Why not?