[The Legend of Rosy Clouds]
[Episode 32]
After treatment,
His Excellency's basically
out of danger now.
The sedative I just gave him
will help him rest,
and the rash will gradually fade as well.
But I'm afraid
you'll have to put in some extra effort
tonight.
Lord Jiang, you mean...
This allergic reaction may cause
skin itching.
You'll need to keep a close eye on him
and make sure he doesn't scratch it,
or it could lead to
sores and infection.
I have to stay up and keep watch again?
Yes, preferably.
-Lord Jiang.
Come here. Come here.
Lord Jiang.
Did you tell her?
I did.
I've instructed Miss Wei
to keep a close eye on His Excellency.
Shisan.
I've done all I can for you.
The rest
is up to you to figure out.
Is this really a good idea?
If Miss Wei
finds out that His Excellency
is actually Gao Ran,
the consequences would be disastrous.
And
if Zheng Tao caught
even the slightest hint of it,
we'd be in trouble.
It's not as serious as
you're making it out to be.
Shisan
can be a bit free-spirited,
but she knows
how to see the bigger picture.
As long as we explain things clearly
to her,
she'll cooperate better than anyone else.
You can't hide the look in your eyes
when you like someone.
Is that so?
How do you know?
I...
When Fan Yun was here,
you enjoyed eating pomelos.
How come the pomelo I gave you
ended up making you suffer so much?
The thing is, when Gao Ran left,
I promised him
I'd take good care of you.
But now look at what I've done.
Gao Ran should have arrived in Jing City
by now, right?
The same moon shines on us even though
we're thousands of miles apart.
Make sure to take good care of yourself
and don't catch a cold.
Heaven help me—
if there's a chance,
could you let me see Gao Ran
one more time?
Just once is all I ask.
Don't touch my headband.
Don't touch me.
You...
No scratching.
Stop scratching. Stop it.
I want water. I want water.
Okay, I'll get it for you now.
Don't worry,
I'll take good care of you here all night.
Tell me if you need anything.
But you can't scratch anymore.
Don't touch my headband.
Impressive.
How did he do that?
Bravo!
I want 4.
Sure. Four for you guys.
Here, hold this first.
What's wrong, Tian Xing?
Our money's gone.
The money's gone?
Where are they?
Sir,
where are those street performers
from earlier?
They left a while ago.
They left in such a hurry
that they didn't even collect the tips.
Those people...
Oh no.
The official seal is gone.
-What?
[Jing City]
What are the Zheng family members
up to these days?
They're probably busy
preparing for the clan leader election.
Jin looks like
he's determined to win this time,
so I suppose he's already planning
the celebration banquet.
The new clan leader will be selected
from the younger generation.
Don't you want to be the clan leader?
Me?
I don't think it's my turn yet.
Jin has always been favored
by Grandfather,
and in recent years,
he's been the one managing Jing City.
I...
But
Shi, I think you could give it a shot.
You might actually have a chance.
So what do you want to do?
It's a bit embarrassing to say,
but actually,
I'd like to learn more from
Lady Fan Yun and the others.
You want to become an official?
But I'm not particularly gifted,
so I never had the courage
to sit for the selection exams.
This time, I finally worked up
the courage to try,
but then the selection exam
was reformed,
and Grandfather just decided
not to let me participate.
Good things never come easy.
Once I become the clan leader,
no one will be able to stand in your way.
The official seal and money are gone,
and there's no way to recover them
for now.
But
let's not lose heart.
We'll figure something out.
Don't you agree, Fan Yun?
Actually,
this is what
the Governor often tells me as well.
What about you?
It must've been the Governor
who taught you this too, right?
To keep a level head
and stay optimistic.
Isn't that right, Gao Ran?
Yes, I learned that from the Governor.
After all,
keeping a gloomy face
won't solve anything.
Your mindset shapes
the world you experience.
So that's how it is.
Then I have a question for you.
Why is it
that you learned nothing of
Gao Ran's temperament and true character,
Your Excellency?
Cut it out. How much longer
are you planning to keep up this act,
Governor?
Zheng Xi.
Look who's here.
[Zheng Xi, Daughter of the Zheng family]
Zheng Xi.
Shi finally came home.
Say something.
Shi, I...
It's okay.
Don't force her.
She's all grown up now,
yet she's still just as quiet as ever.
By the way,
this
is a hairpin I brought
especially for you from Ling'an.
Have a look.
Do you like it?
You still dote on Zheng Xi
just like you always have.
With an older brother like you,
I'm afraid she'll have a hard time
finding a husband in the future.
Zheng Xi is actually great at
managing the household.
Over the years,
she's been the one
handling all the household affairs.
So,
Shi, if you need anything,
just go straight to her.
I do need your help right now.
Tidy up a few rooms for me.
We'll be having guests over.
You'd already thought of that?
I told you.
She's a real expert
at managing the household.
Alright,
tell me everything.
How did you find out who I really was?
It was pretty obvious.
Everyone should have figured it out.
I...
Besides,
the way you conduct yourself
and handle things
is completely opposite to Gao Ran's.
I should have noticed it much earlier.
I really couldn't hide it from you.
In that case,
the one in the Qi Residence...
Of course it's Gao Ran.
But don't worry.
Gao Ran is your brother
and the person I trust the most.
We trained together for a long time,
and we are of one mind.
There won't be any problem.
Alright.
Although I don't know
exactly how you managed to
switch identities with Gao Ran,
since you are traveling
under Gao Ran's identity,
from now on,
you'll have to do everything I say.
Of course.
In Jing City, you're the gate commander,
and I'm your guard.
I'll naturally do as you say.
Alright?
[Jing City]
Come here for a check.
Pass. Pass.
Next.
Sir.
Why are the guards at the city gate
not wearing official uniforms?
They're the Zheng family's guards,
not official guards.
The Zheng family's guards
even have jurisdiction over this?
They can get involved if they want to.
During the clan leader election,
outsiders aren't allowed to enter the city
on their own,
unless
they have documents
proving their identity.
See? I need an official document
just to go home.
Can you believe that?
What's your business here?
Let go of me!
Seeing is believing.
The Jing City
has truly become
the Zheng family's domain.
Turn around.
We won't enter the city for now.
Grandfather.
We're finally home.
Granduncle worked so diligently
to serve the Nine Cities
for so many years.
Who would've thought
he'd end up like this?
The Zheng family is still here.
And I'm still here.
I won't let Grandfather down.
Why didn't you tell me
you were coming back to Jing City, Shi?
Don't you have any regard for me,
the future clan leader
of the Zheng family?
The future clan leader?
Jin, you really are determined
to get that position.
In all of Jing City,
who dares to compete with me
for what I want?
If there's nothing else, Jin,
I'll head back to my room.
You only managed to secure a place
in the Zheng family
because you had Granduncle backing you.
Now that Granduncle has passed away,
your support has crumbled.
I advise you to see things clearly
and start showing some respect
for the rules you're supposed to follow.
This place
truly hasn't improved one bit—
neither the place itself nor the people.
Ma'am.
Can I help you?
My lady and I are passing by
and would like to stay here for the night.
Would that be possible?
Sure, sure.
Thank you.
Come in.
Come on in!
Come on.
Let's go.
♪ Wind sheds rain like tears ♪
♪ Over the whole town ♪
♪ At the second our gazes meet ♪
♪ Past memories roar one louder beat ♪
Gao Ran?
I'm not him.
Oh heavens.
Could it be that I've been
thinking about him day and night
that I actually saw Gao Ran?
No way.
W-Was that a dream?
Gao Ran?
You must have been dreaming.
No, I wasn't.
I saw your face.
Then turn around and let me see.
How inappropriate!
Y-Your Excellency.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Maybe I...
I-I was too desperate just now
and saw it wrong.
You may leave.
No. I still have to take care of you.
Not necessary.
T-Then I'll leave.
Why are you still up?
Aren't you the same?
After sleeping out in the open
all these days,
now that I suddenly
have a bed to sleep on,
I actually can't fall asleep.
It's more like you're worried about
not being able to enter Jing City, right?
Don't worry.
I believe Heaven will bless us.
Here.
Qi Zheng.
Actually,
I'm quite glad
that you
came along this time.
It's nothing.
I'm now your and Tian Xing's
personal military officer,
so of course I'll be following you.
Actually, ever since I became an official,
I've always been prepared to go
wherever I was assigned
on my own.
I never thought
there would be someone
who'd always stay by my side.
Not even Gao Ran,
because
he has
his own life too.
So, are you trying to thank me?
Making me a cup of tea will do.
[Sweet Dew Tea]
I...
Forget it if you don't want to.
I do.
What did you say?
I...
I said I do.
♪ Watch how many flowers
bloom and wither ♪
♪ Count how many springs
and autumns pass ♪
♪ Why the sighs and regrets? ♪
♪ Lovers wait a lifetime ♪
♪ Feelings that can't be severed ♪
♪ How to let go? ♪
What,
do you not want to drink it now?
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
Come closer.
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
Closer.
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
What?
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
Do you
want me to feed you or something?
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix flower bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
♪ All our fates were long inscribed ♪
♪ How to set free grief and joy? ♪
♪ Mortal life is but an ephemeral dream ♪
♪ No mortal soul may rule its life ♪
♪ If women are akin to blossoms ♪
♪ Can they be cherished tenderly? ♪
Is this tea
♪ For whom do they hide tears silently? ♪
good?
♪ How could one bear to lay blame? ♪
♪ Time runs wild with reckless haste ♪
♪ Never mind that
fate dyes pureness crimson red ♪
♪ For whom does ♪
♪ This phoenix flower bloom? ♪
♪ Love fills my years,
and my heart remains true ♪
♪ Let all worldly longing fade away ♪
♪ Fall deep within a single dream ♪
♪ Wait till a breath of wind arrives ♪
Make sure to eat your fill.
-Thank you.
-I'll get more for you.
Good morning.
Morning.
Ma'am, let us help you.
No need.
Make sure you eat your fill.
-Ma'am.
-Thank you, Ma'am.
There's a strong scent of books
in this house.
Is there a scholar living here?
My eldest son
loves to read.
You see, he finally got the chance
he'd been waiting for
after the selection exams were reformed,
so he went to Ling'an to take the exam.
Although he didn't rank among the top,
he did fairly well
and
was appointed to
some minor official position
or something.
It really is
a great blessing for our family.
It seems the governor of the Nine Cities
is truly wise and capable.
This selection exam reform policy
has truly benefited
people across the land.
Indeed.
Then Ma'am,
now that your son has become an official,
why didn't you
go to Ling'an with him?
It's because of my youngest son.
He never gives me a moment's peace.
He's a bit scatterbrained.
Whenever he sees
something fun, he wants to learn it.
Now
he's taken a liking to magic tricks
and spends all day hanging around
with that troupe of performers.
Look,
he still hasn't come home yet.
Magic tricks?
Ma'am,
may I ask where the magic trick troupe is?
It's quite close.
Not far from here.
The people in that troupe
are no good.
They often use their magic tricks
as a cover for petty theft.
I told my son not to go there anymore,
but he wouldn't listen.
So, Ma'am,
what's your son's name?
Zhou Dangfan.
Zhou Dangfan?
That's enough about hhim.
I'll go get you more dishes.
It seems we searched high and low,
only to find it right in front of us.
Those who stole from us
should be right there.
I'll go retrieve them now.
I'll go with you.
You all stay here.
More people will only
make things complicated.
I'll be back in no time.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
[Liu Mu, Gate Commander of Jing City]
Waiter.
Bring me another steamer of buns.
Coming right up.
Here are your buns.
Take your time, Sir.
Sir,
you certainly have quite an appetite.
You've polished off 6 steamers of buns
in a blink of an eye.
Waiter, check please.
Coming.
It's so delicious. Why aren't you eating?
How could I bring myself to eat this?
I've had enough of these cheap joints.
Let's not come to places
like this anymore.
We'll go to a fancy restaurant
next time and see
what the food there tastes like.
A fancy restaurant?
Do you even have the money for that?
You have no idea.
Our Boss got his hands on
a treasure today.
From now on, Jing City
will belong to our Boss.
When that happens,
we'll be able to eat at
whichever restaurant we want
in Jing City.
Really?
What treasure?
The...
The gate commander's official seal.
By then, we'll present this official seal
to the Zheng family.
Surely they'll reward us with
plenty of gold and silver.
Who would still bother
eating these lousy buns then?
Waiter!
Bring the check.
Coming.
Did you enjoy your meal, gentlemen?
Keep the change.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Please take care.
Take care. Come again.
Where did this guy go?
He hasn't paid for the buns!
He ate that much.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
He ate 7 steamers of buns!
Congratulations, Boss.
Today's haul
was incredibly rewarding.
Here, Boss, a toast to you.
Come on, Boss.
I told you,
as long as you stick with me
and work hard,
I'll make sure you live high on the hog.
-Come on, cheers.
Come, bottoms up.
Zhou Dangfan!
Serve the dishes already!
Where's my roast chicken?
Coming right up. Just a moment.
Zhou Dangfan.
Stop rushing me.
I told you to stop rushing me.
I'm the only one here,
and I can barely keep up.
I don't even have anyone
to lend me a hand.
Why are you working all by yourself?
How come I've never seen you?
Who are you?
You don't need to know who I am.
But I came from your house.
Your mother's urging you to go home.
But I'm here to learn magic tricks.
I haven't learned any.
I've just been cooking all day.
Once I master them, I'll go back.
You know what?
What they teach you here
are just ordinary magic tricks,
like conjuring birds and flowers.
But it's different with me.
I know magic that's far more advanced
and mysterious.
Do you want to learn?
You know magic tricks?
Of course.
Then show me one.
Did I do it?
You did.
So you... You really know magic tricks.
Want to learn?
Yes.
Go home right now if you want to learn.
I'll be there in a minute.
Then... Then I'll go home right away.
That Zhou Dangfan.
He's so slow at cooking.
You...
Who are you?
Smells wonderful.
A table full of delicious food and wine.
What,
you're enjoying a feast
without inviting me?
Invite you?
Do I know you?
You do look familiar.
Have we met somewhere before?
Met somewhere before?
Let me think.
I remember now.
At the market,
you even made a bouquet of flowers appear
from my companion's arms.
He...
It's you.
It's him.
Buddies!
Get him!
When we see Boss later,
let's flatter him with
some auspicious words.
That way, when he hands out the rewards,
we can get a little extra.
Of course.
From now on,
we'll eat whatever we want.
We won't be eating steamed buns anymore.
Hey, who are you?
What do you want?
Good mutts don't get in the way. Get lost.
Did you not hear me?
I told you to get lost.
Where's the official seal?
What official seal?
We don't know.
We really don't know.
Where's the official seal?
Our Boss has it.
Where's your Boss?
Whoever has the pouch
is our Boss.
Help!
Someone, save me!
You can't just leave me to die!
Tell me.
Where did the contents of this go?
Who are you?
Why should I tell you?
Come on.
Be gentler,
and faster.
Whose underling are you?
Do you guys still work for me or not?
Then,
take off his other shoe too.
Tickle both feet together.
I won't say a word even if you kill me.
Kill me... Kill me if you can!
Take it off.
I'll talk! I'll tell you everything!
Speak.
I knew stealing an official seal
was a serious crime,
so once I obtained it,
I handed it
over to someone.
To whom?
To
the Zheng family.
Who in the Zheng family?
Who else could it be?
Zheng Jin,
of course.
Zheng Jin?
What are you still doing here?
Get lost!
Stop untying the rope!
Carry me away. Just carry me away!
Boss.
This is our place.
Where can we possibly go?
Cut the crap and just go.
Zheng Jin...
I obtained the newly appointed
gate commander's official seal.
The official seal?
Jin,
why did you take her seal?
What else could it be for?
Besides,
isn't everything I do
for the sake of our Zheng family?
No wonder there's been no news
from them these past few days.
It seems they failed to enter the city
without the official seal.
You and Grandfather went to Ling'an
to ask for the gate commander position
but failed.
I was thinking about what to do with them,
and now they've walked
right into my hands.
It's as if fate is on my side.
There's no time left.
This...
Jin.
They are officials from the Nine Cities.
They'll enter the city sooner or later.
Isn't it a bit too risky for us
to do this?
You...
Why don't you give it a second thought?
Let's return this official seal
back to them.
Useless.
You wish.
It's true they're officials
appointed by the Nine Cities,
but isn't there a saying?
"The mountains are high
and the emperor is far away."
Jin, are you planning to...
Without the official seal,
who would know they are gate commanders?
Send a letter to Ling'an,
saying that on their way here,
they were ambushed and killed by bandits.
At worst, we'll only be blamed morally.
No one will be able to
find any fault with us.
Gao Ran?
Freeze!
Stop running!
Stop right there!
Hurry up and get them!
Get them!
Don't let them escape!
Freeze!
-Stop right there!
-Get them!
Get them! Get them!
-Over there!
-Hurry!
-Stop!
-Just leave me behind.
-No way.
You're a friend that I, Liu Mu, value.
How could I just leave you behind?
Gao Ran.
I can only escort you this far.
For the rest of the journey,
you're on your own.
Hurry and leave!
Liu Mu!
Don't worry.
I won't die.
Take care of yourself.
You mustn't die.
Someday,
we'll meet again!
Liu Mu!
Gao Ran?
It really is you, Gao Ran.
Me?
Yeah... Yeah, it really is me.
You don't remember me?
Years ago at the Shadow Slay League,
you
and I...
The two of us.
Side by side.
Fought.
You pulled me along as we ran away.
That's right.
I knew you'd remember me.
I definitely wouldn't forget.
Definitely not.
Even in the depths of the night,
that horrific battle
still lingers in my dreams.
So it's you.
Yes.
It's me.
So I am...
You are...
You haven't changed a bit, bro.
So what are you here for?
I came to look for something.
Alright,
keep looking then.
I'll leave now.
What kind of illusion is this?
He looks exactly like Gao Ran.
He's not Gao Ran.
How could Gao Ran not recognize me?
I wasted all that time
searching for the official seal.
His Excellency is still waiting for me
to return and report to him.
You're back.
How did it go?
Did you find the official seal?
The official seal had been taken away.
It's now in the hands of the Zheng family.
Buddy.
You're finally back.
Hurry and teach me magic tricks.
Who is this?
Zhou Dangfan.
W-What magic tricks?
You know magic tricks?
Nothing impressive.
Wait,
you don't know?
His face...
It changed just like that!
Have you never seen it?
-We know. We know.
-Now you know.
Then hurry up and teach me.
Rest early.
Alright.
Then we'll head back and rest.
Take your time with the tricks.
Rest early.
-Hurry up and teach me.
-We're going to bed.
How on earth did you do that?
I'll go get some props.
Okay.
Wait for me.
I'll wait for you.
I'll be waiting.
Ma'am.
You mean Miss Fan Yun went to make money?
Yes.
Early this morning,
she came to borrow some writing supplies
from me.
She said
she was going to figure out a way
to make some money.
Ma'am.
Do you know where she went?
I think she went
to the market.
[Letter-writing Service]
Freshly steamed buns!
Thin skin, big filling!
Come in and try some!
I noticed you've been waiting here
for almost 2 hours,
and you haven't had a single customer.
Why not
buy some buns from me
to fill your stomach?
But...
I have no money, Boss.
You're quite honest.
Yesterday, a customer
ate so many buns here,
but he didn't even pay.
Just thinking about it makes me...
Speak of the devil.
Get over here!
You ate my buns yesterday,
but you didn't even pay.
I'm here to pay you.
Give me 2 more steamers of buns
and pack them up for me.
I have to hit the road.
As long as you've got the money,
that's no problem.
Write a letter for me.
Great.
Finally, a customer.
Sir.
What would you want me to write?
Write exactly
as I say.
Go ahead.
I managed to escape.
I still have some things to take care of.
I'll come find you once I'm done.
I have something very important
to tell you.
And?
That's it.
But
there has to be some kind of name
or address, right?
What's your name,
and who is this letter for?
I almost forgot.
I'll write this myself.
Here.
I can't really write,
but I can draw pretty well.
-A willow tree...
-Miss.
Please send this letter
to Qi Residence in Ling'an for me.
Okay.
The Governor?
Please come again.
Buns for sale! Buns for sale!
Thin skin, big filling!
Care for some buns?
Excuse me. Let me through.
Excuse me.
Let me through. Thanks.
Thanks. Thanks.