The Black Wolf is really an amazing force.
Let's go quickly
No time to rest
It's the city lord
castle lord
He is actually the city lord
All nine cities know it
The relationship between the city lord and Fan Yun
No wonder they are so close
It seems it's me
Miss Zheng Si
There's something I haven't had time to explain to you yet
I
Didn't mean to deceive you
Just because of my special status
There is no way to come to Jingcheng with great fanfare
I can only change my identity
You don't need to explain to me
if i were you
I will do the same
It's just that I should have guessed it earlier
castle lord
great uncle
If you really do something you shouldn't do
Then he should be punished
Just people from Jingcheng
Not everyone wants to compete with Ninetowns
Hope the city lord
Don't hurt innocent people
The election of the head of the Zheng family
Started early
Which brother do you support?
My eldest brother Zheng Jin
Act recklessly
And the second brother Zheng Shi
It’s also confusing
Even the third brother has been
My thoughts are getting heavier and heavier
No matter who becomes the leader of the clan
The future of the Zheng family
Unknown
you
You never thought about yourself
I
That's right
My three brothers fought for the position of sect leader
A bloody fight
I already lost my face
If I get involved again
That Zheng family
must fall apart
The meaning of suzerain
To unite the Zheng family
Gathering family strength
Carry forward the family
rather than becoming
a tool for personal gain
Our master this time
He is determined to go against Jiucheng.
This military parade?
Our Zheng Jiajun lost
At this time
We people want to rebel
Isn't this asking for death?
My mother told me
Qi Jiajun really came over
Just run for your life
Go ahead and drink
Zheng Tao is my enemy in Nine Cities
The crime cannot be punished
Put down your weapons now
Spare your life
Forgive me, Lord of the city
Guess you know the current affairs
You're hurt
It doesn't matter
As long as you are here
I can't die
Tomorrow is the day of the suzerain election
can i please you
Will you comb my hair in the morning?
Why do you want me to comb it for you?
You obviously have a servant and a maid.
Such an important day
I want to invite someone important to me
Come and comb my hair
Get a good start
I can't comb my hair
but what if you want
I can take you to the scene
You must also want to go
Exploring news and the like
After all, the Zheng family’s suzerain election
It will directly affect the stability of Nine Cities.
That
I've never combed anyone's hair
The comb is ugly
Don't blame me
I'm looking forward to it
Do you want me to be elected?
Can you guarantee the stability of Ninetowns?
I don't care about Ninetowns' stability.
I've combed it
are you okay
It seems you still care about me
only
When can I drink the tea you brewed by yourself?
Fan Yun
I also combed my hair
When can we leave?
He fell out before he achieved his goal.
I'm not turning against you
It's you who's been procrastinating
how
Are you worried that I will run away?
Or not at all
You didn't want to take me there
Prepare another set of pawn clothes
yes
Originally there were three people: Zheng Jin, Zheng Shi, Zheng Xian
Run for the position of suzerain
But Zheng Shi
He is treasonous
Disregarding human ethics
His brother Zheng Jin
kill
This is too cruel
The second son killed the eldest son
How could the second young master be so cruel?
I received Jin'er
news of being killed
Rush back to Jingcheng from Ling'an immediately
Have pity on me
I didn't even see him for the last time
That being the case
position of suzerain
It falls on Xian'er
I also hope that all clan members
Help Xian'er well in the future
Revitalize the Zheng family's majesty
but
Does he have the ring of the suzerain?
if there is
We all naturally admit that
He is the new head of our Zheng family
Yeah yeah
Of course there is
Our Zheng family has always respected the clan leader’s ring.
Anyone with this ring
Only then can you become the sect leader of my Zheng family
today
I will use this ring
Awarded to Xian'er
help him
Sit on the throne
Why are you so anxious?
Why don't you wait for me?
You are already the sect leader
Do you still have the nerve to participate in the general election?
Why do I have no face
Said I killed my eldest brother
Is there any evidence
evidence
You are bold
you forgot
There were other people around you when you committed the crime.
Don't be afraid
It was my fault that day
I shouldn't have been so harsh on you
Let me see how the injury goes
Can't see
That means no injuries
If Zheng Xian was not injured
Then he was lying just now
Said I killed my eldest brother
It's just nothing
But if it was Zheng Xian, you would kill the eldest brother
Put the blame on me
It's a good move to reap the benefits.
Nonsense
The suzerain ring is now in my hand
I am the leader of the Zheng family
How dare you disrespect the sect master?
Don't be afraid of my giving orders
Deal with your family law
The sect leader's ring has always been kept by the sect leader
The former head of the Zheng family
Living in Ling'an for a long time
You probably haven’t seen her much before.
I don’t even know the secret of this ring.
secret
what secret
Today I am in front of all the clan members
Come and unlock the secret of this ring
bring it
Gemstones in the Lord's Ring
is extremely rare in the world
Polished from bloodstone
The color is not only red like blood
Press hard
There is also blood-like fluid flowing out
actually
Lord's Ring
It is also a token of the sect leader.
This ring does have such a thing
Zheng Xian
You actually tried to use a fake ring to get away with it?
so
It really chills us
Where is this real ring now?
Let me see
Did you have a ring?
It’s not the only condition for being identified as a sect leader.
It also depends on his character and ability
That being said
anyway
What Zheng Xian did
This shows
He doesn't believe it himself
Can lead us to Zheng Zhongxing
You want me to say it?
This second young master
This is the sect leader.
Right, right, right
We all choose the second son
Nonsense
General election today
Has become a farce
Xian'er
grandfather
Don't be embarrassed
let's go
Thank you for your support from all the clan members
Zheng Shi from now on
Will inherit my grandfather’s wishes
Lead the Zheng family to continue to glory
three days later
Please come to my suzerain succession ceremony
OK OK
If there is a chance
May we meet in dreams
My grandson misses you very much
This picture is
The defense map of Jingcheng drawn by Juyun Pavilion for me
With this picture
Jingcheng’s military defense is clear at a glance
He, Zheng Tao, can no longer come up with any tricks.
It turns out you were already prepared
But you just became the sect leader
Are you going to go against the entire Zheng family?
I do this
It's to protect the Zheng family Zhou Quan
People who want to bring the Zheng family into injustice
It's him Zheng Tao
If he really rebels
The whole Zheng family
They will all become public enemies of Jiucheng
When the time comes, there will be internal and external troubles
The Zheng family will be wiped out
Grandfather’s Spirit in Heaven
Will not find rest
Then why are you
Why don't you join forces with the city lord?
If the city lord is really involved in this matter
The Zheng family is about to commit rebellion
Then everyone in the Zheng family will have to bear the blame.
If I could prevent this from happening before it happens
disappear into the invisible
Only the Zheng family can straighten their backs
Continue to survive in Ninetowns
But I believe
The city lord can handle this matter
I don't think so
The Zheng family has lived in a corner for many years
Qi Zheng is just showing his talents
Whether it's compilation or recovery,
In fact, the most difficult thing to win is the human heart
let him be
What I care about is
You should not want to marry a sinner
do you mean
marry you
yes
Aren’t we already engaged?
It's time to hold a celebration
When did this happen?
Are you still in the mood to joke?
Lord Fan Yun
Zheng Xi is back
Second brother
Zheng Xi
Where have you been these past two days?
I
Zheng Xi
How about it
Is everything going well with you?
Second brother
I want to have a private chat with my second sister-in-law
good
Liu Mu reported to me
You have led the Qi family army
When arriving in Jingcheng
I'm so happy
Are you marching this time?
It can be said that it is very fast
Yan Jiang led his troops and did not get lost.
It seems that you are really suitable to be a military commander
otherwise
You abandoned literature and embraced martial arts
Be my deputy
Why
Right
Gao Ran
How are you handling government affairs?
Gao Ran is very conscientious.
diligently
Reviewing memorials every day until late at night
and
Major and minor events inside and outside the Qi Mansion
He arranged everything in an orderly manner
you mean
When I was dealing with government affairs
No more conscientiousness and diligence
No, no, that's not what I meant
The city lord is naturally
Ying Ming Shen Wu
Shine with the sun and moon
Then you say
I compare with Gao Ran
who is better
I don't know this question
Gao Ran is so boring
I stay in the house every day
The mansion was much more lively when the city lord was there.
so
It’s better to be the city lord
I guess you know the current affairs
Although it doesn’t sound like you’re complimenting me.
grown up
The matter of me and Gao Ran exchanging identities
Does any minister know?
The ministers in the city didn't know
only
just what
Say it quickly
It was just after the city lord left Ling'an
Wei Shisan stayed in the house all day
I know a little bit about it.
Thirteen knows
Then they two
as you think
castle lord
I heard about Zheng Tao’s arsenal
I was served by you in one fell swoop
Then he won't be able to make much of a splash.
Why not take advantage of tonight
Let's attack Jingcheng directly
yes
I just finished complimenting you two
Of course not
Don't be anxious about this matter
If you enter the city rashly
It will definitely anger Zheng Tao
This matter needs to be considered in the long run
But what else can we do if we don’t attack by force?
Say it again
City Lord, aren't you worried about Fan Yun?
yes
If we attack the city rashly,
It will definitely hurt innocent people
I won't agree
I also believe
Fan Yun understands me
say so
Gao Ran's identity
You know it all
The city lord is worried about your safety
Let me come back to see you first
Lord Fan Yun
I envy you
If there is a man in this world
Treat me like the city lord treats Lord Fan Yun
I'm satisfied
The city lord asks you to be patient a little longer.
Wait for him to come back
I must rescue you first
Saving me is the next best thing
I'm worried now
If Zheng Tao
We really got into a fight with Qi Jiajun
The people of Jingcheng
Will definitely be implicated
By then, all life in Jingcheng will be devastated.
Definitely not what everyone wants to see
That's a scene no one wants to see
But now Jingcheng and Qijiajun
Like water and fire
The army is approaching
No matter which side takes action first
Najo Castle
There will be a river of blood
yes
both sides
Absolutely no fight
Do you have any ideas?
way
In fact, you can use the deployment map
First infiltration inside the castle
Take control of their military camp
In this way
They have no support
Attack the city again then
to minimize casualties
Zheng Xi
I need you to go out of town now
Tell the city lord
Never attack a city by force
good
I'll go right away
Wait a moment
This is drawn by Fan Yun
Exactly
As if imprinted on her mind
The pen moves the dragon and the snake
Just wait and see
Lord Fan Yun is really a strange woman
The city lord is assisted by Lord Fan Yun
How lucky
Master Fan Yun also asked me to bring a message to the city lord.
Say it quickly
Lord Fan Yun
Let the city lord never attack the city by force.
Your heart is like my heart
Those who know me
Qing Ye
It seems that the night before the sect leader's ceremony
Opportunistic
It's not just me
castle lord
Who are you
No need to pretend anymore
I am Liu Mu
I'm going to kill you this time
Wei Ying Yan Jiang
I am here
We led our elite troops to sneak in overnight
The internal strife in the Zheng family will definitely hurt both sides.
Then kill him by surprise
promise
lord of the castle lord of the castle
What about me?
you
You are the main warrior of tomorrow
Very good
Let these white-eyed wolves fall with the wind
Remember me Liu Chengshou
Guards have been strengthened again
how do i get out
Infiltrated sect
Find out about Zheng Jiajun
and send the message
Pass it to Qi Zheng
Second Young Master Zheng
Tomorrow you will accompany me to attend the sect leader's ceremony
Don't drink too much
Grand Ceremony of the Sect Master
You want me to go with you
What I am fighting for is the position of suzerain.
It's not for the sake of
The so-called overwhelming power
Those they gave everything to
something to fight for
Nothing in my eyes
There are only two things in this world
most important to me
do you know what it is
Grandfather and you
So don't worry
Since I can take you there
It will be arranged naturally
I will definitely protect you
Tomorrow I will be in front of everyone
Give you a new identity
lady
from now on
no one anymore
I can touch you even a little bit
lady
Second Young Master Zheng today
Maybe he drank too much
Even if you declare your identity
It should also be Fan Chengshou’s identity
marry
It's just a delaying tactic for entering the city.
I say it again
Don't take it too seriously
I want to take it seriously
I just hope
you can stay with me
Stop talking nonsense
I'll get you a cup of tea
Sober you up
I really want to pour tea for me
Just pour me a cup of nectar tea
According to the custom of Jingcheng
girls
Make nectar tea only for the one you love
Second Young Master Zheng
you know
my heart is not here
you
I will tomorrow
Will go to the ceremony
But I won't be your wife
I'm just the city guard of Jingcheng
The sect master arrives
Jingcheng City was defended
auspicious time arrives
The beginning of all things
The ancestral worship ceremony of the clan leader officially begins
Second Young Master Zheng
Completed
After all, he is a bad person who never changes his nature.
Uncle, are you so surprised?
Don't you think
I'll sit back and wait for death
When I saw you
I still rely on these charlatans.
Second Young Master Zheng
Zheng Shi colluded with bandits
The crime of deceiving the master and destroying the ancestors cannot be punished
Hanged on the spot
is to kill
Prepare
fall
emission
Go quickly
grandfather
I told you before
i can do it
The position of sect leader must be mine
This first shot
Just a warning
do you want us to
Will everyone be buried with you?
what are you afraid of
you are my grandfather
Of course I will spare your life
Second brother
Let's capture him as soon as possible
Give me the position of suzerain
I'll leave you a whole body
Hiding gunpowder
You let our Zheng family
Are you going to wipe out Manmen?
What are you hiding in the arsenal outside the city?
Why can't I hide it
I can't be the leader of the Zheng family
What value does it have?
uncles
Do you want me to be your master?
good
The third young master is not well
What happened? We were attacked.
How is it possible
The city lord arrives
Jingcheng City Shoufan Yun
See City Lord
Everyone
Xie City Lord
The city lord arrives
Missing the welcome from afar
It's my fault, the Zheng family, for being rude.
But I don’t know why the city lord
I would like to come to my Zheng family for the election of the sect leader.
Grand Ceremony of the Sect Master
do you think
Am I not eligible to participate?
Lord's Ring
How could it be in your hands?
Everyone
Death of Mr. Zheng
There is another reason
Mr. Zheng has foresight
I know the Zheng family is in chaos
It will disrupt the safety of Jiucheng
and will harm innocent people.
so
Sacrifice his own life to save Jingcheng
And hand this sect leader's ring into my hand
You just want me to maintain it
The tranquility of these nine cities
But now you are going in the opposite direction
Set foot on a road of no return
Isn’t this a waste of Mr. Zheng’s hard work?
Yes, yes, that's right
castle lord
The Zheng family is going to rebel
They hid a batch of gunpowder outside the city
I hate that I support the city lord
And forced me to rebel
None of this is what I want
Hope the city lord understands clearly
Zheng Xian
Although I am the co-owner of nine cities
But it’s just the human eye
Demons and monsters
Never encounter it
Occasionally, I make mistakes
Such nice words
Just say whatever you want
I can make up my mind whether I believe it or not
castle lord
you have to believe me
You have to believe me
quick
You order now
I'll help you kill these rebellious officials and thieves
Until now, you are still stubborn
Since I can get the gunpowder outside the city,
You will naturally know who did it
Originally thought
After the Jingcheng incident is over,
Are you asking if I come back again?
I didn’t expect you to be more ruthless than Zheng Tao
Dare to disregard the lives of the people
Aren't you afraid of retribution?
retribution
tell you
I, Zheng Xian, have come to this day
What I'm afraid of is doing nothing
What I'm afraid of is being
Trampled underfoot like grass and mustard
Someone coming
Remove Zheng Xian from his crown
put in jail
strict scrutiny
yes
Get away
City Lord, be careful
Come on
you people
People who stand above others every day
I'm only one step away
Just one step away from killing you all
And you, Zheng Tao
Xian'er
Do you know who killed your favorite eldest grandson?
it's me
from childhood to adulthood
You have a grandfather who loves you
The second brother is loved by his uncle
None of you care about me
Now I'm going to show you
I am Zheng Xian
How to do it step by step
Trampling you underfoot
He is your elder brother
What happened to my elder brother?
Anyway, you have never looked at me directly.
You are crazy and I am crazy
I'm just crazy
I'm completely crazy this time
Just because I'm crazy
So until today
Only once can you look at me squarely
I'm going to take you with me today
Go down and see the King of Hell
As a noble from Nine Cities
You were supposed to work for the welfare of the people
But he ended up like this for his own selfish desires
Everyone