Where have people gone?
little girl
Why are you following me?
I
Who are you?
Are you from the Zheng family?
For the sake of a little girl like you
I don't care about you
Go back and tell Zheng Tao
Your grandfather and I are immortal
Ask him to be careful when walking at night in the future
Tell me first
Who are you?
Stop following me
Otherwise I won't be polite
you just said
Gao Ran
Don't bully Fan Yun
His real name is Gao Ran Tian Xing
You fake Gao Ran
I didn’t expect you to be targeting me
who are you
Everyone wants to know my name so much
what on earth are you going to do
I have to ask you this.
Your Zheng family is lawless
Privately imprison the city guard of Jiucheng
You still want to steal my official seal
Your official seal Your official seal
etc.
You are not Liu Mu, are you?
who are you
We are our own people.
So you two are the newly appointed city guards of the city lord.
Tian Xing and I
He is the guardian of the two cities of Jingcheng who was personally appointed by the city lord.
I'm stroking it
The city lord thought I was dead
So we sent two new city guards here.
But your official seal was stolen
So I can’t prove my identity.
You are a full-time military attaché
OK
That way I won't be afraid
The city lord of Ling'an blamed
I wanted to write down the unexpected situation
Send a letter to Ling'an Qi Mansion to the city lord
It seems that I am in Yanagi Shou's heart
Very special
I
So you and Gao Ran
You can change your identity with this
Then you are the city lord
Guaranteed replacement if fake
Otherwise, who else could it be?
Naqiqifu
Then the city lord and I will
Wouldn’t it be like we wouldn’t know each other without fighting?
Yanagi Shou
I have to tell you something
The matter of me and Gao Ran exchanging identities
You have to help keep it a secret
can you do it
able
besides
This time Jingcheng and his party
i hope you can be
their adjutant
Always following behind them
would you like
It doesn't matter whether he is a deputy general or not.
Fame is like a floating cloud to me
I am willing to follow everyone
That's good
Calling everyone today
I want to invite merchants to join Juyun Pavilion
in the future
Juyun Pavilion is also coming to Jingcheng
What if we don't join?
That means being an enemy of my Juyun Pavilion
That
Mr. Lou warmly invites you
There must be a plan, right?
That's right
Now I need to pool your efforts
Draw me a map
Please also ask Mr. Lou to speak clearly.
What map is it?
City defense map of Jingcheng
This city defense map
We can't agree to it
What if the Zheng family finds out?
It won't be easy for us
Everyone knows
The position of the head of the Zheng family
That's what the eldest son of the Zheng family has in his pocket.
It's him, why is it him?
The sect leader is the eldest son of the Zheng family.
So what do you think I am?
This seems to be the second son of the Zheng family.
What is true or false
Really, really, I've seen him
It's him
The second young master is him
This is the second young master
I am the direct grandson of the previous patriarch Zheng Lao
He is also the leader of Juyun Pavilion in the Nine Cities.
Everyone
They are all veterans of the shopping mall.
Just weigh it a little bit
Then you can clearly understand the benefits of joining Juyun Pavilion
Anyway, I know a little bit
Be friends with Mr. Zheng
It's better than being an enemy with Mr. Zheng
much better
this
Today's plan
You already know
Who wants to disobey
Then I can't get out of this door today.
I am willing to follow the second young master
a few months ago
The city guard's mansion suddenly caught fire
Who ate the heart of a bear or the gall of a leopard?
Dare to go to the city guard's house and set fire to it
Let me find you
I must take you
This place is spooky
Hurry up, hurry up
Too
This Jingcheng is already the domain of the Zheng family.
Why do you need this official seal?
I see you are really full after eating.
Master's business
Just do what you have to do
Don't think too much, don't ask any more questions
Quick, quick, quick
It's going to rain
Go, go, go
that's all
Fortunately, I know how to hold my breath
I hid it from those two idiots
Otherwise, I will really die with my eyes open.
So after your resurrection
Just been lurking here
Find out about Ninetowns
Want to hit the road?
There is no one to go to
Want to go home
Homeless again
I heard that Zheng Tao led troops to Ling'an
Just don't dare to move
stay put
OK now
see you
It’s closer than meeting my own mother
Have a fish
This one is quite lively
Just take this
OK
I also need these two items.
guest officer
You still know the goods?
tell you
These fish are all this morning
The fresh fish I just caught from the lake
Don't you ever ask the price before buying something?
I asked, can I not give you money?
Of course not
Then why do you ask?
You pay
Why am I giving the money?
Your fish
Can it be cheaper?
This can't be cheaper
Sir, please go slowly
Everyone is here
I don’t know that today’s eldest son
What are your instructions for calling us here?
But the sect leader’s ring was found
The new sect leader has been settled
No problem
Lord's Ring
Sooner or later I will find you
Can't find the ring
There are so many things I can't do.
Yeah yeah
That's right
How can I do without a ring?
Extraordinary things should be done in extraordinary times
A lot has happened to the Zheng family recently
The old master passed away unexpectedly
Zheng Tao's grandfather was trapped in Ling'an
There is no one in charge of the Zheng family now.
The city lord is eyeing us again
I
I would like to recommend myself to serve as the temporary head of the Zheng family.
This is a bit hasty, right?
Too anxious
Yeah yeah
this long term
This is a bit hasty, right?
Yes, that's right
who agrees
who objects
The eldest son and the second son are here
why are you here
All the Zheng family members gathered together
How can you miss me?
It doesn't hurt to let you listen
today
All the clan members elected me as the head of the Zheng family
Starting today, the Zheng family
I have the final say
Yeah
Anyone agreed?
Take a step forward and let me see
father
Give me another piece of candy to eat
there is none left
next time
Can I bring you some more candy?
you
what did you feed him
father
The candies he gave me were particularly delicious
Ask him to give me some more
This is the style of the Shadow Killing Alliance
you should have heard
If the second young master can become the sect leader as he wishes,
Everyone has candy
otherwise
The villain resigns
It seems that my eldest brother is not very popular either.
The suzerain election is just around the corner
Why are you anxious at this time?
What kind of acting suzerain should I be?
Zheng Shi
You don't have to be sarcastic here
Everyone
Grandfather passed away and the city guard disappeared
Jingcheng is in chaos
The city lord is worried about the popular sentiment in Jingcheng.
Fan Yun and Tian Xing were sent to guard Jingcheng.
It's also a temptation
As expected
The Zheng family is divided into different parts of the country.
I want to protect Jingcheng for my grandfather
Only extraordinary measures can be used
Please forgive me
You deserve it too
Talking nonsense about protecting the Zheng family
Fan Yun is inseparable from the death of the old sect leader
You are so close to her
Zheng Shi
You want to be Ninetowns' lackey?
Said that Fan Yun was related to my grandfather's death
This is just groundless speculation
Since everyone is so afraid
Fan Yun, who is about to take office
Why don't you let me solve this problem?
I want to marry her
Marry Fan Yun
That's right
Married to Fan Yun
She became the Zheng family
Our Zheng family
Don’t embarrass the Zheng family
What do you think?
That's okay
It's a good and safe way.
Wonderful
On the occasion of the suzerain election
Non-Zheng family members cannot enter Jingcheng
If Fan Yun becomes my second sister-in-law
Wouldn't it be possible to go to the city and take office?
That's not okay
Zheng Shi
I think your marriage to Fan Yun is just a pretense.
The only real thing is to help her get the upper hand, right?
Fan Yun's appointment as the city guard of Jingcheng was authorized by the city lord.
Do you still need my help?
I'm afraid someone wants to stop me.
No more Fan Yun
There will also be Fan Yu and Fan Feng
Come and be the city guard of Jingcheng
If she doesn't take office
Jiucheng will send other city guards.
What should you do
Preventing the new city guard from taking office angered Jiucheng
Big brother
Do you want to rebel?
Have you thought it through?
The young master does not fight for the moment's anger
Don't forget your plan
good
As long as you dare to marry
I dare to do it for you
Then there’s Brother Lao
We can't eat so much, right?
The city lord is lucky that you were born in the Qi family
If this were born
This is not what I see in ordinary people’s homes.
Is it what you paid for?
Fan Yun told me
no matter what happens
Everyone has to eat well
Don’t treat your belly badly
That's right
Only when you have a full stomach can you have the brains to think of a solution
Want me to say
How about you disguise yourself a little bit?
Otherwise, the Zheng family finds out that you are not dead.
We have to create new branches again
City Lord, do you want to disguise yourself?
Discovered by the Zheng family
The city lord is walking around in the street
More details
Don’t you also know that I am the city lord?
This is out of Ling'an City
Who knows what the city lord looks like?
Want me to tell you
Just these few beards of yours
really
City Lord, you don’t know
If I didn’t have a beard
That's so handsome
You are not allowed to boast
I
Juyun Pavilion
So impressive! This is it
A wealthy family
what are you doing
The Zheng family came to deliver the betrothal gift
officiating
A pair of live Jingcheng wild geese
Countless side gifts
He wanted to replace his second son Zheng Shi
Recruiting Fan Jia Jiaojin
who
Zheng Shi
Yes, you mean
Second Young Master Zheng
Want to marry me
It's Mrs.
what madam
This is Lord Fan
Master Fan comes to Jingcheng
But there's something important going on
How can we tolerate child's play?
Don't worry yet
I think this
Maybe there's a reason
I'll ask again
You, the second son of the Zheng family
What else did you say?
The second young master also said
The eldest son is in front of the city gate
Set up a dragnet
If Master Fan Yun enters the city at this time,
There is certainly no way to ensure safety
The second young master is here to help you, sir.
Please act as an adult
The identity of the second young master’s future wife
Entering the city by sedan chair
After entering the city
Never force it
What did I say?
This guy has been plotting against you for a long time.
We haven’t entered the city yet
The horse's legs are exposed
Go back and tell your boss
Don't look for these high-sounding reasons
We have our own ideas on how to enter the city
Take your things and get out of here
roll
You guys go back first
Let's discuss it further
The villain resigns
Walk
discuss
Please drink slowly
Don't drink the tea
Otherwise it will not be allowed
Come
Please help me do the math
When will Fan Yun and the others come back?
This hexagram shows
The return date of the person I miss has not yet been determined
Bad luck
Take a closer look
The tea leaves have all fallen off. This hexagram is not accurate.
I told you to drink slowly.
This doesn't count
Next
I have nothing to settle
Look down on me
How could it be
Then why don't you let me count?
If I were Gao Ran here
He will definitely let me count it
OK OK
You count, you count, what do you want to count?
Let me calculate a marriage for you
I
Hurry, hurry up
Drink
Drink quickly
Red Luan Star has been activated
Good luck
But this direction
But
Why isn't this
Fan Yunzai's direction to Jingcheng
Then you have to take a good look
Who does it refer to?
newspaper
Jingcheng Zheng Tao and Mr. Lu
A fight broke out at the palace gate
How can we fight?
Come, come, come
Take me to Huiyunzhai quickly
I said Zheng Tao
City Lord
Me
Just came out from the meeting hall after doing business
What about after coming out?
I met him at the door
He said nothing
He hits me when he comes up
you see
This belt has been torn off
Give me back the ring and I'll let you go
ring
what ring
The ring of your clan master?
Such an important thing
How could it be here with me?
See for yourself
this
Let me explain it to you
What about this?
It was me and Lao Zheng last time
When there is a conflict
He gave this to me
Smashed
he fixed it
After repairing it, he returned it to me.
This is what I was told
Old Zheng, Old Zheng
I said, why do you ask me to write a note?
So you were waiting for me here
Lao Zheng, aren’t you?
Are you bringing the fire to me?
I don't care
Anyway, when my eldest brother died
As long as he's around
I just ask you for it
That's right for me
How unbecoming is this?
Mr. Lu
Then tell me
This clan leader’s ring
where are you now
no
Here I am
I, I, this
how do i know
Where is your clan leader’s ring?
I said Zheng Tao
Are you hungry?
Have a taste of this pastry. Does it suit your taste?
Can't eat without eating
You've come all this way
I haven't even had a good meal
Why don't you try it?
Fan Yun
I ask you
What on earth do you think
Didn’t you just drink nectar tea that day?
Now turn around
I'm going to get married to someone else.
No, of course not
Didn't they just say that?
Welcoming my bride is just a temporary measure to help me get into the city.
To put it bluntly, it’s fake
Just a show
And we are entering the city now
Isn't it the most important thing?
Are you right? You don’t need to say it anymore.
I've already thought of a way
You've already thought of a way
What can be done
What's this
Lord's Ring
The ring of the head of the Zheng family
Why are you here?
Mr. Zheng gave it to me
Mr. Zheng gave me this ring
It means leaving Jingcheng to me
Zheng Family Rebellion
Don't care
And in the bone marrow
So I came to Jingcheng on this trip
The first is to suppress the Jingcheng Rebellion that has yet to be revealed.
Take the heat out of the cauldron
The next step is to choose the right sect leader
Zhongxing Jingcheng
In this way
Only then can the people of Jingcheng have peace.
Only in Nine Cities can there be peace.
so
Now we have this ring
Maybe we can enter the city smoothly
I see
Then why are you telling me now?
I was thinking about it too
After arriving in Jingcheng
I'll tell you after taking a look at the situation
Discuss with you
By the way, Qi Zheng
That matter
Who else knows
just you and me
Even if it's not right
Now the Zheng family
Can do anything
Not the Zheng family
take out this ring
will they believe it
even if they believe
After we enter the city
Will definitely become the target of public criticism
What do you think?
Mr. Zheng hands this ring to you
Just show
He had long known that the Zheng family was at odds with each other
At this time
Zheng Shi
willing to help us
Check and balance the Zheng family
Why wouldn't we do it?
Why
Need to find another way
This is too unstable
This won't work, and that won't work either.
Is there any other way besides getting married?
Yes
Don't let me find another way
I have to find another way
Come
What
you believe me
It will definitely work
it's you
You didn't expect it to be me, right?
But in the eyes of the world
That's not necessarily the case
Anyway
Thank you anyway
should
Now I'm afraid the city guard can no longer live in it.
But I'm at Zheng's house
The room has been prepared for you
Wait
That’s almost the end of the show
Don't push yourself too far
Forgot your true identity
Mr. Gao Ran’s speeches these two days
Why do I always have a sour smell?
Am I sour?
Thank you Mr. Zheng for your kindness.
We still have government affairs to deal with
Need to go in and deal with it
Don't bother the Zheng family.
Then I'll take you in
Where is the castle guard's mansion?
Government center
Not for you guys
Go in in vain
Don't talk about Jingcheng
Not in the whole of Ling'an
A place I can't enter
Second Young Master Zheng
I think Gao Ran is right
This city's garrison is indeed a place of government.
If you are free to come and go
Not very suitable either
It won’t be talked about until then
That would be troublesome
good
you care about me
Then I will listen to you
let's go
Thank you Mr. Zheng
This Mr. Zheng is really crazy
He actually opened the city gate wide and welcomed Fan Yun in.
It’s simply a shame for the Zheng family
The eldest son calms down
Welcoming the bride today
Just a bluff
ceremony
False name
Speech is not smooth
How do you want me to calm down?
Keep it up like this
The coffin lids of the ancestors of the Zheng family
I can't even press it firmly.
In my opinion
That's not necessarily a bad thing
Sir, look
The leader’s ring is nowhere to be found
at first glance
It’s because the election has lost its basis
But this way
Who will sit on the throne of this sect leader?
It pays more attention to the people's will
popular support
What the Second Young Master did today
Really a family scandal
Zheng family clan
Even the people in Jingcheng have seen it
after all
No one wants the master they choose
Weak and dim
Insult the lintel of the Zheng family
What you said makes some sense
Zheng Laoer lowered his worth in order to marry Fan Yun
I wish I could kneel down and beg for mercy
I've lost all my shame.
How are things going?
Have everything been transported to the warehouse?
All arrived
I see that you have gotten very close to Zheng Laoer recently.
Do you want to be like him?
Step on my head
How could it be?
I just think
Is there any misunderstanding between you?
I don't want you to kill each other, that's all
What misunderstanding can there be?
Do you still want to
Say nice things to him in front of me
See what he has done?
Second brother
It must be for the good of the Zheng family
Fan Yun is still named Fan after all.
It’s the new city guard again
if
Let’s marry her into the Zheng family
That has a lot of problems
It can be easily solved
The whole Zheng family can also be inspired
Can also get rid of the current decline
It seems that after the city guard's mansion caught fire,
No one has taken care of it for a long time
After Yanagi Shou’s incident
Officials are leaderless
No intention to govern Jingcheng
Everything turned into a piece of loose sand
The backbone is gone
Of course I have no intention of working.
You must not have thought of it
How important I am to them
castle guardian adult
We were sent by the Zheng family to help.
I think it's the spy sent by the Zheng family.
Let's take a step to talk.
Then it will be tiring
Let's take care of business first
Walk
Go, go, go
The Zheng family arrested me
imprison me in a dungeon
Everything is caused by this thing
my little life
I almost fell on such a small piece of rock.
But there is one thing
Still feel weird
What's up
What do you think?
If the city guard's mansion had been burned down,
The Zheng family just wants to be in power secretly
After Mr. Zheng died,
The Zheng family is in Jingcheng
Can cover the sky with one hand
They don't even need the city guard anymore.
So what's the point of having this official seal?
yes
Do they want to replace it?
But even if they get the official seal
I can't be a city guard either.
This problem these days
It's also running around in my head
Still a mess
You said they wanted to prevent us from entering the city?
That is a matter of time
You said they want to catch them all in one go?
There will be others besides us
What are they doing?
castle lord
what is this writing
Give me your official seal
The city guard has an order
Taxes cut in half
At this time
Why write this
watching
indeed
This is just a small piece of jade
It cannot be called an official seal
take it
At most it can only prove your identity
Nothing else can be done
Only when printed
Talent is called the official seal
So
what they want
It is the power under the official seal
good
Yanagi Shou
Where are all the files?
All files in Jingcheng are in duplicate
Send one copy to Jiage Library
Send another copy here for archiving
recent months
Even the cleaning people are gone
Although the environment is a bit dirty
But just make sure the file is still there
We can definitely find some clues
We need to investigate clearly
What does the Zheng family want to do with this official seal?
What's more important
behind
Who is instigating this matter?
You must get both the stolen goods and the stolen goods.
Only then can they be convinced
Without further ado
let's get started
Wait a moment
OK
There's no grapefruit in it
Eat
How unbecoming is this?
go
Go and go
Let's go, let's go quickly
The more you disturb it
the louder it gets
it's just lost
Right
What do you want from me?
This is wrong
This is not your seal
This is the seal we brought
Take a look
These two seals are not the same seal
when we come
bumps on the road
The official seal was broken into a hole
So it looks like this when printed
And in the previous dossier
But it is complete
So what documents are included in the new official seal?
These are the customs clearance records of the terminal
New official seal
This shows
after you die
There are still supplies being cleared through customs.
Previously, Jingcheng had a batch of supplies coming to the port.
But the people underneath
Presented weight and price
Nothing matches
Usually this is the case
There are always people who want to smuggle
Salt, grain, poison, iron, etc.
So I didn’t put the official seal on it
put aside
Thinking about it when I have free time
Check it out for yourself
As a result, I forgot about it as soon as I got busy.
now you see
Now it's stamped
It means they hold official seals
Just to do this
But the Zheng family has nothing
If it's just for smuggled supplies
As for expending so much effort?
What on earth is so important?
Also risking death
Don't even think about it
Can this thing still grow wings and fly?
We'll find out if we go and see it, right?
The city lord is right
Jingcheng Pier is released every Friday
It's most likely to be shipped in tonight
I have to at least find out today
The flow of this cargo
But I have to go to Zheng’s house
I'm afraid it will be as difficult as climbing to heaven
Which of you is Fan Chengshou?
I am
This is my parent's son
A banquet will be held at Zheng Mansion tomorrow
Settled in Jingcheng specifically for the new city guard
Receive the wind and wash away the dust
I also ask the city guard to attend the banquet when the time comes.
Come
This is easy
Delivered to your door
good
Since Zheng Jin invited me
Then let's go separate ways
I would like to take a look at this Zheng Mansion
What's so fishy?
Both are city guards
Why not invite Tian Xing?
Liu Mu is right
This trip is dangerous
Let's protect Fan Yun together
You and Tian Xing are waiting outside to take care of you.
We adapt to circumstances
no problem
Tian Xing
And you
Don't worry, I can do it
you in a while
You say it first
I just want to say
I heard them say that this dragon beard cake is very delicious.
Do you want to try one?
good
How about it
really delicious
I just want to ask you
After a while, there will be a feast in Jingcheng
Have you figured out what to do?
I'm thinking about it
wait a moment
eat slowly
Eat so much
Can you still eat it soon?
I'm stuffed
Only then do you have the strength to deal with that Zheng Jin?
Say it again
I don't dare to eat what they prepare.
besides
you see
I've even prepared wine
I'm quite alert.
I also have something to give you
What
What's this
This is a toy from the Western Regions that I brought from my house
Made by divine craftsmen
Look
Just ring a bell
Another bell will also vibrate.
real
Are you dealing with Zheng Jin this time?
Be careful
If any danger occurs
Just ring the bell
I will come to you immediately
Remember?
Remembered
Eat quickly
That’s almost the end of the show
Don't push yourself too far
Forgot your true identity
It turned out to be him
Fan Chengshou
The eldest son is already waiting for you
please
Miss is saying
Just there
Someone passed by with a hiss.
But
I didn't see anyone
I didn't hear a sound either.
Go down
private salt
It's not a special smuggled item.