Take your wife down to make preparations
yes
boss
All the rest are here
We only have one stick of incense at most
The time of a stick of incense
enough
Send my order
people who come from here
Kill without mercy
yes
Let's look for each other separately
We must find Fan Yun
yes
Go, follow me
What's wrong, Sect Master?
Are you okay?
No problem
continue
I
Where am I?
you woke up
you
Zheng Shi
why am i here
what on earth are you going to do
what i want
It's always just you
today
i want you to be my wife
It's Qi Zheng
You, let me go
Zheng Xian’s gunpowder
I know where it is
He didn't finish his order
I can light it up
Zheng Shi
Are you crazy?
If you want to leave here
More people will die
first one
It’s Qi Zheng
you said
I'm a madman
Zheng Shi
you
How did you become like this?
What has become
in this world
I only care about how you and grandpa feel
If these are gone
It doesn't matter what it becomes.
Zheng Shi
Why do you have to do this?
Don't you know there are some things
Can't it force it to come at all?
What does it matter?
days I don’t like
Life is but a moment
favorite day
A moment's worth of life
Come
put this on
No need
I'm here
Have something of my own
I want to wear my hair accessories
It's almost time
Clean up before you come out.
Put on the phoenix crown
otherwise
So he ordered the bridge to be blown up.
Qi Zheng
Qi Zheng, be careful
you should look at me
look at me
The auspicious time has arrived
Fan Yun
You think clearly
Do you want to marry me today?
Let’s worship the lovers of heaven and earth
Qi Zheng
If you can't go out today
I'll let you go
Two thanks to the high hall for marriage
Zheng Shi
You can't threaten us
Husband and wife are united in their love for each other
Drinking nectar tea together
The knot means that there is no doubt about the love between husband and wife
Drinking nectar tea together, there is no doubt about the love between the two
Drink this cup of nectar tea
You are my wife
Zheng Shi
you disappoint me so much
you and i once
are friends
Is a confidant
You obviously know that
I
I don't love you at all
This is the last chance
If you don't drink this cup of tea
I'm afraid there's someone today
Can't get out of here alive
Please tell your people to stop
Really don't fight anymore
How many people have to die before you can do that?
Zheng Shi
I'm still missing one
What do you mean?
Zheng Shi
you call my name
It sounds so nice
I really want to drink
The nectar tea you brewed by yourself
Fan Yun
nectar tea
I've already had a drink with Qi Zheng
so
I will never drink with others again
this bet
I still lost to you
Fan Yun
You don't want to
Then this time
I will set you free
Zheng Shi Zheng Shi
Zheng Shi
Fan Yun
I always thought
Pursue the ultimate freedom
That's the happiest thing in life
Until my grandfather left
I just started to understand what you said
At that time I thought
It's not too late
At least I still have you
So for the first time
Think about people other than yourself
Thinking of what I can do for you
but i found
I still can’t keep anything
I wanted to tell you
The person who killed me was actually you
In that case
I can be the most special person in your heart
Let you never forget me for the rest of your life
sad for me
But I'm afraid you will really feel sad for me
That might be good too
Fan Yun
go in
hurry up
Since I have been entrusted by Mr. Zheng,
Of course I have a responsibility
Select a new head of the Zheng family
Baojing City’s stability and prosperity
Since this time
I've seen it too
Zheng Xi’s courage and bravery
That’s why I recommend her
Candidate for the head of the Zheng family
Zheng Xi
I ask you
are you willing to help me
What about rebuilding Jingcheng?
Dear elders
Zheng Xi has been really lonely since she was a child.
Also taciturn
But I have been with my brothers since childhood.
Study and grow up together
Although I have never thought about it
Be like those ancestors of the Zheng family
Play for Ninetowns
But since I met Fan Chengshou
I just knew
It turns out that the woman
He has such courage that he is not inferior to men
girls
You can also have your own career
and ambition
Now Jingcheng
People are devastated and have no way to survive
Zheng Xi is unwilling to back down
so
If Zheng Xi says she doesn’t want to
That's bullying
Yeah yeah
good
After listening to Zheng Xi’s heartfelt words,
What do you think?
The minister seconded the motion
from today
You are the new head of the Zheng family
I hope you will be firm and never turn back.
I accept the order
You said he was poisoned
Yes, boss
Zheng Shi
Before his succession ceremony
He was already poisoned
How to get poisoned
There was a secret arrow attack before
scratched his right arm
that arrow
soaked in poison
It must have been done by Zheng Xian and his ilk.
Now that I know I've been poisoned
Why are you letting it go?
This poison is unique to Jingcheng
Death will occur within a few days after a toxic attack
Search by all means
This highly toxic antidote is actually a specialty of Jingcheng
nectar tea
We all know that manna tea can detoxify
If you take it early
Not even
It’s hard to get back
You're hurt
It doesn't matter
As long as you are here
I can't die
are you okay
It seems you still care about me
only
When can I drink the tea you brewed by yourself?
Fan Yun
If you don't drink this cup of tea
I'm afraid there's someone today
Can't get out of here alive
You could have survived
Why don't you drink it?
castle lord
Today you and I are not the main ministers
Just sit down and talk
Why are you drinking alone?
Are you worried about something?
castle lord
I have one thing
I hope the city lord can promise me
I want to stay in Jingcheng
You are the city guard
You should stay here for a while
how long do you need
Jingcheng just went through turmoil
Popular sentiment is unstable
I am discussing with Zheng Xixi
How to revitalize this place
As for
How long does it take
I can’t estimate it now.
Let’s discuss this later when you wake up.
sit
I'm sober now
Why discuss it for another day?
I asked you to sit down
The Lord of the City hopes that you will
Just give me an answer
As the city guard of Jingcheng
I asked you to sit down
Otherwise, you will be fired from your job. Do you believe it?
The city lord won't
What makes you think I can't
I'm human too
I also have uncontrollable emotions
What makes you think I can't
Fan Yun, let me ask you something
you want to stay here
After all, is it for Jingcheng?
Still for Zheng Shi
castle lord
Why do you think so?
What kind of person is Fan Yun?
What are you thinking about every day?
Does the city lord really not know?
these days
i have been
What everyone is thinking about is Jingcheng’s funeral.
Isn't it for Zheng Shi's funeral?
Want to stay in Jingcheng as a family member
Keep vigil for him
Is it right
answer me
I let you talk
You haven't thought it through yourself, have you?
Thinking of him becomes a thorn in your heart
He also became a thorn in my side
I also hate myself now
But I just want
Just want to be selfish for once
can be your first choice
I'm waiting for you
Qi Zheng
wait for me
castle lord
The city lord is gone
This is a letter from the city lord to you
He said you probably won't go back
Suyin, please go back and rest first.
Fan Yun
Actually I want to ask you
Would you like to go with me?
But I know your answer
I know
You're not unwilling
It's impossible
Now all the men in the Zheng family are gone
Zheng Xi alone
We have to face a huge Jingcheng city
Just leave Tian Xing behind
I'm afraid it's not enough to cope with
I know you
I definitely want to stay in Jingcheng
Wait until everything works out before leaving
I know all this
But Fan Yun
I'm willing to wait for you
Waiting for you not only to take me
Treated as a city lord
Waiting for the day you come back to me
No matter that day
will it come
Don’t you think my embroidery looks ugly?
I mean
Embroidery is very special
Why are you still here?
Didn't you promise me today
Want to walk around?
you saw
I was transferred
You can change shifts only when you apply
Shen Shi
Do you know what day it is today?
You obviously promised me
How come you don't mean what you say?
in your heart
today is your day
See you in Shenshi
The year is approaching
The city guard is going back to Ling'an to report on his duties.
Lord Arita Xing stayed in Jingcheng
Just feel free to go to Ling'an
You are with him
I'm definitely relieved
My Lords
Liu Mu is with me all the way
Just don't worry
Please come back quickly
Daddy Gao Ran
You are here too
I'm here to ask questions
Return to Ling'an
Why don't you go home first to tell daddy you're safe?
Go back to the house first
Do you know that this dad feels very sad?
daddy
Okay, I'm just coaxing you to play.
Now I'm an official
Of course, you have to meet the city lord first
Go home later
Little whirlwind
Do you still remember me?
haven't seen you for a long time
Little Stick King
I am coming
How good is your health?
good
daddy
please uncle
Let’s all have another drink together
OK OK
Let me tell you
Remember me back then
When I was your age
There is Lao Lu
And Lao Zheng
The First Lord takes us
Galloping on the battlefield
Conquests in the north and south
Never ambiguous
drink
Slow down, slow down, slow down
Let go
Eat more
Come, come, come
Walk and eat more
What are you doing?
We haven't had enough to drink yet
Come back and drink again
Come and eat food
Come, come, come
Come and have a bite
Mr. Lu
When did you come here?
Such good delicacies
How could I be so cold-shouldered?
Yes, he is a foodie
Come
Old Zheng
This is what Ninetowns looks like today
It's what you want to see
Come
Let's have a drink together
try this
Eat more, come on, come on
Eat more
When will you let Fan Yun
hold a ceremony
Do you officially recognize me as your uncle?
Just that much alcohol
And drink wherever you go
Let me say something
Although this sentence comes a little late
Fan Yunwo
Back from Jingcheng safely
thank you all
Thoughts about Fan Yun
Come, come, come
Let's have a drink together
As expected, women are not inferior to men.
Fan Yun
That guy Yan Jiang is probably lost again.
or
Help me find it
I go
look at you
Mr. Zhao keeps talking to me about those days
I really can't get away
All right
Right
It’s easy to get lost in the Phoenix Forest on a snowy night
Be careful yourself
knew
The bookshelves in Qilin Pavilion are like a maze
Fan Yunwo
who calls me
You heard me wrong. Go quickly.
That's good
Then help me greet everyone properly
OK, OK, you go
I
I originally thought
I won’t see you until tomorrow’s morning meeting
I didn't expect you to be here
i every night
Everybody will come here
Qi Zheng
I'm back
Fan Yun
I finally waited for you
I have something to give you
What is it?