Just be obedient
I won't hurt you
Go quickly
Fourth Miss
The fourth lady was frightened.
but
There have been a lot of guests coming and going in the house recently
Please, miss, please stop wandering around.
So as not to disturb the lady
knew
Go down
good
Miss offended
Subordinates resign
Walk
You are the fourth lady of the Zheng family
That wiping forehead
Can you give it back to me?
I
The Zheng family took something they shouldn’t have taken.
I just want to get it back
thank you
Go-getter
do you recognize this sword
People of the same family
official
I'm not a bad person
It's just that your eldest brother did something evil
so i
Big brother acts recklessly
Sooner or later, the Zheng family will be harmed
Thank you very much today
There will be a chance someday
I will definitely repay you this kindness.
This dancer danced one song after another
The Zheng family is so grand
It really makes Fan Yun
Feeling flattered
But wine
But I didn’t drink a sip.
What's the matter, eldest son?
Why don't you just say it?
Today I want to take the opportunity to have a feast
apologize to you
I was too cautious before
Mistaken Fan Chengshou as a thief
If any offense
Please forgive me
From today on
Ronghui of the Zheng family
I still have to rely on adults.
Young Master is joking
Please also invite the eldest son
At the future city defense ceremony
Lots of support
good
Fan Chengshou is indeed a hero among girls.
Worthy of being the person appointed by the city lord
Thanks for the promotion
this cup
Instead, I respect the eldest son.
stop
Don't move
Don't run
stop
This way
Chase faster
Don't run
Come
Fan Chengshou
I even brought someone here
Right now in the backyard
Capture alive
presumptuous
transportation matters
Isn’t it always the third child who is in charge?
bring it to home
What does he want to do?
or
I'll ask the Third Young Master again.
Need not
lock him up
Let him reflect and reflect
The eldest son today
Is there anything else urgent?
That's not as good as
Let’s meet up another day
I thought Fan Chengshou came alone this time
Unexpectedly, a distinguished guest was left behind in the courtyard.
The words of the eldest son
What does it mean?
You are the direct daughter of the Fan family
I am the grandson of Zheng’s parents
You and I are a match made in heaven
if you marry me
Your friends are my friends
I will never neglect
The idea of ​​the eldest son is quite novel.
Don't you have any scruples at all?
Is it your brotherhood?
Anyway, they are marrying into the Zheng family.
Who should I marry?
What if
I don't want to
this matter
It's not up to you
On the sleeve of the dancer just now
There are drugs
Daughter of the Fan family
Plus Jingcheng City Guards
i married you
Not only can you control the entire Jingcheng
We can also have the support of the Fan family
Let’s just cook the rice today
I guess the Fan family
You won’t deny me as your son-in-law, right?
Shameless
Don't run, stop
stop
What did you do to Fan Yun?
don’t worry
The city guard and the Zheng family
We'll be a family soon
today
I have to wrong you first
Take it
Today's castle guard
It looks really charming.
you say
after today
How will the world preach about us?
I would like to entertain the city guard as a landowner.
Drinking for three rounds
We talked happily and pleased each other
It’s a good story, right?
eldest son
you
Come closer to me
You
It's just a dream
Let go
Then I still have to dream
Don't come here
you let me go you let me go
let me go
Second Young Master Zheng
Zheng Laoer, what are you doing?
Anyone who dares to touch me
Aren’t you married yet?
If you're not married, it doesn't count.
Big brother
If you live enough
I can send you off in person
threaten me
Someone is coming
what do you want to do
I tell you
If you dare to touch me
Zheng family members and grandfather
I won't forgive you
if you kill me
You are brother-killer
You can't be the head of the Zheng family either.
I was wrong
Brother is wrong
please
don't kill me
Big brother
Just know you're wrong
don't want
you go away
Don't come here
Don't come here, don't come here
No, please go away quickly
Don't be afraid
it's me
Zheng
Second Young Master Zheng
You haven't worn off the medicine yet
Don't move
Today's events
thanks to you
Thank you
Second Young Master Zheng
Although Zheng Jin’s medicine is addictive,
But essentially
But it's more harmful to the body than other drugs
so
You need to take a good rest
no
I have to go back
Why
because
Because Gao Ran
Still waiting for me
Are you talking about Qi Zheng?
you you
how did you know
wrong
What happened to Qi Zheng?
Is he in any danger?
where am i
where is this
This is the Zheng family dungeon
Who is talking?
who are you
Come here and get me out
come over
You are the third son of the Zheng family
Why are you locked up here?
You don't have to treat me like this
What about me?
Although he is the third son of the Zheng family
But I'm not interested in the affairs of the sect leader
What about Fan Chengshou?
No hostility
I'm locked up here
It was purely an accident
That being the case
Still don’t think of a way out
You don't have to worry about this
With the intelligence of my fourth sister
I'm sure you'll find it right away
Then get me out
Fourth Miss
Second Young Master Zheng
Please send me out
in my eyes
Your safety is most important
No one else has anything to do with me
soon after
It's our wedding
as long as you live here
Whatever you need, I will prepare it for you
Everything will be discussed after the wedding
what are you talking about
Didn't you tell me that at first?
After entering the city
Will you never force me?
Don't look so gloomy
You need to recuperate now
Wait for it to be raised
As long as you don't leave here
you can move around
Zheng Shi
You want to put me under house arrest
It's to protect you
I really misjudged you
Zheng Shi you
Strange to say
Look carefully
There's nothing special about you
so common
But I still like it so much
I'm like this
It must be called true love
Do you have to leave me here?
But why is true love so painful?
If all the love in this world
It would be great if everything goes as everyone wishes
Are you listening to me?
You care about him so much
yes
I'll solve his problem
She climbed up the tree to pick flowers
Want to drive away the birds in the trees
As a result, one accidentally fell into the water.
How could you be so stupid?
Have you called the doctor for diagnosis and treatment?
She insisted that she didn't need it
But luckily it's just the wind and cold
Nothing serious
only
when she was sleeping
Keep saying your name
Wei Ying
Did you see it?
See it
you woke up
You are here
Why do I always have trouble with two birds?
They treat emotions as a child's play
I don't like
What a joke
They always fly here all of a sudden
Fly there in a moment
I never want to stay on a tree
That's because you don't understand it
misunderstanding about it
But it always flies so high
How do I have the chance to understand it?
Maybe actually
It has realized it itself
I've found it myself
A big tree that wants to build a nest
But I never dared to say it
this
It's a recipe I used to ask around.
sachet made of
you put it on
To prevent rash
You to the city lord
It’s also very thoughtful.
Very good
I'm not that bird
I'm only interested in one person
Miss
Why are you here?
Miss, except for those close to me
Others ignore it
Right, right, right
Fourth Miss
Could it be that you are here to find
Third Young Master's
The third young master has disappeared since yesterday.
Even the little one can't find him
I don't know where he went.
Qi Zheng
You must not get into trouble
The second young master is not here
Miss please come back
Miss
Second brother
you
Who are you
This is our fourth lady
Miss Zheng Si
Second sister-in-law
The mute lady talked a lot today
I'm not your second sister-in-law
I am
I
Anyway, for a while and a half
I can't explain it to you clearly
Anyway, she’s not your second sister-in-law
Where is my second brother?
Looking for someone
Maybe you went to your elder brother's place to find someone.
feature
special
Could it be that Miss Zheng Si
You can also help me find it together
He probably
so high
Wearing headband and wiping forehead
Carry sword
Go-getter
right
It's that go-getter sword
Why is everyone looking for someone these days?
Everybody is missing
Even my third brother is missing.
Miss Zheng Si
follow me
good
Sir Fan Yun cannot go out
this
This is also the meaning of the second young master
right
are you sure
It seems
It's time for you to come in handy
If you hand over Gao Ran
This sect leader's ring is yours.
Gao Ran is so important
Worthy of a suzerain ring
How do I know if you are lying?
How to know
Is this ring real?
If you don't believe it
You don’t have to
But I'm afraid in the future
There will be no chance to get it again
You do it for an outsider
Are you willing to hand over something so important?
Only those who are stuck in their ways
That's why you care so much
Is it an insider or an outsider?
for me
Just see if it’s worth it
You wait
My elder brother wants to arrest you
So
Never let your elder brother discover me
Otherwise it will be troublesome
Reckless and selfish
As soon as Mr. Zheng left
position of suzerain
Everyone is coveting it
metropolitan
It should be a burden
rather than fighting for
Miss Zheng Si
So where are we going now?
woodshed
The eldest son please
Watch out for steps
Slow down, slow down
eldest son
Both of them were very obedient.
I have no intention of coming out at all.
but
Let's lock the third young master here
If the master knew
Will you be blamed?
Make you talk too much
yes yes yes
Children shouldn't talk nonsense
I didn’t expect your kid to be at Zheng Laoer’s place
It's quite a treat
This time you are lucky
Fall into my hands next time
But not so lucky
tell me quickly
What did you do to Fan Yun?
Big brother big brother big brother
etc.
Can't enlarge bro
Can't put it down
You are teaching me how to do things
Don't dare
I just want to tell you something
You can decide after listening to it
You useless piece of shit
I don't want to talk to you anymore
what do you have to say
Go tell grandpa
Wait until the old man comes back and tell him yourself
Big brother
I know it's wrong
Give me another chance
OK
I beg you, brother
open the door
yes
Thank you bro
What about me?
You mean this woodshed?
There is also the use of relating to people.
Used to disguise an underground cell
You wait here for me to go
I'll go with you
It would be inconvenient for you to go
I'll just go
take this opportunity
I'm going to explore this place too.
Thank you
I can't bear it anymore
I'll do it first out of respect.
Where is the third brother?
Was there just now
After being taken away by Zheng Jin
Never came back again
You want to let me out
too dirty
Thank you
take off
Thanks again
Where is this exit?
If you don't say anything, I'm leaving.
This way
The exit is over here
Then go this way
That's not right
It's empty here
There should be an agency
Let's look for it
Sure enough, there is a secret passage
how did you find it
I
I pressed it accidentally
How do you know there is a secret passage in this place?
If there is only one entrance to this private cell,
The southeast wind should always be blowing underground
But you still remember
Just now when the jailer was eating
Their fireworks are blowing southwest
This proves
If there is a passage on the other side
Only then will there be wind
Let's go in and have a look
gunpowder
Everything here is actually gunpowder
No wonder Liu Mu can’t find it
That's not right
But that doesn’t make sense either.
Who hid all the gunpowder at home?
Who would do this?
Zheng family
Your third brother
Why are you being held here?
Impossible
Now is not the time to distinguish authenticity
We still have to get rid of these gunpowder first
Dispose of it first
Otherwise, who will use them later?
The consequences will be unimaginable
What do you want to do?
Of course for this batch of gunpowder
Go to the fire
Eat more
long distance
You are all heroes
Come
master
Sir, what's wrong with you?
Sudden palpitations
Probably a little tired
or
Let's go in and have a rest.
Just right here
Second Young Master Zheng
Why are you here?
He is
What happened to him
he
Who is there
Go quickly
Second Young Master Zheng
What the hell is going on?
He seems to be the second son
Second Young Master
The eldest son was killed
Kill the eldest son
everyone
Let me hunt down the second young master.
yes
Where to chase
Why are you there?
I didn’t kill brother
When I arrived, the person was already dead.
Then why are you running?
why did you just
Why don't you explain it clearly to them?
do you believe me
Of course I believe it
according to your personality
kill someone
Will definitely admit it
but i believe
does not mean
They will also believe you
So why should I explain to them
As long as you believe in me, that's enough
Who is it?
Kill Zheng Jin?
I already told him
Don't be self-righteous
There are many people who want to kill him
But you can do it in the Zheng Mansion
Not much really
do you mean
He's from the Zheng family
If there is a ghost in the Zheng family
The truth will naturally surface
Go back and stay with me honestly
Don't run around
Miss Zheng Si
I wonder if there are homing pigeons in the house?
The castle guard's house caught fire
I keep those pigeons
I'll get it
Trouble
Miss Zheng Si
Could you please help me deliver this letter?
Right
When you said you came to save me
Fan Yun is waiting outside the door
Maybe he hid after hearing the noise.
Looks like I have to go find her
this kindness
I will return it to you another day
It's good to owe it
Go a little further in
Wouldn't it be nice if you just pretended I didn't exist?
Who are you
Why did you make yourself like this?
What do you know
I'm so tall and mighty
It's too bright there
It's more hidden here
go
at the appropriate time
hurry up
who
who is outside
Fan Yun
Qi Zheng
Qi Zheng Fan Yun
are you okay
I'm fine
Very good
I finally see you
how did you get in
I
Miss Zheng Si
Okay, let's go quickly
Come on, let's go quickly
It’s really endless
No one is allowed to rest in the middle of the night
brothers
Come, come, come
Come and lend a hand
come to help
Be quick and easy
You can go to bed after unloading this trip
Go to bed early after finishing
One or two
Slow down, slow down, slow down
I said
have you found
This time it's a little heavier than before.
All the same goods
What is sinking or not?
I think you just want to be lazy
Who wants to be lazy
It just takes a little more effort than before
You said so many weapons have come in recently?
Is a war about to begin?
Shut up and don't ask
What does the superior want us to do?
Let's do whatever
The less you know, the longer you live.
Use force
Finally done
brothers
go back to sleep
Slow down
OMG
So much gunpowder
What do they want to do?
master
pack your luggage
Return to Jingcheng
yes
Is this face so worthy of your scrutiny?
Appearances and everything are just clouds
like me
A person who can see the essence through phenomena
As long as I have you in my heart
I see every stone is you
You have such beautiful dimples
You can only smile at me from now on
lord of the castle lord of the castle
castle lord
Have I seen it or not?
Before the city lord left,
I didn’t say what should be done.
If we had known we would have known
I'm dead
Your sister, go ahead
You go, I won’t go
I won't go
You two are a little too loud, right?
castle lord
I have something important to report
Take a look
hoarding arms
this
No wonder that Zheng Tao is so confident
With this batch of arms
The Zheng family is really
Advance, attack, retreat and defend
This Zheng family is really a dragon's pond and a tiger's den.
It seems that Jingcheng will no longer be peaceful.
Lord Wei
Lord Yan
Zai Zai
I issue orders on behalf of the city lord
You two lead the whole family's army
Go to Jingcheng immediately
Bring siege weapons
Just stationed outside Jingcheng and on standby.
Never act rashly
Notify Lord Fan Qi
We'll prepare now
Departure today
Work harder
Be sure to get to Jingcheng tonight
master
According to servants
When the eldest son was killed
I met the second young master and left in a hurry
grandfather
absolutely true
I saw the second brother kill the eldest brother with my own eyes
He also hurt me
I fight to the death
Only then did I protect this ring.
grandfather
You are back this time
But I must avenge my elder brother.
The eldest brother was killed
The position of sect leader has fallen into the hands of Zheng Shi
my generation
There's nothing that can compete with it
if
If Xian Er could have the talent of his elder brother
I'll definitely be able to take care of my grandfather's worries
master
No way
Let the man who killed his brother
Winning the position of suzerain
Third Young Master, don’t belittle yourself.
After all, you are my grandson
On talent
I think you are no worse than others
grandfather
I would like to be your blade
Seize the position of suzerain for you
Comfort my elder brother’s spirit in heaven
Just ask for grandfather
Give Xian'er a chance
Jin'er was killed
Does anyone know
When the eldest son was killed
The master hasn't come back yet
I'm worried that the Zheng family is leaderless
make the fur fly
Message has been blocked
No one will leak it out
Send news to all the clan members
Just say I'm back
Overlord election
Mentioned to tomorrow
in addition
Block the city gate immediately
before the election
Suspicious persons are not allowed in or out
Put all your energy into it
yes
I want to make these nine cities
Jingcheng is gone forever
I see everyone is busy during this time
I'm home alone with nothing to do
So I made some Ling’an’s little wontons
Everyone, eat it while it's hot
Try it now
Eat more
Fourth Miss
are you
I can't get used to it.
basic sound
Do you still have the pasta you made for me last time?
have
You try this
Let me have one too
How about it
That is to say
In the Zheng family
Just a small batch of munitions
A large part of what's left
All outside Jingcheng
Too many to be frightened
Occupies most of the mountain
Just exploded
The whole Jingcheng will be lost.
Liu Mu
You follow me
Go out to the city again
That batch of arms can't stay there.
Must be eradicated
no problem
castle lord
I'm with you
You'd better stay
Now you are the city guard of Jingcheng
You should stay in Jingcheng
Things outside the city
Just leave it to me
Then I'll go with you
I'm here
It will be more convenient for you to go out of the city
OK
Na Suyin and Tian Xing
Just stay with you
There is also a care
Just leave it to me without any worries
Then you
Be careful
be safe
The same to you
let's go let's go
Fan Yun
Zheng Zhengshi
you
Why are you here?
Didn’t you say you only walked around the yard?
But this Jingcheng
Where else?
It's not your yard
this
you
you are hurt
No problem