He graduated in psychology from Harvard.
He messes with your head
until you believe you're special.
Can you not go home
and stay at my condo for one night?
but I have a psychology quiz tomorrow.
Then why don't I tutor you?
You know,
I graduated in psychology from Harvard.
Actually, I think we should study
something else first.
Aren't you dating him?
How could you not know
all the things he's done?
That's enough.
Why does everyone keep acting like
he's some horrible person?
If you want to know
what kind of person P'Jane really is,
try calling this number.
What do you want to ask for?
Just tell me.
Come here! Let go of me!
Let go!
Champ! Let go of me!
Come here! Let go of me!
Let go!
I said let go!
You'll never get away from me!
Go!
Why the hell are you doing this to me?!
Huh? Shut up!!
Who is that?
That's Champ.
Jui's ex-boyfriend.
I thought they broke up?
Why are they getting involved again?
That's scary.
Please let me go!
Please!!
Ow!
You bastard!!
Shut the fuck up!
Hey!
Ah! I'm sorry.
Stay away from me!
Just leave me alone! Hey.
Jane. Hey.
Don't hurt me. Hey!
That's enough!
Enough!
Calm down!
Jui, are you okay?
This is none of your business.
Fuck off.
Come on!
Hey!
Stop!
Look.
The reason I'm like this
is because of P'Jane!
Ouch!
Come on.
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
Ooh
I've been waiting for you for so long.
What are you doing?
I'm making dinner for you.
But..
Isn't today just an ordinary day?
Well, I love you every day.
Go sit down and wait.
Just give me a minute.
P'Jane, do you know about Jui?
What about Jui?
Jui was abused by her ex-boyfriend.
Really?
She had it coming.
Go ahead and try it.
It's so tender it melts in your mouth.
How is it?
It's really delicious.
Really?
But your face says otherwise.
Why do you think Jui deserved to be hurt?
Why do you only want to talk about this?
Jui said the reason her ex hurt her was
because of you.
Just answer me honestly.
Were you involved in this or not?
Jui once came to ask for a contract.
She wanted me to protect her
from that ex-boyfriend.
But I simply refused the contract.
Then she got hurt.
That's all.
I didn't do anything.
Then why didn't you help her?
Jui was beaten because she was cheating.
And she also stole money from her ex.
She does this to everyone.
Sooner or later,
something like this was bound to happen.
She brought it on herself.
But all you do is interrogate me.
As if I'm the one at fault.
I thought you were different from everyone else.
That you wouldn't believe what others say.
And that you wouldn't look at me that way.
I'm sorry.
Let's keep eating.
I just want to ask you one thing.
You're not hiding anything more from me, right?
What do you mean by hiding?
If I just haven't told you yet,
does that count as hiding something from you?
Hmm?
P'Jane.
What are you doing?
P'Jane, don't.
P'Jane.
I haven't showered yet.
Neither have you.
Go take a shower first.
Then I'll let you hug me.
Fine.
Then I'll go shower first.
What are you doing?
P'Jane.
Don't hug me yet.
Hmm?
I haven't showered yet.
Then I'll go to the bathroom first.
(Thanapat Phibulosot)
(Ask me a favor?)
(066 666 666)
If you want to know what P'Jane is really like,
try calling this number.
Jet, Jet?
Watch the shop for me for a minute.
What is it?
I'm going to dance practice.
I know.
Let me borrow your phone.
Just for a second.
I already told you.
I made plans with my friends.
Come on.
You've asked me for help so many times.
And I've always helped you.
I'm only asking for this one favor.
Just a minute.
Hurry up then.
Sigh.
(Ask me a favor)
(066 666 666)
Hello?
don't be scared.
What do you want?
Just tell me.
Hello?
(Blocked Contact)
Three plates, man!
I'm still not full after three!
Damn!
It's like being on my period or something.
But I can't menstrate.
Jane?
Are you even listening to me?
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
You look pale as a corpse.
Nothing.
Sigh.
Looks like it's time for your person.
People like me
have to walk away.
Hello.
Good luck, see you around.
What do you want to eat tonight?
I don't think I'll eat.
I'm not hungry yet.
Then just keep me company.
Or if you're tired of the usual place,
we can try somewhere new.
I want to get home early.
I have a report to finish.
Then let's do it together.
I can help you again.
But this time I want to do it myself.
You've helped me enough already.
Come on.
We're only going to be apart for one day.
I was just taking a leaf out of your hair.
Fine then.
We'll see each other again tomorrow.
Ok.
Bye-bye.
I'll never get used to how fast you drive.
You're probably more used to supercars
than big bikes now.
I...
got in touch with someone
who knows about P'Jane's background for you.
But he only wants to talk to you privately.
P'Dan.
You're P'Dan from Computer Engineering, right?
We used to play football together.
Let's get straight to the point.
Have you tried calling
the number on Jane's business card yet?
He has eyes and ears everywhere.
Connections everywhere.
But don't worry.
This place is safe.
I've already checked.
So...
what do you know about him?
Well...
he's twenty-seven years old.
He studied Psychology and Law at Harvard.
Then he came here for another bachelor's degree.
Smart.
Excellent student.
But there have always been strange rumors.
That if you ask and get something from him
but if you break the agreement,
you'll be punished.
What a load of..
The truth is, he never graduated in Law.
He got expelled from Harvard first.
P'Jane got expelled?
Harvard student expelled
for building an underground power network on campus.
That's P'Jane?
After Harvard kicked him out,
he came here and did the same thing.
He uses his knowledge of psychology
to make it easier to manipulate people.
So this isn't the first place?
From what I've heard,
he does this everywhere he goes.
He's been doing it since high school.
If P'Jane is really doing that here,
and you have evidence,
why don't you report him to the university?
That's P'Jane.
And...
our university president.
I don't know
what favor the president asked from him,
but he's definitely not getting expelled.
Can we tell anyone else?
The police?
Who knows?
Maybe the police owe him favors too.
And people who break the contract..
People who break the favor rules with P'Jane
what happens to them?
Jane, what do you think is the most important
thing in your life?
The thing you absolutely don't want to lose.
My family.
The reason everyone is afraid of Jane
is because he likes to target
the things people treasure most.
So...
You've experienced it too?
If nobody stops him,
he'll keep destroying other people's lives.
That's why
I've been looking for a way to take him down.
But I don't get it.
What does this have to do with me?
I don't have any power.
He likes luring people into his trap.
Making them indebted to him.
Or telling them that they're special.
That he can make their dreams
really come true.
Has he ever said anything like that to you?
Jane, you're far more special than I realized.
More special than anyone I've ever met.
(Congratulations to the new Student President)
(Toy Rattawit Meechai)
I also have no clue
why he's taken such an interest in you.
But I think he's been manipulating you.
Just like he does with everyone else.
Stay away from him.
I don't want to see you
get hurt later.
But if you still don't believe me,
next time he does something
and doesn't tell you about it,
try following him and see for yourself.
He might be carrying out a favor.
(Big Jane: See you tomorrow.)
(Big Jane: What are you doing, Jane?)
We've only been apart for one night.
I miss you already.
What are you doing, P'Jane?
P'Jane.
P'Jane!
I'm not in the mood.
Why?
What are you still suspicious of?
I've answered all your questions.
Why don't you trust me?
Why did you approach me in the first place?
I already told you.
Because you're special.
He likes luring people into his trap.
Or telling them that they're special.
You say that to everyone
who makes a contract with you, don't you?
Do you know something?
I hate being manipulated more than anything.
I've never manipulated you.
You should answer that call.
I'll come back later.
Hello?
I told you not to call me.
I forgot.
I'm really grateful.
Thank you so much.
If there's ever anything you want me to do,
just let me know.
What do you want me to do?
Whatever you want me to do,
just tell me.
Come here, Jane.
Why don't you tell him
what I did for you?
Well...
my house burned down.
And...
I practically lost everything.
So I came to ask P'Jane
for help.
Then P'Jane...
P'Jane raised money
from the Student Council.
So I could continue my studies.
Tomorrow this story will be published
on our university's news website.
They just won't mention that P'Jane helped me.
You can go now.
Next time, just send me a message to thank me.
No need to arrange a meeting like this.
Of course.
Thank you.
I really don't get it.
If you're using your network to do good things like this,
then why does everyone keep saying
that you're a terrible person?
Because of prejudice.
I think the person who is manipulating you
isn't me
but I think it's someone who hates me.
This key.
I've never given it to anyone before.
It's a symbol of my trust.
And a promise.
That you can ask me anything.
And I'll answer everything
you want to know.
Is there still anything you're suspicious about?
Do you..
really love me?
Of course I do.
The Sakwarakul family,
owners of Trust Communication
and ShopChill E-Commerce,
have denied reports of a management reshuffle.
Mr. Chalerm Sakwarakul,
the current CEO, will remain in his position.
And his business empire continues to stand strong.
How's it going?
A lot of customers lately?
Argh.
Not really.
Only you and Put show up.
When is your bike gonna break down?
Oh!
So you can finally buy a new one from me.
It's gonna be hard. There's someone waiting for you.
There, someone's waiting.
Jane.
How'd you come here?
I asked Put.
Do you need something from me?
I want to know about Tee.
You know what
happened to him, right?
Then why don't we go ask him ourselves?
(Restricted Area: No Entry)
I'll wait outside.
You go in alone.
(Restricted Area: No Entry)
What's up?
Haven't seen you in ages.
Hey.
What happened to you?
Was it P'Jane?
Why?
Did he send you here?
He already got me thrown in prison.
What else does he want from me?
Tee.
Calm down first.
I just want to ask you something.
You really asked P'Jane
to make you Student Council President, right?
But if you had a contract with him,
why did he suddenly have you sent to prison?
Because one of God Jane's people
wanted my position.
The guy named Toy?
Yeah.
Another one of his lackeys.
I refused to give up my position.
So he kicked me out.
By having me thrown in here.
Do you know someone named Jui?
Her ex came looking for her.
But Jui said it was P'Jane's doing.
What did you just say?
Champ dragged her back?
No wonder she never came to bail me out.
So you're the guy Jui was cheating with?
She told me she'd already broken up with Champ.
How much does that bastard God Jane hate me?
He's definitely trying to stop me from getting bail.
What's up, Put?
I brought Jane to see Tee.
So did you really embezzle money
from the Student Council?
I did so much for the university.
I deserved some compensation.
But if you hadn't stolen money from the university
or from the volunteer camp funds,
you wouldn't be in here.
What the hell is your problem?
Why are you defending him?
P'Jane is my boyfriend.
Have you lost your mind?
But I'm not defending him
because he's my boyfriend.
From what I've heard,
both you and Jui were in the wrong.
Yet you're blaming someone else.
And your P'Jane??
Is he really that great?
Huh?
You know the Sakwarakul family, right?
The ones who own the mobile network company.
Yeah.
P'Jane belongs to that family.
His surname is Plakorn.
That's someone else's surname.
But in reality,
P'Jane is the eldest son of that family.
Do you understand now
why God Jane has been pulling the strings
behind the university network?
Because he doesn't want anything
to damage that family's reputation.
Listen to me.
That bastard God Jane
is no different from a mafia boss.
Stay away from him.
He'll use you until you're no longer useful.
Then he'll throw you away.
Just like he threw me away!!
(Restricted Area: No Entry)
Jane.
Are you okay?
Put called me.
He said P'Jane asked to clear things up.
Why does P'Jane want to clear things up with him?
He already knows
that Put brought you to see me.
So now he's suspicious of him.
I was careless.
I didn't think he'd catch on so quickly.
Where did P'Jane ask him to meet?
Take me there.
Excuse me.
Are you a member here?
Only members are allowed inside.
Put isn't answering.
I guess they're still talking.
I already have an appointment with P'Jane.
All set, sir.
Wait.
Only people with a card may enter.
Follow me inside.
I'll go by myself.
Be careful.
Alright.
Wait here.
If someone comes out,
then you can go in.
Why are you interfering between me and Jane?
Jane asked me to.
He wanted to know about you.
And why was it your business
to take Jane to see Dan?
Stop staying silent and say something.
I...
I want to make a blood pact with you.
I want to ask
that you leave Jane alone.
And what are you offering in exchange?
You can ask anything of me.
I'd even trade my life.
Your life isn't worth that much, Put.
Why?
Do you like Jane?
And what about you?
Do you like him or are you just using him?
If you're getting involved with him
without really caring about him,
then I'll be the one
to take Jane out of your life myself.
Who do you think you are
to order me around?
You do know,
what someone like me
is capable of doing to you, right?
Stop!
Jane.
Don't do anything to Put.
Stay back.
I can't believe this.
Jane, listen to me first.
Didn't you say you had nothing to hide?
I know everything about Jui and Tee now.
Who do you think you are
to control other people's lives however you want?
Including mine.
Listen.
I've never controlled your life.
That's enough.
I've been trying to protect you.
I've been trying to trust you all this time.
But all you've done is keep hiding things from me.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I hate myself whenever I'm around you.
Let's stop seeing each other, P'Jane.
I don't want to see your face anymore.
You're such a liar.
Wasn't this necklace supposed to be a promise
that you'd always tell me the truth?
Well??
I never should've dated a piece of shit like you!!
A piece of shit?
What have I ever done that's so shitty?
Have you ever actually seen me
do any of the awful things
those people accuse me of?
They came to me for help.
And then they broke their promises.
So who's really the piece of shit?
In the end, you're no different from everyone else.
I'm sure
that one day, you'll be like them.
You..
will be the one crawling back
to ask me for something.
Stop it, Jane!
Come with me.
Listen to me.
I will never ask you for anything.
Fuck!
This is P'Dan.
He's a senior at my university.
Jane.
Give me your hand.
Are you interested in me?
Why are you here?
You're not right for Jane at all!
Hey! I've already transferred the money.
It's mine now.
Are you okay?
Ow!
Are you sure that you don't feel anything?
If you're just here to cause trouble,
then you should leave.
Jet!
What happened?
Is that Jet?
Jet's older brother.
I'm going to break that bastard Jet's fingers.
One finger a day.
Argh!
Ugh!
You walk in with a warning sign
Just one look and already falling for you
My friends tell me not to cross that line
But I’m already out of time
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You can paint me with all your darkest sides
And I’d still wear them like they’re paradise
If this love is a perfect crime
Then I’m guilty for life
You tell me,
don’t be too emotional that’s rule no. 1
I’d give up everything to be your only one
Ooh
You’re the only one
I know the truth, I taste the sin
It’s wrong but I don’t want it to be true
I’m losing all my discipline
You’re all I’m thinking of
and I’m breaking all the rules
just because…
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I know you’re dangerous
If it burns, let it burn me alive
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line
You’re a red flag but I’m colorblind
I’d give up anything for you
Even if it burns, I'm willing to melt away
I can't hold myself back, I’d cross every line