(Previously)
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ to you ♪
Lion, what are you doing here?
No one suits me better than you.
Veha, I'm sorry.
Will you give me a chance
to make things right?
You left the party without telling me.
You looked so caught up in the moment.
Who'd want to marry
someone who makes you cry?
You still have a chance.
Let's be boyfriends.
You really didn't have to walk me up.
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Please?
Not yet. Let's take it slow.
Take it slow?
We already slept together.
Sex from sadness doesn't count.
Okay.
What are we now?
Hmm… We're in the talking stage.
Just the talking stage?
Does that mean you'll talk to
a few other people too?
Hey, what kind of person do you think I am?
I talk to one person at a time.
I'm not like Lion.
Stop talking about him.
That's why I suggested
we get to know each other first.
I don't want to trust
anyone too easily again.
I'm scared of being disappointed.
Don't compare me to that guy.
I might not be as rich as him,
but my sincerity is
definitely Top 5 in Asia.
Be patient.
I'm not that easy.
Bye now.
I'll go jerk off while I wait.
Why are you so savage?
Go.
I bet you like it.
TOTO AND KANIT
ARE NOW BOYFRIENDS.
"A Dog and A Plane"
(Episode 7)
3 MONTHS LATER
Nit.
Mm.
Hmm? Can I get 5 more minutes?
You've been staying over at my house
a lot lately.
Well, your house is homey and cozy.
Homey, and also horny?
Hmm… no!
If it's so cozy, why don't you
change your official address to mine?
Hey, isn't that too soon?
No.
I'm an impatient teenager. I want to
cuddle my boyfriend every morning.
Enough.
We just started dating,
so of course you're all over me like this.
Pretty soon, you'll get bored.
I've been through all of it.
I know the steps.
I don't know what steps
you've been through, but here's mine.
Once I'm into someone,
I make them feel more loved every day.
Can we redo last night?
Stop it. Let's take a break.
Come on.
You're dating a rescuer.
You always have to be ready.
Ready for what?
Ready for action.
You want it?
I'm ready for action.
I'm ready.
Bring it.
Hey, bro!
Oh.
Hey!
- Lew!
- Gosh!
The food is in the fridge.
Go heat it up yourself.
Yeah, sorry.
There's a kid in your house.
It's not safe here.
Hey.
Let's have some morning fun.
No!
Hey!
Jerk off!
Whoa.
You cooked a lot today.
How could I not?
I hope you don't mind me joining you.
Let me join too,
since we're leaving together anyway.
Where are you going?
Today we're doing a charity event
at a children's foundation.
Boss Seng hosts it every year.
Do you want to come with us?
The more the merrier.
The kids will be happy.
You two can make
merit together in this life.
So in any future life,
you'll still end up with To as your man.
Sa…
Dhu!
Come on, To.
I was making a wish for you.
You hit me so hard.
He can't go.
He's on flight standby.
But I want to go.
I'm on standby anyway.
If I get called in, I'll deal with it then.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Have some omelette.
Well, a single guy like me
might as well go eat in the toilet.
Are you really going?
Let him go.
THE WINNERS RESCUE FOUNDATION
Come on. I'll help.
Let me put this here.
I didn't think you'd really come
to make merit with the foundation.
Come on. What do you think I am?
Someone who's mean and hates kids?
No.
You look so friendly
to the world's animals.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have mercy
on a dog like me.
Hey, don't play around.
The box is heavy.
Stop it.
Go away, you brat!
What took you so long?
You left me doing this alone for ages.
Doing it alone?
Your boyfriend is helping you.
Shut up. Don't tease me.
We're in the honeymoon phase.
I want to have fun like you do.
Just you wait. Calm down.
Hello.
Hello, Kanit.
Hey.
You two called a truce, right?
If someone's realized their mistake,
why wouldn't I give them a chance
to redeem themselves?
I gave you a chance.
Why wouldn't I give him one too?
Awesome!
Finally, the flight attendant war is over.
The villain is dead.
The two flight attendants and the rescuers
live happily ever after.
Who said anything about being with you?
Yeah, the rescuers around here
are full of themselves.
What?
Let's go.
Stop posing.
Idiot.
Share the milk with your friends, okay?
Yes.
Okay, here you go.
Don't forget to share.
Thank you.
If it's not enough, come and ask for more.
Sure.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
You seem to love kids.
You'll make a great father.
Are you serious or flirting?
Both.
Close your eyes.
Come on, close your eyes.
Mm, my eyes are closed.
Close your eyes and picture this with me.
Mm.
Imagine
we live together in a
cute house by the canal.
It's going to be heartwarming and…
we're going to have kids.
How about two kids?
We'll name the first
one after his papa's job.
Little Siren.
Wee-woo, wee-woo, wee-woo!
Siren, baby.
Then we'll have another one
who we'll name after your job.
Little Jet.
Vroom!
Then our family of four
will receive the Family of the Year award.
What do you think? Wouldn't that be cute?
That's cute,
but I think the award you're going to win
is probably
Most Delusional of the Year.
What?
Don't you like it?
It took me a while to come up with that.
Hey, To.
Hey, Por.
You're here too?
Mm.
I'm here to take you to file your taxes.
Oh, shit. I forgot.
Just kidding.
I've already done it for you.
Thank you so much.
Without you, I'd get massive fines.
Thanks a lot.
Oh.
This is Kanit.
My former greedy creditor.
Now I owe him my heart.
What are you talking about?
Come on. It's true.
Hello.
I'm Por.
I'm an accountant for the foundation.
Your name is Kanit. Does that mean
you like solving math problems?
Oh.
I guess so.
But it's actually my favorite
and strongest subject.
Me too. I love it.
Meanwhile, I suck at every subject,
but one.
Love, right?
I see right through you.
Hey!
You can't be reading
both my mind and my heart,
Mr. Kanit.
I'm going to get back
to handing out the stuff.
Nice to meet you.
See you around. Bye.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can we please
have three more?
That wasn't enough, right?
You want three more?
But there are four in a pack.
What do we do?
One. Two. Three. Four.
There's one extra. What do we do?
Who wants some snacks
from this handsome guy? Hands up!
Let's hear it. Is he handsome?
Yes.
He's handsome like a prince.
He's handsome like Soda Pop.
Geniuses.
Now, is this handsome guy
perfect to be my boyfriend?
No.
Oh.
You guys aren't geniuses anymore.
Alright, here you go.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Are you feeling better now?
Kanit has forgiven you.
Yeah, I'm okay.
It's like I got to cleanse my mind of sin.
It's a result of making merit.
Now both your body and mind are pure.
Good deeds can't erase sins.
But thank you
for inviting me to do something like this.
Your job is actually interesting.
I might join you often.
Really?
But my job isn't exactly cushy
like being a flight attendant.
It's grueling and unpredictable.
It's for someone handsome and tough
like Akki.
What do you take me for?
My job isn't easy.
Looks aren't all it takes.
I've been through a lot.
Being handsome isn't everything.
I'm sorry.
I was just kidding.
To get where you are today,
I know what you've been through.
You ignored me
when I was a pimple-faced kid,
and now you want to claim me?
It's not that easy.
You need to put in a lot more effort.
My effort
is heading straight for you.
I'm going to play with the kids.
Wow.
The sea is beautiful.
Are you taking me on a honeymoon?
Honeymoon? No way.
I'd take you to a better place
for the honeymoon.
Really?
So pretty.
Look at this.
Hey!
So cool.
Your car can do that?
What do you think?
Roomy, nice, and comfy, isn't it?
It's amazing.
I've been in this car since Bangkok
and I'm not sore at all.
Of course not.
You haven't done anything.
Oh? Are you sulking?
I offered to drive, but
you wouldn't let me.
I'm not sulking.
You drive the rescue vehicle all the time.
Let me drive you for a change.
Hey.
Where are you taking me?
I'm scared.
I'm going to have my way with you.
Oh, go ahead. I love it.
Come on. Let's do it.
Hey, once we get closer, I'm taking you
to do something even more thrilling.
What are we going to do?
Just wait. You'll find out soon.
♪ Fly with me, free my heart ♪
♪ I'll take you anywhere, near or far ♪
♪ Coffee or tea… or me tonight? ♪
♪ Could I be the one on your side? ♪
♪ Fly with me, free my heart ♪
♪ Don't be shy, just open your heart ♪
♪ Wanna come aboard, give it a try ♪
♪ Love is gonna take off now ♪
What do you think of that activity
for pool villa teens?
Was it a wild ride?
Oh, it was so wild.
It was so wild I completely lost my cool.
I was screaming the whole time.
Woo! The whole time.
You know what?
The image I built up is completely ruined.
Great.
I think I last went on a banana boat
10 years ago with my family.
When you're with me,
you don't have to put up a front.
It's okay to be scared and scream.
You should feel comfortable
being yourself around your boyfriend.
Wow.
Any more comfortable and I'll start using
the Gu-Mueng pronouns with you.
No.
I don't want you to be rude with me.
I want you to be the
only politeness in my life.
In that case, should I just call you To?
Total couple vibes.
To?
I like that.
- You want that?
- Try calling me that.
Let me call you that.
To, come eat.
Stop treating me like a dog.
To, babe.
I'll call you Nong Nit.
Can I call you Nong Nit?
No.
Nong Nit sounds so tiny and cute.
I want you to call me Kanit.
It's cool.
You know, it's cool.
It has nothing to do
with being big or small.
It's all about the vibe.
Your vibe wants me to take care of you.
Come on. Let's play in the water.
Ahh!
I'm sexy, right?
Hey.
I never thought I'd fall for
a poser like you in my life.
Well, you've already fallen for me.
I'm just going to pounce on you here.
- I can get you on land.
- Don't.
Stop. Don't pounce on me.
I have no energy to fight back.
Here, I applied a serum on you.
I thought we were going to kiss.
Who's kissing?
I'm going to kiss you.
Apply it.
Apply it for me.
Ugh!
Mm.
You look handsome now.
Hello, Mom.
(Are you in Bangkok, Kanit?)
(Are you flying? Your dad and I
are going to Bangkok tomorrow.)
Why are you coming?
(We're going to Nui's graduation.)
(I'm taking your dad to see
a heart doctor in Bangkok too.)
(You're not flying anytime soon, right?)
(Your dad wants to meet
your pilot boyfriend.)
Oh, he and I...
(Just bring him.)
(This is a good opportunity
to win over your dad.)
(Your dad's calling me. I have to go.
(See you tomorrow.)
Your family still doesn't know
about the thick-brow guy?
Yeah. I was going to tell them,
but I didn't get the chance.
I'm afraid I'll disappoint Dad.
He bragged so much to everyone.
Besides, he has a heart condition. Any
little shock could be dangerous for him.
How about this?
If your family hasn't met him yet,
I can pretend to be your captain boyfriend.
Are you crazy?
Who would believe you?
Come on. Why not?
You just have to transform me into a pilot.
Just to get through this period.
Later, when you're ready,
you can tell them the truth.
By that time, they'll already love me.
But it's a very risky plan.
Even if it's risky, we have to try.
I like a challenge.
Like this.
Stop it.
I thought you said you were just going to
lie down and do nothing.
I told you I was going to pounce on you.
The first step is to
train with a real captain.
Becoming a pilot in such a short time
isn't easy.
But in this crash course, I'm going
to teach you how to carry yourself.
Chest out, shoulders back.
Look handsome, cool, and sharp.
Give a friendly smile
to all the passengers.
Let's try that.
Hello.
I'm Captain Toto.
I'm ready to grind to the horizon.
You look like a street punk
doing a party-truck dance.
Come on, let's try again.
You already look handsome.
Can you act as handsome as you look?
Give me one more shot.
Hello.
I'm Captain Toto.
Fly with me, free my heart.
How is it?
Dry.
It's dry, dry, dry, and dry.
How are they any different?
Of course they're different.
Each bottle of wine
comes from a different place.
They taste different.
My dad loves drinking wine.
If you're going to approach him,
you have to study these things.
Can't we talk about herbal liquor instead?
I know all about their health benefits
and how they taste.
“Stomping Horse”
gives you physical strength.
“Never-Drooping” boosts sexual performance
and supports your muscles and tendons.
“King Tiger” helps relieve gas.
“Hundred-Husband Girl”
nourishes female hormones
and boosts your energy.
I'm an expert.
What kind of names are those?
Hey, don't worry.
I get along well with older people.
They all like me.
Look at you.
You used to hate me so much,
but you like me now.
I don't like you now.
Are you sure?
Mm.
Look, my dad might not be
one of those people.
He has very high standards.
Even I have a lot to prove to him.
Then I'll impress your dad.
Even if I have to drink dry wine
until my tongue turns purple,
I'll do it
for my father-in-law.
Father-in-law?
Mm.
Alright then. Cheers.
Cheers.
My name is Akki, the king of snakes.
Fast strikes,
and a venom that pierces right to the core!
Hey, no!
I'm scared.
Oh? I thought you wanted to see
what I do in a day.
Here's one of my tasks.
Catching reptiles.
Do you catch them every day?
Hmm… no.
Some days, it's a fire.
Some days, it's a car accident.
Today, I'm lucky I got to catch a snake
and show you.
Please put that away.
Did I look cool just now?
I can't believe he showed off
catching a snake to his boyfriend.
Oh, no.
We're still flirting.
Oh, but you kinda look like you're dating.
I'm serious about him.
You're this handsome.
I'm not letting you
slip through my fingers.
Are you pursuing me
because I'm handsome?
Come on. Didn't you upgrade yourself
this much for me?
I like you now.
If I weren't good-looking now,
would I even be in your sight?
What's wrong?
I like you outside and in.
Hmm…
What do you want?
Hey.
Veha.
Come catch my snake.
Don't go yet.
Veha!
Hey, congratulations.
You graduated from med school.
Now you can treat your parents.
Just open a clinic, and
you'll make a fortune.
Kana also opened a dental clinic
near our house.
Oh.
Your dad is so proud
that his son is a dentist.
Kanit,
you're a flight attendant, right?
Yes.
He's dating a captain.
He said he'd bring him to meet us,
but I haven't seen him yet.
It was like this at the wedding too.
I didn't see him.
I don't know if he's really dating anyone.
Please wait a bit, Dad.
He's coming today. I said he is.
Let's eat. The food is good.
It's good, right?
Can you eat spicy food, Kana?
A little bit.
Everything here is delicious.
By the way, Kana,
I heard you're dating a big-shot cop.
Yes, we're getting to know each other.
I hope we can share some good news soon.
Wow!
You're faster than your brother.
Who knows when he's going to get married
or if he's even dating anyone.
Hello.
I came straight here as soon as I landed.
I might be late, but here I am, baby.
Hello, sir.
Hello, ma'am.
- Hello.
- I'm Thee.
I'm a captain and Kanit's boyfriend.
Oh, you can speak Southern?
Are you from the South?
No. I can speak it, but not very well.
I practiced specifically
to talk to Kanit's family.
You're amazing.
Definitely a captain.
You have that aura.
I brought some gifts for you all.
JARN KUB KAO
Here, this is for you.
This is for Kana.
Thank you.
And this is for you, ma'am.
This brand is over 200 years old.
It smells luxurious. Just perfect for you.
Thank you so much.
Wow, that's authentic.
It's so expensive back home.
That's not all.
Here's a vintage wine from France.
It's for you, sir.
Oh, I love it.
Would you like to have some wine with me?
Are you serious?
If you are, I'd love to keep you company.
I'm talking about you and Kanit.
Are you serious about him?
I never date anyone casually.
If you're serious about him,
announce your wedding now. Do you dare?
I'm not afraid to do it.
If Kanit is okay, I can propose now.
Hey, my dad is just kidding.
But I'm not.
I've loved you from the moment we met.
I want to fly with you
for the rest of my life.
Will you marry me?
Pued!
Pued has a fishbone stuck in his throat!
Please don't!
Don't shove your finger down your throat.
It'll push the fish bone further down.
Here, have some water. Take it slow.
Slowly.
Small sips.
A little more.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
I thought I wouldn't make it.
A captain can do that?
I thought we'd have to
call in a rescue team.
We had emergency first-aid training.
In fact, captains undergo training and
practical exams on safety procedures too.
Even though our main duty
is to command the aircraft,
the safety of our passengers
is our highest responsibility
and our top priority.
This is my son-in-law.
He's amazing.
You're amazing.
Everyone in my family
was so impressed by you.
Did you hear it?
Your dad officially announced me
as his son-in-law.
Hold on.
Don't celebrate just yet.
My dad accepted you as a son-in-law
because you're a captain.
Come on. By the time he finds
out the truth, he'll already love me.
Alright, he might scold me a little,
but eventually,
he'll take me in as his son-in-law.
And what was that earlier?
We just started dating,
but you suddenly proposed like that.
Wasn't that too much acting?
Come on.
It's not Toto without being extra.
I saw you, though.
When I was proposing,
your eyes were about to say yes.
I was just playing along.
- Just going with the flow.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Hmm?
- Hey.
- What?
Just think about it.
If I said no, we'd have been caught.
Would you dare say no?
Hmm?
Hey, stop.
Let's make sure we get away with it
this time first.
I'll find time to tell my dad myself.
But thank you for today.
Thank you for being my handsome, cool,
and sharp boyfriend.
Don't you have a reward
for this handsome guy?
What reward?
Come on.
Hmm?
- What?
- That's it?
Come on.
I barely got to enjoy it.
I even left the rescue vehicle
to fly an airplane.
That's all I get?
Bummer.
Enough?
If that's not enough,
I'll give you more tonight.
It's not enough.
Get in the car.
Come on.
Hey.
Hurry up.
You haven't picked up my calls
since yesterday.
Are you training for the Spartan Race?
Do you really like me?
I already told you.
I was a pimple-faced kid.
You even threw away my gift.
Why do you like me now?
It's because I got more handsome, right?
Who said I threw it away?
I still have it.
Yeah, it's true that I like you
because you're handsome.
I'm not bullshitting you.
But I like who you are on the inside too.
That doesn't make me feel any better.
Alright, are you ready?
It's time.
I have a session with my trainer.
You should go.
I have nothing left to say.
I'm going to join the
Spartan Race with you.
I'm not giving up that easily.
I'm going to seriously pursue you
until you accept me.
Let's go.
You wear this uniform every day?
I have to get ready to fly later.
I stopped by to see you two off.
Sorry for the trouble.
Are you going to be late?
It's no trouble at all.
Taking care of Kanit's family
is my pleasure.
I should go.
Alright.
Take good care of Dad and Mom, Kana.
I know.
Take good care of each other.
We will.
Let's go.
Let me walk you over.
Take care.
Thank you.
Whoa.
I didn't think I'd make it.
I felt so pressured.
Oh, you're amazing.
I almost believed you.
Of course. I look like a captain.
Wait, no.
I think I'm more handsome than
that thick-browed captain.
Hey, why are you talking about him?
Stop that.
You're definitely the most handsome.
Alright, I'm off to fly.
Under the highway.
Wait.
Thank you.
Go.
Hey!
Keep it down! I'm trying to sleep!
No. I have to prove my love.
You're even in disguise to prove yours.
I have to do it my way.
Damn. Look at our lives.
We have to work,
and we have to make our love work.
Why is it so freaking hard?
Well, we fell for them on our own.
They didn't even ask for it.
You're right.
(Requesting rescue unit.)
(62-year-old male, heart attack.)
(Experiencing chest pain in a taxi.)
(Location: Bangna-Trat Road.
(History of heart disease.)
(Rescue unit needed immediately.)
You don't have to go.
I will.
I'll ask Beer and Ja-O to come with me.
Mm.
But aren't those two off today?
You and I are going. Hurry.
I think we can make it in time.
THE WINNERS RESCUE FOUNDATION
Help!
Ma'am.
Why are you wearing a rescue uniform?
How is he?
He suddenly became weak
and couldn't speak.
Let's get him out.
Ready?
How long ago was your father doing fine
before this happened?
Around half an hour.
Ki, get ready to monitor his vital signs.
Okay.
Sir.
Sir, can you hear me?
Don't worry.
We're waiting for the ambulance.
Hey. How's my dad?
He's with the doctors now.
He'll be okay.
Why did you lie?
Do you have any idea how he would feel?
Coffee?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I…
I ruined our plan.
It really was a coincidence.
Why are you apologizing?
You saved my dad's life.
My family owes you.
I guess
I'll have to work off our debt.
You don't have to. I was just doing my job.
I'm just worried your dad's
going to lose it when he wakes up.
What if he relapses?
This isn't how I wanted
him to find out, either.
But I'm kinda relieved.
It's exhausting pretending to like
someone who's not the real you.
Honestly, I like Toto, the rescuer,
not Toto, the captain.
Your dad will be okay,
and he'll accept me as Toto, the rescuer.
The new boyfriend of Kanit,
the flight attendant.
We'll get through this together.
No more captain's uniform?
Did you come straight from gardening?
That's a fertilizer giveaway shirt.
Hello, sir.
Hello, ma'am.
He greeted you.
Why didn't you say anything?
He saved your life.
Not even a thank you?
It's alright. I was just doing my job.
Dad, you don't like that
he's just a rescuer, do you?
No.
I don't like that he lied.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry, ma'am, for lying.
I lied to everyone in your family.
I'm really sorry.
You said you were serious.
Are you sure you weren't lying?
Dad,
all of this was actually my idea.
I told him to dress as a captain
to fool everyone.
You knew it was wrong.
Instead of stopping each other,
you encouraged it?
How is that even okay?
Why did you do this?
Do you think I really enjoy this?
Do you know how much Dad's expectations
have weighed me down my whole life?
Always having to land a good job,
get good grades,
and even find a good partner
who's rich and good at making money.
Why? Can't it just be someone ordinary?
Is just loving each other not enough?
Can't he just be a rescuer?
You need money to live, no matter what.
Love alone doesn't pay the bills.
Stop being so naive.
If you're going to keep seeing each other,
you better improve your life.
Make yourself worthy of my son.
If you can't do that, then break up.
Are you okay?
You've been quiet.
I'm sorry about what my dad said
and for asking you to pretend.
A few harsh words won't shake me.
It was nothing.
Are you okay?
I'm used to it.
My dad is rarely proud of anything I do.
So I guess I don't stand a chance, huh?
I see things differently from your dad.
To me, it doesn't matter
if I have enough to get by or not.
It doesn't matter if I'm dirt poor.
I can sleep anywhere.
Just don't make me sleep near a cheater.
I don't care anymore.
If he wants to disown me, let him.
I want you as my boyfriend.
Hey, don't say that.
I understand your dad's concerns.
He wants you to meet
someone who can really take care of you.
Hey, I can take care of myself.
I just want love.
But love alone isn't enough.
Life has expenses.
I eat cheap. You eat expensive.
What if one day I can't afford
to eat with you?
Then I'll pay for you.
I can eat cheap with you.
But I can't eat expensive with you.
Don't worry.
I'm not giving up.
I'll prove to your dad
that I'm the best for you.
Thank you.
You never give up. That's why I like you.
Isn't it because I'm spicy?
Well, a little.
♪ All the storms that have come to pass ♪
♪ Keep them as mere memories ♪
♪ But here today it's you and I ♪
♪ We've proved this
love could carry us high ♪
♪ No matter how hard the journey was ♪
♪ In the end we arrived,
completed a good flight ♪
(Next Episode)
Why have you been seeing me a lot lately?
Because he's busy.
He's working multiple
shifts and jobs right now.
You need to bring back
the spark in your relationship.
Sir, if you'd like to have some,
please use your mouth.
I'll start eating now.
Since we started dating,
we've had no time for each other.
I've been trying to find days
off from flying to see you,
but you always have somewhere else to go.
Are you working a lot these days?
Why do you look so exhausted?
Is this rescuer not good enough?
I don't get to sleep.
I don't even get to spend time with him.
Is what I've been doing really worth it?
If you're exhausted, why
don't you take a break?