Hello!
May I ask how long it will be before you arrive
I'll be there soon
It would be nice to be able to get a ride on a rainy day
The number is 2377
Yes
Bro
In a safe situation
Help me a little faster
Thank you
Man, you're carpooling
No matter how fast it is, I'll have to give him off first
Lulu
Where have you been
Why aren't you at home
You don't know where I'm going
I'm flying today
And you
Why are all stuffs gone
I've moved everything to the dormitory
I'm coming to see you now
Don't come to my place
I'm going to fly soon
There will be flight delayed
What are you playing
Pork
Weed
Smells like a burnt sour
It must be sea cabbage
Sick
Bro
Could you please change the route
I'm not going to the airport
Go to the nearest police station
Stop the car
Pain
Pain, pain, pain
Smoke too much？
It's electric.
The number you dialed is temporarily unanswered
Please redial later
Not answering the phone
This Gu Chaoyang
It's okay
He won't deliberately not answer the phone
There must be something.
Let‘s go
Pretty fast
You're all in the same group
Then go with me
Back to the Drug Enforcement Unit
Then
It depends on whether you have the life to leave here
Go
Squat down
Zhao
How's that
Don't worry
They answer everything after get them in
Don't worry, I'm here
Go to the airport to find Dong Lu
The phone is turned off
It's probably departured
Why do you keep falling out
Do you want to marry her
Of course I do
The ring has been bought
Just know the rings
I think you don't understand women at all
It's not the ring that she cares about
Don't know me at all
He says I lose my temper all day long
Why can't he think about it
It's his own problem
What problem do I have
She's on the plane every day
She always greets passengers with a smile
As soon as she got home, she gave me a cold shoulder
I worked all day
I'm tired
Could he be
a little more attentive and patient with me
Your Chaoyang is a rough one
You know it
He is quite observant of passengers
That's my duty
I have to look for suspicious people
You guys
Both have given a lot
Dong Lu is doing it for you
She has given up the chance to go abroad
Gu Chaoyang wants it either
He wants to let the two of you spend more time together
Give up on the criminal police force
And be the air police
The young couple communicate more
I won't talk to you anymore
I'm leaving now
I told you last time to apply to the anti-drug team
Think it over again
Forget it
Boss
I'd like to ask for absent
Go to Uraya
Enjoy it
Ok, thank you
I know
I have a problem
In daily life
I'm not careful enough either
I never did it because of work
Angry with you
I'm a civil aviation worker, too
Of course I understand your job
But you're an air police officer
You're in charge of what's up in the sky
Do you also have to be involved in land matters
It's just run into it this time
Then neither am I
I don't think you really know me at all
Nor did you take our future seriously
I have something urgent and I'm leaving first
Lulu
Civil Aviation Administration of China Public Security Bureau
Air Police Lu Chengfei
This is my colleague
Qin Cheng
Hello, Captain
Here is the information related to this escort mission
Du Jiulin
China wants serious criminals
He was caught in Uraya recently
Negotiated
The Uraya police has agreed to hand it over to our country
Because it happened suddenly
In order to avoid something will be happened
Send Du Jiulin back to China as soon as possible
Instructions from superiors
This escort mission will be carried out by us
We will take this flight
Today is a special day
Everyone works up
If something unexpected happens in the cabin during the flight
Be sure to report to me immediately
And follow the arrangements of the air police officer
Got it?
Got it
Good
Check the cabin
Please check the emergency equipment in each door area
Gate Area 4
All emergency equipments are on standby
The automatic fire extinguishing system in the restroom is functioning properly
Thank you
Chief Flight Attendant
Meals are being transported
Please take off your sunglasses
Check
please
What?
What's in the bag
What are you talking about? I don't understand?
Maybe you have something, contraband
Can you speak Chinese?
Open your bag
Speak Chinese
Please open your bag
Okay, you can go
Chinese
Don't touch my bag
What do you mean
You don't move you don't move
I can translate for them
Okay
He said he would check it
There might be contraband inside
Bullshit
Contraband? What contraband
This craft
I just bought it at the airport store
Explain to him
He says that is
There are the handcraft sold in your country
You let me go
Look at that
He has that bullet in his neck
They can all get through
I won't pass?
What is this?
This
Empty handicrafts
Fake
Okay, you can go
Hold on, all of them can go
Why can't I leave
You can't take this knife
You will need go to inspection
He means he would take you alone for the inspection
He surely won't let you carry this knife
Why I can't take it
Such an expensive knife is not to be brought
No
Did you not explain it clearly to them
Don't go
Hey you shouldn't bother this people man
I suspect
he has the XYY chromosome
Supermale syndrome
Could anyone help me explain it again
Two hundred and twenty meals for passenger
12 for the crew
And two special meals requests
Alright, thank you
Thank you very much. And this is for you
Have a safe travel
Bye. Have a nice day
This isn't the one who always quarrels with us
How did they change the person today
Maybe ask for absent
Inform the escort team to board the plane
Nervous
No
It was a little nervous at first
But seeing the real person doesn't seem so scary
Relax your mind
But don't let your guard down
Don't worry, I'm here
I'm not a humanoid camera
A professional foodie
I practiced before
Could there really be something
One punch one down
Sister Dong Lu
I'd like to ask you for a favor
I'm going to take the air police exam
I heard my brother-in-law is an air police officer
Could you let us have a meet
I want to study from him
Ok inform the ground
Get ready to pick up passengers
Look
Look at this overseas airport
How big
How good
Foreign airports are bright, huh
There's nothing you can think of in Li Jie's live streaming
There's nothing you can't buy
Okay
What a wide boarding gate!
Only myself
Babe, check out by yourself
Look up
Look at the first class
You haven't taken any of them
Stop messing around
Sir
Let's go inside first
Make way for the passengers behind
What to make way
Make it
That has to make way
You look really hot
Just add me on wechat
I'll scan you
Wechat can't be added during working time
Please inside
understand
Understand
I'll scan your wecaht after we get off the plane
Good noon. Welcome aboard
Sorry, welcome aboard
Tao Tao
What a naughty kid
Who are you referring to as a naughty kid
Welcome aboard
You're the mother of the child
What's wrong?
He knocked my phone to the ground and didn't see it, did you
You blocked it for so long yourself
Don't you know?
What the hell are you arguing with me about
Sir
Madam, madam
Take it easy. Let's take it easy for now
Apologize and pay the phone, hurry
What apology?
You got stuck there for so long
What to yell?
What are you yelling at me
Let's find a seat first
Your kids hunt here
Bumping into my phone
Did you hear the flight attendant?
Who is it again?
Me
What
The flight attendants don't speak well huh?
Am I good at talking
Okay
Speak louder
Damn
Shame on you
Sit there
What can't be done
Especially him
Tell me
Inside, please
Lao Nian is here
Could you please show me your boarding passes
thank you
Air ticket
Where are the tickets?
Where are the air tickets?
It's okay, it's okay, no rush
The ticket was gone in a short while
Here it is
Let me check your seats for you
When is it? Joking with the flight attendants
Your seats are in the fifth lane in the front
Let me take a look at your seat
Here, please
Good
Lulu
Get away
Good noon. Welcome aboard
Let me take a look at your seat
Front row 4
Thank you
Where shall I sit?
Look by yourself.
Good noon
Welcome aboard
Let me take a look at your seat for you
Good noon. Welcome aboard
Good noon, welcome aboard
Hello, welcome boarding
Sir
I've put your bag here for you
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
Handsome guy
Hello
How can we connect to the wireless network
Search for Qiuyuan Airlines in your wireless network
It's not your job
I'll find it by myself
Who do you call a handsome guy
It's not the time for you to flirt with the flight attendants again
Young man
Come here
Hello!
What can I do for you
I have high blood pressure
Heart disease
This is on the plane
Not breathable
My seat is sandwiched in the middle
What if I have an attack
Sorry
Our plane is full today
There are special arrangements at the back of the plane
What special arrangements are there
No seats for us
Auntie, please calm down first
Let's all take a look
Calm down first, Auntie
Someone is exercising special powers
It's okay
Just three people
Take up three rows of seats
Is there any reason for this
Is there any law
- Auntie - You're an Internet celebrity, right
Just right to take a picture of him
Exposing them
Auntie, calm down first
Hello, Auntie
What
I'm the chief flight attendant of this flight
Chief flight attendant
If someone who has privileges, it will also be in the first class
Not at the tail of the plane
Auntie
Let's switch.
Though I'm not by the window
But it might be a little better for me to be by the aisle
I want a window position
What's the point of exchanging with you
I'll give up my seat
Auntie
This passenger is willing to change seats with you
What do you think
OK, OK, OK
Thanks, Sir
Yeah
Thank you, young man
Thank you
If you need anything, call me at any time
OK, OK
Thank you, Sir
Yeah, any time
Hi, man
What a coincidence!
Good to see you
Me too
Ladies and gentlemen
Our plane is about to take off
Please cooperate with the safety officer for security checks
Put away the small table
Straighten the seat backrest
Request for takeoff
Tower Tower Tower
8U746 requests takeoff
8U746 can take off
First and second engines start
Captain, we can take off
Thrust stabilization
The flight is from Uraya to Qiuyuan, China
Estimated flight time
Five hours and fifty minutes
The flight distance is 5,200 kilometers
Ladies and gentlemen
Welcome aboard
Qiuyuan Airlines
Flight 8U746
From Uraya to Qiuyuan
The flight will take about five hours and fifty minutes
The flight distance is 5,200 kilometers
Thank you
I delivered the food
Give me the money
Thank you
Ladies and gentlemen
Our plane has entered level flight
Cabin service is about to begin
We have prepared a lunch for everyone
Hello
Call me whenever you need anything
Thank you
What the hell is this?
It's dry
It's not delicious at all
You can taste it
Hello, this is the special meal you ordered
And note not heated
Okay，okay，thanks
He has a special meal and I want to have a special meal too
Stewardess
Give us the special meal, please
Sorry, Sir
Special meals need to be reserved in advance
Then can be served now
It's okay, thank you
I won't eat.
Chief Flight attendant
Wait until you're not busy
Could you call Dong Lu for me
I'll go and see
If not busy
I'll drag her over here
Thank you
Du Jiulin
Having wandered outside for so many years
The taste of home is still better
If you had known so
Why did you do it back then?
Big Brother, I was wrong
Big Brother
I can't hold it any longer
I really didn't mean to step on your shoes
I, I came all the way here
I didn't see you
I hit you and I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Sir, Sir
May I ask what you need
Sir
What do I need
I need to use the toilet
You can use other restrooms, Sir
Bullshit
If the other restrooms are empty
Can I come here
I'm in first class
No way
Sir
Big brother!
Why don't you let this gentleman go
Use the restroom first
There's someone inside.
I need to use the toilet, too
Here you go, here you go, here you go
Thanks, big brother
And someone else
Are you a big brother or a big sister
Brother or Sister
Hurry up! I've pulled it out
I really pulled it out
It's sticking out
Officer
I'm not eating
Why doesn't work this net work
It's connected
8U746 Please answer
Commander
8U746 timed out and did not respond
Keep calling
8U746 This is Qiuyuan
Please reply upon receipt
Qiuyuan, Qiuyuan
I'm 8U746
Captain
There seems to be something wrong with our communication equipment
The 8U746 hung out the 7600
Open the emergency channel
Keep calling
8U746 Please answer
The plane can't fall down
My heart is pounding
How could that be
How many times have we sat there
Sir
Please fasten your seat belt
Please sit down
Relax
Relax, right, exactly
Relax, relax
Nice, keep breathing
Auntie
What's wrong with you
Dizzy
It might be just, you know, airsickness from being nervous
Try to looking out the window
Try
Ask her
Does she has epilepsy or
Pheochromocytoma
Auntie
Do you have epilepsy or pheochromocytoma
No No
Good
Try this
This is metoclopramide
It will help
Exactly
Relax
Nice, cool
Ask her rest sometime
Thank you sir
Yeah no worries
Let her rest and go back to your seat
Are you a doctor
Me
Kind of
But not as you are thinking
I'm a psychologist
You know, I got airsick too
That's why I'm carrying this
What do you do for work
Alright
Let me guess let me guess
Doctor
Programmer or lawyer
Or
Police officer
Alright, alright, alright
Okay, okay, man
You're always quiet, bro
We've been talk to each other， maybe we can switch the contact
Okay
Chief Commander
8U746 has the emergency code 7500 attached
8U746 is flying southward
Activate emergency plan
Close the route to Uraya
Inform Uraya immediately
Ask them to prepare contingency plans
Clear quickly
Uraya Uraya
This is Qiuyuan of China
Flight 8U746 has Emergency Code
And it has been hijacked
Hello
I'd like to look for your chief flight attendant
The chief flight attendant is busy
What do you need to tell me
Isn't our route back north
Why are we going south now
Air Traffic Control Sir
Okay. Thanks
You're welcome
Air Traffic Control Sir
Sir
Excuse me
This is first class
Please go back to your seat
I'm going to the restroom
Sir Sir
Let go
Don't fight
I'm an air police officer too
What?
They
She's a fake flight attendant
Better or not
Captain, we just had a hijacking
Forced to change course
The route has now been restored
Good
Just got the captain's confirmation
The plane was affected by wireless interference
Unable to get in touch with the ground
Now both of you are suspects
but I can't verify your identities immediately
Here is my police officer ID
You can check my police number
I can prove that he is an air police officer
He
He's my ex-boyfriend
I still need to check with the ground
In the meantime
Hope you cooperate with our work
Is she attacked you
It was her
But among them
There should be an accomplice
I heard the sound
It was a boy
Ask them to change their course right away
Fly to Verogue
Stop!
What conditions?
We can talk
Adjust the flight route immediately
Fly to Verogue
That is to say
Among these male passengers in the first-class cabin
One of them is the hijacker
Yingzi
You go to the first-class cabin
Wake up these passengers
Ask about the situation
Okay
Sir
Wake up
Hello, Sir
Hello, madam
Wake up
Sir
Ladies
Wake up
Why can't I wake them up
Chief Commander
Uraya has send
A new situation has been provided to us
Chief flight attendant
Are there any other anomalies today
No other anomalies
The one who prepared meals for our flight today
Not the usual one
It's new here
Is there anything wrong with that
deliver man has been killed
Shooting dead
If he was bribed to silence him
Then
There's a good chance they'll play tricks on the flight meal
I analyze
Someone was in the first-class meal
Tampered with
Has the radio signal of the 8U746 been restored
Top priorities
The task is to find the male hijackers
And reasons for interfering with the signal
Lu Sir
We have a first-class passenger
He went to the bathroom in the rear cabin
He hasn't come back yet
Yingzi
Could you go and check the situation in the bathroom of rear cabin
Okay
Wait a moment
Call the sky guard Xiao Xu
Cooperate with you
I can assist you
I can't confirm your identity yet
So please go back to your seat first
Okay
If needed
The flight attendants can help with the investigation
Follow me
Open the door
Binbin
Take him to the first-class cabin
Could I be in any danger
We will let you stand in court
Without any danger occurs
Okay, okay
Rest rest
Okay, okay, okay
Hey, what happened to him
I don't know
Wake up
Dafa
You can go
Wake Up
Dafa
Lu Sir
In the rear cabin restroom
This jammer was found
Wake him up
Dafa
Wake Up
Why bring this jammer
What Jagger
How did you come in
The jammer doesn't have to have been placed in the restroom by him
There were also people who had entered the restroom before him
Big Brother, I'm wrong Big Brother
I can't hold it in any longer
Hello, Sir
Air police of the Civil Aviation Administration of China Public Security Bureau
Please cooperate with the investigation
Hello, Sir
Sir
I'm an aviation security officer of the Civil Aviation Administration of China
Please cooperate with the investigation
What happened
Sit safe
Nothing to do with you
Which luggage is yours
Luggage
I left my luggage over there
This one?
Right
This one
Yellow one
Calm down
Don't come here
If you come again and I'll kill him
Don't be impulsive
What demands can we talk about
No
Get out
It can't be here to kill me right
Shut up!
Calm down!
Do you know what are you doing
If you get closer to me and I will kill him
Yingzi
Back
Get away!
And you, Old man
Get out of here
Let's talk
Hurting him won't be benefit to you
Enough!
Be calm
It won't help that you catch me
You all have to die
Go
All will die
Come here
Don't panic, everyone
It won't hurt you
When that fat guy was caught
He said we're all going to die
What does it mean?
Will it be on the plane
What dangerous goods are there?
Check
Why they take my bags
Why they check bags
Isn't that a violation of privacy rights
Is this your bag
It's not mine
Whose bag is this
This is my bag
Lu Sir
What's wrong?
Show me what is it
Is this a bomb
Bomb
Calm down
Calm down everyone calm down
No problem
Calm down, everyone
Bomb
Don't panic
We'll handle it
Lu Sir
There must be a misunderstanding
There's no way you understand
Yingzi
Mr. Air Police Officer
It's impossible for him to do such this thing
There must be a misunderstanding
Isn't this guy a good thing
At the security check
It was him
Detain your phone first according to law
Take it away
There's really a problem
What do you look at? Huh?
Police officer
I just saw a man behind me
Rummaging through that area for a long time
Are you sure?
I'm sure it's him
He's been flipping through it for a long time
Which one?
Just the man with disheveled hair behind
Me?
Make sure you said is true
I'm sure is him? He doesn't look like a good person
Police officer
Let me explain it to you
I was carrying my own bag
Besides, I didn't do anything, right
Xiao Xu
Control him
Hello, Sir
Please come forward and cooperate with our investigation
I
Please cooperate
OK, OK, I'll cooperate with you
Don't look
All passengers
Please keep calm
Everything is under our control
Xiao Xu
Deal with the bomb, please
I'll inform the captain
Chief flight attendant
Please move the passengers from the back row
Evacuate
Ok
Walk and take him to the front
We fasten our seat belts
Fasten your seat belt
It will be handled
Why did they all move forward
If they go ahead, we should go too
Let's move forward a little
Move forward a little
Thank you thank you
Could you fasten your seat belt, Sir
There is a virus app in this phone that can't be uninstalled
What is the sequence code
I really don't know
You said the explosives in the backpack weren't yours
So isn't this phone yours
Captain
A new situation has been found
A bomb was found in a passenger's backpack
Bomb bomb
Go ahead
I have only one life
Sit down first
I'll make sure everyone is safe
We have airpolice
Sit down
Sit down, OK?
Please sit down first
Thank you for your cooperation
Let's go look for our luggage first
Set up the explosion-proof platform
Okay
I'd like to apply for hovering in the air
Give us some time
Okay
I apply to the ground
Qiuyuan, Qiuyuan
This is 8U746
Request to hover in the air
What are you doing with my bag
Ladies, we
Don't be nervous, everyone
We are looking for some soft luggage
Surround the bomb
Avoid as much as possible
Bomb debris can cause harm to everyone
I'm a Chinese-race bomb disposal soldier from Uraya
Here is my ID
You can verify my identity at any time
But the prime priority
Deal with those explosives immediately
Here you go
Thank you
I have a soft luggage here
Take it
You calm down
That's a bomb
What if it explodes?
Get out of me
Don't you all have bags
Take it
What if it breaks
You calm down
Everyone look for it
Let's all look
Take it together
Stewardess! There are still two here
Do you have any bags?
Let go
We get along together
Can we exchange contact please
Okay
Be careful
Sorry
It's that person
Don't speak
Shut up, everyone
Sir
My friend
Hijacking
Chinese police are not to be trifled with
I owe him
When I was a mercenary
I was ambushed by drug dealers
If Du Jiulin didn't risk his life to save me
I would be died man
I must repay him
I don't know how many policemen on the plane
We need to have more people
I plan to split up
You
buy security checks
Bring the jammer aboard
Get them out of communication with the ground
Yu Qi
Your job is take control of first-class
Then force the captain
To fly to Verogue
At the same time
I'll look for opportunities in economy class
It will draw everyone's attention
We feint east and attack west
How can we do without this thing
Two hundreds and twenty for passengers
Twelve for the crew
And two specials
Hello, here is the special meal you ordered
Note not heated
Okay， thanks
Please, everyone
Good
Bro, I have money
I can give it all to you for sure
Okay? Big Brother
Big Brother
I'm commanding you to change the route
Don't you get it
Change the flight route for me immediately
Give me
Brother, brother, let him go
Brother, brother
Brother, let him go
Stop crying
Babe
If you don't change the route as we said
We'll take the passengers
Kill them one by one
And also skilled in military-style boxing
You're not amazing anymore
Stop fighting
You're awesome!
And you
What level
Little Cop
Boy Scouts
You are amazing
You're awesome
Stop fighting
It's gonna be killed
Is that you
Are you okay?
Are you okay
Stop fighting
Stop fighting!
I hate little yellow hair the most
Tell the captain about entering the thunderstorm cloud
Okay， fat guy
Stop fighting
Take these air police officers to the warehouse
Be careful by yourself
I'll inform the captain
Get into the thunderstorm cloud
Take care of the passengers
Xiao Xu
Are you okay
Captain Captain
The air police are applying to enter the thunderstorm cloud
Use the weather to disrupt the robbers
Look for opportunities
Resolve the crisis
Get into a thunderstorm cloud
It's too risky
Chief Commander
This is Air Police
Send message was brought by the flight attendants
I think we should trust them
Okay
Captain
I trust the decision of the air police officer
But be sure to be careful
At the same time, make sure the passengers are safe
Roger
Chief Commander
I will do my best
Circling through the thunderstorm clouds
Get more time for air police
Arrest robbers
Good
Inform the airway of clear airspace immediately
8U746
We'll wait for you to come back home
It is to ensure the completion of the task
To die so young
What a pity!
Brother accompanies you to have a good time
In a moment the plane will go into a thunderstorm cloud
We need to seize this opportunity
Count me in
No
This is too dangerous
Count me in too
Both we were born and raised by our parents
Why should they bully like this
Let's go and fight them together
Absolutely not
You are passengers
We have to keep you safe
Tell the passengers
Fasten your seat belt
Ok
Fasten your seat belt Fasten your seat belt
Fasten your seat belt
Fasten it
Please fasten your seat belt
Fasten your seat belt
Sir
Are you okay, Sir
I'm fine
Fasten your seat belt
The plane will encounter turbulence in a moment
Don't worry
Where is the fat guy?
He's in cargo compartment
Did I make you rape?
Lu Sir
Wake Up
Come up
Here!
Alright
Get up
Are you okay?
Keys
Captain
We're about to enter the thunderstorm cloud
Ring three times
Hint of the cabin
Heavy jolts
The plane is about to enter a thunderstorm cloud
This is our best chance to counterattack
Good
Let's do it together
Qin Cheng
Go up and see what's going on
Roger
Cuff him
Find a chance to go up
Leave this to me
Hurry
Let's go up and rescue the passengers
I'll leave this to Gu Chaoyang
Babe, what are you going to do
I'm fighting them
What are you looking for, go up
Up up
Don't hit my wife
I'm fighting you
Go together!
Chinese police
But that's it
Once I'm down with you
I'll take care of your friend up there
Let me show the world
What kind of cops you really are
Stop fighting
Hurry to capture these criminals
and ensure the safety of the passengers
Understood
You underestimate our Chinese air police too much
In order to make the plane land safely
Let every passengers return home safely
Even if it means risking my life
I will also stop you
They
Don't move
Lulu
The detonator is in my hand
Anyone who dares to move again
We'll die together
Did you hear me?
You let her go
Dad
Leave this matter to everyone
There should be an accomplice among them
I heard it was a boy
Ask them to change route right away
Fly to Verogue
Good boy
Chief flight attendant
Inform the captain
Adjust the route immediately
Fly to Verogue
Or all dead
Impossible
Stop
Du Jiulin
All your accomplices have been subdued by us
Confessing your guilt and bringing it to justice is your only way out
Stand there
You stop
Fired!
Don't move!
Let me go
Don't move
You're working so hard
Is it worth it?
Yes
I'm wearing this police uniform
It's just to make the people on the plane
All can go home safely
Are you okay?
I'm fine. How about you
Don't live all
Surround us quickly
Go
Xiao Xu Xiao Xu
Control him quickly
Come on! Hurry up!
Wait for me
There's liquid nitrogen under the emergency slide
Help me get it quickly
I'll get it
Hurry
Traditional bomb disposal methods are too late
What to do
Adjust the temperature of the bomb
Lower it to minus 130 degrees
Freeze the electronic circuit board
It will take time to freeze the bomb
Your hands won't hold up
I can't care about that much
Trust me
Liquid nitrogen
Get some more blankets
Protect Dong Lu
Gu Chaoyang
Gu Chaoyang Your hand
Stop making noise
Trust the police
Shut up, everyone
Your hand
Chinese air police good
Good
Applaud
Ladies and gentlemen
Please fasten your seat belts
Put away the small table
Straighten the seat back
Our plane is about to land
Qiuyuan, China
We're home
Home
Hold on a little longer
It will land soon
It's okay, go back and sit
Take a break
Report to the chief commander
8U746
Request for Landing
Permission to land
8U746 Welcome home
Xiao Song
Well done
Motherland
We're back
It's time for off work
Can you add me on wechat
Let's get on the ambulance first
Come here
Welcome home
Must add
Good
I'll treat you to dinner some other day
I haven't finished speaking yet
What do you like to eat
Be gentle
Slow down, slow down
Slow down
You don't even know
What did I just go through with Lao Nian
Li
Don't do this
This is all we should do
And
Sorry
Weak legs
Family members
Right
Let's make a grand introduction
Remember this guy's face
Air Police
Our hero
It was he who led us on the plane
Fight with the bad guys
None of that is what we should do
Remember that
Tonight
It's the designated headline news tonight
Right
Follow me and Sister Li's live stream in the evening
I'll tell you all things
I'll talk it seriously