[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] Monte Carlo algorithm is
a type of randomized algorithm
that uses repeated
random sampling
to obtain numerical results
for complex problems.
Instead of a single,
deterministic outcome,
it generates many
possible outcomes
to estimate a solution,
making it useful for problems
that are too complex
to solve analytically.
Ever since our nudes got leaked,
I keep trying to solve
the problem.
Given all the possible outcomes,
I can't seem to think
of a solution.
And just when I feel like
I‘m finally getting somewhere...
the unexpected happens.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
This doesn't make sense.
Why would she do that?
Why would she leak
her own photos?
Actually, someone else
leaked April's photos.
Still, why would she do that?
[LESTER] Well, number one...
she‘s competitive.
Number two...
jealous.
Number three, crazy.
Number four...
[CHUCKLES] All of the above.
[COLE] And I think...
April is seeking revenge
for what you did to her.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Cole, that was
a million years ago.
She can't be holding
a grudge until now.
You don't know April.
Dad beat her because
of what you did.
She couldn't even walk
the next day, Marla.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA] Okay, but tell me...
why would she leak the photos
of the other girls?
Maybe they...
were just...
collateral damage?
She knew you would pin
the blame on us
for leaking your nude photos
so you'd never suspect her.
[COLE] Right?
All of you blamed me.
I don't know why.
I don't know
what happened to her.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LESTER] That...
bitch of a sister of yours, bro?
Crazy.
Crazy!
I mean...
Come on, would you believe
that she told Daphne that
I leaked her photos?
[LESTER] Okay, yes, I know,
I'm an asshole.
But I would never, ever
leak her photos in public.
Ever.
I agree with Lester.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll talk to her.
- I‘ll get the truth--
- Marla, let me.
I‘ll handle it.
[MARLA] Cole...
Babe
[COLE] Marla, let me.
[COLE BREATHES DEEPLY]
I know...
I've disappointed you
many times already.
But...
maybe you can give me a chance
to make it up to you, babe?
Please?
Please, let me help.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
Promise.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Boys, let's go.
Let's go.
- [LESTER SIGHS DEEPLY]
- [TABLE THUDS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ISOBEL] I don't know
what they said to you,
but you do know
you can't trust them.
They're just distracting you
because
they know that when you win,
our rights on the
honors list will get reinstated.
I know! I know, Isobel.
Okay, okay,
enough with the chit-chat.
Let's do it, okay?
We shouldn't be fighting!
Right, we only have ten minutes
before the hacka-thingie!
- What the hell! Ten minutes?
- Ten?
Yes, you have 10 minutes
to read these books now!
Use your photographic memory,
and use it for a good cause.
Oh, sorry, girl!
Isobel, are you crazy,
or out of your mind?
Marla can't read all that
in 10 minutes!
[ISOBEL] Yes, she can
[DAPHNE] She‘ll combust
or something.
[ISOBEL] Really?
She'll combust, Dessalyn?
- Shut up!
- You look combusted.
What if I blast your face off?!
- Try!
- Shh!
- Oh, I would!
- Shut up!
[MARLA] Shut up.
- It‘s Isobel‘s fault.
- Shh!
April got knocked out
because of this woman.
[ISOBEL] It was for Migo,
not her!
Shhhhh!
It's for us to shut up, okay?
[NYX] Marla needs
peace and quiet
so she can retain
all the information.
Can you go any faster?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[WARREN] Good luck, Marla.
You can do it.
Thank you.
Good luck to him.
[EMCEE] Let us welcome back
our coders to the stage.
For our final round,
please welcome
Marla Briones versus
Migo Alcera!
[CROWD CHEERING]
For our final round, our coders
will try to create a password
and then secure it.
They will then try to hack
each other‘s password.
Whoever cracks
each other's password first,
wins!
Coders, please take your seats!
On my cue...
In three, two, one
code!
[MIGO SHOUTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
[YAWNING, GRUNTING]
[MIGO LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY]
Marla!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Has your system crashed already?
[SNICKERS]
You know, Marla,
the important thing is
at least you tried.
[MIGO] It's not your fault that
you know nothing about coding.
And you challenged the king.
[MIGO] I didn't know
it would be this elating
to beat the batch's number one.
Please don't cry
when I beat you.
Okay, I'm going to crush you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIREN BLARING]
[COMPUTER PINGS]
You'll be the one crying, Migo.
And I heard there hasn't
been a day
you didn't cry since
April left you.
[CROWD GASPS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
After this,
you'll be crying again.
After I beat your ass!
[SCOFFS]
Beat my ass?
You fool!
[CHUCKLES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
He's so easy to distract,
especially when he gets cranky.
[MIGO GROANS, SNIFFS]
[MIGO] Almost there!
Hmm What?
What now?
What now, Migo?
You're such a loser!
Is that all you got?
How would you hold
when I beat you?
Didn't you say that
I have no experience in coding?
I guess...
you're just weak.
- I'm not weak!
- [TABLE THUDS]
You're weak! You fool!
[MARLA CHUCKLING]
Oh my, oh my,
he's about to cry...
Oh, no.
What a poor, pitiful baby!
[MARLA] Perhaps,
your mom didn't love
you that much?
I can tell.
[LAUGHING]
You don't talk about my mother!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I hit a nerve?
[MARLA] I'm so sorry,
you poor, pitiful baby.
You know, Migo,
I'm sure,
if your mother can
see you right now,
oh boy,
she'd be so disappointed with
how you turned out to be.
A loser!
I'm not!
My mommy told me
I'm not a loser!
She said I'm a good boy!
Oh, hey, are you crying?
Jeez. Cry, baby, cry!
Cry, baby, cry!
[CHANTING] Cry, baby, cry!
He's about to cry!
- Cry, baby, cry!
- [COMPUTER PROCESSING]
- [CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- Cry, baby, cry!
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
[SYSTEM PROCESSING]
- Cry, baby, cry!
[HOST] Migo Alcera's
really going to cry because...
we have a winner!
Marla Briones beats
Migo Alcera to become
the Best Programmer at
State Omni-Standard High!
- [MIGO CRYING]
- Marla Briones,
you are our
Hackathon Champion!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[DAPHNE] Oh my god,
I've never been prouder!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Go clap for her.
Come on.
[APPLAUDING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
- [HUMMING]
- [NYX] Yes! You ate that!
- You slayed!
- We are so proud of you!
- So proud of you, girl!
- Yeah!
- [DAPHNE CHUCKLES]
- [NYX GROWLS]
Hey, you're proud, aren't you?
- Right, girl?
- Hmm?
- Come on...
[ISOBEL] Good job.
- Yeah.
- Hmm...
She said, "good job."
Really?
Oh?!
Rise and shine!
[CHUCKLES]
Welcome back to you,
and welcome back to the
young and beautiful world!
You slayed earlier, girl,
as if you're sleeping beauty!
But!
There's nothing beautiful...
with all your morning glory.
- Plus...
- You were drooling.
Wipe it off your face,
your drool marks, so gross.
Okay.
April, Marla was
like the big winner!
She destroyed Migo.
Well, I did predict that...
there's an 87% chance...
that you'd win.
So... [MOUTH CLICKS]
There! As usual.
Wow! Congrats, Marla.
Thank you.
But are you really happy?
That we won?
Of course.
I just hoped
I didn't fall asleep.
[NYX] Speaking of that...
Isobel's got something to say.
Hmm.
- I have nothing to say.
- Hey. Pst!
Girl, just admit it.
Come on...
You guys are enjoying this
and I don't like it.
[NYX] Hmm!
Come on, Isobel.
- We believe in you.
- [ISOBEL SCOFFS]
[NYX] Yeah...
Don't you know
how to say sorry?
- I do, Dessalyn.
- [DAPHNE] Then say it!
- [RETCHES]
- [NYX] Oh...
[BREATH QUIVERS]
I'm...
- [NYX] What was that?
- [ISOBEL] Sorr...
Huh?
S-So...
- What?
- What was that?
[ISOBEL SIGHS] I'm so...
[SIGHS] I'm so...rry.
- Oh.
- Zero energy?
- What?
- One more!
[ISOBEL BREATHES DEEPLY]
I'm sorry!
Why does your apology
feel like a threat?
- Nonchalant.
- Exactly.
Why don't you try
to be more sincere?
Try harder.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I'm sorry.
It's okay,
I accept your apology.
[MARLA] But, guys...
Migo was a total loser.
[DAPHNE] I know, right?!
- He'll get kicked out.
- Right!
- That's so right! For sure!
- I'm so excited!
[PHONE CHIMES]
They just posted our long test
results from Mr. Ramirez.
- Huh?!
- [GASPS]
What?
- [NYX] What?!
[DAPHNE] What the hell!
How?! Migo...
Passed?!
This is anomalous!
Anomalous?!
- Oh my god, how did he pass?
- Crazy as heck!
Why did Mr. Ramirez give Migo
such a high grade?
- I know, right?
- He doesn't deserve it!
But do you, guys,
actually think...
that Migo's connected
with Mr. Ramirez?
I never saw it in that angle.
Perhaps we should look more
into Mr. Ramirez's background.
[APRIL] It's probably just
a fluke.
Maybe, Mr. Ramirez has nothing
to do with Migo.
So, let's put a pin on that.
[MARLA] No!
I think Isobel is right.
Mr. Ramirez should be
our next target.
It's not right
that we're keeping a teacher
who's an enabler,
and then he just keeps
getting in our way.
What is going on?
Why are we on the same page?
[NYX] Wow! Shh! Shh!
Oh?!
What's with you?
Ha!
I think...
[ISOBEL] Is something itching?
I think there's a 40% chance...
that Mr. Ramirez helped Migo.
He is a man after all.
Men only protect other men.
Don't go down this rabbit hole.
If Mr. Ramirez finds out that
we're investigating him,
we'll face the principal again.
We'll trigger Principal Mckenna.
[NYX] Ah! Principal's Office?
I agree with her.
Let's not do this, please.
I think we should focus
with the boys.
With a capital Z.
Mr. Ramirez looks harmless
anyway.
Yeah, and I'm sure
Migo just hacked the system
to alter his grades.
I don't think Mr. Ramirez
would even...
help Migo,
or risk his reputation
for someone like him.
He's one of the best teachers
in SOSH.
Okay.
But I just have to ask, April...
Why are you defending
Mr. Ramirez?
Woah!
[APRIL] I'm not defending him,
Marla.
All I'm saying is
we need to get a grip.
You're all becoming obsessed
with revenge.
You're getting too emotional.
You're imagining things.
I'm saying...
let's reorient to the data.
[DAPHNE SCOFFS]
You want data?
Well, here's some data for you.
Did you know
that Mr. Ramirez is getting
cozy with students?
- It's true!
- [APRIL] Was it with you?
Yes--
I mean, not with me!
He's fooling around even if
he's got a fiancée.
[NYX] No way!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKS SHUT]
[NYX] You swear
on Beyoncé's life?
Yes, girl!
I swear on Beyoncé's life!
- That serious?
- I swear!
Why? You think I'm delusional?
Yeah.
- [DAPHNE] No, as if!
- An itchy one.
[DAPHNE] I got this straight
from Scarlet.
Mr. Ramirez ghosted her
after months of fooling around.
But, why didn't you report it?
Actually,
I was already going to, but...
Scarlet filed
a leave of absence,
and eventually, she dropped out.
Besides, I don't have
enough evidence.
I thought, is it worth risking
my scholarship?
That's it.
That's not data.
That's gossip.
Besides, Scarlet is
your main source?
Does she not use...
...ChatGPT?
- Oh my!
- Eww!
Who uses ChatGPT?
If we're able
to get a proof of that,
we can have Mr. Ramirez fired.
And even better,
get Migo kicked out!
- Double whammy!
- Double!
- Double whammy.
- I see the growth, Marla.
Baby steps.
[APRIL] You're all going off
on a tangent.
Do whatever you want.
I'm out.
Huh?
Huh?!
First, she slept on us,
now she's walking out?
Gosh!
[MARLA'S PHONE CHIMES]
She's got an attitude,
doesn't she?
Totally.
Cole: "Go to room 106
in 10 minutes."
- [LIGHTS SWITCH OFF]
- [GIRLS GASPING]
[ISOBEL] What the--
[NYX] Again?
- Ugh!
- [LIGHTS SWITCH OFF]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREACKING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC BUILDS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[DOOR CREAKS SHUT]
[BAG THUDS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait.
Did you help Migo pass?
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
Why does it matter?
[SMOOCHES]
[EXHALES]
So, you gave him a passing grade
even though he's been flunking?
It's just grades.
Come on, we don't--
We don't have a lot of time.
No!
Did you know that Migo
leaked my photos?
My whole life became a total
system crash because of him.
How could you just
let him pass, sir?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know what I've been through.
I tell you everything.
Migo has been harassing me.
You know that Cole has
been treating me like shit.
I've been telling you
everything.
So, why did you let him pass?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Because...
he knows about us.
What?
How?
[MR. RAMIREZ] I don't know.
But he has evidence.
Enough to threaten me with,
that's for sure.
He even wanted to go
to the school board.
You know what would
happen to me
if he did that?
My teaching license
would get revoked.
He won't do that.
He's just all bark no bite.
Migo's a coward.
[SIGHS]
Look.
I only did it because
I wanted to protect you.
Come on, I'm the only one
who cares about us.
Do you really think...
I'd let you get hurt?
I'll talk to Migo.
I'll troubleshoot this problem.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
No. Don't.
I've fixed it.
Okay?
He needs me to pass,
so I let him pass.
So that he'll leave us alone.
Just...
just ignore the guy.
No.
[SIGHS]
I won't let Migo bully me
ever again, okay?
If we let him get away
with this,
then he'll just keep
blackmailing us.
Migo is malware,
and I have to remove him.
You think this is a game?
- No.
- No, right?
No, it's not a game.
But for some reason, your age
is really showing here, April.
My job is on the line here.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I know, that's why...
- I'm trying to...
- No. No, no... nope.
No, you don't know.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Look, Migo and I
already talked about this.
He needs me...
to pass.
It's a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
So, just...
leave the guy alone.
Unless...
you want me
to leave you alone.
What?
You want me to end this?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
Okay.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
You're the only person
who understands me, April.
I wouldn't know
what I'd do if I lost you.
No.
I can't lose you, Sir.
So...
promise me...
you'll leave him alone?
I promise.
Promise?
So let me do my job.
[SMOOCHES] Good girl.
[MUSIC BECOMES DARK]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[KNOCKS]
Migo!
I know you can hear me, Migo.
Open the window.
[KNOCKS]
Migo, I'm not fooling around.
What?!
What are you...
Just open the window.
Migo.
- [KNOCKS]
- Open it.
Migo, you know...
[KNOCKS]
Open the window, Migo!
[COINS CLINK]
Here's some spare change.
You've got some nerve.
Can't you just pass on your own
without resorting
to blackmailing?
So, you know that I know
about you and Mr. Ramirez?
Shut up!
How'd you know?
Of course.
I did a bit of online
surveillance, April.
You mean stalking.
[MIGO CHUCKLES]
Was it only cyberstalking,
or were you also
following me around?
My God, Migo,
you are such a creep!
[MIGO CHUCKLES]
Get out of the way. Shoo!
You're really one to talk.
You're calling me a creep?
Yet you're the one who
suddenly wanted to break up.
For what?
To flirt with a teacher?
With Mr. Ramirez?
[CHUCKLES]
April, if I'm a creep,
you're a fucking whore.
[SLAPS]
[CHUCKLES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
I missed that.
You know, April, it's so clear
that you don't know
who you're dealing with.
We've been together
for so long...
I've always been the one
saving you, and...
I think it's my duty to...
tell about you and
Mr. Ramirez to
the board,
the whole school.
It's my duty.
I'm here to protect you, April.
I hate you.
- [MIGO CHUCKLES]
- I hate you so much!
The more you hate,
the more you love.
Okay?
April, I'm just so concerned
about you.
Can't you see?
You're such a fool!
[SCOFFS]
I can see things clearly, April.
And it's so obvious that
Mr. Ramirez is just using you.
And it's also very obvious,
that you're just bitter.
[SCOFFS]
You know, April,
you're a good person.
If you'd like to help
Mr. Ramirez,
the only way to protect him is
break up with him...
and get back together with me.
[MIGO CHUCKLING]
You're ridiculous, Migo.
Do you even hear yourself?
You're like vaporware.
[CHUCKLING]
I'd rather get kicked
out of Omni-Stan
than get back with you.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
April, when this is
all over and done,
you're going to lose everything.
Everyone will see
who you really are.
Marla, Cole,
all your so-called friends
will see you for who you are
and they're all going to
leave you.
I'm the one who's going
to be here.
We both know that
I'm the only one who's
going to love you like this.
Remember that, okay?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Move.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Fuck you, Migo.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Marls, what's up?
What's with the
miting de avance?
Oh, my God, girls...
you are not going to believe
what I'm about to tell you!
Sophocles once said:
Do nothing secretly,
for Time sees and hears
all things, and discloses all.
Look what I saw!
What's the tea?
Yay, I'm so excited!
But, wait,
wait a minute,
where's April?
Actually,
I have something
to show you, guys.
So, I was about to confront--
I mean,
girl talk, one-on-one talk
with her...
until I saw this.
Also,
he really is inflating
Migo's grades
so he won't get blackmailed
for being a predator.
April is Oliver-zoned, too?
Okay, well...
hear me out.
Girls, be honest.
Sir Oliver is such a cutie...
but!
It's wrong! Very wrong!
He's a grown man!
A teacher.
- Our teacher!
- Right.
That's wrong on so many levels.
They say, "Not all men."
"Not all men." But girl...
it's always men!
So crazy. Gosh!
Figures.
That's why she was
defending him.
But Mr. Oliver should've
known better.
- That's not all.
- [NYX] Huh?
- There's more.
- What?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
Oh my God.
Nyx? That was perfect!
Girls!
Listen, this is not a joke!
As you can see,
April leaked our nude photos.
Aren't you angry?
Don't you feel betrayed?
[NYX] You're overreacting!
That's fake!
It's AI!
A scam!
I thought it was AI at first.
But I got this straight
from the Javier household.
So...
you would rather believe
Cole than April?
Cole, who cheated on you?
Girl?
He cheated on me with you.
Yes!
Old news.
Moving on.
You saw it with your own eyes.
He uploaded your photos
to their GC.
He assured me he didn't.
And you believe him?
So pathetic!
Didn't you see?
You even read their messages.
April could have...
faked all of that.
What?
Or...
Cole is just lying to you.
No.
Marla's right.
We can't trust that
two-faced bitch anymore.
April will totally betray us.
Didn't she cheat in the exams?
But wait,
are we just gonna trust Cole?
Isn't he a cheater as well?
What if, this was
Cole's plan all along?
To tear us apart?
Divide and conquer technique.
- Exactly.
- Mm.
But evidence
doesn't lie.
Told you.
But...
what if Cole was
just forcing April?
See?
Girl, we all saw
how Cole bullies April.
Really? What an April apologist.
I'm just being
a devil's advocate.
What if April's
just being cornered?
Why don't we give her...
the benefit of the doubt?
Benefit of the doubt?!
I've been!
But Flannery O'Connor once said,
"the truth doesn't change
depending on our ability
to stomach it."
So we have to do something.
We have to confront her.
How will we know
if we can trust her?
That's where you come in.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[TAPPING FOOT]
- Marla.
- Warren.
Can I tell you something?
Sure.
Um... [EXHALES]
It's kinda embarrassing...
Go ahead.
I'm really nervous...
Marla...
Yes?
Um...
Warren, I'm so sorry,
I have to get to class, so...
please, spit it out.
Uh...
M-Marla, have you heard of
mere exposure effect?
Yes, familiarity principle.
Yes, so, famili--
familiarity principle.
Mm-hm.
It's a psychological phenomenon
where people develop
preference for some things when
they're familiar
with the stimulus.
Okay? And then?
Okay so, coming from an
evolutionary standpoint,
new things can be dangerous.
And it's...
easier for our brain to process
stuff that we're
already accustomed to.
The ease of processing
or perceptual fluency.
As much as I love this lecture,
I really need to go.
I'm gonna be late.
What's your point?
[WARREN EXHALES SHARPLY]
Sorry. I'm just nervous.
Following the principle,
I wish I could be
one of those people
you'd consider as someone
familiar and easy to process.
Um, someone...
who'd make you feel safe,
not dangerous from a...
f-from an evolutionary
standpoint.
And if...
if...
you'd consider me
as someone familiar,
maybe there's a chance
you'd have a...
preference for me.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm so sorry,
I'm so lost.
What?
Evolutionary standpoint?
Preference?
What?
Marla, will you go
on a date with me?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
U-uh...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Sorry, I said too much.
You know what,
you're running late,
just forget
everything I just said.
Yes.
Y-Yes?
Yes, I‘ll go out
on a date with you.
Um...
A-Are you sure?
Really?
Mm-hm.
[CHUCKLES] Um...
A-are you free on Saturday?
Yes.
U-um...
Then...
it... it's a date?
Okay.
Okay, I'll be going.
- Okay, okay...
- I'm late.
- Okay!
- Good luck with class...
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Oh, my god.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Mom?
Mommy?
Meding, where's Mommy?
She's out bar hopping
with her friends.
Your mom's broken-hearted
once again.
Which friends?
I don't know.
I hope she doesn't
drink and drive.
I hope so.
You know that mom of yours,
she gets wild when she's drunk!
Thank you, Meding.
[LINE RINGS]
Hello?
Hi, Auntie Claire!
Good evening.
Are you with my mom?
[CLAIRE]
Marla, dear, I went ahead.
I left your mom at the bar.
Which bar?
[CLAIRE] I forgot!
We went to so many bars,
and met so many foreign dudes!
No.
Auntie, just tell me what
was the last bar you went to?
[CLAIRE] I don‘t even remember.
Sorry, I gotta go.
My man is here!
- [GIGGLES]
- [CALL DROPS]
Okay.
[PHONE THUDS]
Marla...
Cole...
What are you doing here?
S-Sorry...
Sorry, I know it's late.
I just wanted to check on you,
and I know you're shocked
with the revelation about April.
I'm okay.
Really?
Are you okay?
You don't seem like it.
It's because of Mom.
What happened to her?
I can't find her.
Let's go, I'll help you.
No, it's okay,
I can do this on my own.
Just go home.
Marla,
I won't leave you.
I'll always be here, okay?
Let's go.
I'll help you. I'll go with you.
I know how worried you are.
Please?
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CAR ENGINE HUMMING]
[METAL GATE SQUEAKS]
Ma!
Auntie!
[SONYA SULKING]
Ma, you're drunk again!
Where did you come from?
Take me back to the bar!
That Aunt Cindy of yours
is such a buzzkill.
I thought,
we‘re going to the...
other bar.
It's okay, Ma. Let's go inside.
- Come on.
- Hey! No, no, no!
I still want to drink...
I want to... celebrate!
[CHEERS]
Celebrate what?
Well...
your wonderful Papa...
has annulled our marriage,
so that he can
go and marry his mistress.
Cheers!
[CHEERS]
- Please be careful...
- Papa left us a long time ago.
Aren't we doing okay?
Are we okay?
Do I look okay?
Of course, you look great.
You're beautiful
even when you're drunk,
You always do.
Aww...
You‘re such a little liar,
like your Papa.
I'm not lying, Ma.
I mean, where else
would I get my charisma,
if not from you?
I didn't just get your looks,
I also got your fighting spirit,
okay?
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay. Let‘s go inside.
- Let's go, Auntie.
Come on, come on.
Oh! Oh...
It's Cole, Auntie.
Cole!
Javier?
Oh, wow! Long time, no see!
What are you doing here?
Auntie,
I'm just helping you get home.
It's nice to see you, Auntie.
[SONYA CHUCKLES]
I can‘t say the same
for you, dear.
Why'd you break up with Marla?
I mean, you're so lucky
that she chose you.
Anyone would be
so lucky to have her.
But you,
you just broke up with her?
As if you‘ll find...
someone better.
[MARLA] Ma, okay...
[COLE]
Not my finest moment, Auntie.
I admit it was stupid of me
to let Marla go.
You're right.
There‘s no one better.
Of course, I‘m always right!
That's why I'm trying
to get her back, Auntie.
Oh...
Cole, listen up.
If...
you hurt...
my baby again,
huh?
I'll rush to your house.
I will...
drag you by the hair
and drown you
in your fabulous swimming pool.
Understood?
Yes, Auntie.
[SONYA] Really?
[COLE] Really.
- Okay, okay, okay, come on.
- Let me help you, Auntie
Let's go, let's go, Mom.
- Hold on to me.
- Let's go inside, come.
Okay, there.
- Let's do it together.
- I wanna drink some more...
[MARLA] Oh, no. I think
you've had enough, Mom.
You've drank enough
for one week.
- [SONYA] Let's party...
- [MARLA] Okay.
- [MARLA] Oops! Wait!
- [COLE] Be careful.
- [SONYA] My gosh.
- [COLE] Watch your head.
[GATE SQUEAKS, CLOSES]
You know, Auntie's right.
I was so stupid.
If I could just go back
to that moment...
I wish I'd been stronger.
I shouldn't have let
my dad scare me.
I understand.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry I was a coward
when you needed me, Marla.
I let you down.
To be honest,
I haven't been able
to move on, either.
I think you should go.
Marla babe
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's okay...
even if I get kicked out
of school...
even if I graduate
without honors...
even if I lose my internship
at NASA...
I'd accept it all.
But please, Marla...
I just don't want
to lose you again.
Please give me another chance.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I get it.
Perhaps it was just
your trauma response.
Fear is so ingrained into you
because of your dad.
So, maybe you panicked
and you broke up with me.
I‘m sorry, babe.
Thank you.
Since it was April
who leaked our photos...
[COLE] Marla...
that's how much I love you.
I'd wait for you.
I'd never, ever leave you.
I promise.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
...maybe I can learn
to trust you again.
I promise.
I swear I'd do anything
to earn your trust back, Marla.
I'll wait for you.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
Girls,
cheers to winning the Hackathon!
- Slay!
And also, welcome to my home.
Thank you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ISOBEL] Mm. It's good.
[MARLA] Of course.
[ISOBEL] Nice one.
[GLASS CLINKS]
[CLEAR THROAT]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Isobel
What...
What did I drink?
Did you put in
some sleeping pills?
It‘s not sleeping pills.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What? Then what's this?
Did you poison me?
Is this... poison?
[ISOBEL] Chill!
I'm not gonna poison you yet.
[APRIL] Why can't I breathe?
- It's hot.
- Just kidding. Um...
[ISOBEL]
It's just a truth serum.
Truth serum?!
What is a freaking truth serum,
Isobel?!
It‘s a cocktail
of psychoactive drug-sedatives
like barbiturates
and scopolamine used to compel
people to reveal information
they otherwise withhold.
You spiked my drink?!
Why?
[MARLA] Actually...
it was my idea.
Isobel didn't wanna do this.
But it had to be done.
We need to know the truth,
April.
What are you talking about,
Marla?
Did you leak our nudes?
Huh?! Why would I do that?
Well, why indeed?
What are you talking about?
You saw their GC, didn't you?
You've read
the boys' messages.
You could have easily
manipulated those images.
And why would I do that, Marla?
[MARLA] Because you're
still mad at me
over the cheating scandal
before?
Are you joking?
That was history, Marla.
Besides, you were the ones
who approached me.
I was minding my own business
when you asked for my help.
Hey, girls, you know,
I think she's right.
She has a point.
We were the ones who approached
her in the first place.
Uh...
[APRIL] Why?
Who told you
that I leaked the photos?
Cole.
He showed me your video.
Why would you even believe Cole?
He‘s a liar!
Here.
Look at the video, April.
Isn't that you in the video?
April, that's not AI.
It's legit.
So tell me right now,
did you leak our photos?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what?
I don‘t need to explain
to all of you.
You know what, Marla,
you think you‘re better
than everyone else.
When in reality, you‘re just as
bad and horrible as everyone.
And you, Daphne?
You're just like a minion.
- You‘re like Budget Marla or...
- [DAPHNE SCOFFS]
...Marla Lite.
Don't you have
your own identity, huh?
You want me
to beat you up?
Budget Marla, huh?
And you, Nyx,
you act all sweet and sensitive,
when you're just
a people pleaser.
You want everyone to like you,
and you're so desperate for it!
Goodness, girl!
I'm trying to be neutral here.
And Isobel,
you act like you don‘t care.
Can you please stop the act?
Because you know, deep down,
nobody likes you.
Oh.
So the truth serum is effective.
[MARLA] So. are you done?
We won't stop
until you admit it.
So just tell us now,
did you leak our photos?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APRIL SIGHS]
Fine.
I did it.
Why?
Because Cole asked me to.
It was his idea.
I told you, Cole is a liar.
Cole's idea?
Why would he make you do that
just to rat you out?
I don't know, Marla.
He wants to get
on your good side?
I don't know!
It doesn't make sense, April.
He broke up with me!
I don't know!
What I know is Cole
is a dangerous person.
And I don't know
if you've noticed, but...
he‘s not the Cole
we used to know.
You can‘t trust him.
We can‘t trust you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Fine.
- I quit!
- [DAPHNE] Dream on.
You have no right to quit!
You‘re fired!
I quit first.
Shhh!
Come on, girls.
Who's getting fired?
Why this instant?
Can't we do like a...
warning?
Verbal warning,
written warning,
any warning?
Hey.
Consider this your warning,
April.
Stay out of our way.
[MARLA] Look at you...
pathetic,
manipulative,
desperate...
bitch.
You know what the worst part is?
I apologized to you.
I said sorry to you.
[APRIL SNIFFLES]
And you smiled to my face.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I thought we were friends.
You're no better
than your brother.
Cole is not the enemy.
You are.
So get the hell out of my house!
You don't belong here.
Go.
Get out.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Whatever.
[NYX] Hey.
Marla, you can't be serious
right now?
Feel free to follow her
if you want to.
Anybody who follows April
will be considered my enemy.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Cole!
Why'd you tell Marla
that I leaked their photos?
But that's the truth, right?
Right?
But you asked me to do it.
Hey.
Did I force you? Did I?
Now you're blaming me?
No.
There we have it.
It was your choice.
I did it for you, Cole!
I did it to help you.
Help me?
Or help yourself?
I didn't do it for revenge.
I don't care
that Marla ratted me out.
But I can‘t just stand here
and see you suffer
from Sir's hands.
You told me that it
will help your rank,
and so I helped you.
And maybe,
a part of me also hoped that
it'd bring us closer again.
We used to be there
for each other, Cole.
What happened?
Yeah.
Until the moment
Dad gave up on you,
when you got
to the lowest section
because you cheated, remember?
So here I am now,
reaping all the pressure
from the undivided attention
from Dad...
from Sir!
This is all your fault,
why all this is happening to me!
We shouldn't be fighting, Cole.
[BREATH QUIVERS]
We should be helping each other,
just like before.
[SNIFFLES]
Okay.
You want some advice?
I'll give you some advice.
You know, April,
all those crazy friends
of yours,
they're not your true friends.
They're not on your side.
April,
I'm just trying to protect you.
We're a team, remember?
We're siblings.
Liar.
You don't care about me.
You know what,
you're right.
[CHUCKLES]
You are right.
[RETREATING FOOTSTEPS]
[SNIFFLING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
[APRIL EXHALES DEEPLY]
Hey.
- [OBJECTS CLATTER]
- Wait,
let me help you.
May I see your hand?
Ouch!
- Sorry, sorry!
- Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You still call that a face?
Just kidding.
I just wanna make you laugh.
You're not funny.
I'm not?
Just joking! [CHUCKLES]
Don't be so sensitive,
I'm trying to help you here.
Why aren‘t you gloating?
I mean,
you warned me
that I could
get caught cheating.
You said,
this would happen.
You have every right to mock me.
Top one cheater.
And add insult to injury?
I know why you had to do it.
I warned you
not because I'm afraid
you'd get caught.
I warned you
because I know you'd
get double or triple
the beating you'd get from Sir
if you got caught.
See.
Look at yourself.
You look like a panda.
Just be careful next time, okay?
I was very careful, Cole.
One last subject.
But of course,
that stupid
human citation machine
had to ruin everything.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Playing Miss Behaved!
Marla?
Yes.
Your self-righteous friend.
Why are you smiling?
Hey.
Here I am helping you out,
and you're just after the tea.
Let me see your other cheek.
Want more gossip?
I'll press this real hard here.
Okay.
Cole,
aren't you tired of all this?
Don't you wanna leave?
Where'd we go, then?
Besides,
everything we need
is right here.
We can buy anything we want.
I know, I know.
We are provided for.
But, at what cost?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm always very fearful
of Dad.
I'm always afraid
to make mistakes.
Always trying to read his mood.
But,
it's tiring already.
Why don't we just leave?
Leave?
And what would we do?
Where'd we go?
How can we survive
without money?
We can work.
Hey, we haven't graduated yet.
What work?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
What if we work
at a fast food chain?
Wow.
Fast food?
- Yeah.
- Can you handle that?
With how fussy you are?
You can't even take
care of yourself, see?
I can do that.
Besides, I didn't do this
to myself.
If you want, then go ahead.
You have to come with me.
I'm not the only one
getting beaten here.
April.
You're my sister.
I love you, okay?
But I know
the future
that I want for myself.
I want to graduate with honors.
Study abroad.
Move to the US.
And,
of course, my lifelong dream
of working in NASA.
And finally be free.
I don't wanna be stuck with Dad.
I don't want us
to be his punching bag, okay?
I don't want a mediocre life,
and I can't do all that
if we will just work in
a fast food restaurant.
Our expenses would cost more
than our salary, wouldn't it?
I hope you know that.
Don't cry.
When will this end?
[SOBS]
I'm just here, okay?
I'm so tired, Cole.
[SOBBING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
"Marla, are we still good
for tomorrow?
I'll pick you up.
So excited to see you."
"I'm so sorry, Warren.
I'm sick with the flu.
I think
I can't make it tomorrow.
I'm really sorry."
"I hope you're okay.
Get well soon.
Let's just reschedule?"
"Thank you, Warren."
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, girls.
Let's get back to business.
Our next target is
April Javier.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]