I am...
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
I'm your...
guardian angel.
Your target is the hotel owner.
Shit!
Arms dealing is Roswell territory.
Boom.
But did I hear that right?
Ma'am Aemie is coming too?
What was it again?
I can't remember anymore.
Why are you asking
Auntie so many questions?
Girl, calm down.
I'm just curious.
There's going to be a meeting.
An underground meeting.
You mean we're about
to do something bad?
Why do they all have guns?
But why did all that happen?
What is it that you
really want me to know?
That...
That I'm a Mafia boss.
Uh...
Isn't that...
what you're asking me before?
You're just joking, right?
This is just a joke, right?
Because aren't people
in the Mafia bad?
You're not a bad person.
I'm telling the truth.
You mean you're
a bad person, Zeke?
Hey!
Guys!
Help me out here.
Is Dong really a bad person?
Wait.
You guys know it too?
You've known all this time?
That Zeke's a Mafia boss?
My husband...
is a Mafia boss.
But, Zeke...
What exactly is the Mafia?
Are they...
are they burglars?
Scam syndicates?
People like that?
Are they a cult?
People who steal slippers?
Is that why you're rich?
Zeke, seriously.
You could've just borrowed them.
Why did you have
to steal slip—
Ouch!
I'm part of an
underground society.
Sometimes, I steal...
other people's properties.
I pull down
every underground business
that poses a threat to us.
I hunt down those who try
to compete with my work.
Hunt down?
So you kill innocent people?
No.
I mean...
if I need to.
So that means you're
a bad person, Zeke?
Huh?
Have you killed a lot of people?
Yes.
It all started when I was eight.
After Mom's death.
My dad started to train me.
He taught me all the things
I needed to know.
About business,
and in the mafia.
Every morning...
I would wake up in pain.
My body was full of cuts
and bruises from training.
Uhh, Dad.
Kaizer's inviting me
to go to Jerson's house.
He has this new video game.
Wallace is there too.
No, you don't have time
for such an immature play.
Get back in your room
and prepare for training.
You need to be strong,
to avenge your mother.
Remember, you still
have a lot to learn.
But still,
I needed to learn.
I needed to learn
how to be numb.
Is that all you got, son?
Are you going to
end up like the rest?
Weak?
Pathetic?
At the age of 10,
I learned how to pull...
the trigger without mercy.
What?
Are you a coward?
Everyone around you
will die like your mother
if you stay spineless like that!
Kill him!
But Dad...
I said!
Kill him!
Sir!
Please don't, sir!
Have mercy, sir!
Please don't!
That's when I started
to become a killer.
to become...
Evil.
That was the birth
of the new me.
Merciless and cold-hearted.
I endured every curse and
humiliation my father threw at me.
He blamed me for Mom's death
because I couldn't protect her.
What could an eight-year-old
possibly have done?
The man is a damn sick moron.
My training wasn't fun.
It was survival.
It felt like...
I was playing hide-and-seek
with death every single day.
Not by choice.
But because...
I needed to learn the skills,
to hunt down...
the bastards who
murdered my mother.
I've never...
felt real love or care
since my mom died.
And I stopped believing...
that I'll ever feel
those things again.
I know a lot of terrible things
happened in your past, Zeke.
But you don't have
to keep living there.
And I'm sure that's what
your mom would've wanted too.
What do you mean?
I'm here for you.
I'll never leave you.
You don't hate me?
For who I am?
And for the things I've done?
I'll be honest with you, okay?
When you told me
you were a Mafia boss,
I got really scared.
But after you told
me everything...
I realized you're not
really a bad person, Zeke.
Because...
the Zeke I got to know
was never a bad person.
I love you, Zeke.
Even if you were the
most evil person in the world.
Can you say that
again for me, please?
Are you deaf or something, Zeke?
Come on! I said...
"Mahal kita."
In English.
I...
love—
I love you even more, wife.
Huh!
Why did he laugh?
Did I do something wrong?
Hey, maybe I should ask
someone to teach me how to kiss!
Maybe Kaizer?
No?
Oops! Porn!
- What the fuck?!
- Shit! Not you, boss!
- Mr. Roswell, wait! Don't!
- Don't!
A lot of women would be left mourning.
No, wait!
Aemie!
Oh, right. Right,
don't kill Kaizer, Zeke.
Don't.
- Mmm.
- Don't.
Give me one goddamn
reason and I'll spare his life.
Oh no!
Hey!
Uh...
Oh no! Is there a call-a-friend?
Hey! Wait! Wait!
This is so hard, let
me think first. Wait!
Uhm...
Oh no, I can't
think of anything.
Wait!
- Wait. Uhm...
- Aemie, hurry!
Oh! I got it! I got it!
Because...
I still need Kaizer to
teach me how to kiss.
Huh?
Boss, wait.
Mr. Roswell.
Fine, Zeke. Just kill Kaizer.
Oh, crap.
That's her husband?
Aemie is so lucky.
Where have you been, Grace?
We've been neighbors for a while,
yet you're still behind on the gossip.
Aren't you heading home yet?
It's getting late.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet, Amesyl.
Alright.
Go home.
Eat at your house.
Alright, Amesyl.
I'll get going first.
Yeah.
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
Don't worry.
I'll deal with it.
See you then.
Auntie?
Oh, why are you still awake?
It's still early.
Where have you been, Auntie?
I just went somewhere.
Why?
Is something wrong, Auntie?
Who were you talking to earlier?
You were even speaking English.
Huh?
Forget about that.
Oh.
No.
I was just practicing my favorite
lines from the movie I watched earlier.
You know, those
Hollywood movies.
Wait.
Niece.
It's getting late.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
You have an early
class tomorrow.
Alright.
Good night.
Those two really are
mother and daughter.
Should I tell cuz
about our adventure?
She might get jealous, you know?
It was like we were
in an action movie.
There were so many...
Bang, bang, bang.
And those guys.
Those really tall guys.
I love you.
Hey, where'd you get that, Dong?
Does it matter?
Of course.
Everything that
occupies space is matter.
Can't you just say,
"I love you too"?
I love you too.
But...
Come on, Dong.
You know my favorite
color is pink, right?
Red is the color of love.
But pink is the color of me.
Myself and I.
Where's your ring?
This is not it.
This one's very plain looking.
Let me get that.
Hey!
You're the one who took my ring?
No.
Why would I take it?
I bought a new one.
No way!
Seriously?!
Seriously.
You're the one who stole it.
You weren't taking care of it.
Seriously!
Do you know how worried I
was when it went missing?
And then you just took it—
I'm almost done.
As of today,
only one of those
bastards is still alive.
Is this about your mom, Zeke?
The others are dead?
I mean,
I was almost done
with my dreams.
But you arrived
and gave me another.
A dream I never imagined
I would want to fulfill.
Why are you dragging me
into your dreams, Dong?
I thought we're good now.
We're good, right?
You love me, right?
Dong.
Can you teach me how to shoot?
Why?
I'm always here to protect you.
Well...
Because...
No buts.
Oh, but what if it
happens again?
What if we're not together?
What if something
even worse happens?
How can I protect myself?
I should be able to protect
myself and protect you too.
No.
No buts, hubby.
You're going to teach
me how to shoot.
And that's final.
End of conversation.
Fine.
Really?
Yes!
Thank you!
How's everyone?
Where's ?
We got separated.
But he's on his way.
Sit down.
What happened?
Doing good?
You look pissed.
What happened?
Come here.
Any news on the boss's ex-wife?
Wait.
We're down to Young's last target, right?
What if I can't bring
myself to kill the last target?
Then you're dead.
So is she.
And Aemie too.
Along with everyone
important to her.
Is that what you want?
Hello, Baby Eisz!
You're so cute!
You're just too
adorable, Baby Eisz.
There are still so
many lights, Moo.
Your imagination
really runs wild, Moo.
Wow!
Cheers, Moo!
Cheers!
Is there anything else
we need to discuss?
Because if not,
I'm leaving.
Why are you in
such a hurry, Young?
Do I have to explain
everything to you?
Huh?
Young.
You better watch your tone.
Breakfast is ready.
Don't make me wait for too long.
I love you, wife.
Oh?!
Y'all got one of these?
Hmm?
Oh!
Hey, Dong!
Pink's my favorite color, right?
I know.
So—
You're just messing
with me, huh?
Eat first.
Uhm...
Ah, Dong.
Didn't you...
say you'd teach me how to shoot?
Yeah.
Later.
Huh?
Really?
Really!
Yes!
I can already
picture my training.
Watch this.
Please!
Don't!
No!
Drop your gun.
Come on, girl.
There we go.
Ouch!
Ow!
Oh my god!
Busted!
I have a stunt double.
You can leave!
I can handle this.
No.
No, no, no, no!
No, wife!
Please spare me!
I surrender.
Please!
No, wife!
Wife, please!
Don't!
Please spare me!
No!
Hey, woman.
What crazy things are
you imagining this time?
Oh, nothing.
I was just imagining
what it'd be like when
you teach me how to shoot.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure you
learn everything.
I said learn.
That doesn't mean you
can do whatever you want.
I'm still the boss.
Just a reminder.
That's not fair.
Ah, wife.
Hmm?
Can you keep it a secret?
That I'm a Mafia boss
in the Mafia world?
And also,
what happened at the hotel.
Mm.
Of course, Dong.
Your secret is safe with me.
Good.
Of course.
If he gets caught, then
I'll end up in jail too.
Right?
He really doesn't
think things through.
Come on.
Let's eat.
That girl earlier said
we looked good together.
Right?
She probably thought
we were dating.
As if?
You wish.
Because, you know,
this is you, and this is me.
We really look perfect
together, Momo.
Huh.
Why?
I'm this one?
Yeah.
- That's you?
- Mm.
We're not a match.
Why not?
Human and animal.
Not a match.
Because you're an animal.
Oh, Momo.
Hey!
Hello, guys!
Hey, Kevin!
Amesyl.
Hey.
Louie.
Cuz!
Hi, Louie!
Hi, Kevin!
Hi!
Sabrina Swansea.
Oh, hello!
Momo, I'm gonna head out now.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Cuz, I have a story to tell you!
An adventure!
Oh? What is it?
Too bad you weren't there.
We went to this
really fancy hotel.
Then it was like we were
inside an action movie.
Yeah, there were all
these really tall guys.
And they were all carrying...
I hope I won't run into anyone.
Zeke!
Aemie, carrying what?
Uh—
Uhm...
Carrying wine!
And then...
we filmed an action movie.
That's all.
Goodness.
That's it?
You could've just texted me.
Don't I get any food?
You can have this.
Wakwak left anyway.
He hasn't touched it yet.
Oh?
Are you looking for something?
Cuz, where's Moo?
Looks like he didn't
come to school today.
Huh?
I don't know.
Oh no, where could he be?
Where could—
Guardian angel!
Oh no!
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm fine.
And you look fine as well.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
She's so pretty, isn't she?
Hi, Fauzia!
- Hey.
Aemie.
As much as I would
love to see you, guys, all...
talking to each other.
Hopefully you'll
excuse us. Okay?
Hey!
You, new girl.
Watch your tongue.
I'm warning you.
- Hey, Cuz.
- What?
What?
Maybe I should rip that—
Cuz, cuz, cuz.
Just calm down. Sit first.
Sit down, sit down.
Let's go.
Keep saying "oops" and
I'll drag you out myself.
Who does that witch think
she is, treating you like that?
That's Fiona, Zeke's ex.
His ex-girlfriend?
Yeah.
She's just an ex-girlfriend.
That means I should
beat her up even more.
Come here.
Just relax, okay?
You know...
She's actually nice.
She's just a little weird.
Sometimes she's
kind of like you.
Me?
Why?
Why are guardian
angel, Fiona, Kevin,
and Kevin's
girlfriend all together?
Are they friends?
Hey!
Come on, spill the tea.
You gossip queens
probably know something.
You guys are so stingy!
Are they friends?
We're here.
Hi, guys!
- Ma'am Aemie.
Yo, Aemie.
Are these guys really from a mafia group?
They don't even
look intimidating.
They're actually really nice.
Wow!
So many!
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe,
which one should I choose?
One, two.
This one? Oh, this one?
Ow!
I thought you were going
to teach me how to shoot.
Later.
Fine.
If you won't teach me how to
shoot, then I'll just learn how to kiss.
Kaizer?
Huh?
What is it?
Kaizer.
Teach me how to kiss.
Damn it, Aemie. I know I'm
handsome, but I still value my life.
Try Lerwick.
He's the expert.
Yeah!
Lerwick.
What?
She wants you to
teach her how to kiss.
Hey!
What? Why me?
You!
I know I'm an
expert at that, but...
Come on, man.
A lot of women
would cry if I died.
Pfft!
Coffins for sale.
Buy one, take one.
Hearse for rent.
Hey!
You guys won't teach me?
It's not like that, Aemie.
It would be better if Boss would be
the one to teach you.
Right?
Mhm.
Let's go!
Yay!
Hey!
Are all of these ours?
Ow!
Why'd you always have to flick my hand?
Do not touch the
guns until I say so.
There are many types of guns.
But the type of gun
that's best for you,
is this.
Semi-automatic pistol.
Perfect.
Is it easy to use, Zeke?
A beginner's a beginner.
But there's no reason you
can't learn to shoot with this.
I see.
Can I have two of those?
You know what?
Let's go home.
Hey!
Why?
We haven't even started,
and we're already going home?
Because you talk too much.
I was only making a suggestion.
Shh!
Focus.
Can I try it now?
Like I said, later.
This is a semi-automatic pistol.
The magazine holds the rounds,
and slides easily,
quickly into the grip.
The trigger pull is lighter,
allowing you to fire
multiple rounds quickly.
I like that one!
But not too quick.
You're amazing!
So many!
Me too, I want that. That many!
Please? I also want too. It's my turn.
I can do it.
I'm going out for a bit.
Go ahead.
Wow!
How did you become so good?
Finally, you have the courage
to pull out your gun.
The question is, do you
have the guts to pull the trigger,
Nico Jeisz Young?
I'm going to be a Mafia?
Why are you here?
This place looks familiar.
And you think this place
has answers to your questions?
Finally.
You have the courage to pull out your gun.
Who are you?
What?
Okay, okay. Where do I go?
Where are you?
Whether you like it or not, wife...
life...
is really not fair.
If not you,
who's behind it?
Dead?