[Episode 8]
- What's in here?
- I'm not sure.
Probably employees' belongings.
Can we open it and take a look?
Of course.
Captain Zhou, there's nothing here.
Captain, we've finished collecting evidence
from the liquor.
We didn't find anything unusual.
Take care, officers.
Let's go.
Let's go, Yi.
Take your own stuff home.
And starting tomorrow,
you don't need to come here anymore.
Why?
Who do you think you are?
I don't repeat myself.
Let's part on good terms.
Don't taint my livelihood.
About that contract today...
Chen Yi.
Do you want to have dinner together tonight?
I have to spend Spring Festival with family.
After the Spring Festival,
wherever you want to go, I'll drive you there.
I told you your people were reliable.
I'll have legal contact you
about the contract details.
Great.
See her out. Linda, this way, please.
Bye.
Take care.
What's all the noise?
Bin, Mr. Zhai. He framed me.
He said I brought in counterfeit liquor.
How could I?
I've worked diligently here for so many years.
- How could I possibly do such a thing?
- Manager Zhao, come with me.
Come with me. Bin, you...
If you have something to say,
just say it to me.
It isn't like that. You little punk, just wait.
Stop arguing.
Help me take the lid off the pot.
We're here to pay New Year's greetings.
- Uncle Zhou.
- Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Uncle Zhou. Wen.
- Come on in.
- Come in, come in.
- Are you two cooking?
- Yes.
You even put up the couplets.
Nice.
You brought things too?
- Of course. We can't come empty-handed.
- It's New Year's.
- Jing, come here.
- What is it?
This is just for you.
I have a gift too?
What is it?
This is a secret between girls.
You guys, no peeping!
Happy New Year, Jing.
Happy New Year.
Chinese New Year isn't until tomorrow.
Isn't this gift a little early?
It's about the festive spirit.
Don't always be so old-fashioned, right?
- Is the food ready? I'll go help you.
- Not yet.
Let's go.
Fine. Then we'll stay out of it.
You just wait to eat.
Listen, we have your favorite roast goose.
I waited in line for half an hour.
There are plenty of dishes at home.
Here. Put it here.
[Phoenix to the Rising Sun]
Super big beans.
Here, have a shrimp.
You eat too.
This soup is really good, Jing.
It was stewed for a long time.
Jing's cooking keeps getting better.
That makes Zhou and me feel more at ease.
Even if you go study away from home later,
you can take care of yourself, right?
I haven't decided where to apply yet.
I might not get used to somewhere too far away.
A big city would still be better.
Let's see how your scores turn out.
There are surely more opportunities outside.
You're young. I'm all for you
going out and making your own way.
Anyway, Wen and I will always be here.
Whenever you miss home, you two can come back.
I'll think about it.
I'll see if there's a chance.
I'll think about it too.
The college entrance exam is half a year away.
It's okay.
All right.
We're happy today,
so let's not talk about school.
Next,
we have something serious to tell you two.
Go ahead.
Next year,
we'll be able to give you red envelopes.
You're getting married?
At the end of the year.
Let me say this first.
Once we're married,
don't call us "Uncle Zhou" and "Sister Wen."
It messes up the family hierarchy.
Then what should we call you?
Zhou?
That's good! Make me sound younger.
Don't listen to him. Call him brother-in-law.
Two happy occasions at once.
Let's have a little drink.
Sure. Just a little.
What about mine?
You can have orange juice.
You're still young. Don't drink.
Next year.
Here, Zhou.
"Brother-in-law."
Good. That's fine. Thank you.
All right, then.
- Happy New Year!
- May everything go smoothly.
Congratulations on the wedding.
May your studies go well.
I hope you get into a good university.
Come on.
So beautiful.
This one is good.
Be careful.
Step back a little. Careful.
This is the one bad thing about Teng City.
It's this cold and there are still mosquitoes.
This liquor is good.
Beats that bottle you showed me
from District Seven.
Teng City really is a good place.
At least here, no one asks where you come from.
There are opportunities everywhere.
I have to correct you there.
Opportunity and danger
have always gone hand in hand.
The bigger the opportunity,
the greater the danger.
Understand?
I know you've kept your distance from them.
And you do your work properly. You're reliable.
But I still want to remind you.
Kuangxia has never been very clean.
Uncle Zhou.
You went to District Seven
not because of counterfeit liquor, right?
I'm a public servant.
Do you think I can answer that?
Fine. I won't ask.
That's enough for tonight.
Wen, why aren't you going home
for New Year this year?
There are too many troublesome things
back home.
I'm not going back this year.
Once things are settled,
I'll go back next year.
Besides,
you have the college entrance exam this year.
I came to keep you company.
Is something on your mind?
You clever little thing.
Since when can you tell
if someone has something on their mind?
I can feel it.
Jing.
What major do you want to study in university?
Finance or psychology?
You'd be good at people-facing work,
and at reading people.
That way your talent wouldn't go to waste.
But maybe that's not good either.
That kind of work can wear you out easily.
Maybe accounting, although...
Don't change the subject.
You wouldn't understand even if I told you.
You're still young.
This is what growing up is like.
You run into a lot of frustrating things.
There are a lot of worries.
You're still so young.
Don't worry about anything else.
Just focus on living happily, okay?
Save those unhappy things
for when you're older.
If having worries means growing up,
then I'm already grown up.
All right. Then I hope...
you become a happy adult.
Okay?
Or maybe...
do you have any private stories,
or first-crush stories you want to tell me?
I don't.
- You don't?
- Really!
You can tell me.
I definitely won't tell your brother.
I won't tell anyone.
- It's awkward.
- Is there one?
- No.
- No?
Your face mask is peeling off.
Let me see.
Don't change the subject.
Don't dodge it. Is there one? Tell me.
You're making me laugh my mask off.
I watched you two grow up.
I can barely count as your elder.
I really don't want to see you and Jing
in any danger.
Don't worry.
I won't let any stain touch her.
She'll be like girls from other families.
She'll go to school and live her life.
She'll have a normal life.
Sometimes you need to think more
about yourself too.
Don't worry.
No matter what, I will protect you both.
Go to sleep.
I won't be coming over tonight.
Miao Jing has winter break classes
in senior year.
I'll reply to Linda.
I have to go. Something came up.
No, no. Who...
What are you trying to do? Talk.
Nothing. It's a misunderstanding.
I was just angry, so I came to scare her.
Nothing else. I swear.
It's really a misunderstanding.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
- Let go. So many people are watching.
- It's fine.
A fight?
Don't let there be a next time.
Are you hurt?
No.
Why are you wearing so little?
How come you're not here when we had plans?
I missed you.
What's wrong?
- Miao Jing, go pour me a glass of water.
- Okay.
Miao Jing, come downstairs for dinner.
- Can you still drink?
- I'm fine.
If you can, let's play another round.
Sure. Let's keep playing
that dice game from earlier.
All right. Come on.
Really?
Three fives. I call.
Open.
You really do have them.
How about I drink one for you?
You really have had too much.
- Can I drink for my boss?
- Sure, sure.
Come on. I'll drink with him. I'll drink too.
- Let's go again.
- Impressive!
Impressive. You can really drink.
Sir, I feel like you're not convinced.
We're out of liquor. I'll go add some for you.
Fill it up.
Yi, what's been going on with you lately?
You've been acting weird.
Yeah, something feels off.
How?
It's just... my chest feels restless.
I can't sleep at night.
I keep thinking
about all kinds of messy things.
It's annoying.
This is pretty normal.
You got someone on your mind.
So who's on your mind? Do I know her?
Get lost.
I'm analyzing it for you.
In your situation,
you'll be fine once you get a girlfriend.
It's about time you got one.
Otherwise, you'll really start acting abnormal.
I shouldn't have run my mouth.
Really?
Of course. Would I lie to you?
Get a girlfriend,
and you won't feel so restless.
What are you talking about?
- Nothing.
- What is it?
Linda, Yi said he wants a girlfriend.
He wants a girlfriend?
Didn't you tell me before
that you had a kid at home?
I was joking.
Joking? Then which part was the joke?
Was having a kid the joke,
or was wanting a girlfriend the joke?
What if I said...
I wanted to be your girlfriend?
Would you say yes?
I don't know how to be in a relationship.
Then...
Let's start with going on dates.
Come on.
Miao Jing, let's go.
Why don't you stay home and review?
After your college entrance exam,
I'll take you to the amusement park.
No. I'm going. I already told Bo.
You're wearing lipstick?
That looks great.
- Yi.
- Let's take a photo together. Come on.
Listen to me. I found you the perfect spot.
- A little more that way, a little closer.
- Closer.
Okay. Come on.
Good.
Got it. Come on.
Three, two, one.
- Looks good.
- Beautiful.
So pretty. One more.
- Another pose.
- A bit closer.
Three, two, one.
Oh my!
You made it look like a family portrait again.
Let them take it.
- Come here.
- Let's take another one.
Fine.
Come on. Three...
Don't sulk. Come on, look nicer.
Three, two, one.
Good. Nice.
This one looks good too.
Come on.
Great. Together. Come on.
Closer.
Come on, say cheese.
Three, two, one. Cheese.
Good. Let's take another one.
Is it our turn yet?
Soon. The ticket check is right up ahead.
Let's go.
Really nice.
Let me see.
Yeah.
Do you want to sit with us?
There are five of us together.
Excuse me.
Tickets.
No.
- Let's go.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Selfish.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
- What?
- This way. I'll...
- This way, Chen Yi.
- Let's go over here.
- Let's go.
- Let's go to that one.
- Let's go too.
Teng City is actually a pretty nice place.
Coming here to look
for business opportunities was a smart choice.
Then what do you like most about it?
My home is here too.
I think this place is nice too.
Easy. Comfortable.
Everything feels simpler.
Your hair.
They kissed. They kissed.
Yi finally gave away his first kiss.
Shut up.
You have a pimple.
- There it is.
- Did they just kiss? Did they?
I think so.
Then what's he still restless about?
Didn't he just give away his first kiss?
Look at them.
The two of them just...
We have a kid here.
Fine.
There you go, acting like an adult,
going on about "kids."
Try this.
- Here.
- Let me do it, let me do it.
- This one.
- Let me help you.
It's fine. I'll do it myself.
Come on. Take some first.
Let me say something.
Let's welcome Linda to Teng City.
Welcome.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
I don't know much about fish,
but tofu is Yi's favorite.
And on the way here,
he specifically told me to order one for you.
- I want some tofu.
- Thank you.
Yi, you won't get jealous
if I serve her food, right?
- Go ahead.
- I mean, you should serve her some too.
Serve her more. Wouldn't it be
weird if I kept serving people food?
- Come on, quick.
- Yeah.
Yi, hurry. Get her some.
One more?
May I?
Yes.
- Thank you.
- Food from Yi must feel different.
Is that so? Then I have to try it.
Of course.
It must taste much better than what I served.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- It's not good.
- Did you get scolded by a teacher today?
Learn some manners.
Eat your food.
- What's wrong?
- It's rude to talk nonstop while eating.
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
I'm a little curious.
Are you two really siblings?
I don't mean anything by it.
I just think you're different in every way.
You don't look alike.
Your temperaments don't match either.
You look like someone from the streets.
And your sister is such a nice, naive girl.
Exactly. She doesn't know anything.
They're not actually related by blood.
But now they're closer than family.
Now that you're here, you're family too.
Then what do you think we are?
That depends on what he thinks.
Cheers.
Come on. Cheers.
- You're our sister-in-law.
- Here. Sister-in-law.
Linda, you didn't know Yi can cook, did you?
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
- You can cook?
- Don't catch a cold.
I'm not cold.
Can you make this tofu?
I do all the cooking at home.
You cook? That's impressive.
Is my cooking good?
Yes.
Her cooking really is good.
Yi's cooking is even better.
Then if I get a chance,
can I come to your home and try your cooking?
- How about tomorrow?
- I have an exam tomorrow.
Then go take your exam.
She can try Yi's cooking first.
Yi is an amazing cook.
Aren't you free tomorrow?
Well, I'll buy groceries tomorrow. Tell Yi
what you want to eat, and he'll let me know.
- Sure.
- Alright. I'll just...
- Great.
- Tell Bo, yeah.
Then I'll bring over the cake
I brought specially from Lingang.
Great! Really great!
- That's fantastic.
- Then it's a plan.
All right?
- It's a deal, Chen Yi. It's a deal.
- I can eat it.
I'll buy you some groceries tomorrow,
and let Yi really show you what he can do.
His cooking really is pretty good.
Do you like it?
No.
It belongs to someone else.
I have to return it tomorrow.
I'll buy you a new one on the weekend.
I don't want one.
It's fine. I'll buy it for you.
Focus on studying.
Don't get caught up in all that flashy makeup.
It doesn't suit you.
Here.
This shirt was just washed.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to me.
Your business has nothing to do with me.
I drank too much yesterday.
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Do you like it? Consider it my apology.
No need. I'm not mad.
Then it's not an apology.
Consider it a gift for you.
Give it to your girlfriend.
Anyway,
I can't wear things like this at school.
She's not my girlfriend.
Just take it.
From now on, if you're angry or anything,
just tell me directly.
Don't hold it in.
Don't give me the silent treatment.
This doorway opening is too small.
There are only a few days left.
How are we supposed to fix it?
What a pain!
Can't you just take a quick look
and let us start?
Did you just graduate
and don't know how work works?
Move faster.
No. Hu, look.
The main hall opening has reached 300.
The load-bearing capacity
of the lintel material isn't compliant.
Not compliant?
Then just make the size a little smaller.
You get what I mean?
Make it smaller? No.
The drawings have been approved
and the walls have been measured.
It's not as easy as you make it sound.
There are a lot of other things involved.
We can't just do it because you say so.
- It is that simple.
- Yeah. We can do it.
- He doesn't understand me.
- No.
You're the smart one. Teach him.
No, I understand what you mean, but...
Handsome, just do it the way I say.
College graduates don't know how to work.
The new project manager Mr. Zhai sent is here.
So what? Do I need to go welcome him?
Do you know his name?
I think his name is Chen Yi.
Chen Yi?
Yes. We only managed to land
this fat contract thanks to him.
Isn't he the one
who hooked up with the Lingang businesswoman?
Now he's here to share the profits, right?
That's arrogant as hell.
The Kuangxia project is chasing us like mad.
And this is who they send from above?
He doesn't understand anything.
How are we supposed to work with him?
If everyone were professionals,
why would they need us?
As long as the project payment is fat enough.
Still, outsiders shouldn't lead professionals.
It's too disrespectful.
Enough.
There are some issues.
You can read drawings?
I can understand some of the dimensions.
That's still better
than those people who know nothing.
I don't think I've seen you before.
I just got here and wanted to
walk the site first.
You're working
on construction sites this young?
You've had it rough. Nice muscles.
Why didn't you keep studying?
I wasn't good at it. It wasn't for me.
In today's world, even graduates
from Hai City University have to come back.
Tiny salary.
Taking orders from clueless amateurs.
Why haven't you started work?
Why are you still chatting?
Ignore him.
Am I paying you for nothing?
Hu.
Manager Chen.
Why didn't you tell us you were coming?
Manager Chen, you came at just the right time.
The plans and drawings
for this project are all over here.
I've handled everything.
It's all under control.
Look.
The safety helmets are paper-thin.
The construction isn't following the drawings.
Is this how you manage a site?
Is that so?
The helmets have already been arranged.
The next batch will arrive soon. Don't worry.
We'll switch to grade-4 helmets this week.
Since you're free right now,
go arrange it immediately.
Understood. I'll go right now.
I'm leaving.
Next time, arrange a better helmet for me.
- Manager.
- Got it?
Liu Jun.
Chen Yi.
- Chen Yi.
- Xu Lin Feng.
Sorry, Manager Chen.
I didn't recognize who you were just now.
It's fine. You were saying
you didn't stay in Hai City.
What's wrong with Hai City?
It's mainly the cost of living.
It's not easy to live with dignity
in a big city.
Back in university,
I relied on money from my family.
Exactly. That internship barely covered rent.
All right. Tell me the details.
[Teng City Experimental No.1 High School]
Miao Jing.
Miao Jing, bye.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
What's with that look?
Can't I come pick you up?
What has he been busy with lately?
Linda's project is almost finalized.
He's been going all over the place
with the clients lately.
He's also worried it isn't safe
for you to walk alone at night.
So he asked me to come take you home.
No, don't go.
Three threes.
Four fives.
Four fives? I have them. I have three.
I win.
Drink.
You won again.
Zhai, then I'll finish it.
I'm going to win.
- Again, let's go again.
- Come on, come on.
Yi.
Four fives.
Four sixes.
Do you have any sixes?
Here. Mine are all sixes.
Let me look.
I don't have any.
Then I win. Mine are all sixes.
I lost again.
Zhai, I lost again.
I've finished my drink already.
Come on, Yi.
Isn't this the French liquor Bin got?
It tastes awful.
I can't tell good from bad either.
But gifts from Mr. Zhang must be good.
Mr. Zhang puts special care
into anything involving you.
He even chooses the gifts himself.
Don't be fooled by how Bin is now.
Once he has money, he starts squandering.
When we were young,
we grew up drinking loose liquor.
Why drink this kind of stuff?
I actually envy the bond you two have.
You've been together for so long.
You're no different from family now, right?
Yi.
I can tell. You're not an ordinary man.
You chose to work for me. Why?
Do you want to become my family?
I wouldn't go that far.
But I know I can make money with you.
If I can make money, I'm set.
Well said.
Zhai.
- Zhai.
- Come, drink this.
Drink this. Pour it for me.
This is the right taste, I'm telling you.
That's enough.
- That's a lot.
- Drink a bit more.
Make up for the ones earlier.
Yi, lock down those Lingang clients,
and you're set!
- I'll do my best.
- Cheers.
Finish it.
Come on.
Zhai, I'm going to win it back.
Win it back.
This doesn't seem right, Zhai.
I'll straighten it out.
Right in front of me?