[Episode 9]
Yi. Mr. Zhang has been waiting for you.
Bin.
Did you drink?
A little.
How are things with the project?
Moving forward steadily.
The whole main beam can be handed
over next week.
If Kuangxia can work
with the Lingang businesspeople long-term
and shift into construction sites,
then my investment will be worthwhile.
Well.
The inspection team will come here to check
on companies.
You need to pay attention.
Keep an eye on Mr. Zhai for me too.
Drink less.
Have you eaten?
I have.
What about you?
Are you dating Linda?
What did you say? I didn't hear you.
Nothing.
How has your revision been lately?
Don't talk if you don't feel well. Drink this.
Miao Jing.
Actually, not staying
in Teng City is a good thing.
A fresh start.
Together?
I'm going to sleep.
[Teng City Experimental No. One High School]
- It's okay.
- Good.
Everyone, look this way.
Get ready.
Three, two, one.
Cheese.
We graduated.
- Sign my school uniform.
- Do you like blue or purple?
If you don't do it before graduation,
you won't get another chance.
Use this one.
Forget it.
Miao Jing.
Sign your name.
Once we're separated in different places,
we'll have to rely on this as a keepsake.
Where do you two want to go have fun?
- Right here?
- Anywhere you want.
If you don't sign it, I'll make you sign on me.
Can I sign my name here?
Wait for me.
- Wait for me.
- Good luck.
Miao Jing, can you sign one for me too?
Sure.
Why didn't you ask me to sign?
Well, where's your school uniform?
I'll sign one for you too.
No need.
Who are you saving that for?
It must be the person most worth remembering
from these three years.
No. I just didn't bring it.
May your future be bright.
You too.
Come on.
You haven't signed my school uniform yet.
Miao Jing, can you sign mine?
Sure. Got it. Thanks, man.
Let's drink together another day.
Sure.
The food is here. Hurry up and eat.
Why are you still in the mood to eat?
News just came in.
The inspection team's watching us.
What do we do?
There shouldn't be any issue.
Your money all went into the project, right?
The blank tax receipts we used before...
Got rid of all of them.
The shell companies
that cooked the books are registered as closed.
Even if they trace it back to us,
they'll just go through the motions.
They have no evidence.
If you're still worried,
get someone to make contact.
Let's sound them out.
Moving forward, do you think Yi can be trusted?
Didn't I tell you before?
Yi...
He gets things done, looks respectable,
and knows how to handle things.
But...
This concerns both our fortunes.
I don't feel safe handing it to an outsider.
Eat more.
You make roast goose,
but you don't eat roast goose.
Don't I order extra for you every time?
So troublesome.
If I'd known being rich was this troublesome,
I wouldn't have gotten rich.
I should've just kept selling roast goose.
Is that enough?
Enough.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
No need to thank me.
One mango pomelo sago.
Sure.
Did something happen lately?
Why are there so many police cars?
They're probably helping some team check
into a tax thing.
I don't really understand what it is.
Anyway, I heard they're not just strict
in District Seven.
Even Kuangxia, the leading company around here,
is under heavy inspection.
Forget it. It has nothing to do
with ordinary people like us.
You just study hard.
Don't get mixed up with those street people.
I just heard the police cars during self-study.
Sorry. The number you've dialed is unavailable.
Hello, Bo.
What's Chen Yi doing?
Why isn't he answering his phone?
Yi is with Linda.
Miao Jing. Are you asleep?
Miao Jing?
[Something came up. I can't pick you up.]
[What is it?]
[Construction Department]
Look.
The number of examinees increases every year.
The score cutoff keeps rising too.
Based on past years, to get
into Jiaohai's science or engineering programs,
you'll need at least this much.
And if you want to apply
for information technology,
mechanical engineering, international trade,
or other popular majors like that,
your score needs to be even higher.
Can both arts and science students apply
for economics and law?
Yes. Political science and law are
in a different school from ours.
Anyway, the higher your score, the better.
By the way,
the second mock exam is over, right?
How did Miao Jing do?
Just all right.
Top ten in the top class at No.1 High School.
That's good. Then she's set, right?
Get off work early. Thanks.
No problem.
Hello?
Are you out of school?
I looked up some application information.
The major you wanted was related
to law and politics, right?
I'm studying. We'll talk later.
What do you want to eat after school?
I'll bring it back for you.
Anything.
[Family (1/1): Miao]
What time is the flight?
Yuedong Airport.
Okay.
All right. I'll go over.
- You scared me!
- Are you going to the airport?
- To see a friend off.
- Then I'll go with you.
What's the rush? I'm not going now.
Go study.
My coworker graduated from Jiaohai University.
With your second mock score, getting
into Hai City University shouldn't be an issue.
You just need to think more about your major.
I never said I wanted to apply to Hai City.
Fine. Then focus on reviewing first.
Who are you going to see off?
Linda. Her flight is tonight.
I need to see her off.
Then help me review vocabulary first.
You're not short on these few minutes anyway.
Destiny.
Eternity.
Forever.
Sign my school uniform.
What should I write?
Whether in Teng City or anywhere else,
we'll always be together.
We'll never be apart.
[Good luck on the College Entrance Exam]
Leaving so suddenly?
Businesspeople have to know
which way the wind is blowing.
When you already smell blood
in the water, you run.
A few days ago, through me,
Zhai Feng Mao ordered a batch of
premium Pu'er tea at a Lingang auction house.
Was it a gift for...
What a shame.
Kuangxia is only thinking
about transforming now.
It's already a little too late.
Kuangxia is in deep?
Put it this way, Kuangxia has gotten too bold.
In the past few years,
they've become less and less restrained.
Their tax receipts are guaranteed
to be found once there's an investigation.
In short, that ship is destined to sink.
I'm afraid you'll be dragged
down sooner or later.
Chen Yi.
Do you want to seriously consider leaving
with me?
Let's do business overseas?
I promise it's a hundred times better
than eating dust here every day.
Thank you, but no.
Miao Jing has the college entrance exam
in a few days.
I have to stay home and cook for her.
I can't leave.
Honestly.
Your intercity flight number 13184
will be taking off shortly.
Go be her cook, then.
- Passengers who have not yet boarded,
- You brat.
Please go to Gate Two for boarding immediately.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
College Entrance Victory Combo.
One hundred points isn't enough anymore.
Seven hundred points.
Guaranteed Tsinghua or Peking University.
Top Scholar Congee.
And this. I've never dressed like this before.
Then why aren't you wearing a qipao,
which means "victory from the start"?
Are you crazy?
Hello?
I won't be going to the construction site
these two days. I can't get away.
When you took Linda to the airport,
did she say anything?
She wanted to poach me from Zhai Feng Mao
and have me work for her. I'm not going.
I still have a major investment
to take care of.
What major investment?
Eat.
Then I'll eat more and score higher.
Check again. Do you have your identity card
and exam admission ticket?
Do you know which exam room?
I have everything. Exam Room 36.
I checked last time.
Good.
Also, don't be nervous.
Pay attention to
whatever the teachers tell you.
I'm not nervous.
Good.
You can bring water, right?
How many times have you asked me?
Just be my driver.
Wait for me to become the top science scorer
and bring honor to the family.
We're not even on the same household register.
Whose family honor?
After the exam,
I'll take you out for a big meal.
Check your identity card
and exam admission ticket again...
Stop! You've said it countless times.
You're making me nervous.
Don't be nervous.
Just perform as you normally do.
- Don't think about anything else.
- Got it.
All right, students.
You may start entering now.
Everyone go in. Parents, step back.
Then I'll go in.
Off you go. Don't be nervous.
Do your best.
I'll take you out
for a big meal after the exam.
- I'm going.
- Go ahead.
Good luck.
We will now show the sealed test paper bags.
[Subject: English]
[Subject: Integrated Subjects]
[Subject: Physics]
It's over. It's over!
Miao Jing, here.
Here. Here!
Here!
Let's go.
Careful. What's the rush?
I think I did really well.
That's good. That's great!
How did it feel?
I think I did really well.
Is this for me?
Yi is being romantic, Miao Jing.
Do you know the meaning of sunflowers?
What?
It means sunflower seeds are really tasty!
Isn't it funny?
My lame joke was pretty lame.
Why are you two blushing?
You're the same color as your clothes.
All you think about is food.
You two go back and watch the place.
I'm taking the college student out to eat.
Aren't we going to eat?
You can go back to the construction site
and eat boxed meals.
Let them...
You're the best!
Celebrate properly. Bye!
I don't want to eat out. Let's eat at home.
But we won't have time to cook when we're home.
Just see what you feel like eating later.
Let's go.
I want to eat at the coffee table.
Why? Where are you going?
Isn't that stupid?
What are you doing?
Miao Jing.
Look.
It's nice.
Look how you butchered that pomelo. Be careful.
It smells good.
When do you fill out your university choices?
The twenty-eighth. There's still time.
I checked Teng City Normal's past cutoffs.
I'm definitely above them.
You're really not considering Jiaohai?
Hai City has better resources.
And it isn't that far from home.
I can't even ask? Such a temper.
There's still some time before applications.
Let's talk about it later. Okay?
[Blessed that you came, blessed that we met.]
- Does this tightness feel right?
- I think it can be a little tighter.
Sure. I'll adjust it for you.
And this veil...
- Spread it out a bit more. Okay.
- Sure, I'll do it.
Miss, you really have excellent taste.
This gown only arrived at our shop yesterday.
- It's a new style.
- Really?
- It suits your temperament perfectly.
- Thank you.
- Is there anything else you'd like adjusted?
- This is fine. It's quite good.
Okay.
We'll iron all these creases
for you before then.
Don't worry.
Remember to fix the cuff and the wrinkled parts
before handing it to me.
Let's see what she'll choose.
Wen.
This is about right. Put that away.
Look. What do you think of this one?
It's beautiful. You look good in anything.
That's right, miss.
You have such a special presence.
You look just like the model
in the sample card.
No matter which one I wear,
you just say it looks good.
You're brushing me off just like Zhou Kang An.
Since we're here anyway,
do you want to try one too?
No. I don't need one.
It's not like you can only wear one
when you're getting married.
- Just try it.
- That's right, miss.
Tell me what style you like,
and I'll bring it for you.
Our girl really has grown up.
She's getting prettier and prettier.
Jing. Do you have a boy you like?
No.
Really?
I see. Girls grow up and can't be kept at home.
Once they grow up,
they'll start hiding things from adults.
Is there one? Is there someone you like?
There is someone.
I always think of him and want to see him.
But once I see him, I'm afraid we'll part.
Jing. Young feelings are rare and precious.
Be brave. Don't leave yourself with regrets.
Getting married is such a hassle.
It's exhausting.
You little brat, stop making sarcastic remarks.
When you get married someday,
you'll know whether it's a hassle.
Let me show you something good.
Pretty, right?
What's that face?
I'm thinking, Wen has such good taste.
Would she really like this kind of gold ring?
You don't understand. You're too young.
Girls all like gold.
Diamonds may be sparkly and shiny.
But they don't hold value like gold.
What about you? Are you seeing anyone?
I'll wait until Miao Jing finishes university.
I'm not considering it for now.
What does your marriage have to do
with her going to university?
You've been with Wen for so long.
Why did you wait until now to get married?
It's a long story.
When I first started working,
I didn't have much saved.
Her family already didn't think much of me.
How could I have the nerve
to bring up marriage?
Now I've worked
for a few years and saved some money.
I also wanted to
make a couple more achievements.
At least I'll have something to offer her
after she marries me, right?
A lot of people must have pursued Wen.
Aren't you afraid
she'd get tired of waiting and dump you?
Whose side are you on?
But honestly, I did feel a bit of pressure.
See? I just joined CID and solved a few cases.
So I immediately brought some fine tea
and cigarettes
to visit my future father-in-law
and get the marriage settled.
You have to seize the moment.
When you start your own family,
you'll understand.
One small move affects everything.
And I need to remind you.
Don't rely on being young and hot-blooded.
If you want a good life in the future,
don't do anything you'll regret.
Hear me?
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
Where are you?
We ordered already.
Stop rushing us. We're downstairs.
What about you?
Here.
Look what I brought you.
Your favorite.
My favorite aged Pu'er tea.
Thank you.
Why did the fitting take so long?
Are you tired?
Wen treats me the best.
Look at Yi.
He's more attentive to Miao Jing
than you are to me.
I just praised you,
and you're already getting careless.
- This big drumstick is for Jing.
- Thank you.
Here, Wen. Have some chicken.
Jing.
Have you thought about where you want to apply?
She just finished her exams,
and you're asking this?
Can't you read the room?
I'm just asking.
Miao Jing is smart and hardworking.
Her score definitely won't be low.
I'll stay in Teng City.
I think Teng City Normal is pretty good.
You don't want to go out and see the world?
For university,
you should go out and broaden your horizons.
Teng City Normal is good,
but Teng City is a little small.
Right?
My home is here.
I can't bear to go too far.
Miao Jing.
Don't tell me some punk boy tricked you
into staying in Teng City together.
I... I can't bear to...
I'm the one who can't bear to let her go.
All right.
It's just the two of you at home.
Of course you can't bear to part, right?
Let's eat.
Come on, eat more.
Is there not enough food?
I'll go downstairs and order two more dishes.
Yi, come on. Come downstairs with me.
You eat first.
Jing, don't mind him. It's fine.
Don't worry. I'll talk to him properly later.
What did Uncle Zhou ask you just now?
Nothing.
Just a couple of questions about Kuangxia.
Impossible. When I was upstairs,
I heard you two talking there the whole time.
I heard your voices. You were...
All right.
- It's going to rain.
- It's about to rain.
- Let us drive you two back.
- Okay.
No need. My motorcycle is still parked outside.
If it gets soaked, it'll break down again.
We'll hurry back.
Okay. Be careful.
Take it slow.
You talked a lot today.
Did I?
Let's go.