[ Watch on kissasia.li ]
[♪ upbeat music plays]
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
SOME SCENES WERE GENERATED USING AI
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
[Jiui] My punishment was long overdue…
and I think it's finally time.
A friend of mine died because of me.
On an island.
I'm the one who sent Seonu out to sea.
I swore I'd never allow myself
a moment of happiness…
but I guess I got too greedy.
[Jiui sighs]
EPISODE 11
RECONCILIATION, HEALING, AND…
You all saw the news, right?
About how Dr. Do's on medication.
-Shut that mouth of yours.
-It's just, the meds he's on--
Hey, I told you to shut it.
Name one person here who isn't on meds.
So stop yapping and making
such a big deal out of nothing.
Jeez, why do you keep telling me
to shut it?
I was just trying to say
that someone must have ratted out Dr. Do.
It's not like we're gonna
gossip behind his back.
We're all family here.
You worry too much.
That's the part that bothers me a little.
-That kind of personal info is top secret.
-Of course.
So who could have snitched
to the county office?
That's true.
Whoever it was must have held
a grudge against Dr. Do, you know?
Oh, my! Chugging soju this early?
Hey, Geumja, give me
a bowl of seafood ramyeon.
Seafood ramyeon? Okay.
So what are we talking about?
Were you talking about that doctor?
Damn, that one's a riot.
He's on medication.
So you think someone
being on medication's a riot?
It's a bit late,
but isn't it such a relief
that such vital information
has come to light?
So, were you the one who did it?
STYLE
::cue()
Did you ruin his future
because he kept meddling in your affairs?
Have you lost your marbles, old man?
What the hell are you talking about?
If you don't want that jaw of yours
to get dislocated again,
you'd better tell me the truth.
Were you the one who ratted him out?
[scoffs] "Rat him out"?
What do you mean, "rat him out"?
I'll knock your teeth out, damn it.
You want to go?
Being old won't save you.
You little shit…
"You little shit."
I don't go easy on thugs either.
What? "Thug"?
-Say that again!
-Oh, no…
I'm not holding back anymore!
I'm busy, so why don't all three of you
jump me all at once?
Come on.
Bring it!
[groaning]
[sighs]
[Yeom groaning]
But you said
you don't know how to do this.
What?
You said you don't know how to do this!
Oh, I don't know how to do this?
-Yes.
-That's right.
Unfortunately, the only doctor who knows
how to reset a jaw is currently suspended.
Wait.
[yelling]
Just so you know, I'm pretty bad at this.
-[bones crackling]
-[Yeom groaning]
[Ms. Hwang] Hey, take your meds.
That'll be 1,100 won.
Does the staff here hold a grudge
against me or something?
Are you really asking
because you don't know?
It's because you keep going around
spreading weird rumors!
"Weird rumors"?
What do you mean, "weird rumors"?
Damn it!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Where did it…
[Hari] Here.
-[button clicks]
-[both chuckle]
[Ms. Hwang] Here it is.
Oh, Dr. Do's not in right now.
Can we talk for a moment?
[Hwayeong] What's going to happen
to Jiui now?
Once he's removed from his post,
he'll be leaving this place,
and he'll be serving the rest of
his military service on active duty.
I heard from Dr. Do
that he lost a friend on an island.
And that he's receiving
the overdue punishment now.
STYLE
::cue()
But you know what?
I don't think he should be punished
for what happened.
He did nothing wrong, after all.
I can't let him hate himself
while he's being punished for it.
Well…
Ms. Yuk.
Please don't hold Jiui back.
What?
Don't break Jiui's heart anymore
with words like that.
[chuckles]
I was the one who told the county office
that Jiui was on medication.
What?
But why on earth would you--
I thought you heard all about why
an island is hell for Jiui.
Jiui and I suffered for a long time.
People say you should
get over your pain, right?
[chuckles]
No.
The only way to treat unbearable pain
is to run away from it.
That's why Jiui wants to leave.
It's because he wants to live.
I'm here to ask you…
not to try and stop Jiui from leaving.
I'm begging you.
Do you really think…
leaving the island will help him recover?
He'll get better
once he leaves this place.
TRANSFER DIRECTIVE FOR DERELICTION OF DUTY
BY PUBLIC HEALTH DOCTOR
NAME: DO JIUI
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
Want to have a drink?
Are you really going to leave?
I'm sorry for putting you through
so much trouble.
There's no need to apologize.
It just sounds a bit selfish. That's all.
I don't think PH docs should have to
take the fall for something like this.
STYLE
::cue()
PYEONDONG GODDESS
[line ringing]
[voicemail] The number you have dialed
cannot be reached at this moment.
What the heck?
-Ms. Hwang.
-What is it?
Did Ms. Jeongseon go somewhere?
I haven't seen her today.
Lift your leg.
She used her monthly leave,
saying she had to go somewhere urgently.
Huh? Why did she use
a monthly leave all of a sudden?
Why are you asking me that?
You, of all people, should know what's up.
Did you get into
a lovers' quarrel or something?
[stammers] No, it's not like that.
Are you sure you're not
just unaware of it?
She did seem kind of down,
but are you suggesting that was a fight?
You really don't know?
You don't know
whether you got into a fight or not?
Did we really get into a fight?
I swear she was happy, though.
How on earth did you get into
the College of Korean Medicine?
-[line ringing]
-It's the darndest thing.
[phone buzzing]
LOVELY NINNYHAMMER
-Thank you.
-[gynecologist] Thank you.
-Take care.
-Okay.
[phone buzzes]
[Jucheon] Where are you, Ms. Eom?
Have I upset you by any chance?
-Ms. Eom Jeongseon.
-Yes.
Please come into the examination room.
Okay.
Your blood test came back as 110,
which means you're definitely pregnant.
I see.
So I really am pregnant.
I really am.
It's still early, so I'm not sure
we'll see a gestational sac,
but would you like to do an ultrasound?
-No.
-Huh?
I don't want to do the ultrasound.
I don't think I need it.
I see.
But my morning sickness has been
causing me some trouble, so…
I'll write you a prescription.
Please wait outside.
Okay.
DAILECTIN
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[Hwayeong] He'll get better
once he leaves this place.
Ms. Yuk.
Ms. Yuk?
Oh, hey.
What's on your mind?
I called you multiple times.
It's nothing.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
I'm good.
I took it off because it's hot.
Right.
But since I took it off,
let me hang it on you for a bit.
[Hari sighs]
Looking out into the sea
always brings me peace of mind.
It's always there for me,
just the way I remember it.
No matter when I return,
or how I've changed,
it's always right here.
Even if everything else leaves me…
the sea will always be here for me.
But I found out…
that this everlasting ocean…
was a source of never-ending pain
for someone else.
And that really…
[voice cracking] …breaks my heart.
Dr. Yong, what are you doing here?
Ms. Eom!
Where on earth were you all day?
I couldn't reach you at all.
Did we have a fight?
What are you talking about?
Right?
So we didn't fight, right?
Then why didn't you pick up the phone?
-I was kind of scared for a bit.
-[chuckles]
That's no reason to wait
in front of my house.
It's cold outside.
Well, there was something
I wanted to discuss with you.
Discuss with me?
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs] This is nice.
I'm actually dying to know
where you've been,
but healthy relationships need boundaries,
so I won't ask.
So what did you want to discuss with me?
Uh…
Well…
The thing is…
I have to apply for a transfer soon.
Transfer, huh?
I've thought it over,
and I think I should work
somewhere near my dad's hospital next.
What do you think?
I guess you should do that.
To be honest,
I was really conflicted since you're here,
but to start working at my dad's hospital
as soon as I'm done being a PH doc,
I'll need a lot of clinical experience,
but the cases around here are all
pretty much the same, so…
By your dad's hospital,
are you talking about the one in Seoul?
Yes, on Baeng Baeng Intersection.
You're getting farther and farther away.
What?
It's nothing.
But why bother discussing that with me?
You should go if you have to go.
Of course, I should ask you.
This is a very important decision for us.
Besides, we like each other,
so we owe it to each other
to discuss important matters beforehand.
[gags]
Oh, my…
Gosh.
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
[Jeongseon] Yikes, you should really watch
where you're going.
-Are you okay?
-[Ms. Hwang] Yeah.
I didn't see a frozen patch on the ground.
You should have been more careful.
Being careful won't help you avoid
the inevitable in life. [chuckles]
Yeah, you're right.
Ms. Eom, something on your mind recently?
STYLE
::cue()
Something on my mind?
Not at all.
Yeah, right.
You've been acting really strange.
You don't complain or pout
as much as you used to.
Something feels really off.
Nothing gets past you.
Well, what is it?
It's just, I feel like I'm damned if I do
and damned if I don't,
so I'm just trying to figure out
which way would hurt less.
You're "damned"?
What do you mean you're "damned"?
Huh?
What the…
I guess it's a secret.
-[chuckles]
-[scoffs]
When every path seems
to lead you to a cliff
and it feels like the whole world
is out to get you,
you just need to stick close
to the people who are on your side.
It won't hurt as much when you fall.
Having someone who can cry with you
will make it a little better.
Is Dr. Jucheon not up to the task?
It's not like that.
Tell me if you ever need me.
You know I cry easily.
Having someone to cry with you
will make it a little better, okay?
We can pass the tissue around and all.
Okay.
[Ms. Hwang] This too shall pass, okay?
This too shall pass.
Goodness.
[mouse clicking]
Someone on my side?
STYLE
::cue()
What the…
What was that…
DON'T SKIP YOUR MEALS, DR. DO
FEELING DOWN?
HERE'S A PICK-ME-UP!
[sighs]
[phone buzzes, chimes]
[Hari] Dr. Do,
can you help me with something?
Ta-da!
You're here.
I mean…
What is all this?
Let's make Christmas preparations
for our clinic together.
[exclaims]
Come on, is that the best you can do?
It's too high up.
I got it.
-I got it.
-You got it.
Does the clinic always set up
a Christmas tree like this every year?
I wouldn't know.
This is my first Christmas here too.
Ah.
I just wanted to see you
and needed a good excuse,
so this is what I came up with.
It seemed like a solid excuse
to trick my awkward boyfriend
into coming down.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm the one who should be apologizing.
I had no idea what you were going through,
but I clung to you anyway.
I was the one who said
you should cross the ocean,
and I'm the one who begged you to return.
You must have struggled so much here,
surrounded on all sides by the ocean.
Surrounded or not,
I wanted to hang in there
because I had you, Ms. Yuk. But…
I'm sorry.
Looks like we just keep having to
apologize to each other.
I had a million lines to say
to get you to stay…
but seeing you now,
I don't think I should.
Can you just…
promise me one thing?
That promise you made to yourself
to never be happy again.
Don't keep it.
I really want to hold on to you so much,
but the reason I'm not doing so…
is because I want you to be happy.
STYLE
::cue()
[Hari clears throat]
Come on.
You weren't very good in art class
when you were a kid, right?
Hey, I was even in an art club
back in elementary school.
My teacher said I was really good at art.
Who was your teacher?
They really filled your head
with lies, huh?
Ms. Hwang.
[Ms. Hwang] What's all this?
It's Christmas,
so we wanted to liven things up.
[chuckles] It sure is nice to work with
such young coworkers.
Wow, it looks like
a department store in here.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
So pretty.
I left something here,
so I'm just here to get it.
Oh, that hurts.
Jeez, I don't see it anywhere.
Goodness.
Goodness me.
Where could I have put it?
Is everything all right?
It's nothing.
Now, where could it be?
It's nothing? You can't even see
what's right in front of you.
Hey, I told you it's nothing.
-Take a seat here for a moment.
-I told you I'm okay.
Seriously.
[Jiui] I think you should go
to the hospital right now.
Hey, I'm okay.
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm not a patient or anything.
Or I could introduce you to a doctor--
I told you to leave me alone!
I'll take care of it myself!
Ms. Hwang, why…
Oh…
I just need to wait it out
a little longer.
Something felt off about my eyes
a few months ago, so I got insurance.
But I was told that
I'd have to wait another three months
before they could cover my condition.
It's pretty ironic that a nurse is trying
to ignore her own illness, right?
But what can I do?
Life will go on even after
I'm done treating my sickness.
If we go bankrupt because I'm sick,
how will we pay for our son's education?
[voice cracking]
Our eldest son's a very smart boy
and he said his dream is
to study overseas in the States.
He's got a dream, okay?
What kind of mother would I be
if I got in the way of his dreams?
Things were better when I was young enough
to only worry about whatever ailed me.
Now, the sickness doesn't scare me.
The bills do.
Life can be really unfair.
So unfair.
I wasn't done making dinner,
so I should hurry back.
Thank you.
[clears throat]
[door opens]
-[sighs]
-[door closes]
STYLE
::cue()
I came across people like her
a lot in the ER.
People who hide their condition,
not because they're scared of it,
but because of the costs.
Whether it's then or now,
there's still nothing I can do for her.
[phone buzzing]
Just a sec.
-Hello?
-[Jinbae] Hey, Hari.
You need to come right now.
LUCKY SUPERMARKET
What is it, Granny?
-This man came into the supermarket…
-[man groaning]
…looking for painkillers
and then just collapsed.
He's sweating bullets
and shaking like a leaf.
I told him we should go to the center,
but he was vehemently against that.
Goodness.
Are you okay, sir?
I'll try pressing you
like I did back then.
[groaning]
[groans intensely]
Dr. Do.
-It's the same symptoms as before.
-Should I call a chopper?
The painkillers made the pain go away,
and the folks at the hospital
said the scans came out clean.
I already feel terrible
for causing the death of that pilot
and damaging your reputation.
I'm just going to go now.
[groans]
-Sir.
-Dr. Do.
We should get him to a hospital.
Okay.
Hang in there, sir.
No, you can't…
[line rings]
-Yeopoong-gun operations center.
-This is Pyeondongdo.
We have a suspected appendicitis
needing immediate transfer.
[official] Isn't that
where that accident happened?
We can't dispatch anyone
under current emergency protocols.
What's that got to do with this?
There's a patient here.
Well, the sea fog is too thick,
and we don't have any choppers on standby.
A man is dying right now!
I'm sorry, but due to protocol,
we can't offer you any assistance.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey--
Hello?
[Jinbae] Hey, do you have a minute?
We could use your help here.
Careful. Take it slow…
Won't it be dangerous, Mr. Park?
We can't let a man die
because it's a little dangerous,
not after I lived like that!
If you say he needs to go,
we're getting him there!
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't say that.
Why would you feel sorry
for wanting to live?
You just hang in there, okay?
[Hwayeong] Jiui.
Think it over.
You're on probation.
If something goes wrong,
you might actually have to
step down as a doctor for good.
Let's wait it out a little longer.
What if he were to lose his life?
STYLE
::cue()
We'd be powerless to do anything,
just like back then.
-Let's go, Mr. Park.
-Okay.
Hold on tight, folks.
The winter winds are brutal!
Let me help you put one on.
Please take good care of him.
Save him! That's all we ask!
Oh, mighty Dragon King,
please grant our people safe passage.
Goodness…
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[sirens wailing]
This is a patient
previously transferred for R/O appy.
He now has
localized RLQ tenderness and rebound.
He's running a temp of 37.7
-and experiencing chills.
-Got it.
EMERGENCY DISPATCH
[sirens wailing]
[sighs]
[breathes shakily]
[chuckles] Dr. Do, here.
Have a sip while it's hot.
-Thank you.
-[chuckles, sighs]
Damn, that really
hits the spot. [inhales sharply]
[sighs]
[smacks lips, inhales deeply]
[sighs] By the way, Dr. Do…
Are you really leaving?
Come on.
Why not fight for yourself a bit longer?
Would that be too much to ask of you?
I'm sorry.
[Mr. Park sighs]
What's causing you so much pain?
When I heard you were on medication,
hearing that really broke my heart.
You risked your life many times to save us
while taking medication yourself,
so sending you off like this
without protecting you…
[sighs] It just doesn't feel right.
At times like this,
living on an island feels like a crime.
[chuckles] It truly does…
[both sigh]
[footsteps approaching]
[Hari] Dr. Do!
They just started operating
on the patient for appendicitis.
It went unnoticed last time
because the appendix was obscured,
but he's just gone into emergency surgery.
[sighs]
They said it was a really close call.
You saved this patient's life, Dr. Do.
[chuckles] Wow. So he made it, huh?
He made it. [chuckles]
Goodness.
STYLE
::cue()
What's on your mind?
That appendicitis patient.
He apologized to me.
Despite the pain and fear of death.
[Hari] Treatments that would be considered
trivial on the mainland
aren't very accessible on an island.
That's why people end up
losing their lives… [sighs]
…over some stupid lights or appendicitis.
To save someone's life,
one must put their own life on the line.
I guess that's why
islanders here apologize
before begging the doctor
to save their lives.
Because they're afraid
someone might get hurt because of them.
But that's unacceptable.
Hmm.
I mean, wanting to live shouldn't be…
something you have to apologize for.
-[Mr. Park] All right, let's go!
-[Hari] Okay. Let's get up.
-[Hari chuckles]
-[inhales sharply]
You two go on without me.
-What?
-[Mr. Park] Huh?
Dr. Do!
Huh?
2025-2026 YEOPOONG-GUN
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CARE
MODERNIZATION PLAN
Handle things quietly from now on
if you want to keep your job
as director, got it?
Yes, sir.
[Mr. Choi] You can't just
barge in here like this.
I said you can't!
[Changmok] What the hell?
[panting]
It'll be in your best interest
to talk to me right now.
Otherwise, I might just take these files
straight to those reporters
that you like so much.
Leave us.
[door closes]
I can't accept your decision
to remove me from my PH doc post.
[laughs]
Well, I guess you're here
to throw a tantrum like a baby, huh?
INSPECTION OF FAULTY HELIPAD
CONSTRUCTION IN YEOPOONG-GUN
[Jiui] I have evidence that proves
that out of the 20 helipads
renovated in Yeopoong-gun,
17 had faulty lighting.
Even on the night of the accident
at the Pyeondongdo helipad,
the lights weren't working properly.
[Changmok sighs]
So it wasn't a misdiagnosis,
but the helipad was the problem?
I mean, why should we believe
the words of a PH doc
who's taking psychiatric medicine?
Regardless of that fact
and the possibility of misdiagnosis,
the helicopter should've landed safely.
A proper system is what saves lives
in medically underserved regions,
not a skilled doctor.
A system that gets patients
the care they need as soon as possible.
What killed that pilot
was Yeopoong-gun's shitty system.
The hell did you say? "Shitty system"?
Apologize to the family
of the crash victim right this instant.
The only reason I'm giving you
a chance to fix this
is because I also believe
that system could save lives.
YEOPOONG-GUN
HEALTHCARE MODERNIZATION
Dr. Do Jiui!
[sighs]
Do you really think
you can bring about change?
The more you provoke the governor,
the worse things will get for you.
STYLE
::cue()
PH docs are civil servants
which gives the governor the power
to discipline and penalize them at will.
[♪ sentimental music plays]
PH docs…
[sighs]
…are also doctors.
Even when the odds are against us…
we have a duty to save lives.
[Geumja] Here.
[Mar. Park sighs]
-[Mr. Park] That looks amazing.
-[Jinbae] And it's perfectly seasoned.
[Mr. Park] So you're saying you don't have
to leave anymore, Dr. Do?
That you'll be here for the full year?
[Jangsu] Geez, stop asking him that.
He said it hasn't been settled yet.
No, I'll make it so.
[Jangsu] Oh, right.
That's great news,
considering all you've been through!
I know, right?
We were worried sick that he might
get dragged off to active duty.
[all chuckle]
Thank you.
About that medication I'm on--
No. You don't owe us an explanation.
Everyone's on some kind of medication.
I take twenty pills
a day just to keep going!
[Jangsu] Exactly.
If taking medicine is a crime,
then everyone in this room
is serving a life sentence.
[Sugwang] That's true,
a life sentence. [chuckles]
[Geumja] Goodness, hurry and eat now.
[gags]
[Jangsu] He's more of a softie
than you might think.
Keep crying like that,
and you're gonna make me cry too.
DAILECTIN - FOR NAUSEA
AND VOMITING OF PREGNANCY
[indistinct chattering, laughing]
Oh, my…
How are your eyes?
[chuckles] Well, you know… [clears throat]
[sighs]
I wanted to ask you something.
Yes?
How did you muster
that kind of courage? Hmm?
If it hadn't turned out
to be appendicitis,
you really would have lost your license.
Um… [sighs]
Well, we had to save him first…
before we could worry
about what happens next.
[♪ sincere music playing]
Besides, I had known it all along.
Known what?
I knew the people here
wouldn't turn their backs on me,
no matter what happened.
Of course not! [chuckles]
Of course not.
[Mr. Park] Dr. Do!
What are you doing? Come here for a drink!
[chuckles] Yes, I'm coming.
Where are you?
What are you doing here? Get back in here.
-I said I'm coming.
-Don't make him drink too much.
-Hey, come here.
-Sit.
-[Geumja] Go easy on him!
-[Jangsu] You're all dead meat today!
[Sugwang] Yeah, right.
-Bring us more booze!
-All right.
[Mr. Park] It's a drink-off then, okay?
[indistinct chattering, laughing]
[line ringing]
Hey, honey.
I need you to come
to the hospital with me on Monday.
I think I'm a little sick. [chuckles]
[exclaims]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
Are you leaving now?
Yeah.
I never thought we'd stand before
the ocean together like this again.
I thought it would never happen again.
[inhales deeply]
Jiui.
When I walked out on you back then…
I didn't do it
because I blamed you for it.
I felt like if we stayed together…
[inhales deeply]
…we'd just end up resenting each other.
But…
since I've been here,
I couldn't help but think…
"Would things have been more bearable
if we had stayed together?"
You weren't the only one
who walked out on me.
I did the same thing.
I ran away from everything
that reminded me of Seonu…
constantly blaming myself
for failing to save him.
But…
don't you think things might have
turned out a little differently…
if someone had helped us out back then?
If only we had…
gotten to the hospital a little sooner.
If only…
Seonu had gotten proper treatment sooner.
Don't you think things might have…
turned out a little differently
for Seonu and us?
Hwayeong.
Why don't we…
forgive ourselves now?
We tried our best back then.
[inhales sharply]
[breathes shakily]
[chuckles]
[cries, sniffles]
What about you?
Have you forgiven yourself?
STYLE
::cue()
[breathes shakily]
We should find happiness now.
I'm sorry.
[inhales sharply, cries]
[sniffles]
What brings you here?
Do you have anything to tell me?
What are you talking about?
I'm asking if you have
something to tell me.
Stop talking in riddles.
You're pregnant.
[♪ soft music playing]
Was the reason
you haven't been feeling well recently
because you're pregnant?
When you suddenly took a day off,
did you go to the hospital alone
without telling me?
I did.
And you had no intention
of ever telling me, right?
Right?
Say something!
Why did you do that?
It's because
I haven't made a decision yet.
You're only here temporarily, Dr. Yong.
You may feel like you're really into me,
but your world is back in Seoul,
at a high-end clinic
on Baeng Baeng Intersection
where you'd be a big-shot doctor
of Korean medicine.
And my world is this tiny, dusty village.
I don't think people like us can coexist
in the same space for too long.
Is that why you weren't
ever going to tell me?
Do you really have so little faith in me?
This isn't about you.
I don't have any faith in myself.
Ms. Eom.
This is just the way I am…
so don't waste your time
worrying about me.
I'm going to do things my way.
-[ship horn blows]
-[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
Here, try some.
-Is it good?
-Yeah!
It's good, isn't it?
[chuckles]
[exclaims]
I love this. [chuckles]
What do you mean?
Having you here. [chuckles]
[clears throat]
So…
I'm going to go see Seonu tomorrow.
Because I haven't said goodbye yet.
Oh…
Can you come with me?
I feel like I'll be able to go
if you come with me.
[♪ sincere music playing]
KIM SEONU
IN MEMORY OF OUR FRIEND,
KIM SEONU,
WHO WOULD HAVE MADE
AN AMAZING DOCTOR
HANGUK UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL SCHOOL CLASS OF 2014
Seonu.
[cries] Seonu, I'm sorry.
[cries]
I'm sorry I kept you waiting so long.
[crying]
[crying continues]
[Jiui sighs]
Thank you…
for coming to see Seonu with me today.
Thank you for staying with me.
[both chuckle]
[Jiui] I think
this is where I first met you.
What was that like?
Did you think I was cute?
[inhales sharply]
Hmm…
You were a little scary.
What the heck?
Seriously?
They say there are three things a PH doc
must avoid on an island, you see.
Three things? What are they?
They say if you don't avoid
those three things,
you'll never leave an island.
Incidents…
STYLE
::cue()
people, and…
love.
[both chuckle]
I think I knew back then…
that I was never going to leave.
[♪ romantic pop music playing]
[♪ music fades]
[tires screech]
ON OFFICIAL DUTY
[♪ dramatic music playing]
YEOPOONG-GUN
We're with the Yeopoong-gun
Audit Department.
Stop what you're doing
and cooperate with our investigation.
Dr. Jiui! This is bad!
You need to come down
to the center right now!
DO NOT APPROACH
Those are patient records.
You're not supposed to touch those.
Excuse me!
Keep going.
What do you think you're doing?
We have reason to believe this center
is involved in a kickback scheme.
Kickbacks? What are you talking about?
A recent internal audit uncovered evidence
that this clinic accepted
kickbacks from Manu Pharmaceuticals
in exchange for procuring its drugs.
An investigation is currently underway.
As a result, operations
at the Pyeondong Health Center
will be suspended until
the investigation is concluded.
You're suspending our operations?
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
Hey, Dr. Do Jiui.
I wonder if you received my response yet.
I hope you enjoy a little taste
of that shitty system you mentioned.
The system that teaches
a lowly civil servant
not to mess with the governor, got it?
The kind of system that shows a guard dog
what happens when it barks at its master!
Better get in line.
Punk-ass bastard.
Ko Changmok, that son of a bitch.
[♪ soft music playing]
THAT PROMISE YOU MADE
TO YOURSELF
TO NEVER BE HAPPY AGAIN…
DON'T KEEP IT.
THE BEST KIND OF RAMYEON
IS THE KIND I'M SHARING WITH YOU
SOMEONE ON MY SIDE?
HARI AND I ARE THE SAME AGE
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
[Jucheon] We'll be transferring soon.
[Ms. Hwang] It's about time
you returned to your place.
[Hari] I have something to tell you,
Dr. Do.
[car crashes]
Hey!
[Ms. Hwang] If any of you touch
a single thing here, it's theft.
I don't think the center
should be shut down,
which is why I've come up with a solution.
[Hyeon] I'd say this is a no-brainer.
[Hari] I'm the one who stole this, so…
[Jucheon] Something terrible will happen
if you keep this up!
[Jiui] I'm going to keep
fighting until the end.
Translated by Yoon Hyuk Park