Well then, let's end our friendship now.
I've done it now... I've really done it now.
With Kazumi of all people!
Maybe that wasn't enough after all?
I'll try harder so you're satisfied.
You idiot, Kazumi!
So I was just a game to you?
I thought being best friends was fine.
I got dumped!
Huh? But you two seemed so close.
He said I wasn't what he expected.
He wanted "someone more mature and refined".
That sadness that she's hiding,
because she can't show her true self...
What about you?
Someone asked you out again, right?
Oh, right.
Well, but I don't think I'll date them.
Why?
Same reason as before.
They have expectations,
and then leave when you don't meet them.
Huh...
That unpretentious way she takes
my deepest feelings in stride with a "huh".
Gosh, I wish we could just stay friends
and talk about everything.
Then what if I became your boyfriend?
Huh?
No way!
Then we wouldn't
be able to talk about everything.
You think so?
Yes.
The words that come straight
from her heart, shown so innocently...
Her smile,
so bright and warm like sunshine.
Could you take a look at it in advance?
Bring it over later.
You're a lifesaver.
She shows me expressions
she wouldn't even show her lover.
Why?
That's what I want to know!
That was the privilege
of being her best friend.
Rather than a relationship
that fades and ends,
I'd rather be your one and only
unchanging person.
But it didn't work out.
That just wasn't enough.
In that moment,
I was confronted with a Himari I didn't know.
Wipe it, wipe it...
Whether we're compatible or not,
I don't think you can really know
unless you try it.
I realized that if we stay best friends,
there are things we can never touch.
S-Sorry, did I wake you?
Still hungover?
Should I make you some breakfast?
Huh?
Wait... is this your place, Kazumi?
You don't remember?
You were drinking with Ando
and the others yesterday, and passed out.
Oh.
Wait, so... did we...
Are you curious?
Did we...
We didn't.
You were completely out of it,
so I held back.
I see...
Huh?
Held back?
What do you mean, "held back"?
So you're saying you wanted to?
Himari?
Wait, if I had a dream like that,
does that mean I actually...
Are you okay?
I-I have to go...
I need to get home and get ready,
or I'll be late for work.
You don't have to rush off.
No, thank you so much
for letting me stay! Bye!
That was fast.
I've got to tell her properly this time.
Having a dream like that...
[Vextos]
Shibasaki, good morning.
Morning, Ando.
So, what happened after?
Did it go well?
Huh?
I mean, with Hojo.
I'm so sorry for the trouble the other night.
No worries.
So, any progress?
Progress?
I mean, a guy and a girl
who missed the last train, out on the town...
there's no way nothing happened, right?
No, no, no.
Really?
You're not gonna say you had
a passionate night or something?
No, me and Hojo are just friends.
That's suspicious too.
Honestly, it's obvious you two
like each other.
The only one I act like this with...
is you, Himari.
What did that even mean?
So really, nothing happened?
Nothing.
You know, you should've come too, Okada.
I'll plan another one,
so make sure to drop by then.
Sure, I'd love to.
Everyone gets more hyped when you're around.
No way, that's not true.
Kurahashi, thank you for your help.
Hojo, long time no see.
Thanks for everything.
The section chief is in the meeting room.
This way, please.
Thanks. See you then, Okada.
Yes, thank you for your help.
Shibasaki, Ando, good morning.
Morning.
Was that a client?
Yeah. They're really nice to me,
but I get a lot of personal invitations too.
So Hojo has been acting as a buffer for me.
I see.
Being cute sure comes
with its own problems.
No, that's not it at all.
I see... so that's how it is.
But to think Kazumi might actually like me...
Could that really be true?
I mean... we've been together for nine years,
there's no way he'd suddenly like me now,
right?
Like what?
You scared me!
Don't just talk to me from behind like that,
my heart can't take it.
You're the one who was spacing out too much.
What were you thinking about?
Work stuff.
I should get back.
Hold on.
I didn't have time to say it this morning,
but I've been thinking,
I need to talk to you properly.
Can I grab your time tonight, Shibasaki?
Huh?
Before the girl I like slips away,
I need to confess properly.
You get what I'm saying, right?
Huh? Wait, what?
But we have the department
drinking party today, don't we?
After that.
Let's go home together.
Huh?
Wait...
The person Kazumi likes... is... me?
No way...
Shibasaki, your face is really red.
Are you okay?
Huh?
I was just running a bit.
He's not supposed to turn this into romance.
Kazumi was supposed to
just stay my best friend, right?
Shibasaki, want to go to
the drinking party together?
Yeah, yeah, you're right. Let's go.
Anyway, I need to calm down first.
Our ace! Good work today.
Good work.
- Good work, good work.
- Excuse me.
I'm glad we made it through this month
without issues.
Thank you so much. The section chief's...
We're sitting so far apart.
But that's fine.
Shibasaki, here you go.
Thanks, but just a little.
You can't drink much?
- No, I just messed up previously.
- Messed up?
Huh?
How's work going?
It's your second year,
so it's no problem, right?
- No, I still have a lot to learn.
- That's not true.
Your layouts have gotten better,
and your copy is more eye-catching too.
You're just a good teacher, Shibasaki.
Wow, that's nice to hear.
Looks like they're having fun over there.
Yeah.
Hey, don't act all composed
and drink like nothing's wrong!
At least show some sign of being flustered!
Are you curious about them?
Huh?
No, not at all.
So you and Hojo have known each other
since college, right?
Yeah.
And you just happened to end up
at the same company?
That's crazy.
Nah, my old workplace
was a total exploitative sweatshop.
And when I hit my limit,
Hojo recommended this place.
But Hojo seems nice on the surface,
don't you think you can't really tell
what he's thinking underneath?
Like, he's got that smirking-cyborg vibe.
Whoa, you don't hold back.
Smirking cyborg.
You get what I mean?
I can kinda see it.
But...
that's not true.
He pays attention to people around him,
and I think he's kind.
- You like him.
- Huh?
I mean as a person.
Well... yeah.
You're cute, Shibasaki.
You're so easy to read.
Don't tease your elders, rookie.
Scary.
What's up?
Nothing.
See you. You can walk, right?
See you.
Next round, let's keep it going.
I'm heading out.
I'll take off first.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay, Nihei, let's check around
for any forgotten items.
Got it.
Heave-ho.
Whoa...
If you're feeling sick,
you shouldn't push it.
Want me to call a taxi?
- I'm fine.
- Thanks, Nihei.
I'll take care of Himari.
I'll make sure she gets home.
Got it.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'll go grab your stuff.
The drinking party's over.
Don't do stuff like that.
Stuff like what?
Saying things like "leave Himari to me".
You know, it might start rumors.
I don't mind if rumors start.
Because I want that kind of relationship
with you.
I like you, Himari.
I've always liked you.
When I said let's end our friendship,
it wasn't some impulsive thought.
From the very beginning...
We're drinking at Tomoya's place today.
You in, Kazumi?
Nah, I think I'll pass today.
Come on, don't be so antisocial.
Sorry, invite me again sometime.
Alright, fine. See you tomorrow, Kazumi.
Yeah, see you.
From the very first moment I saw you,
I've been in love with you this whole time.
I wanted to tell you that.
I want to date you,
and I want to stay with you from now on.
What do you want, Himari?
I had no idea.
He never showed any sign of it at all.
I'm really happy.
I want you too, Kazumi.
But...
Is something on your mind?
Even if we become lovers,
will we still be able to have
this kind of relationship?
Then let's go on a trial date.
Next time, just the two of us.
We'll go on a proper date as lovers.
And if it feels right,
we'll officially go out, okay?
Alright, it's settled.
Let's take it slow and get closer.
Hey.
I know we're just a trial couple...
But can I kiss you?
Even though I know it's just a trial,
I don't want to let go.
I'm the one who said it's a trial,
but I don't want to let go.
But that's not okay.
If we really become a couple,
then next time...
- I want to be with you.
Are those two dating or what?
Huh?
I'll say this as a fellow new grad,
but it's so obvious
those two like each other.
Either they're dating already,
or it's only a matter of time.
Okada, what do you think of Hojo?
Huh? He's handsome!
He's good at his job, kind, reliable...
What?
Are you not on good terms with him?
No.
He seems nice on the outside,
but deep down, he's a cold rationalist.
Rather than being kind,
it feels more like
he just isn't interested in others.
You think so?
That's not how I see him.
Earlier, when I was talking with Shibasaki,
our eyes met with Hojo for a moment.
That look...
wasn't just jealousy.
Don't tease your elders, rookie.
Scary.
What's wrong?
It's totally baseless,
and just a gut feeling.
But for Shibasaki...
if she does get together with Hojo,
I have a feeling she might end up
really hurt someday.
You make such a cute face
in front of your lover.
- Aren't you embarrassed saying that?
- Not at all.
I don't think how long you've known someone
really matters.
I don't think I can get along well
with someone who has too many secrets.
The things you want me to do, Himari...
If I make all of them come true,
will you tell me?