THE APARTMENT JOB
TRUE VALUE STATE
2025 BEST APARTMENT COMPLEX TO LIVE IN
LONG-TERM REPAIR RESERVE FUND
USED FOR FLOOR REPAIRS
The usual, right?
Thanks.
HK TRADING AND INVESTMENT
Good morning, sir.
BREAK ROOM ACCESS VOUCHER
Hello, sir.
Good luck.
Nothing special came up last night.
This is bad.
Let's just do it by ourselves.
Come on, let's begin.
All right, let's do this.
-Hold on.
-What's going on?
-Show us your hand.
-Oh no.
Hello, sir.
This is good!
I won!
I only won once.
-Twenty.
Hey, Mr. Park!
Luck is on my side today.
Thanks.
He's here often these days.
-The Lizard?
-"Lizard"?
He's known for avoiding blame
and slipping away
whenever a gambling den is raided.
Let's see. Red, red…
What does he do?
He's an apartment facility manager.
An apartment facility manager?
Yes, but he's a VIP here.
No unpaid debts either.
It's two pair!
A VIP facility manager…
The job must pay pretty well.
-Take good care of him.
-Yes, sir.
And Mr. Oh is here,
so we've made preparations
for your meeting.
It's been a while.
-Let's go see him, then.
-Yes, sir.
Do you really have
a top-tier credit rating, Mr. Oh?
Of course.
They only accept members
with a Grade 1 credit rating.
But your card loan interest rate is 19.9%.
If you take out three card loans
and max out your cash advances,
you should be able to pay us back.
Mr. Park, I can pay you back
once I sell my apartment.
I'm telling you, I'm good for it.
But that's not in Seoul.
The housing market is dead out there.
We don't know when it'll sell.
What about the interest?
We'll take out loans
with the personal info you provided
when you got your access card.
You'll get a verification code.
Hey, you're really hurting my feelings.
-How can you do this to me?
-Please stop.
-Let go of me!
-Relax. You'll only hurt yourself.
FACE RECOGNITION FAILED
Smile, Mr. Oh.
NARA BANK CARD LOAN VERIFICATION CODE
It's 236745.
The loan went through.
All right. Meeting's over.
Sir.
We got Mr. Choi's location.
Really? Are the papers ready?
-Yes, I printed everything.
-Okay. Let's go.
Yes, sir.
29TH ANNUAL NATIONAL YOUTH CONCERT
CHOI YE-WON
Mr. Choi is here.
-Stop right there!
-Get him!
He's heading to the hall!
Get him!
You're late.
-Your daughter's performance is over.
-Mr. Park.
I'd like to speak with you in private.
Don't come closer. I'm completely broke!
What can you do about it?
There is something I can do.
Your fingerprint.
What is this?
I checked your dormant bank accounts.
You had about three million won.
I bet you didn't know.
Stamp the paper
to authorize the withdrawal.
And cancellation papers
for the life insurance policy
your wife took out.
You look surprised. Didn't you know?
No.
We're canceling it anyway,
so live a long life. Go on.
We also looked into the land
your ancestors had.
My ancestors?
Your great-grandfather's land
was taken by the government,
and some compensation money
was never claimed.
That would be enough
to clear the debt
you owe me.
LOSS COMPENSATION AGREEMENT
-Big Guy.
-Yes, sir.
Give it to him.
Don't skip your meals.
HK TRADING AND INVESTMENT
BREAK ROOM ACCESS VOUCHER
Oh, come on.
Please help me, Mr. Park!
Your guests have been waiting a long time.
Get ready.
No!
Everything you own is ours!
-Catch that bastard!
-Mr. Choi!
Get him!
Wow.
I can't believe
you even looked into his ancestors' land.
You really are amazing, sir.
I can dig up anything.
Making threats even before digging
is for amateurs.
15TH ANNUAL CHILDREN'S FIELD DAY
First place!
It was my first time hiring someone
for the role, so I was worried.
But you even won first place. Thank you.
It was nothing.
I added a little extra.
I'll always try my best
to satisfy my customers.
Call me when there's another event.
-I'll give you a 10% discount.
-All right.
Thank you for today.
-Bye, then.
-Goodbye.
Yes!
My goodness.
It was way too obvious
that you weren't her mom.
You didn't even look at the kid.
Running fast isn't the point, you know.
Think about your customer's needs.
Let's be professional, okay?
I know you're good at this, Ha-ri.
Hey, I won first place.
I made her feel proud
that her mom was the fastest runner.
I left her with a great memory.
How long are you going to live like this?
For a while, at least.
So you'll keep sending me gigs, won't you?
Why did you have to lie
and say you got a job at a law firm?
You said your sister manages your salary.
You're going to have to keep faking
a salary you don't have.
Why in the world did you lie
about passing the bar exam?
I never lied about passing the bar.
I just never told her that I failed.
Whatever.
Just tell your sister the truth
before this gets out of hand.
You could get in huge trouble.
Choi Woo-shik says this
to Song Kang-ho in Parasite.
"Father, I don't consider this fraud
or any kind of crime,
because I'm going to get into
this university next year."
Ha-jeong, I'm going to pass next year--
Kang Ha-ri.
What?
What is it?
Don't you have something to tell me?
This is it.
I'm going to tell her the truth.
Ha-jeong, I…
To be honest…
I knew it. Look.
You stole my clothes
and were playing dumb?
We're completely different sizes.
Why would you wear such huge clothes?
Don't you know
oversized clothing is trendy?
This is fashion. You're just clueless.
What's this?
What? Hérzina?
This must've cost a fortune.
Hey, you're a lawyer now.
You should have at least one suit
that fits you properly.
Ha-jeong,
you really didn't need to buy this.
Pay me back, then.
Your tuition and your clothes.
I'm charging 19% interest on it. Got that?
What kind of sister
charges loan-shark rates?
Kang Ha-jeong!
Excuse me. Coming through.
Excuse me.
Attorney Kim, it's going down.
It's going down.
B3.
WEE PARTNERS
FREE LEGAL CONSULTATION
Hello.
FREE LEGAL CONSULTANTS
Oh, wow.
You're dressed like a lawyer today.
You look cool.
Thank you.
Is that something to be grateful for?
CONSULTANT KANG HA-RI
SEXUAL ASSAULT, INJURY, DEFAMATION, FRAUD
Hanging in there, Mr. Park?
I'm fine!
Just look at him go.
We're almost there.
Let's stay strong, everyone!
You must be quite hungry.
It's not much,
but I put something together.
You made these yourself?
Of course.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
CHIEF OF INVESTIGATION, SON DAE-UN
This is good!
You could open a restaurant.
KOREA'S FINEST EEL CUISINE
-Customer number 256!
-That's me.
Here's your food, sir.
Thank you.
Of course it's good. It's premium eel
from the most famous spot in Gangnam.
Mr. Park can do anything.
He even booked tickets
to a Lim Young-woong concert
when no one else could.
I had to use a bot to score a reservation.
Okay!
He even got us
a limited-edition luxury bag
that my wife was desperate
to get her hands on.
HÉRZINA WAITING LINE
I lined up at the department store
at 4 a.m. for this.
It's all thanks to you.
I even made some dessert for you.
Sir.
-And for you.
-Right.
And my first gift to you, sir.
You really didn't have to.
Here you go, sir.
I always prepare high-quality food
that won't upset your stomach.
I shouldn't smoke,
but it's impossible not to
with this amazing view.
But I don't have a lighter.
You all quit, right?
-Yes.
-Yes, we all quit.
Too bad. This is my last one.
I can't just throw it away.
I'll go grab it.
You're like a pro badminton player,
Ms. Kim.
-I've improved a lot thanks to you.
-I can see that.
My goodness.
My father
was great at hitting and smashing things
back in the day.
No wonder. He's extremely skilled.
But are you his son, then?
Yes. I'm his son, Park Hae-kang.
Nice to meet you.
Goodness.
You're handsome, just like your father.
I don't resemble him,
but I am quite handsome.
You're taking your meds, aren't you?
This is better than medicine.
This is really good spring water.
You should be taking your meds.
You'll die if you don't take them.
I'm saying this for your sake, Boss.
Not mine.
This is nice.
You'll really die
if you don't take care of yourself.
Are you kidding me?
Are you challenging me
now that I'm retired?
You want some hitting and smashing?
I'm just worried about you. That's all.
I won't die.
What if you do?
I won't die until I spend
all the money you keep sending me.
But you sent a lot this month.
Why did you give me so much?
Well, you're the owner of the business.
It's only natural.
Still, I'm just the figurehead.
You're supposed to give
the figurehead a cut.
It would be rude not to.
Right. We shouldn't live like thugs.
But…
how long will you run that gambling den?
It's not easy to manage it,
and it's dangerous.
Save what you're giving me
and help the others settle down.
You make a clean break too.
You've made enough money now.
What are you talking about?
After greasing everyone's palms,
there's nothing left.
Plus,
I have to earn a lot more
to help the guys follow their own paths.
What about you?
Is there anything you want to do?
Gyeong-nam, Je-gil, and Big Guy.
They all have dreams,
even if they may be small.
Dreams?
I don't have anything like that.
Make sure to take your meds.
You'd better not die on me. Or else I'll…
-You little brat!
-Geez.
You're still swift.
Bring it on, you punk!
I can't even see your hands.
-You're too quick.
-Gosh…
Let go of me!
I'm not leaving.
Lend me some money!
Why can't you lend me money?
Is his credit still top-tier?
He's become our VVIP.
Hang on.
What?
Mr. Park! Perfect timing.
These assholes…
-They won't listen--
-Sir.
When did you become our VVIP?
Hurry up and lend it to him.
I knew it.
Things get done quickly
when I talk to the boss directly.
Did you hear…
You jerk. Why are you giving me that look?
Hey.
I can pay back everything
if I just work for a week
at my apartment complex.
Don't look down on me.
-Lend him the money.
-Yes, sir.
I'll see you again, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Park.
-I'll work really hard.
-Let's go.
You're all dead!
Just you wait! Let go of me.
Don't carry me…
Make sure we get
the money back right away.
-I've got a bad feeling about this.
-Yes, sir.
-Yun-seo.
-Yes?
Is the representative election
notice ready?
I'm just editing the text.
It's almost ready.
-Okay.
-Right.
Don't put so much work into it.
Nobody cares.
Sang-tae.
Shouldn't we do our best to make sure
our residents pay more attention?
We should make announcements every day.
Right. Sorry.
Ha-jeong.
We'd like you to keep doing
that job for us.
I told you, I can't.
I said I'd stop when my sister got a job.
Ha-jeong.
Your sister's situation
is separate from yours.
I'm sorry, sir.
I really can't keep doing it.
I've told you many times
that you won't get in any trouble.
Mr. Choi! Can you come out here for a bit?
Mr. Choi.
Can you please tell me what's going on?
How can floor repairs
cost 365 million…
Oh my gosh. This is insane.
Three hundred million won
is actually a bargain.
Bargain or not,
the construction company
should be taking care of this.
Why would you repair this
with the residents' money?
Who said you could use
the repair reserve fund?
This is exactly
what the repair reserve fund is for.
You shouldn't spend it freely
just because it isn't your money.
I'm so thirsty.
Give me something to drink.
It's not my money,
but I'm spending it appropriately
for the right purposes.
That's my job.
Mr. Choi.
When spending such a large amount,
you should get
the residents' approval first.
Well…
This was an urgent matter.
Urgent? Did the floors
crumble down or what?
Don't be ridiculous.
Ms. Jang, you're so…
invested in the complex's affairs.
Of course, I am.
Hello, everyone.
You're here.
-Hello.
-Hello, sir.
Hello.
I received these as a gift,
but I couldn't eat them all by myself,
so I thought I should share.
Oh, you didn't have to. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you for always thinking of us.
I'm just glad you all enjoy it.
Let me get you some coffee.
It's fine. I was only dropping by.
You must be busy. I'll get going now.
You're quite the beauty.
Oh my.
-Me?
-Goodbye.
-You heard that, right?
He said I'm quite the beauty.
PINE TREE FARM
TAEGOWON
Up we go.
Goodness.
-Hello.
SENIOR SECRETARY FOR CIVIL AFFAIRS
SONG U-SIK
PROSECUTOR GENERAL
CHOI SEUNG-HO
How have you been?
SUPREME COURT JUSTICE
YOO GWANG-HO
PRESIDENT OF GONGYEONG DAILY
LEE SANG-GYU
I sent Mr. Kim a bonsai tree.
What?
You already got Mr. Kim acquitted
and made him a presidential candidate.
Why would you send him that?
He's right.
Our newspaper took plenty of heat
covering for Mr. Kim too.
Just thinking about it makes me…
I just wanted him to see
the evergreen pine all year long
and remember
that we'll make him the president,
no matter what.
Mr. Song, do you think
Mr. Kim really has a chance?
Right now, he's the most likely candidate.
"Most likely" isn't enough.
We've spent a fortune on him so far.
We need him to win
the presidency this time
so it doesn't go to waste.
And I'm certain
you'll all make sure that it happens.
-Gosh.
-Of course.
Thank you in advance.
Of course.
You're here.
It wasn't hard to find, was it?
Say hello.
He's been eager to join our club.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kwak Ju-gwon.
-The police commissioner?
-Yes.
He spent nearly 30 years
in public service, climbing the ranks.
I begged Mr. Song here
to let me meet you all.
Justice Yoo.
Your rulings showed consideration
for the underprivileged
and protected
the people's fundamental rights.
I really admire you, sir.
The president of Gongyeong Daily.
You stood firm against media censorship.
I truly admire you.
And our Prosecutor General,
who led the charge for reform.
You really are my role model…
Hey, cop.
Are you at a fan meet or what?
Pardon?
This isn't a social gathering.
Didn't the Senior Secretary tell you that?
I was going to…
Look at that, huh?
But not anyone can join us, you know.
Yes, I know. That's why I--
Ten billion!
Do you have ten billion won?
Excuse me?
The people here
are worth more than ten billion won.
If you want to join our One Club,
bring ten billion
for the membership fee.
That's the least you can do.
I've explained the membership requirement,
so please head back safely.
Ten billion won?
That's what he said.
The membership fee is ten billion won.
Ten billion for a membership?
That makes no sense.
Nothing makes sense in this country.
If the most powerful people in Korea
want ten billion,
then ten billion it is.
What will you do then?
You know that I didn't climb this high
by playing clean.
I built a few connections
and took some money.
But thinking back now,
I wonder if I should have been
even more corrupt.
Even if I scrape together everything,
it's hardly two billion.
I need eight billion more.
Sir.
Why would you gather that money yourself?
What?
Squeeze it out of someone
who can't make a peep
as you bleed them dry.
That's impossible nowadays.
There's someone perfect for that.
Someone named Park Hae-kang,
who can do just about anything.
Who is this guy?
He runs a gambling den like a business.
He's ruthless when it comes to making
and collecting money.
Come in.
Mr. Park, you have a visitor.
Mr. Son.
What's the occasion? You didn't call.
Your office sure is nice, Mr. Park.
You've succeeded.
Succeeded? I still have a long way to go.
But what brings you here all of a sudden?
I know you can pull off anything.
At least, from what I've seen so far.
-What is this about?
-Ten billion won.
Get me ten billion won.
Ten billion?
What kind of scary joke is this?
Sir.
Have I done something wrong?
If I have, please forgive me.
-From now on--
-I'm not joking.
Just think of it as paying it all up front
instead of paying in installments
your whole life.
How could I possibly have that much money?
Let alone in cash.
Mr. Park.
You've made a lot of money
with us watching your back.
And I know how many customers you have.
What's more,
you're Park Hae-kang.
You can make money out of thin air.
I have nothing left
after greasing everyone's palms.
I should clear things up
with you today, sir.
Do I look like I'm joking right now?
I can show you that I'm not joking.
-Sir.
-Let go of me.
-Sir…
-Let go!
Mr. Son!
What's going on, sir?
He wants ten billion won.
Ten billion won?
Well, this isn't the first time.
It's time to grease some palms.
He must be short on money.
The usual, right?
Yes. Thank you.
-Move aside, please!
-Move!
Excuse me.
I'm an employee here!
I'm telling you, it's my first time here!
Please proceed quietly!
Here's your coffee.
I'm calling my lawyer!
Let go of me!
I just followed someone here!
Please pick up.
MR. SON, SEOUL POLICE CHIEF
This is crazy.
I can't believe this.
Hold on.
What's with him?
Geez.
This place was a gambling den?
Apparently, only people
with top-tier credit ratings got in.
I'll call you back in a minute, sweetie.
Okay.
Are you okay? That jerk!
He hit me!
-Why'd you hit me?
-Are you okay?
-He's beating me up!
-What?
A thug hit me! Call the cops!
-Call the cops!
-Cops!
When did I hit you? I…
-What's going on?
-A thug hit me!
-He's obviously a thug.
-No, I…
All right. I tripped while I was walking…
Sir, you're under arrest for assault.
You have the right to remain silent,
and you have the right to an attorney.
MR. PARK HAE-KANG
We're conducting a Breathalyzer test.
It's 0.09. Your license will be revoked.
-What?
-Please step out.
But I didn't drink!
I can't drink at all.
I can't drink a drop of alcohol.
MR. PARK HAE-KANG
Get in there.
Wait.
Sir, wait.
Why am I in here?
You were reported
for illegally filming women's bodies.
What? Hang on. Illegal filming?
My phone is right here. Look.
All I have are photos of bread!
MR. PARK HAE-KANG
Here. Look.
That's my phone. Wait…
Give it back!
About that issue…
Mr. Park Yong-man
of HK Trading and Investment?
What's this about?
ARREST WARRANT
You need to come with us.
We raided the gambling den,
so we have to bring in the figurehead.
Don't take it too personally.
I've brought everything I could.
I'll take this in return
for releasing your men.
You'll need them to get your work done.
I'll give you three months
for the ten billion I mentioned.
Bring it to me in three months.
And Yong-man?
I need to have some insurance too.
I'll exchange Park Yong-man
for the ten billion.
OUTSTANDING ATHLETE AWARD
PARK HAE-KANG
SPORTS AWARD
DAEJUN HIGH SCHOOL
PARK HAE-KANG
Who is it?
What are you doing
in someone else's house?
You must be
Park Hae-kang.
Who are you?
This…
is the loan agreement your father signed
to borrow 30 million won from me.
And you, Park Hae-kang,
are the collateral.
Where is he?
Yes!
What the hell?
What?
You crushed my dream,
and now you're selling me too?
How can you do that to me?
What kind of father are you?
What are you waiting for? Kick him out!
You should manage your business properly!
You little brat!
And he calls himself my son?
How can a father do this to his own child?
Let go of me!
Let go!
Leave while we're asking nicely.
Are you done crying?
I can't do the "I'm your father" thing,
but you can work for me
until you piece your broken dream
back together.
Park Hae-kang.
The food here is amazing.
Perfectly balanced meals…
Just hang in there.
I'll get you out soon.
It's fine. Take your time.
It's not my first time here.
It feels like my old hometown.
Hae-kang, don't strain yourself too hard
to get me out.
I don't have much longer to live anyway.
Find a way to save the others.
They're all relying on you.
Cut the nonsense.
Ever since I took you under my wing
20 years ago,
you've already been
a good enough son to me.
So stop taking care
of other people's lives
and focus on your own.
No.
Don't be ridiculous.
You all went through a lot.
Mr. Park.
Are we just supposed to
take this lying down?
We have enough dirt on Mr. Son too.
It'll be more than enough
to take him down.
He won't stop at Yong-man.
He got to you guys too.
He can easily destroy your lives.
Still, it's ten billion.
Where would we get ten billion won?
We've been extorted
out of over one billion won so far.
But ten billion?
Go live your own lives now.
I'll take care of this.
We're not some gang anyway.
And I'm not your gang leader.
I'm just the CEO,
and you're the employees.
Think of this as quitting.
I'll give you
your severance pay later.
What about our old boss?
What will you do?
He's like a father to me.
I'll take care of him.
Go.
Guys.
Are you sure it's okay to just leave?
Go on.
I'll get going.
Bye. I'll call you.
What are you waiting for?
Bye.
Wait.
Guys.
I'll see you again later.
CHEERS TO YONG-MAN'S NEW BEGINNING!
Sir.
I'm not going to quit.
I won't quit.
Sir…
I…
I'm not quitting either.
What's with you guys?
When Gyeong-buk…
was just an infant,
our boss would change his diapers
and read to him.
He practically raised him.
I couldn't graduate from law school,
but he was the one who secretly paid
for my tuition.
He always praised my cooking
and said I had incredible talent.
He even said
people would line up to try my food
if I opened a restaurant.
He's the one who helped me find my dream.
Mr. Park,
let us help you
save our old boss.
We're not a gang now,
but we're more than just
a CEO and staff, aren't we?
He's right.
We live together, and we die together.
Let us help you!
Are you sure you won't regret it?
-Yes.
Then let's do this.
Ten billion.
I'm sure we'll find a way.
A double-eyelid surgery is quite simple,
so there's no need to be nervous.
Dr. Han, if you don't pay me back,
you might end up
under permanent anesthesia.
COURTHOUSE
Mr. Prosecutor, sir!
The defendant today
was up for habitual illegal gambling.
Can I sue someone for not paying back
their illegal gambling funds?
Why has it been so difficult to reach you?
YOON JEONG-BOK
You'd better pay up now.
Hello. It's been a while, sir.
Hello.
But who…
Hi there.
This is True Value.
At this price, you got a great deal.
We collected unpaid debts
and even sold my car and apartment,
but this is all we got?
Geez.
A 1st birthday party two weeks ago,
and now Man-sik is having
his 60th birthday party next month.
Who celebrates
their 60th birthday these days?
I know everyone collects money
after retiring, but that jerk…
I mean, he's taken
over 100 million from us.
Hang on.
It was his kid's 1st birthday,
and he's turning 60 next month?
He had a kid at 59 years old?
Did you hear anything
about how much he collected
at the birthday party?
I'm not sure how much,
but I heard he bought an apartment
after the party.
An apartment? Where?
-In Gangnam?
-Yes.
We should host something too.
-Host something?
-We've been giving out money.
I bet it's at least 600 million.
We'll gain it all back this time.
What kind of event?
A wedding!
Wouldn't weddings bring in
the most cash gifts?
That's a good idea.
But we don't have a bride.
How may I help you, ma'am?
WEE PARTNERS
FREE LEGAL CONSULTATION APPLICATION
My son's dead.
People keep telling me
I have to renounce the inheritance
or something,
but I don't have the money
to hire a lawyer.
You came to the right place.
We're here to help people like you.
-You filed the death report, right?
-Yes.
Take these files.
Thank you so much.
Of course. I get paid to do this.
Ms. Kang.
Yes?
Well…
Don't you know we send up customers
for cases like that?
It should've been a paid case.
YEONG-JU
She didn't have much money.
You're unbelievable.
-What?
-Are you free this weekend?
There's a gig for you.
-What is it?
-Can you afford to be picky right now?
You need to send money to your sister.
Deal.
WARMEST CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR BEAUTIFUL UNION
-Hello!
-I'm here.
-Hey.
He's here.
Wow.
Am I in a crime movie or what?
Who's getting married?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
GROOM
PARK HAE-KANG
PARK HAE-KANG & KIM MIN-JI
CONGRATULATIONS, HAE-KANG
YOUR BROTHER, TADAYOSHI
Boss!
-Move over for a bit.
-What?
Do I have to go this far?
One of you can do it. Why me?
We already told you.
We'll get more cash if you're the groom.
Wow.
You look so handsome.
Your lips are very nice.
He's the most handsome customer
you've had, isn't he?
See?
Mr. Park!
All our retired members are here.
The venue's filled with guests!
But we're already out of beef tartare.
Is the bride here?
Me?
I'm getting married today?
That's what I'm telling you.
Hurry up and change.
You need to get your makeup done.
There must be some kind of mistake.
I thought I was going to be a guest.
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
I heard you were referred by Yeong-ju.
You can't back out now.
How would we find
another bride last-minute?
-I'll pay you generously.
-Ma'am.
Didn't you see those men out there?
They look like thugs.
The groom must be someone
in the underworld.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you can't just leave now!
We don't have time.
Five million won.
Deal.
The wedding of Park Hae-kang
and Kim Min-ji will begin shortly…
I know this must be overwhelming,
but I'm counting on you.
In any case, let's do this.
Hold on tight.
…let us meet the bride and groom.
Please welcome them
with a big round of applause.
The bride and groom will now enter.
-Park Hae-kang!
Sharing a life as husband and wife
is not easy, of course,
but if you live as each other's half
and live faithfully together,
you'll…
Live happily together.
Next, to celebrate this joyful union,
the groom's colleagues have prepared
a special performance.
Please welcome them
with a round of applause.
We're going to smile, smile again
This is a happy moment, happy day
Straighten your shoulders
And erase all your worries
Forget your sadness, never cry
Beneath the blazing sun, sunny day
Just wish for only good things
To come your way
Like the vast sky, laugh louder
And think bigger
Forget your tears, never cry
Like the bright sunlight, sunshine day
I'll pray that your days
Will be filled with happiness
Park Hae-kang!
Congratulations, Park Hae-kang!
Picture-perfect, Park Hae-kang!
All right.
Then lastly, why don't the bride and groom
kiss for the photo?
-Kiss! Kiss!
Mr. Park, you have to kiss!
Two million more.
-Kiss! Kiss!
It's okay.
I got paid more.
So it's fine.
Is it the right amount?
Two million extra for the kiss.
Yes. Everything's in there.
But it wasn't a proper kiss.
What?
The kiss.
I only kissed my thumb,
and it was next to your lips.
Still, we touched.
Do you even know how I feel?
I paid a fair, I mean…
I paid you plenty for that.
Should I worry about your feelings too?
You hired a fake bride
and held a grand wedding.
I feel like I'm involved
in some huge scam.
It just feels wrong.
What's more, there's this…
There was some touching involved.
Well, you were the one who said,
"Deal."
You said it so willingly.
Anyway,
this was unpleasant for both of us,
so let's not cross paths again.
As someone working in law,
let me tell you something.
Stay on the right side of the law.
Let's just focus on helping Yong-man.
Focus.
We're still 6.5 billion short.
Is there anything else?
There's only the Lizard
to collect from, but…
Luck is on my side today.
Thanks.
-But what?
-I visited his management office,
but they said he's currently wanted.
Wanted? For what?
Embezzlement and breach of trust.
Find him before the police do.
Tell him to pay me back
with the money he embezzled.
I just got the Lizard's location.
He's in Osan.
Get him. Now.
I'll pay you back! Please!
Please don't kill me!
Mr. Park is here.
Sir!
Mr. Park!
What took you so long?
Tell them to let me go.
I'm freezing right now.
-Please, help me!
-What about my money?
We retrieved 20 million,
and we checked his credit rating.
It's Grade 8.
Then he can't pay me back.
You assholes!
Are you a bunch of thugs or what?
You're just lowlifes earning petty cash
from a gambling den!
You can't kill anyone!
Come on, then! Kill me!
Get on with it! I'm freezing!
-I'll either freeze to death or fall!
-Level 2!
Just try…
Help me!
Help me! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
I won't act up, I swear.
Mr. Park.
Are there about 10,000 households here?
What?
This apartment complex!
Are there about 10,000 households?
There are 9,800.
I saw on my way here
that your apartment complex is having
a building representative election.
I have a great idea.
Just hear me out.
Get rid of him.
-Just throw him off. Let's go.
-Wait!
There's easy money
in this apartment complex
that you don't know about!
Check my jacket.
There's a notebook
and some account books in my pocket.
You'll believe me once you see it.
Let him go for now.
Thank you.
It's the other way.
Isn't this going a bit too far
for a prank?
What is this?
Records of what I've been skimming off.
I inflated the maintenance fees
and procurement costs
and received payments
from bidding competitors.
I gambled with money from all that.
So this is proof that you're trash…
I can pay back everything
if I just work for a week
at my apartment complex.
PLUMBING MATERIALS
ELECTRICAL SUPPLIES
CHRISTMAS EVENT
EXTERIOR WALL CONSTRUCTION
MAINTENANCE FEES, SECURITY SERVICE…
SENIOR CENTER REMODELING
SUPPLIES ORGANIZATION, LANDSCAPING…
Four billion?
You pocketed four billion won?
Our apartment complex
only has 1,200 households,
and I skimmed that much.
But this place
has almost 10,000 households.
Then how much do you think
you can skim off?
A billion? Two billion?
That's pocket change!
You could even skim off ten billion!
I'm serious, Mr. Park!
Ten billion?
Yes.
We can skim off
ten billion won
from this apartment complex?
THE APARTMENT JOB
How do we skim off ten billion then?
Become the building representative,
then the president.
Would there really be ten billion here?
Ask them how much
the long-term repair reserve fund is.
Long-term what?
There's 17,857,420,000 won.
The complex residents
aren't doing anything?
Everyone's busy with their own lives.
They don't even care about it.
-You have to run for building rep.
-Do you live alone?
I've never seen anyone living alone
run for building representative.
We need a family
to take that repair reserve fund.
Mom, Dad, Grandma, Grandpa.
People like that.
Let's work on something together.
Play the role of my wife for three months.
-Play the role of what?
-My wife.
A hundred million.
A hundred million for three months.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park