Why do you think
I let you go in the first place?
Please.
You have to be happy.
My happiness
is fulfilling your wishes.
If that's what you want...
I can arrange for you
to return to the company.
Whether it's destroying the people
who kicked you out or anything else...
Just give me the order.
Takaaki said something so terrifying
with a completely straight face.
So, what is your order?
Forever...
Stay by my side forever.
He listened to my answer.
And started coming to
my place three days a week.
Since then, I haven't
given Takaaki a single order.
Even so, Takaaki still takes care of me
just like before.
The only difference is...
We haven't slept together.
"The Servant Prince"
(Episode 2)
Are you still working on that?
Do you really need to dry
that plate so thoroughly?
I'm almost done.
Damn it.
What should I do?
Before, whenever I wanted to do it,
I'd just get ready...
And then I'd just order him.
Come here.
Let's do it.
Understood.
Other than that,
I have no idea how to initiate it.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Um...
Naoya?
Beer.
Once I finish cleaning up here,
I'll dry your hair for you.
No, thanks.
I can do it myself.
Oh, man.
This is bad.
He was cute enough before, but...
Hey, what are you doing?
Hurry up and do it.
Understood.
This is way cuter
than I ever imagined.
Honestly...
I want to pin him down right now.
If he'd just give me one order...
You haven't dried your hair yet, have you?
It's fine.
You'll catch a cold if you leave it wet.
I said I've got it.
Hey, Takaaki.
When do you usually feel like doing it?
Whenever you order me to.
Anytime is fine.
If you don't want to, then never mind.
Naoya, you've got it wrong.
I've always been
in a state of "waiting."
What?
I'm always waiting for you
to give me the green light.
You ask when I feel like doing it?
As long as it's you, Naoya,
I want to all the time.
If you let me touch you
without waiting for an order...
You'll definitely regret it.
You...
Back in high school...
Here.
Lick it clean.
Naoya's orders were always the best reward for
someone constantly suppressing his desires.
Understood.
You really do
whatever I say, don't you?
If I ordered you to kiss me,
would you do that too?
What is your order?
Today...
Do it until you're satisfied.
So cute.
Understood.
Even when I was tormented
by near-fatal despair...
He would hold me
until I drifted off to sleep.
And when I woke up...
I'd feel like I could keep going.
(Goto Construction)
That company name...
Isn't that my parents' company?
Good morning.
Don't "good morning" me.
Are you doing business with them?
I told you, whether you want to go back
or crush them, I'll do whatever you order.
I've already laid the groundwork.
What you said back then...
you actually had a concrete plan?
You're burning up.
You have a slight fever.
You should rest today.
It doesn't matter what day it is.
Every day is a day off for the unemployed.
Get some proper rest.
Stop treating me like a child.
Be good.
Unemployed...
Living in a studio
apartment provided for me.
With this body that can only survive
by relying on someone else...
Can I ever pull myself
out of this rock bottom...
And return to normal society?
I want to...
become strong too.
Yes.
Just like Takaaki.
Just like my father,
whom I could never resist.
Even though I know
I'm not cut out for it...
I just can't bring myself to give up.
Understood.
Damn it...
It's delicious.
Understood.
He said "Understood" at the end...
But even so, there's probably
nothing I can do.
Well, that concludes our regular meeting.
- Thank you.
Hey.
Is this a good time to talk?
Oh, what a surprise.
I didn't expect you to call me.
I thought I'd better make things clear.
About last night...
Actually, this morning too.
Forget all of it.
Wipe it completely from your memory.
Forget what?
Everything, you idiot!
Understood.
Damn it...
I'm not letting him
have his way with me anymore.
*Sigh*
"I want to become strong," my foot.
No matter how you look at it, I should
start by learning to support myself.
All right.
(President Goto Taketoshi)
Two years ago, on the day Naoya called me
to say he had lost everything...
Naoya.
Takaaki.
Sell this apartment as soon as possible
and find me a cheap studio.
Anywhere is fine,
as long as it's out of the way.
If there's nothing left after paying off
the mortgage, I need you to cover the rest.
Once the bankruptcy is finalized,
I'll move in immediately.
Understood.
Everything here is exactly the same
as it was when I came by two days ago.
Takaaki, you're here.
You should eat something.
No.
I called you here to sleep with me.
Now...
Go take a shower.
Understood.
While I held him...
He cried himself to sleep.
It was a cycle that kept repeating.
Excuse me.
President, the car is ready.
Good. Thank you.
Regarding the matter we
discussed the other day...
Here are the compiled details.
I see.
From our standpoint,
we cannot make any further concessions.
You're talking pretty big.
I hear you're also considering
partnering with other companies.
You're well-informed.
It would be a shame, but...
If you insist on forcing through
your original budget...
We'll have no choice but
to terminate our partnership.
Are you sure you want to say that?
You're just a newly established startup.
If you lose your contract with our group...
Your cash flow will dry up,
and you'll be ruined in no time.
You don't need to worry about that.
Please give it some thought.
Over the past two years...
as Naoya's hair grew longer...
his mind and body slowly began to heal.
But...
Sell this apartment as soon as possible
and find me a cheap studio.
Takaaki, you're here.
You should eat something.
No.
I called you here to sleep with me.
Please.
You have to be happy.
I want to...
Become strong too.
The people who pushed Naoya to the edge...
I will never forgive them.
[He's scrolling through
part-time job applications]
[A listing for a wait-staff position
at a Western style restaurant]
(Preview)
My name is Goto Naoya, and I start working
here today. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Wow, Goto-kun
is a natural at this.
Well, if it isn't Naoya.
I wondered where you'd been hiding.
I never expected to find you here, doing
grunt work that even a monkey could do.
Goto-kun.
Will I see you tomorrow too?
Yes, I'm on the schedule.
Did something happen?
Hey, hold me.
You can do whatever you want with me.
I'm the only one he has left.