I'm so excited.
Superhero movies are always so exciting.
Yeah.
Especially sequels. The hype is real.
Saeki, who's your
favorite superhero?
A superhero, huh?
- What about you, Wataru?
- Me?
I'm a die-hard Jet fan.
I knew it. I totally called it.
During summer break,
even on days we weren't
visiting film locations,
we'd still hang out, watch
movies, and grab food.
Just spending time together doing nothing.
Have you decided yet?
Yeah.
But it's a secret.
What?
Now you've got me curious.
The trailers are starting.
But then, out of nowhere, it would hit me.
Hey.
What are you smiling at?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Come on.
Now you've got me curious.
No, really.
I just thought...
you look cute when you pout.
I like you.
Ouch!
Look straight ahead. Watch the screen.
Okay, okay.
Wandering through doubts and confusion,
they slowly search for answers.
Where will their future lead them?
In the end, I couldn't focus at all.
Maybe we hyped it up too much
because it was a sequel.
Huh?
Well, you sighed so loudly,
I thought you were disappointed.
Oh...
Yeah, I guess so.
It wasn't bad, though.
But maybe it's because
they changed directors for this one.
Yeah.
But there are other movies to see this
summer. Let's look forward to the next one.
Yeah.
By the way,
where are we going for our next pilgrimage?
Oh, let me see...
The tonkatsu place from the middle of the
movie, and the beach from the final scene.
Let's start with the closer one,
the tonkatsu place.
Ah, that tonkatsu place.
The one that saved the protagonist
from the depths of despair, right?
Man, I'm starving just thinking about it.
When should we go?
Let me think.
I have work shifts coming up.
How about the 10th?
The 10th, huh?
Hmm? What's wrong?
You don't seem very excited.
Oh, do you already have plans that day?
No.
I'm free that day.
I was just wondering... Does that mean
we won't see each other until the 10th?
Huh?
Come on,
that's not that far away.
Besides, we'll see each other
at the national mock exam on the 6th.
Yeah, I guess so.
But to me right now,
that feels like forever.
Oh, really?
Wataru, you know...
You always pout when you're embarrassed.
I am not pouting.
And I'm not embarrassed.
You totally have a grumpy face right now.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
Being with Saeki is just as fun as always.
Even though nothing has really changed,
What do you want to eat?
I can't help but feel...
Ginger pork.
How should I put it...
Hey, Wataru.
How've you been lately?
My heart just won't stop fluttering.
What's that about? Wataru, you pervert!
No, he's just in heat.
What about you guys?
Great, we're doing great.
Man, it's boiling hot every day.
And I'm just practicing judo all day.
Do you have club
practice today too, Hiraoka?
No, today's my day off.
Then do you want to go to karaoke
after the mock exam?
Oh, yeah! Let's do it.
- Are you in?
- Wataru, you're coming too, right?
Oh, do you have work?
No work today, so I'm in.
Karaoke? Can I come along too?
Uh, it's Asada.
What's with the "uh"?
Nothing!
I was just saying "uh-huh, sure!"
Classic Guchi.
Quick on your feet.
That's not a compliment.
So, what's the plan?
Who's paying?
- Hmm...
- Let's decide by our exam scores.
A score battle, huh?
I like it! I like it! I like it!
- Huh?
- Sorry, I'm just...
How should I put it...
My heart is fluttering a bit.
"My Summer Of You"
(Episode 3)
♪ When we first met, I never imagined ♪
♪ That a day of parting
like this would ever come ♪
♪ Making good things better ♪
♪ No, it's all in the past now ♪
♪ We were merely piling
up the moments we shared ♪
♪ Exhausted in body and soul ♪
♪ What you loved was
nothing but my illusion ♪
Wataru, I queued up the next song for you.
Whoa! What is it?
(A Little Love Song)
I hope you find love this year.
Shut up.
♪ Among the countless
stars in the vast universe ♪
♪ In the wide world of this blue planet ♪
♪ This tiny love will find its way ♪
♪ To you on your tiny island ♪
Man, I'm exhausted.
A table for four?
- Please sit anywhere.
- Okay.
Isn't this booth a bit too big for us?
- This one?
- Yeah, seriously.
Alright, let's eat, eat, eat!
Cola, cola.
Cola again?
- Yep, cola again.
- I think I'll get the hamburger steak today.
I feel that.
- Oh?
- What's up?
Hey, isn't that Saeki over there?
Are you a cat person or a dog person?
Birds.
Hamsters.
Hamsters?
Do you have a hamster?
I used to have one.
Oh, what color was it?
Grey, I think.
Whoa, he's with two girls.
The popular-kid energy
over there is insane.
Excuse me, there's a girl right here too.
Huh? Where?
Do you need to get your eyes checked?
- Seriously.
- Your prescription must be off.
Wait, really?
Wait, isn't Hiraoka a girl?
- No way!
- Stop joking around.
- She has zero game.
- But still...
- No way, no way, no way.
- Come on, that's not true.
Honestly, Wataru looks
more like a girl than she does.
Huh? Me?
No way.
That brings back memories.
In seventh grade, when Wataru had soda for
the first time, it shot right out of his nose.
I remember! It came out of both nostrils.
It sprayed so far.
It did not shoot out of my nose!
Maybe a slight exaggeration?
Just a little bit.
But it just means
you were so innocent and cute back then.
Compared to the rest of us
sweaty guys in the judo club,
Wataru is still pretty cute.
I'm just pure-hearted, unlike you guys.
Oh? Even though your heart is fluttering?
I told you, it's not!
Are you still on that?
He's seriously so cute.
- What was its name?
- Huh?
What was it again?
- I forgot.
- No way, you just said it.
But I think I get what you mean.
In elementary school, I
always hung out with boys too.
But gradually, it became
harder to talk to them.
But with Toda, it's totally fine.
Why is that?
Wataru is just a boy at
heart. A pure-hearted boy.
Pure-hearted boy.
I'm going to get refills.
- Same thing?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- Toda is basically the nation's little brother.
- Hey.
Hey, cut it out.
You guys are definitely not praising me.
- Pure-hearted boy.
Uh...
Oh, my brother's calling me to come home.
- I'll head out first.
- Ah, I should probably head back too.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
What are you guys going to do?
Aren't you going to get dessert?
Well...
I have time. I can stay and eat with you.
Thanks.
I'll decide what to get right away.
Hey, Wataru.
Could you pay for these, please?
Sure, no problem.
Thanks!
- We'll head out first. Bye!
- Bye.
Bye. Talk to you later.
- Have you decided yet?
- Not yet.
You're still thinking about it, aren't you?
Huh? The dessert?
No, not that.
Saeki and his friends.
You've been staring
over there this whole time.
No, I haven't.
If you say so.
I was wondering...
if the person Saeki likes is in that group.
So you still don't know
who it is, do you?
Are you still on about that?
I told you, I don't know.
- Really?
- Really.
Even if I did, it's not like I'd
go around gossiping about it.
True.
That makes sense.
Oh, by the way.
Did you take any photos
during your pilgrimage?
Well, yeah, I did.
- Let me see!
- No way, I'm not showing you.
Come on, why not?
I just want to see the scenery.
- Yeah, right. Nice try.
- Hand it over! Come on!
You just want to look at handsome guys.
I can't deny that.
Wataru.
You're here too.
Yeah...
I'll text you about the 10th.
I'll head out first.
Did something happen between you and Saeki?
Huh...?
You guys are going on
another pilgrimage, right?
He seemed so excited about it before,
but he seemed so distant just now.
We're just getting pork cutlets.
It's normal to be casual about it.
But Saeki...
He's been stealing glances
at you this whole time.
Really...?
So I was wondering
if he has you on his mind.
Wait, did you just smile?
- What's that about?
- Huh? I didn't smile.
- Come on, just order already.
- I know, I know.
Hurry up.
Give me a second.
Hmm...
- You're going to order pudding again, aren't you?
- I'd love to, but...
A parfait, huh?
- Want to share?
- Sure, why not?
Wow, that looks delicious.
- Let's eat!
I'll go with the sesame dressing.
Hmm...
Then I'll use the onion dressing.
Wow, this looks so good.
It's delicious!
This is amazing.
- It's so good, it's incredible!
- Yeah.
This is the best pork cutlet I've ever had.
I knew it would be good,
but it was totally worth the trip.
It definitely was.
You know,
food in movies and on TV
always looks so much better.
I know, right?
I have a weak spot
for simple food.
Like rice balls.
Oh, I totally get that.
But seriously, this is so good.
What's wrong?
You have a grain of rice on your face.
Huh? Rice?
Where?
Right here.
How embarrassing.
It's so cool sitting in the exact same spot
as they did in the movie.
Yeah.
Oh, we should take a
picture before we finish.
Oh, right.
Hey there, handsome fellas.
You came here because
of "Sea of Light," right?
- Yes.
- I knew it!
Actually, I was an extra in that movie.
The scene where the main character
cries because the cutlet is so good...
You remember that, right?
I was the clerk
looking at him with concern.
I was just an extra,
but I accidentally stole the scene.
If you'd like,
I can take a photo of you two.
Oh, yes, please.
- Then we'll...
- Come on, get together. No problem.
Okay, I'm going to take it.
Ready, set...
Huh...?
*Click*
*Click, click*
Yay!
- Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you very much.
- Come back soon! Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you for waiting.
Table for four, right this way.
- That's a great souvenir.
- Yeah.
What should we do next?
Is there anything fun to do around here?
Oh, Higashimura Park is really close.
It's only about two stops away.
Yeah.
Wow, this brings back memories.
Can we stop by?
Huh...?
- Come on, let's go.
- Oh, alright.
Great, let's go!
Wow, it hasn't changed at all.
I fell into this pond once.
Why?
Well, I think I thought
I could walk along the fence.
Are you serious?
I can totally picture that.
Hey, you're laughing too hard.
Geez.
Everyone treats me like a kid.
Asada even called me "the
nation's little brother" the other day.
Really?
Yeah.
What about you, Saeki? Have you been here?
Oh, I think so.
With my ex-girlfriend.
Oh...
Come to think of it, I think this is the
first time I've heard you talk about this.
By the way,
Wataru, are things
going well with that girl?
Which girl?
The one you were with at the diner.
Asada, right?
You two stayed behind alone.
Huh?
It's not like that at all.
It's just that Asada really wanted dessert,
so I stayed to keep her company.
- Oh, I see.
- Yeah.
Hmm...
I thought she and Wataru
looked good together.
What is with you today?
First your ex-girlfriend,
now Asada.
And another thing...
Back at the diner,
you talked to me so casually.
Usually, when you see the person you like
having a good time with someone else,
doesn't it make you feel uncomfortable?
It doesn't bother me.
Oh.
I told you from the start.
Just being able to tell you how I feel,
and having you treat me normally,
and even going on
this pilgrimage with me...
that's more than enough for me.
I want you to do whatever you want, Wataru.
I get it.
Huh?
Someone's crying.
- It's that little girl.
- Mommy, it hurts!
- What's wrong?
- It hurts!
- Chiharu!
Are you okay?
Mommy, it hurts!
Did you fall?
Let me see your knee.
Ouch, that must hurt.
Let's go over there and
put some medicine on it.
- Medicine...?
- Yeah.
She seems fine now.
Yeah.
Her name is Chiharu, too.
My name was also chosen so it
could be used for either a boy or a girl.
I see.
Oh.
Come to think of it, when I was little,
I met a crying little girl here, too.
Really?
She was crouching and crying,
just like that little girl.
I couldn't just leave her.
She said she was lost,
so I took her to find her parents.
Are you okay?
But that little girl...
Wataru.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
If you don't want this,
you can push me away.
Wait...
What are you doing?
What if someone comes...?
Yeah... I know.
He said that was enough,
and put an end to
his feelings on his own.
But when he expresses his
feelings to me so wholeheartedly...
Even I...
The reason I want to return his feelings...
Maybe it's all because of summer.
(Next Episode) Once this arrangement
is over, what will become of us?
Showing someone your room feels like
being stripped bare. It's so embarrassing.
Thank you.
I heard Saeki took the day off today.
If you ever stop liking me...
That's...