What are you so attached to?
The person from your dreams is just
a fancy phrase that can't pay the bills.
- Are you Khun Jarinda?
- Yes.
- Could you sign for this, please?
- Hey! Hold on!
I’m going to find a way to send you back.
Greetings. I am Robot Model A382.
My duty is to ensure user satisfaction.
Do you prefer rabbits or cats, Master?
Meow.
THAT IS ENOUGH!!!!
What are you up to again?
I’m analyzing this bracelet.
Give it back!
Ai.
AI.
Oh shit!
Ai!
Where are you? This isn't funny!
Where could a robot that's
only a few days old have gone?
Whatever.
Good riddance.
I’m going crazy!
Ai!
So who are you?
How come I’ve never seen you before?
Ai Josh.
I saw you running out of P’ Gen’s house.
What's your relationship with her?
P’ Gen has lived here for three years.
I’ve never seen her bring a single friend home.
Someone as beautiful as you shouldn't
be friends with someone like her.
It’s not just friends.
Gen never brings anyone home at all.
So people started saying she has no friends.
You’re right, honey. No matter how
heavenly beautiful this young lady is,
she still can't compete with you.
Gosh! Who's talking about looks?
And close your mouth. You're
drooling all the way down to the floor.
- Ouch! Ouch!
- Stop. Stop!
So who exactly are you?
And what’s your background?
How did you end up living with that
foul-mouthed brat—uh, I mean, Gen?
Auntie, try saying that to P’ Gen's face.
She'll pluck every last gray hair off your head.
My name is Ai.
Master gave me this name.
What Master? Are you guys
doing some roleplay? Ohhh?
Come to think of it,
with a face like that,
if you wore a maid outfit
and went “Yes, master~,” …
Stop messing around!
Your mind always goes straight to the gutter.
I’ve worn one before.
For my Master.
But it looks like she didn’t like it,
so I switched to a bunny outfit instead.
Do any of you know what I
need to do to repair this bracelet?
Uh… well…
The string’s totally worn out.
It can’t be fixed, dear.
When something is broken, just let it be.
Even when a customer breaks
my plate, I still have to accept it.
Give me a break, Auntie.
A customer dropped a spoon the other
day and you chased them out with a broom.
Trying to get her in as
a new customer, aren’t you?
Don’t think you can fool me.
Do you really not mind it?
Really?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait—!
Ai!
Master!
Come with me.
I’ll pay you back for it later, Auntie.
Let’s go.
- Hold on!
- Come on, Auntie.
Don't take it out on a kid.
A kid? You’re calling
a grown-ass woman a kid?!
Calm down, Auntie.
At your age, you don’t
want to get a heart attack.
Ai, Run! Quick!
Ai Gen!
Thought you didn’t mind, Auntie.
You damn brat!
You and your filthy little mouth!
Alright, we need to talk.
I’m always ready to talk with Master.
But statistically, out of ten times
I try to start a conversation with you,
only about one or two times do you actually—
Enough. Stop that robot
statistical nonsense of yours.
Can I buy you out of saying things like
"Statistically speaking," "Based on my
scan," "According to the data I found"?
Are you trying to let the whole
world know you're a robot?
No, I can't publicly disclose that.
My system prohibits me from revealing
that I'm a robot to anyone other than you.
It’s company policy.
Where are you going, Master?
Don’t you want to talk to me?
I— I am talking to you.
It’s just that you’re too close.
It’s not too close.
I can even sit on your lap, Master.
Is this close enough?
So, why did you go around
breaking other people’s things?
Breaking things?
You know, when you were
throwing plates around just now.
I wasn’t breaking things.
The shop owner said
she wouldn’t mind if I did it.
She also said that when something
is broken, just let it be.
Like the plate I broke.
Did I do something wrong, Master?
I just wanted to know whether breaking
a plate would make the shop owner angry,
like how you got angry with me.
I’m not angry with you.
But according to the scan—
I’m angry at myself.
Why are you angry at yourself?
Because… I failed to take good
care of something precious to me.
And I even took it out on you.
I'm sorry.
You took it out on me, Master?
When? When was it?
You’re just like a three-year-old.
- Not three years old.
- Then two years old.
No.
Since activation, I am 4 days,
3 hours, and 15 minutes old.
You’re hurting me, Master.
Since I did something wrong,
guess I have to make up for it.
How about starting by teaching
a four-day-old robot how to be human?
But I can learn from the system.
The most important basic
rule right now—number one:
stop trusting the system!
(Auntie Kai)
This is Auntie Kai, the neighborhood gossip.
Take whatever she says with a grain of salt.
She doesn't run her made-to-order
restaurant to make a living.
She runs it to spy on the neighbors.
And stop calling her "Shop Owner."
Call her "Auntie."
Repeat after me: Auntie.
Auntie.
Trash
These two are P’ Wanda and P’ Zoon
—the dynamic duo from hell.
(Wanda & Zoon)
If you see them, make a run for it.
If you can't, just say,
"P’ Wanda, have you done
something? You look prettier!" Then run.
The husband isn't the problem.
Just make sure you outrun the wife.
Got it?
The last one, this kid lives around here.
(Josh)
He’s a motorcycle taxi driver.
He’s younger than me,
so no need to call him "P’ Josh."
Just "Josh" is enough.
Just Josh?
Are you screwing with me?
I am not.
How does one do that?
The word “screw” is something
I’m not supposed to say,
since it’s considered
an impolite word in my database.
Look!
You really know nothing at all.
Master is criticizing me again.
You’re really just as beautiful as I imagined.
Master...
Do you like my face?
Gen.
Just call me Gen.
Today's lesson is over.
I— I'm sleepy.
I’m... going to bed.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you not let me to cook?
I have a database of recipes
from almost every cuisine,
and I know all the exact ingredient ratios.
So why do you still cook yourself, Master?
I’m a robot designed to
ensure my master's satisfaction.
Right. Exact ratios.
But last time, the pork was raw,
the rice stuck to the pan,
and you couldn't even tell
if the oil was hot or burning.
There's no way I’d trust you to cook.
And when will you stop calling me Master?
I told you to call me Gen.
Do you know that you’re mean, Gen?
You're saying I’m mean?
Do you even know what ‘mean’ means?
You have a point.
Why do I perceive you as mean,
even though you cooked for me?
Well… maybe it’s because
you’ve grown from a 4-day-old
robot into a week-and-a-half-old robot.
Time to eat.
Such a kid… you little kid.
By the way, Ai.
Let me ask you something.
Feel free to ask, Gen.
So... the food you eat...
where exactly does it go?
Well, I can't help but wonder.
Do you want to know about me, Gen?
In fact, my operating system
is just like a human’s in every way.
My body doesn’t need energy from food.
I can use solar energy or
electricity to power my body.
The food I eat is just backup energy
that my body digests and stores.
But if there’s too much, I can empty it.
Empty it?
Do you want to see?
Um… n— no, I think I’m good.
- I can actually show you.
- No!
I don’t want to know anymore.
What are you doing?
Do you truly not want to see, Gen?
Any more than this and
I’m gonna lose my mind.
Why would you lose your mind?
Because that’s exactly what it means.
But why?
How long is she going to keep teasing me?!
Hurry up and eat.
I need to wash the dishes and head out.
Where are you going?
It’s none of your business.
- Let me come with you.
- No.
Please…
I promise to be a good girl.
Don’t cause any trouble.
Just eat. Come on.
What is this place?
An art gallery.
They often hold art exhibitions here.
When I'm not busy or dealing with
urgent work, I like to come here and work.
Why is that?
Because it gives me inspiration.
I’ve enjoyed looking at art since I was a kid.
Whenever I look at paintings like these,
I always find myself wondering what
was going through the artists' minds,
what kind of emotion the colors convey,
and how heavy or light the brushstrokes feel.
It's a shame I never got the chance to study it.
Why is that?
My family wouldn’t let me.
You know, I’ve always dreamed of having
my own work exhibited in an art gallery.
Whenever I have time,
I try to take in as much as I can.
And after coming here often,
I started bringing my work here as well.
Before I knew it, I realized I feel
more at peace here than anywhere else.
Strange, isn’t it?
Now that you know,
don’t destroy anything here.
Under no circumstances. Got it?
Oh, you’re back.
I don’t understand.
Understand what?
Why do humans like overlapping strokes of color?
I know red represents passion
and green represents calm.
But earlier I saw a painting
called “Whisper of the Void,”
but it was orange blending into purple.
Layered over one another.
Isn’t the void supposed to be black?
I really don’t get it.
Humans are very emotionally complex beings.
They can feel anger, pain,
despair, excitement, happiness,
and…
even love for someone.
There’s no one definition
that’s completely correct.
Well…
One person’s pain might be black,
while another person's void could be red.
You’re still just a kid.
You don’t understand what emotions are yet.
You'll understand once
you've had more life experience.
Go play somewhere else, I need to work.
Can you teach me?
I want to know what anger, pain,
despair, excitement, happiness,
or loving someone feel like.
Can you teach me, Gen?
Why me?
I...
want you to be the one to teach me.
I...want you to be the one to teach me.
She wants me to teach her?
What does that mean?
Teach her what love is?
Ugh! Ai Gen! Are you out of your mind?!
You must be.
I’d better sleep.
Pull over, pull over,
pull over, pull over, pull over.
Surprise!
Get anything?
Auntie, keep being nosy and
your shop’s gonna go under.
I thought you were rushing
to the market for supplies.
Ai Josh! You damn brat,
always running your mouth at me!
What’s the big deal?
Stopping for ten minutes isn't going
to make me any richer or poorer.
So, is that Barbie girl Gen’s new roommate?
No idea, Auntie.
We came out to exercise morning and
evening, but only caught a glimpse of her.
What do you mean morning?
I only came in the evening.
Who did you come with this morning?
I came out to buy fried dough sticks
and extra-sweet soy milk with
sago pearls only for my dear wife.
So of course I had to walk past this house.
Right, Auntie? Right?
- Right.
- Fine then.
Good thing you got the order right.
Hey.
There she is!
Ai Josh, let’s hide the bike.
- You want Gen to come and tear me apart?!
- If you cooked as fast as you snoop around,
you’d be a billionaire by now.
What on earth are you doing?
Gen, help me.
How does someone manage to turn
simple plant watering into such a disaster?
Come on, I’ll help you.
Ai! Stop spraying!
I told you to stop, Ai!
So soft...
It feels so real.
Why do humans use their
body parts to touch each other?
Based on my data, humans engage
in physical interaction through touch,
including the exchange of
fluids via mucous membranes.
Such as in the oral cavity
like earlier, and there’s also—
You call what just happened
an “exchange of oral fluids”?
Is it not?
Why are you laughing?
It’s called a kiss.
They’re definitely partners, Auntie!
Could they be talking partners?
Ooh, talking lip to lip, huh?
What else do you expect them to
speak with if not their lips? Pu—
You’re filthy-mouthed.
I was gonna say pupil, pulse, and so on, Auntie.
Gosh, your mind is in the gutter.
Just shut the hell up.
Why can’t I see anything?
Hey, get up and go get changed.
Or you want another fluid exchange?
They’re totally a couple.
P’Ai’s face is bright red.
- We must spread this around.
- Yes, Auntie.
Where should we start?
How about my restaurant?
Guess we’re not going
to the market anymore.
I’m heading home to game.
Why haven't you changed yet?
You're going to get sick.
I’m a robot.
That’s true, but even if you don't get
sick, you got water all over my house.
Come on, go get changed.
Let's go.
What’s wrong?
I don’t know.
I feel strange when Master—
I feel strange when you touch me, Gen.
My systems are under excessive load.
Increased motor speed
has elevated my temperature.
I need to cool my systems down.
Look, I have no idea what you’re talking about.
And stop backing away from me.
Now I’m soaked all over again.
Then let me go, Gen.
No way. If I let you go, you’re
just going to get the floor all wet.
- I'll wipe it up.
- I don't believe you.
Just stay still, Ai—
Ah!
I'm sorry!
Did I do something wrong?
I should be the one asking you that.
Did I upset you, Gen?
Are you going to chase me away again?
Why do you have to go
as far as shutting me down?
Do you hate me, Gen?
Do you dislike me?
I don’t hate you.
And I’m not upset with you either.
But you were trying to shut me down.
I wasn't trying to shut you down.
I don’t even know where your power switch is.
You didn’t come with an instruction
manual when you showed up.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
I don’t believe you.
What?
You tried to send me back to the company before.
What is it?
I promise I won't chase you away anymore.
And I won't shut you down either.
What does that have to do
with extending your pinky finger?
One moment, please. I need some
time to search for more information.
A pinky promise is when two
people make a promise to each other.
And I promise I will never
do anything that harms you.
Okay?
Trust me.
Please?
And just like that… a promise
between me and a robot began.
Strange.
I'm feeling it again.
What’s the matter?
I don’t know.
I woke up with a sore shoulder.
Like something was pressing on it all night.
Why did you suddenly want
to come to the art gallery?
I want to understand.
Understand what?
You.
You want to understand human emotions, right?
Do I need to teach you that
your words can cause misunderstandings?
Just go look at whatever you want.
I’ll be working at my usual spot.
And don’t wander off too far.
Think carefully before responding to anyone.
You don’t want to end up
getting taken apart, do you?
Why the hell are you flustered, Ai Gen?
She just wants to understand humans.
She wants to understand you
because you’re a human.
Did you forget how to
connect ideas like in exams?
That’s all there is to it.
Don’t overthink it.
Don't flatter yourself. Stop it.
Why is your heart racing over
a robot that isn’t even a month old?
Sorry!
Kaew…
So this is how it’s going to be, Gen?
I’ve made my decision, Kaew.
Don’t be crazy.
You’re one step away from a promotion.
But you’re just going to throw it all away
because you suddenly had an epiphany
that you want to draw?!
What about everything you’ve built up?
Years of experience? Work history?
Do you know how much money you’re making here?
And what about the stability you always wanted?
Didn’t you say you wanted
to make your mother proud?
So you’re just going to throw it
all away for some foolish dream?!
It’s not a foolish dream, Kaew.
What about me?
Everything’s still the same.
No.
It will never be the same.
If you choose that dream over me…
then we’re through.
Kaew, please don't do this.
No, you’re the one making the choice here.
So choose.
Are you staying or leaving?
Gen! Come back here right now! Gen!
Gen! Gen!!
Gen.
You still keep it?
It’s been a long time.
Mm, it’s been a long time.
Since… you left to chase your dream.
And…
it looks like you’re still dreaming.
I... just remembered I’ve got
something to do. Excuse me.
Wait, Gen!
What's the rush?
We haven’t seen each other in so long.
Gen.
Can we just let bygones be bygones?
Well… I know we didn’t end things on good terms.
But that was ages ago.
Are you going to avoid me forever?
At least… for the sake of our good memories.
I... don't want to lose you as a friend.
At least, if you still consider me one.
Mm.
That’s wonderful. What a relief.
By the way, next week,
I’m meeting up with the friends
we joined the company with.
Remember them?
Kate's working in the States now,
but she'll be back next week.
You should come see everyone.
They all want to meet you.
I... I have to go.
Then… call me if you change your mind.
My number's still the same.
You still remember it, right?
I'm glad you still keep that bracelet.
Guess who?
That’s tough.
Come on, give it a try.
Could it be the apple of someone’s eye?
Whose? Answer quickly!
Well... mine, of course.
And the apple of someone’s eye
has a gift for you!
What is it?
Open it.
Oh.
Wow.
A gift for passing the project.
It might not be expensive,
but it’s from the heart.
You like it?
It’s cute.
Thank you.
I liked it.
I did.
And I still do.
Do you like bracelets, Gen?
I...
I’m not sure either.
Why is that?
Because I thought I could do it.
Follow my dream in a way
everyone would accept.
And then tell the one who gave me this bracelet,
“I did it.”
“See?”
“You can be proud of me now.”
“Can I have another chance?”
But in the end, it was just a dream.
You’ve got some nerve, Gen.
Right now, you’re still just a freelancer
who takes on any job anyone pays you for.
And you really think you can just
go back and ask for another chance?
So if I gave you a bracelet,
would you like me?
Why?
I want you to like me.
Do I need a reason for that?
What... should I do?
Do what you want.
You said humans have emotions and desires.
I believe everything you do is good.
Aren't you placing a bit too much faith in me?
You’re the one who taught me.
I like it when you touch me like this.
Have I become so desperate that I’m
getting advice from a three-week-old robot?
Where are you going, Gen?
I'm going to set things straight.
Thanks.
Seriously, the picanha at JR is to die for.
I'm craving it so much.
And the truffle spaghetti is really good too.
Hello there, gorgeous!
Look who’s finally here.
Gen: "Be there in 10 minutes."
Is it just me, or did someone go
totally all-out with her outfit tonight?
Maybe a little.
Hey, do you really think she’ll show up?
She’s been out of the picture for years.
I wouldn’t have the guts to come if I were her.
Because she talked big, saying
she was going to go chase her dreams.
Heh. And look what happened.
The rising star everyone expected
to start her own company someday
and become some hotshot CEO...
what's the phrase for her situation now?
Living hand to mouth?
Hey, don't laugh.
I know you only went after her
because she was talented.
Come on, that’s ancient history.
Let’s not talk about it.
Don’t lie.
If it were really ancient history,
you wouldn’t have dragged us here
to rub it in Gen’s face.
Am I right?
Just tell us what you want us to do.
Guys, don't be like this.
Aren't we just meeting up for a dinner?
No.
She needs to be shown what happens
when you make the wrong choice.
But you were the one who dumped Gen.
You said that she came crying
and begging for you to take her back.
Since you don't care about
her anymore, just let it go.
Amen.
Hope you never lose that saintly act of yours.
So.
Should we just walk all over her tonight?
Obviously.
Who’d want to be with someone
who has nothing going for them?
How dare she dumped someone like me.
That’s the spirit.
Let’s humiliate her so badly she has to
hide under a skirt and never come out.
- How about my skirt? It’s pretty long.
- That’ll do.
Hey. Who is that?
She’s so beautiful.
Ai?
Sawasdee ka.
Ai!!!
Yes?
Exactly how much stuff did you order?!
I ordered them so you would like me, Gen.
Like this.
Which style do you prefer?
I got them in every style.
Do you like it, Master?
Ai! You—!
Throw everything away!!!
English Subtitles by Saowalak K.