Hyun Jae.
Kim Hyun Jae!
Where did he go?
Please leave a message after the tone.
- Brother!
- Khun.
How have you been?
Seems like Korea was fun.
Who's this?
Friend...
My boyfriend. Shin Jae Min.
Jae Min.
Yes?
He's my cousin.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shin Jae Min.
- Must have been troublesome to get here.
- No, not at all.
By the way, your Korean is amazing.
I spent a few years in Korea because of work.
Khun.
You like Korea, don't you?
Yeah. It's damn great.
- Let's go.
- Let's go eat.
No, stay seated.
Thank you.
This is actually a secret lodge,
only open to family members.
I've never seen Khun bring anyone else here.
Thank you.
For helping Khun come back here.
Enjoy your meal, Khun.
Aren't you eating with us?
I only stopped by to check on Khun.
See you again.
I'm leaving.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Why aren't you eating?
Why don't you eat?
Well, I don't know where to start.
They all look so good.
Whoa! What is this?
It tastes so good!
How is it so good? What is it? Huh?
Cute.
Hm? What?
I said, you eat well.
Hey, you should try it, too.
It's out of this world.
From this day on,
you are going back to being trainees.
We have decided that you
can't make a debut by yourselves.
The boy band project has been scrapped.
Is this because of Jae Min?
Not necessarily.
The board decided to
focus on Hyun Jae's solo debut.
So don't get any ideas
and concentrate on your training.
Let's go.
Is this about Jae Min?
We could just do without Shin Jae Min.
What's with all this drama?
- How does this make any sense?
- It doesn't.
There's no way.
We already had a debut song.
This is some hidden camera prank, right?
What happened?
What do you think?
Didn't you hear?
You knew about this, didn't you?
You knew, and you still did all that?
It's the company's decision.
- What was I supposed to do?
- You knew!
You knew, and yet...
You took me out to eat.
- You even took me to bed.
- This isn't new for us.
It's not the first time this has happened.
Ah, Hyun Jae. There you are.
- I was looking for you.
- Sir.
What is it?
The American producer that
I told you about last time...
We got the contract.
There's a Zoom meeting in an hour.
Meet me in my room.
Yes, thank you, sir.
I have great expectations for you.
I'll do my best.
That's the spirit.
You do your best, too.
You'll get a chance someday.
I've never been to a house
with a private pool before.
You're a good swimmer.
I like being in water.
That's one more thing...
I know about you now.
Slow down.
Trying to pass out again?
It's not like that.
I have a question.
What is it?
Your reply to my letter.
My reply.
It's too late.
We should sleep.
Which room do you want?
Just pick one.
I want to stay with you.
Make me some ramen, will you?
I never should have brought him here.
How am I supposed to live here now?
This is mockery, nothing less.
Hyun Jae, we need to talk.
Still have something to say?
I'm fine with not getting to debut.
I can congratulate you on your
solo career with my whole heart, so...
- Hyun Jae, please, just...
- Yoon Soo An.
This isn't like you.
I'll take anything, just not this.
You never used to be like this.
This isn't the real you!
What's really wrong with you?
Since when were you so clingy?
Just stop already.
Thank you.
I could finally breathe, thanks to you.
If I had stayed in Korea...
I've been thinking, watching you here.
You must've needed a place to breathe as well.
That's why you came to Korea, right?
It must be hard for you being here.
You did this for me, didn't you?
If it's too hard for you...
we can go back to Korea first thing tomorrow.
You know...
I can breathe anywhere with you by my side.
- Has anyone got a hold of Hyun Jae yet?
- No, he's not picking up.
Well, he has to be somewhere, right?
Where on earth did he go?
We're supposed to be recording today!
Come on, pick up.
He's not home, either.
We just couldn't find him anywhere.
He's gone without a trace.
Darn it. Come with me!
No one is available to take your call.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Who's calling?
I just thought of somewhere I want to go.
I teamed you two up for better performance...
but apparently, you've been dating.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Were you spying on me this whole time?
Kim Hyun Jae.
Want to see something funny?
You thought you made it
because you're talented, didn't you?