Get ready for a poster photoshoot.
Our group is going to be a hit.
You’re really going viral.
Here, the views have already passed 100,000.
I’m afraid that I’m not a good leader.
Our group’s already hanging by a thread.
This is gonna make things worse.
We should increase our fanbase
with the trial dating thing.
Cutter with Yu. Jeng with Mai.
Have you ever been to Talad Noi?
Not yet.
I’ll take you there.
(Welcome to Talad Noi.)
Have you ever been here?
Yeah, I like hanging out around here.
I’ve never been here before.
It’s so photogenic.
Hey, can you take a pic for me?
-Who’s more handsome?
-One,
two, three.
Who’s more handsome?
Boo.
This isn’t giving like Cutter said.
But this guy…
is cute.
Go on. It’s your turn.
Let me see how Mr. Handsome poses.
Alright.
One, two, three.
So? Do I look handsome?
Well.
A little less handsome than me.
I won’t give in to anyone else
but you, Leader.
Wanna take a photo together?
How about over there?
Alright, one, two.
Can you smile a little?
Let’s try again. Give me a smile.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Let me see.
Much better.
See?
You look so cute when you smile.
Smile a little more.
My smile is already right in front of me.
Don’t go smiling like that at just anyone,
got it?
Whoa, whoa.
Wow.
Why do you look so happy?
Because this cartoon is funny.
I used to watch it when I was a kid.
Never thought I’d get to watch it again.
It makes me so nostalgic.
Sometimes I’m jealous of you.
Jealous of what?
You get excited about everything.
Like the whole world is full of wonders to you.
What about you?
Don’t you get excited?
Or are you speaking from experience?
How?
Well.
If you keep comparing everything
to what you’ve already experienced,
nothing will feel exciting.
You’ll only end up disappointed.
But…
If life has been rough,
just think of it as experience
because there's always a new beginning
after every failure.
I wish that boy could think like you.
He fought for his dream all by himself,
but the adults looked down on him,
and sent him back for no reason in the end.
He fought for 10 years.
All he could do
was keep doing what he loved
without chasing that dream anymore.
Until he met someone.
Someone who gave everything to his dream.
And that person’s smile
made the boy dream again.
That person is…
Hello, Tian.
I’m heading back.
Alright, I’ll come see you.
Okay. See you.
I'm already in touch with them.
I guarantee our client willl love it.
Yes, I'm giving it my all.
Oh, Boss Si Tian.
What a coincidence.
Bai Liu.
So this is
Mr. Si Tian, the owner of Ultimate Woof,
or should I say Ultimate Woops?
Boss.
Is this the guy you mentioned?
The fake one?
Ooh.
His acting was terrible.
Someone should send him to acting school.
He was so fake during the live press conference.
So it’s him?
Fake?
My label is the real deal.
At least we’re not some dying label
like a certain label around here.
Oh my, Shining.
Stay cool.
Sorry about that, Tian.
Don’t take it personally.
Actually, I’ve been rooting for you.
I hope your next song
becomes a huge hit.
Let’s go, Shining.
We’ve to pick up our new trainee from the airport.
I wonder if he's landed from Korea yet.
That’s right.
See you later.
Kamsahamnida.
I better start learning Korean
since we have a Korean trainee now.
What a joke.
Hmph.
-Medyer.
-Yes?
I want to talk to you about the song.
Got a minute?
Of course.
I want you to make our song go viral.
I heard the boys talk about a random dance at Siam.
Maybe we can work something out with our sponsor.
Boss.
What if nobody joins?
We have to try.
There’s nothing to lose.
I’ll leave you to it.
Don’t worry. I’ll do my best.
I’ll make our label go viral and iconic, Boss.
Good. I’m counting on you.
I don’t want our label to fail.
Honestly,
I never wanted to compete with that label.
I just hoped
they’d think we're decent.
Don’t worry, Boss.
This time, underdogs like us
are gonna take down that giant.
Let’s have a drink.
Alright, I’ll take care of it.
Everything will be perfect.
Our marketing plan’s going well.
Thank you for your hard work.
No problem.
Ah!
Who is this?
I’m scared.
Don’t be scared. I’m your friend.
Look closely.
Take the mask off. There’s no one here.
Take it off!
I already did!
Okay.
Let me tell you something.
You don’t even need the mask.
Just wipe off your makeup,
and people will think you’re a man.
No one will recognize you.
Hey, show some respect to my makeup.
Why?
Girl, I look this gorgeous.
Gorgeous where?
What about you?
You’re not prettier than me.
-Big talk.
-Hey!
You two are at it again.
Seriously.
Can’t you stop fighting for a day?
Everyone’s gonna notice us at this rate.
And you’ve been gone for a while. Let’s get to the point.
What’s their next move?
I checked it out.
They’re going to do a random dance.
A random dance?
Yeah.
A random dance.
They’ll play the songs from their label
and let random people dance.
It’s a promo event.
Good idea.
But it’s kinda risky.
What if nobody shows up to dance?
They said they’re going all in.
Even if they fail, they don’t care.
I hope it works out for them.
Young master, I’ve got something to tell you.
What is it?
Si Tian said
he never wanted to compete with you.
He just wanted to prove himself.
And from the way he looked at you,
I swear he still has feelings for you.
You do too?
What feelings? Don't be silly.
Fine, fine.
So how do you wanna help Si Tian?
Any ideas?
Oh.
I just thought of one.
You’re amazing.
You’re always so quick witted.
Where is P’Medyer?
She told us to meet here, but she isn’t here.
She’s probably finding the location for us.
Hey.
Guys.
Don’t you think…
something feels off today?
Why’s everyone eating bitter melon?
Is it some new Chinese trend?
Did I miss it?
Wait!
Is our song popular now?
Wow.
Then tonight I’m checking the market
to see if bitter melon’s sold out.
I think it’s real.
That’d be amazing.
We started a new trend.
I hope so.
We’ll know soon enough.
Just wait for tonight.
If people come out and dance to our song,
then it’s real.
Guys.
The venue’s all set. Let’s go.
Everything’s ready.
It’s our time to shine. Let’s go!
Let’s do this, guys!
Yay!
Dang.
So many people.
Whoa.
I haven't danced like this in a while.
Nervous?
Yeah.
So many people.
Just hold my hand.
You’ll feel better.
You’re really nervous, huh?
Your hand’s so sweaty.
Shut up.
That’s enough. Someone will see us.
No one’s looking.
Alright, everyone.
Ready?
Ready!
I already added our song to the queue.
We’ll dance to other songs first,
then our song will come next.
Okay?
Yep.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Before we begin, I’ve a little gift for you all.
What is it?
Whoa!
No way!
These are Champion shirts.
I talked to the brand,
and they like how this event motivates young people.
Here. Put them on.
Whoa, these are sick.
Thank you.
Once you’re done changing, bring them back to me.
Medyer asked me to take care of them for you.
Oh.
Where is Medyer?
She’s meeting with a client,
trying to get our group on Hiwwhee channel.
Nice.
Hiring her was the right call.
She’s such a pro.
I’m sure we’re gonna be a hit.
Alright, let’s go get changed.
I’m happy we can wear something this cool.
Great job.
Excuse us.
-Sorry.
-A superstar is coming.
The first song’s on.
I can dance this one.
Calm down.
I want to be Mabelz!
Mai.
Hm?
Are people gonna dance to our song?
Of course.
Our song’s quite popular.
It’s Toon Alie Blackcobra.
I wanna dance already.
Yo!
It’s our song!
This is our moment!
But…
Why isn’t anyone coming out?
Someone will come soon, Jeng.
Jeng.
Just one look into your eyes
I almost lose my mind
I keep thinking about you every single night
Be happy to…
Hey, do you eat bitter melon?
Wanna be my love?
I can’t look away from you
I’m going crazy because…
Hey, are you Google?
You can find anything
What should we do?
Should we go out?
Whatever!
Hey, bro!
Be happy to…
Hey, do you eat bitter melon?
Wanna be my love?
I can’t look away from you
I’m going crazy because…
Hey, are you Google?
You can find anything
But you’re my everything
I’m so fluttered because of (you)
How could they dance?
I’ve never heard the song. Do you know it?
Can you dance to it?
Do you know this one?
There are so many people here.
For real.
Too bad no one danced to our song.
Hey.
You guys did great.
Didn’t our song do well, Boss?
You all did great.
Guys.
Huh?
I’ll go back first.
Okay.
What’s up with him?
Jeng?
Jeng!
He’s leaving too?
I’m so tired.
Why is it so hard?
Everyone’s amazing.
They really are.
Every single one.
But I dragged them into this mess.
Jeng.
What are you even good at?
You’re not good at anything.
Everyone else isn’t a loser.
Maybe I’m the only loser here.
Me.
Jeng the loser.
Jeng!
Where are you?
Huh?
Did Boss send you to look for me?
So where are we celebrating tonight?
We’re so–
It’s okay to cry.
You’ve been doing well,
Leader.
Hey.
You can leave me alone.
Go hang out with the others.
They’ll be looking for you.
I’m tougher than I look.
I’m Jeng.
I'm an amazing gem, right?
I know,
but I don’t want you to be alone.
Let it out, Jeng.
Cry as much as you need.
I’m here.
A leader
shouldn’t be a crybaby.
My name is Jeng,
so I have to be the strongest gem.
You don’t have to be the best.
Just being you is enough.
I’m sorry.
For what?
This.
Can I kiss you again?
What are you laughing at?
I just got shy.
Can you not smile like that at anyone else?
I’ll get jealous.
Seriously,
today was just too much.
Don’t you think?
It sucked,
but it’s not that terrible.
Really?
No one knew our dance.
I feel like you have to face this because of me.
Why are you blaming yourself?
Because…
This all started with me.
I asked them to join the group.
I told them we’d make it.
That we’d get famous.
But…
Now it just feels like I wasted everyone’s time.
That’s not true.
Really?
Everyone’s talented.
Yu.
Fong.
Cutter.
You too.
Me?
No, I’m not good at anything.
I’m neither a great dancer,
nor a rapper.
My voice isn’t that good either.
And my looks…
are nothing special.
I’m just a jack of all trades,
master of none.
But you’re amazing.
You can do anything,
and work well with the team.
That’s you.
How?
Fong is too serious.
Yu gets too nervous.
Cutter is too confident.
You’re the one who keeps us balanced.
That’s how special you are, Jeng.
My strongest little Jack.
You should be proud of yourself.
Be proud every single day.
I’ll be watching.
That’s kinda mean.
How?
Because…
You’re...
making my heart race.
Can you hear it?
Mine is racing too.
From now on, you don’t have to be alone anymore.
I’ll stay by your side, and not going anywhere.
So, are you tired?
A little.
So…
Are you heading home, or are you going somewhere?
I don’t know.
By the way, won’t the others wonder where we went?
Nah, I already told Brother Tian I was coming to find you.
And I told them to head home first.
Wait, what did you just say?
I told everyone to head home first.
No. I meant when you called him Brother Tian.
Oh.
Boss Tian?
Yeah.
I mean Boss Tian.
Jeng.
Hm?
Can I steal you away for a bit?
Where to?
You having fun?
Yes.
Why’d you bring me here?
Well.
When I was a kid,
I never got to go to an amusement park.
I never rode a roller coaster,
a Ferris wheel,
or even a carousel.
I just wanted to know what childhood was like.
So you brought me here to ride the carousel?
Yeah.
You’re such a goof.
I just wanted to try enjoying things like a kid.
It’s not goofy, but it’s so much fun.
Now we get to be kids together.
Let’s see who’s faster.
Deal.
Ready? One, two, three!
Go, my boy!
You’re catching up!
No way.
Don’t give up yet.
My horse is about to pass out.
Yours is done for.
It’s exhausted.
Not just the horse, we’re exhausted too.
Thank you
for letting me experience childhood.
And…
Thanks for helping me dream again.
Hey! Jeng’s back!
Our leader!
Guys.
I’m sorry.
Sorry for what?
You don’t have to be sorry.
I’m sorry too.
I haven’t been giving my all,
and spent too much time at aerobics practice.
I’m sorry too.
I haven’t practiced enough, and I’m still not good enough.
I’ll work harder.
We’re all good, right?
Of course we are.
I’m more chill than the whole random dance floor.
Aww.
Thank you, guys.
We’ll get them next time..
Next random dance,
everyone’s gonna come out and dance to our song.
I turned our dance into an aerobics routine.
A lot of people loved it.
Really?
Aerobics?
Don’t underestimate the grannies.
Guys.
I got a good idea.
How about this?
Let’s target the right audience
by going to the aerobics area
to win the grannies over.
I’ll borrow my mom's truck with the speakers.
Then we’ll drive around promoting us.
What do you think?
Great. I’m in.
I’ll bring the rescue truck too.
Maybe we should skip that.
People might think there’s an emergency.
My mom’s truck should be enough.
Let’s do it.
Can you guys help me cheer Jeng up?
I know you’re all exhausted.
But Jeng is too.
He’s carrying more pressure than you think.
I know.
Honestly,
we should be thanking Jeng.
He's the reason we started dreaming again.
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger.
This isn’t Jeng’s fault.
I just expected too much,
and put too much pressure on him as our leader.
I also owe him an apology.
I haven’t been trying hard enough.
I promise I’ll do better.
I won’t let Jeng’s trust go to waste.
Thanks, guys.
I know we’re a team.
Come on, Leader.
Let’s do this.
Hello, everyone.
Cutter the rapper is here to rock your day.
We’d like to ask for your support.
Please support our group.
Pretty lady, please take this.
Our song’s a total gem.
Thanks. Take as many as you want.
Download our song today, and you get a free bitter melon.
Come on over.
Our song’s called 'Do you eat bitter melon?'
Here, pretty lady.
Come on over, please.
Come on, beautiful ladies.
Please support our group.
Wow.
You are all so handsome.
Please support us.
What number are you running for? I’ll vote for you.
And don’t forget to take care of the stray dogs.
We’re not running for election.
We’re idols. Like singers.
If you download our song today,
you’ll get a free bitter melon.
Perfect. I want to eat bitter melon soup.
-And…
-You come to the right place.
We also have a free aerobics class.
Please come join us.
Aww, you boys are adorable.
I’ll buy all the bitter melons.
Please come.
Is it fresh?
Fresh as can be.
Hello there.
Are you celebrities?
Yep, please follow us.
Will I get free snacks?
No, but it’ll be fun.
Here, have this.
You’re not handsome.
Unlike my boyfriend Robert.
Come on, Robert.
Let’s go for another ride.
Yeah.
You’re handsome enough for me.
But this brother is handsome.
Can I take a picture with you?
Sure. Come on.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
They’re so cute.
Oh, Cutter. Where’ve you been?
Oh, hey, Auntie.
I thought you stopped selling stuff.
I’ve been busy lately.
I’m chasing my dream of becoming a rapper.
Good for you.
Five members?
Yes.
With faces like these, you’re gonna be famous.
You think so?
I want to eat bitter melon soup today.
If you’re craving bitter melon,
please check this out.
This is our song, Do you eat bitter melon?
Sure thing.
My son loves bitter melons.
Let’s get started.
Do you eat bitter melon?
Whoa, look.
Everyone knows the dance.
I told you.
The grannies are a great army.
So many people.
Boss, you’re here too?
Check this out.
Hello, Boss.
Whoa.
Do you eat bitter melon?
Don’t underestimate the grannies.
Some of them are social media pros.
Even I’m shocked.
People started making a melon challenge from our song,
saying how sweet it is.
Look.
It's really going viral.
Then, we gotta celebrate tonight.
Cheers!
Boss.
Yeah?
Treating us like this.
Do you still have
enough money for yourself?
Hey.
I’ve a lot of money.
I’m loaded.
Don’t worry.
This is nothing.
Eat up.
Don’t hold back.
How is it, guys?
It’s so good.
Eat up. Your boss is so generous.
So eat your fill.
Oh, this is my friend, Play.
Hi.
He’s half Korean and owns this Korean restaurant.
Is it good?
It’s amazing.
What’s the restaurant called?
'No deposit needed.'
It’s really good.
Eat as much as you want.
-Want some soju?
-Sure.
Pour me one too.
Let’s have a drink.
This is my restaurant, you know.
My friend’s place is like my place.
So, why did you call me last night?
My aunt’s been stressing over the music industry.
She asked me to ask you something.
Remember my cousin who went to train in Korea?
It turns out the company never gave him a song,
so he came back to Thailand.
What’s he gonna do now?
Well…
He’s interested in your ex’s label.
I mean, your old friend’s label.
Kami…
Kamikeme?
Yeah, that one.
He wants to know if it’s legit.
It’s good.
Really good.
Seriously?
It’s one of the top labels.
-Top tier?
-Yeah.
-For real?
-Yep.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
I’m serious.
Nothing to worry?
You can rest assured.
Awesome, I’ll let my aunt know.
Speak of the devil.
I have to take this call.
Hello?
Yes.
Yeah.
Mai, are you okay?
You look kinda stressed.
I’m fine.
Guys, this is my cousin, Jun.
Hi, everyone.
He just came back from Korea.
Wanna sit here?
Hey, hey.
I'm at my limit.
Another round?
Pour it up, Boss!
Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
Come on.
Everyone.
Alright.
Cheers.
Eat up.
Let’s order more.
Another round?
Oh.
Jun.
Yeah?
So…
That label
is good.
Really good.
I heard they’re planning an Asia tour soon.
If you can get in,
I’m happy for you.
It’s an amazing label.
But why did you come back to Thailand?
My project got canceled.
I already told you. Are you drunk?
I just warned you.
Don’t rub salt in the wound.
How could you hit the boss?
Hey.
Hey, hey, wait!
Mai.
Don’t worry, I’ll handle it.
They’re having a blast.
Easy there, guys.
-They’re having a lot of fun.
-Shut up!
Why are you being fussy? I’m your friend.
How’s he gonna feel?
Hey, wait!
I’m kidding.
I’m tougher than I look.
This is nostalgic.
I gotta use the bathroom. Come with me.
Sure.
This really takes me back.
It’s been a while, Mai.
Small world, huh?
Never thought I'd see you again.
Me neither.
So…
You’re with this label now?
Mhm.
I hope we get to work together someday.
I hope so too.
I’m glad you didn’t give up on your dream.
Mai.
Are you happy?
I am,
but I still don't know how to handle it.
Our song just hit a hundred thousand views!
Yay!
The company’s running out of money.
We can’t quit halfway. Let’s go all in.
We can start over, Jeng.
Let’s start again together.
With your brother's money again?
I don’t want to be a burden to him anymore.
But you’re the one who reignited my passion.